This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
[MY SHY BOSS]
I've always thought that
I'd be gone if I didn't have him.
Please... don't do this.
It was a mistake.
Kang Woo Il...
wouldn't do such a thing by accident.
If it wasn't a mistake...
then...
that means...
Stay back!
I'll hate you instead.
I can't hate Kang Woo Il.
No matter what he does,
I can never leave him!
So if you're truly sorry...
stop pretending to be good,
and disappear.
Please.
You don't look so good.
I'm sorry, but let's see
the exhibition another time.
Yes, that's okay!
You should go to the hospital.
Oh! CEO Kang! Eun Yi Soo
went to the hospital with Boss.
She didn't look so good.
That's right. Eun Yi Soo
invited me to your wedding.
I want to bring a gift,
but I don't know...
Is he embarrassed?
Ro Woon, you came?
Yeon Jung!
But it looks like...
I'll have to look at your art by myself.
Oh. I guess Hwan Ki
only came here to see me.
Hey, I'm sure he
didn't come just for that.
From now on, you'll feel ignored and sad
because of me. Use my art for comfort.
The art will help you calm down.
Follow me.
When you were talking
about Secretary Chae's family...
you didn't mean Chae Ro Woon, did you?
You're right.
She's Secretary Chae's younger sister.
St... Stop the car.
Are you all right?
Did you know...
Chae Ro Woon made Woo Il fall for her?
Why do you think I pretended
I didn't know anything?
I was so scared that Woo Il
would end up like this!
That's why I needed to pretend
like I didn't know anything.
I didn't want the same thing
to happen again.
But she's her younger sister.
What is this ill-fated relationship?
Do you think there's a chance
she did it intentionally?
Did she plan to steal
Woo Il away from me?
She doesn't know anything yet.
And he was only interested
in her for a short while.
What is this?
Did you know about it too?
If you knew, how could you...
Who is Chae Ro Woon to you? Who is she?
Who is she that you're
cornering me like this? Tell me!
Do you actually love her?
Are you stupid?
You two will never work out.
It looks like you're about
to expose everything for her
but your relationship will end
as soon as you do so!
So let go of her.
I'm sorry, but please make the sacrifice.
Gosh.
Seriously. What's going on?
It was our first date,
but I was dumped for his sister.
And he's not even contacting me.
No.
I shouldn't let myself
be pushed aside so early.
I won't contact you first.
I'm not going to talk to you
until you talk to me first!
Gosh!
I won't. I won't.
[CHAE RO WOON]
Where are you?
Is something the matter?
I won't bite!
I'm scared by myself.
Why aren't you leaving?
I'll leave when Mother comes home.
Are you worried I'll do something
if you leave me by myself?
Are you stupid?
You two will never work out.
[EPISODE 13: GO BACK]
What do I do?
What's wrong? What's the problem?
You even found a mysticism artist
who is difficult to contact
and the client approved.
Yes. It was good up until that point.
But the problems arose after that.
Here. Have some coffee
and tell me about it.
Latte? Americano?
Thank you. Latte. No, Americano.
No, Latte? No, Ameri... Gosh!
This is the problem!
I'm stuck between two sides,
but I'm unable to do anything.
Well, your samples are pretty out there
so I'm worried they won't
appeal to our consumers.
Um, don't worry.
I have experience
in business-related projects.
But isn't the purpose of a collaboration
to graft my art as well?
Our company's aim
is to sell our products.
That's how we make money.
Don't you agree, Gyo Ri?
Wait, that's not... that's...
Oh, it's really out there.
Oh my. Oh my. Oh my, what is this?
I don't like this. Tell her to bring me
pretty designs! Pretty designs!
Pretty? What do you mean by that?
If you tell us what you want
in more detail
it'll be easier for us
to do what you ask.
I'm telling you... I want pretty designs!
Yes, so pretty in what way?
Oh my, listen to him. Oh my.
I understand both sides.
But it's still driving me crazy.
It's not like I can take sides.
Then, drink both.
- Pardon?
- I'll make another one for myself.
Oh, really? Thank you.
They're both so good
despite what's going on.
What did I tell you?
I told you it won't be easy!
Geez.
And where's the general
who came up with this great idea?
I'm right here.
Geez. Hello, there.
But I still think Se Jong is better
at interacting with your clients.
But I have the habit of saying
whatever is on my mind
so both sides are unhappy with me.
That's why I'll be going to the
meetings alone from now on.
At this rate,
what if our project founders?
Hey, we can't let that happen.
I'll meet both clients
and see what I can do.
Really? Thank you so much!
No.
I'd like you to finish what you started.
But still, she lacks experience...
This is a valuable experience for you.
Yes, I understand, Boss.
No, Mr. Hwan Ki.
What is this?
Nothing has changed since last time!
The worth of our products will decrease
and the aesthetic sense will fall too!
Look at this.
If it were you, would you buy this?
If your boyfriend bought it for you,
would you wear it?
I know it's a little unique...
What's this? It's empty.
Let me get you another one.
Well, in comparison to
when that male employee was here
I feel like we have an understanding.
Oh, really? What a relief...
Oh! Oh my gosh!
Oh my! Why is it raining
all of a sudden? I forgot my umbrella!
I'll go and buy you an umbrella!
Oh, what brings you here?
It's late, and I heard
it was going to rain.
Who is this?
- Oh, this is...
- We don't have titles at our company.
I'm a driver right now.
- Huh?
- Let's go.
Oh my! You didn't have to...
No, this is for Gyo Ri.
- Pardon? Me?
- Not me?
Please take this.
You're only giving me an umbrella?
Shall I call you a taxi?
No, my company is close by...
Then, please return safely.
- Please get in.
- Wait, but...
Get in.
What is this? What is this situation?
But can we really do this?
Maybe we should have
taken care of our client first.
Didn't you leave because
you finished your meeting?
Yes, that's true...
but I don't deserve this treatment.
You were there as a representative
of Silent Monster.
You did what a CEO does,
so you should be treated like one.
Hey, there's no way...
I'm really uncomfortable right now.
If you can pull over so I can sit
in the front passenger seat...
Oh, then... I'd be uncomfortable.
Oh, I see.
I wonder why I ever thought you
were scary and difficult to approach.
I realized you had a cute side
when I got to know you.
I think I was just being sensitive.
It's because you feel more emotions
than the average person.
Me?
That's why you feel more anxious,
and you're sad more often than others.
It must be difficult for you
but feeling emotions
that others cannot feel
is a great advantage.
No one has ever said that to me before.
Everyone just asks me why I'm so weak.
The ability to feel the emotions
others cannot sense in someone else
is something only you can understand.
I think you, Boss, no, Mr. Hwan Ki,
would know more about that.
But for how much longer
will you call me by that long name?
Pardon? Oh.
I'll call you by a
shorter name from now on.
Hwan Ki.
- Make it short.
- Yes.
Yes, Hwan Ki.
You want it to be prettier?
If you're only looking at the business
aspect, there's nothing in it for me.
Just like what I said last time
Isn't the aim of this collaboration
to graft my art onto these pieces?
Of course. Your art and your designs are
already valuable in an artistic sense.
But, ma'am...
Oh my... Oh my!
If this is how it's going to be,
I'm going to cut our budget!
That's what I'm saying!
Our company's aim
is to sell our products.
But, General Manager...
unique designs are the
popular trend these days.
Everyone has the desire to wear
something that no one else has.
Wouldn't you also want to give your
girlfriend a pretty, yet unique gift?
- A little bit.
- A little bit?
Gyo Ri! Gyo Ri! You convinced both sides?
How did you do that?
Well, I didn't say much.
I just listened for the most part.
You told me it wasn't easy.
- I'm impressed, Gyo Ri.
- No, it wasn't me.
It was all thanks to Hwan Ki.
Where are you going this time?
I heard you gave Gyo Ri a ride yesterday.
Who are you planning to
spend time with tonight?
It feels like
I have a cheating boyfriend.
That's why I told you to go home.
Are you meeting Yeon Jung, by any chance?
It must be true!
Smile.
Hey.
Why are you taking pictures
all of a sudden?
It turned out so nicely.
- I'm sending it to Ro Woon to brag.
- Hey, stop joking around!
I'm not joking. I'm just pretending I am.
I'm worried that if I keep clinging
to you, I'll drag you down with me.
If it gets too difficult,
just come to me, Hwan Ki.
Yeon Jung.
- I...
- Why do we keep getting mixed up?
I'm pretty upset about it, to be honest.
But I'm starting to think
that this must be our fate.
For letting me hear your thoughts...
I'm thankful to you.
I'm the one who's thankful.
Thank you for listening to my thoughts
that I can't reveal to anyone else.
If we were only left with scars after
we broke off our childish relationship
it would have been hard to share our
deep thoughts after meeting again, right?
That's true.
- Let's continue being friends...
- No, I'm saying...
Let's not draw any lines if we don't
know what will happen in the future.
If I don't think it'll work,
I'll leave on my own.
I'm old enough to do that much.
The same goes for Ro Woon.
You don't know how much time
you have left together
so be with her while you still can.
You can still do that for her.
[YEON JUNG]
I had a date today with Hwan Ki.
It looks like I won today!
Gosh, Yeon Jung...
Is she my enemy or is she on my side?
I can't figure it out.
The day when snow becomes happiness...
The day when snow becomes sadness...
The snow is falling like...
like flowers, as it
congratulates us on our love...
Your actions always told me
you were just a fool...
This was unexpected.
You haven't left yet?
Never mind. You are a fool.
After drinking wine with a pretty
and cool woman like Yeon Jung
you crawled back in here so quietly.
Why are you playing guitar
all of a sudden? Can you play?
Yeah... a little bit.
What about you?
Hand it over.
Wow.
The chubby, baby pig...
He begs for milk, oink, oink, oink...
The mother pig comes...
- The baby pig asks for milk...
- What... What is this song?
Pardon? Why? Don't you like it?
- I sang it just for you.
- Are you telling me to be the baby pig?
Yes.
Gosh, give it to me.
I'm not the baby pig.
I was kidding.
- Geez, look how chubby they are.
- They're not.
- Okay, it's my turn.
- Yes.
I'm not very good either.
I want my warm lips...
to touch your soft lips...
I wish for my love...
to reach your heart...
If you still haven't realized...
my feelings for you...
I'll love you more than anyone...
in this world.
I'll love you forever...
I'll love you just as I love you now...
I'll love you more than anyone else...
in this world.
Oh no! You weren't
supposed to see that, CEO Kang!
Oh, well, the truth is...
I prepared this song
to sing at your wedding.
Huh? You're leaving again?
Isn't he being too much these days?
He used to be such an
antisocial and reclusive man.
This is strange.
Three years ago...
if I had chosen Ji Hye instead of Yi Soo
you never would have talked to me again.
You were one of my reasons
for not choosing Ji Hye
but now, you're protecting
Chae Ro Woon instead of me?
I'm not telling you to take
all of the responsibility.
I told you, we're in this together.
No matter what happens...
I'll be right beside you.
As long as you decide
to expose the truth.
How much...
does Yi Soo know?
Everything.
Yi Soo...
is also hiding something from you.
- What is that?
- Let Yi Soo tell you.
I was the one who covered everything up,
but walk out of those doors yourself.
I think you and Yi Soo need to do that.
You want me to do it myself?
Anyhow, I won't tell you
to stay with Yi Soo anymore.
I shouldn't have asked you to do that.
I was wrong to think that that was
the best way to protect you and Yi Soo.
I'm really sorry.
That's why you don't need
to feel guilty about Yi Soo.
I don't deserve Yi Soo.
I don't know what she's hiding
but I'm sure it's not
as bad as my secret.
She knew I betrayed her...
and she knew you took the fall for
my faults, but pretended not to know.
She just smiled when she was with me.
That sounds like Yi Soo.
You've suffered for long enough.
Let's end it here. Okay?
Gosh! This is annoying!
Oh. When did you get here?
My pencils...
- How did you...
- Wait.
I needed to calm down too.
That's why I tried to copy you.
But this is just pissing me off.
Just use a sharpener. Give it to me.
Hey, wait.
Please teach me how to do it.
It keeps... doing this.
Okay, find the correct angle
between the knife and pencil.
And push it out smoothly.
Like this?
No, no, not like that.
Hold it near the tip
loosen up your body,
and sharpen it with smooth motions.
- Like this.
- I'll loosen up and try it again.
- Like this...
- No.
Gosh.
Like this. Smoothly.
But when did you... get so close?
This won't work.
If we want to draw a line
between us and slow down...
- I can only think of one way.
- And what's that?
You'll see.
Yes! Nice!
I put it down! Three!
I have eight points!
- One go!
- One go?
One go!
I can't kiss him,
so do it for me instead.
Oh yeah!
What are you, a gambler? Seriously.
- Just give it now.
- The score isn't final yet.
We need more.
Gosh, not good.
Oh no, I feel so sorry. How pitiful.
Here it is!
Hooray, I'm loving this.
I won! I won.
As you promised, make my wish come true.
I told you. It can't
involve taking off clothes.
No touching, either.
I won't allow any unreasonable wishes.
Do that thing for me.
What you do alone, early in the morning.
What I do alone... early in the morning?
- I saw it all.
- You saw it?
Yes.
It's on!
Start!
Hurry.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Come on. What is that?
Do it with more passion.
Do it like you mean it.
You were good last time.
Match? match?
I'm tired.
My stomach hurts.
[WOO IL]
One second, please.
Hi, Woo Il.
I'm getting my makeup done.
Why don't you come by to
get your hair done, Mr. Groom?
You're here?
Yi Soo...
Can you come with me?
- Where are we going?
- Well, where should we go?
Is there any place you've wanted to go?
What?
Or something you've wanted to buy?
I want to buy you a present.
Actually, there is one thing I want.
But it's just too expensive.
That's no problem.
Be careful.
- There are no refunds.
- Tell me what it is.
Time with Kang Woo Il.
It's usually expensive,
but it's even more expensive to me.
Can you stay with me
until the wedding ceremony?
That's all I want.
This means you kidnapped
the bride on her wedding day.
But the kidnapper is the groom.
Wow, it's interesting.
Ah, I just remembered
where I want to go.
- How about an amusement park?
- An amusement park?
The playground in my neighborhood?
How is this an amusement park?
You have to protect your
fractured rib for a month.
You must be cold, too.
It's a free pass, so keep it on.
If you lose it,
you don't get to ride anything.
This is the Viking.
Do you want to sit
in the middle or at the end?
- I will sit in the middle.
- Middle? Got it.
Welcome to Woo Il World.
The Viking is about to start.
You have to think this is the Viking.
Let's sit at the end.
All the way at the end!
Ah, it's too high. Too high.
This is a roller coaster.
Can you ride it?
You might not be able to.
It's fun, but we have no safety bar.
Five, four, three!
Gorilla.
Orangutan? Monkey?
- No way.
- Yes, you can do it.
Show me some animals.
Give me a piggyback ride.
Grab those.
- What for?
- You're too heavy.
- This is a carousel.
- This is?
You grab the bar and
ride back and forth like this.
- Feels like a carousel, right?
- No, not at all.
If you close you eyes
and do it, you will feel it.
Watch me.
What is this now?
It's the highlight of our date.
Sitting atop a palace.
This makes me feel like
we're back to being kids.
I miss it.
I also wish I could
go back to those days.
That's why...
I think we need to draw the line here
before anything else happens.
Let's go back.
It's almost time for our wedding.
Yi Soo, be careful.
Stop pretending you're okay.
You can stop putting up with...
such a coward like me now.
You knew what happened...
What was going through
your mind all this time?
It wasn't your fault.
I've made a huge mistake
that I can't reverse.
It affected both you and her.
That's true...
but like you said, if that's
spilled milk and can't be reversed...
wouldn't it be better
if we just buried it?
I told myself the same thing
for the last three years.
I want to stop.
Go home.
I will tell your parents everything.
Don't do that. Don't tell them.
Please don't say anything...
I need you.
How do I look?
Your sister's wedding is tonight.
You don't need to go. Don't go.
But I even practiced a song for them.
It'll be a family gathering.
What was that?
He's telling me to stay out
of his family gathering?
I even got a wedding present for them.
Why is this here?
What are you drawing?
Well, it's what this guy
is looking at all the time.
This guy?
Do you have a boyfriend now?
What? No!
He's just a co-worker.
Was it CEO Kang?
A wedding is a major life event.
They just want us to have
a meal together and be done?
I just can't accept this.
It's the trend to keep
it simple these days.
I'm sure it's because of your election.
You're all about empty
formalities and vanity like me.
Why are you alone?
Where is Yi Soo?
I'm sorry, but she won't be coming.
I knew it. Even you thought a
wedding shouldn't be like this, right?
Yi Soo was trying to be considerate
because you don't have any family.
But this is a once-in-a-lifetime event.
That's not it.
I... just can't marry Yi Soo.
What did you just say?
I've been deceiving you
with dirty lies up until now.
As for the secretary who jumped from
our office building three years ago...
the truth is...
she killed herself because of me.
- What?
- What are you talking about?
Then it wasn't because of Hwan Ki?
He took the blame instead of me.
What on earth did you do to her?
I... had feelings for her.
I betrayed Yi Soo and chose her.
In the end, I betrayed her too.
Oh my goodness...
You...
I will give up everything
you've ever given me and leave.
How could you?
To me, you were...
Thank you for being my family.
I tried to become someone like you.
I don't deserve to
become your real family.
He gave us such shocking news
and is just leaving now?
Honey, you're going to
just let him go like that?
Beat him up or something.
Do what you usually do, Honey.
Honey!
Oh my gosh. Seriously.
What's going to happen to Yi Soo?
Chae Ro Woon.
This drawing...
My late sister drew this, right?
I'm the late Chae Ji Hye's sister.
I know that.
Actually, I was going to come see you...
What were you two to each other, exactly?
Did you love my sister?
Then why? Why did she...
What on earth did you do to my sister?
I have the same necklace.
Ah, do you?
This is a special necklace to me.
Let's go now.
I wanted to see Hwan Ki too...
Did you give this necklace to my sister?
I'm sorry.
I had no idea...
I very deeply regret hurting her.
Did you break up with her?
How did you break up with her?
Did you do it in a
nasty and hurtful way?
She was the one I wanted to be with.
She killed herself because
she thought I dumped her.
Is that what happened?
You destroyed my family...
in order to save yours?
I begged him to do that.
I told your parents everything.
I also told Yi Soo everything earlier.
Why did you tell her alone?
I asked you to do it with me.
You've carried everything
on your back alone this whole time.
I should do it myself from now on.
That's the right thing to do.
- Where is Yi Soo?
- I dropped her off at the house first.
- She might be home...
- Is she alone now?
Boss.
I'm sorry, but I have to go to her.
Please answer, Yi Soo. Please.
Your call is being redirected...
After you're connected,
you will be charged for the call...
How?
How could you? How?
How could you?
[YEON JUNG]
Why are you so uncomfortable?
Is this your first time here?
Come this way.
Sit there.
You probably didn't eat yet,
so let's eat first.
I'm sorry, but I'm actually
not in the mood for this.
I heard from Hwan Ki.
He sent me here.
He asked me to check up on you.
How did I end up falling for him?
That's what I want to say, too.
I'm his so-called "first love."
But he's asking his ex-girlfriend
to care for his current girlfriend.
Isn't he being too harsh on me?
Good. Just laugh about it.
If you want to cry,
just sweat it out instead, okay?
Let's eat first though.
If my sister had seen me,
she'd have been so frustrated.
I was naive enough
to fall for him briefly.
I thought the necklace he gave
my sister was a present for me.
So I cherished it.
Gosh, I'm such a moron.
If your sister had seen you
she'd have said "Good job,"
or, "I'm proud of you, Sis."
The truth would have stayed buried
if it hadn't been for you.
Boss was the one who revealed the truth.
Boss was probably the one
who convinced CEO Kang.
But you don't resent Hwan Ki, eh?
He chose to protect
his sister three years ago.
And this time he walked away
from you to go to his sister instead.
Why wouldn't I? I hate him for that.
But I have a feeling
that he had a good reason.
In fact, that's what scares me.
This might not be the end of it.
Even if I let myself inside the door,
there will be another door to stop me.
Honestly, Hwan Ki is like that.
No matter how hard you try,
you're never really close to him.
When you think you've figured him out,
he keeps turning into somebody else.
It's not easy to love such a person.
Right about now, you should
try to attack me again
saying I should let you take him.
You know me so well.
To a tiny little kiddo,
he's a very difficult man.
Thank you, Yeon Jung.
If you're going to throw it away,
can you give it to me?
Can I see the list of visitors?
You're CEO Eun, aren't you?
How can I help you?
Did Yi Soo come here, by any chance?
Ah, she just went upstairs.
Actually, that necklace...
should've been given to me.
You look like you know what happened.
Are you feeling better now?
Your late sister still
took Kang Woo Il away...
even after her death.
I know that you're a victim, too.
Chae Ji Hye...
I killed her.
Don't blame Kang Woo Il.
He's innocent.
What do you mean?
Are you saying...
that my sister... didn't kill herself?
Stay back.
I just wanted to take back what was mine.
Don't be scared.
I won't hurt anyone.
Because there is only...
one person I want to hurt.
No!
- No, you can't!
- You're putting yourself in danger!
- Don't do this!
- Let go of me!
I killed your sister!
So I will kill myself,
just like how she did!
Let go of me!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I'm asking for a one-on-one
conference tomorrow.
You know tomorrow is
Valentine's Day, right?
It's chocolate for Valentine's Day.
But Ro Woon doesn't want to confess, huh?
I've had a few drinks today, so...
You stay with the company.
You will be by yourself from now on.
But I can't do it without you.
- Did you eat?
- Not yet. Want to eat with me?
We can do it again tomorrow?
- To Silent Monster...
- He must have a lot on his mind.
Shouldn't we help him a little?
He put the hood back on.
Can you start not wearing the hood?
This is my present for Valentine's Day.
I want to kiss you.