This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
[MY SHY BOSS]
Dad! The food is ready!
Okay. Let's eat.
How does it taste?
It's good.
That's a relief.
Gosh, Dad. I wish you'd start
telling me what you're thinking.
Why? I think it's fine.
No, it's not.
Gosh, I'm going to be late.
Are you planning to
continue working there?
You entered that company
with ill intentions...
Ji Hye was the one who sent me there.
Buy this for me instead.
I have a really important audition
after my last performance.
If I wear this, I feel like
they'll acknowledge my worth.
I found someone who understands me
and I found a place
that acknowledges my worth.
And Ji Hye was the one
who made it happen.
That's what I think.
But I heard that necklace
wasn't even a gift from Ji Hye.
But instead,
I received a prettier necklace.
Geez, it's blinding me!
Hey, is that a food tray or a mirror?
It'll burn a hole in the ground.
What's wrong?
I know you're not here to do dishes.
It's because you want to talk, right?
- Well...
- Tell me.
Don't stay all serious
and quiet by yourself.
Don't you realize how
that makes other people feel?
- Really?
- Are you really asking me that?
Do you think I just want
you to understand me?
I want to understand you too.
Stop reading into what
everyone else is thinking
and tell us what you're thinking too.
I wasn't reading anyone.
Well, I guess I did often
try to go the easy route.
I thought I could see what everyone
was feeling. That I could read it.
But it wasn't true.
I deluded myself into thinking
I knew and understood them.
But it was dangerous.
- What do you mean?
- I'm talking about Secretary Chae.
It's possible...
that it all started because of me.
That...
Boss!
I was worried about you.
Where were you all day?
I told you not to close your doors!
No more secrets.
It hasn't been long,
but you're being stubborn again.
Um, Boss.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Why...
are there always more reasons
for why we shouldn't be together?
Pardon?
[EPISODE 15: ONE REASON THAT IS MORE
IMPORTANT THAN 99 OTHER REASONS]
You're CEO Eun Hwan Ki, right?
Yes, but who are you?
Well...
I'm just... Ro Woon's
neighborhood friend.
Oh.
I see.
It looks like you feel relieved,
thinking that it's all over.
But what do we do?
You don't deserve to
smile next to Chae Ro Woon.
- You don't.
- Pardon?
There is something you don't know.
Ji Hye...
didn't like Kang Woo Il, but you.
Um, wait...
I'm not sure what you're saying.
Of course you had no idea.
I'm sure you didn't
give her the time of day.
I think you're mistaken.
The way Ji Hye got involved
with Kang Woo Il...
is beyond me.
But that also started because of you.
She wanted to hear something
from your friend, at the very least.
Should I ask CEO Kang
to deliver it to him?
He could give it to CEO Eun for me.
In the end,
I couldn't give him my drawing.
The woman he's seeing...
is a professional curator
who takes care of real art.
But as for me...
The drawing I drew...
Stop it. You can't even drink.
But I don't hate that woman.
Thanks to her,
I got to go on a short date with him.
I... I was really nervous and excited.
- Pardon?
- Thank you for your help.
Oh.
Hey.
Bad boys are not in style anymore.
Stop being tacky...
He's not a bad person! He's warm.
If a guy mistreats you nine times
but is nice to you once, you're happy.
If a guy's good to you nine times,
but treats you badly once, he changed.
Why can't women do the calculations?
If they're good to you nine times
or once, it's so obvious...
Are you all that stupid?
You're right. I'm stupid.
Even though I know I have no chance
I can't help but to look at him.
The more I look at him,
the more miserable I get...
but I can't seem to stop.
Then tell him! Tell him you like him.
Then I'll never see him again.
I don't think I can live
if I can't see him again.
This is nothing more
than a one-sided love...
Why are you going overboard?
[CEO KANG WOO IL]
Yes, CEO. Right now?
Oh, okay. I'll be there soon.
- Yes.
- Hey!
Who would call you back
to work at a time like this?
- What the heck is that?
- It's not him.
What? You just said "CEO."
You're dumber than I thought!
I'm sorry. I'll pay for the drinks, okay?
Hey. Hey, Chae Ji Hye!
Don't go.
Thanks for listening.
I'm glad I have someone to vent to.
I'm sorry.
You could have looked at her, just once.
You could have
listened to her, just once.
She was always
earnestly looking at you...
How could you disregard her so brutally?
More than anyone else...
you hurt her the most.
you are responsible.
But...
you want to be by her sister's side?
Reporter Woo...
worked really hard by himself
to expose the truth three years ago.
But he was stopped near the end
and he was even fired
by the publishing company.
But he never told me about this.
I think he wanted to...
respect Secretary Chae.
She would have wanted
to keep it a secret.
Then...
Ji Hye...
wasn't miserable because
she was rejected by CEO Kang.
It was because...
she couldn't face you again.
I guess the misery of not
being able to take it all back...
was what pushed her over the edge.
Please.
Please... pick up.
The number is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone...
CEO... CEO Eun.
The intended recipient
of Ji Hye's drawing...
was not CEO Kang, but you.
- What are you drawing?
- Um...
It's a view that someone
is always looking at.
I thought there were always
a lot of people around CEO Kang.
I thought that was why she drew
a picture of many people in a building.
But it wasn't true...
CEO Eun.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just...
I realized, on your window sill...
there's no dust. It's clean.
I do the cleaning.
You don't have to worry about that.
Yes, I apologize.
The view that you always
admire outside your window.
The flower shop and bakery
on the first floor...
A cafe on the second floor...
And a hair salon on the third floor.
Is that right?
I guess...
she wanted to fill that
concrete building with people.
Because you're always alone...
I think she wanted
warm people to be by your side.
Here.
Take it.
The picture finally found
its rightful owner.
Why are you looking at me like that?
No, it's just... that you look different.
I've never seen you
so laid back, even at home.
It wakes you up, doesn't it?
I'm sorry.
This is the real me.
No, you look comfortable.
I am.
I don't have to dress up
because I'm always at home.
And I don't have to say
what I don't want to say.
I don't have to strain myself because
of what others might think either.
You're always home?
Mom and Dad want me
to stay home for the time being.
- They must be embarrassed of me.
- Hey, no way.
They're worried...
Anyway, I sneaked out just now,
so I have to go back soon.
Why did you call me here?
I... was worried about you.
I didn't think you
were lacking in any way.
I thought you were someone
who didn't need my help.
That's why when you did anything
for me, I took it for granted...
No.
I even found it bothersome at times.
I didn't even know I hurt you so much.
That's why I feel so bad.
Forget it.
It wasn't because of you.
Hey. You're doing it again.
You're being considerate to me again.
You said you were
comfortable not dressing up.
You're prettier...
than ever before.
So stop holding it in.
If you have something to say, say it.
Fine.
It was all because of you.
I hate you.
That's better.
But it's still weak.
I don't want you to be happy without me.
I hope you fail in life.
Is that all? I don't think it's enough.
Keep going.
You mean bastard. You son of a bitch!
You bastard.
Yeah.
I deserve at least that.
I didn't think I'd see you again.
I thought you'd run away
if I told the truth.
I thought it'd all be over.
Geez.
What are you taking?
Health is also a skill.
Oh, I'm not sick.
These are diet pills.
- Who are you trying to impress?
- It's not like that!
I'm going to change.
I'm going to take care of myself
and love myself from now on.
What are you doing later tonight?
Oh, tonight...
I'm sure you don't have plans. I know.
Don't sit in your room checking other
people's relationship statuses, okay?
Geez, I really thought
about you for this one.
Here.
What is this?
It's a concert
that Brain PR is working on.
Go see it. I'll go with you.
Geez, I'm such a great colleague.
I'm thankful,
but I have prior commitments.
With whom?
- With myself.
- What?
There's a lecture on promotions
tonight that I'm going to.
What? Since when do you go to those?
Since now! I told you!
I'm going to take care of myself
and love myself from now on.
Let's go together next time.
Wait...
Hey!
Hey, approach her in a warm way.
Gyo Ri is delicate,
so she'll be attracted to a warm man.
I think you have this wrong.
Are you trying to be a bad guy by joking
and saying what you don't mean?
That makes you a horrible person!
No.
Go to this.
Oh! These are concert tickets! Hey!
Thanks! I should go
to this with my husband.
These are diet pills.
Um, about that lecture.
May I come with you?
Oh.
Would you like to come?
In exchange, I'll buy dinner.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
See? What did I tell you?
Gosh, you're so lacking!
Why are you doing this to me?
Gosh, have some chocolates instead.
- I hate sweet things!
- Eat it and get yourself together!
- Stop this!
- Wake up!
Thanks to you, I had a
valuable time learning about PR.
But you dozed off the whole time.
Geez, why am I in this state?
All of our team members have found
their place and have started to grow.
But all I do is get into accidents.
You said you had another dream
of becoming a celebrity.
That's true.
But I still feel like...
we're getting more distant.
And these days,
I feel like you're older than me.
Once you also start on
your path to your true dream
you will change too.
What is this?
You're pushing me out too easily.
- I guess you feel no affection.
- What do you mean?
- I used to like you.
- That's why...
What did you say?
Would you like stop by my house?
Wait, excuse me? All of a sudden?
Your parents must be home.
Um, wait.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I knew you'd have that expression.
It's because of where I live, isn't it?
Me? Not at all.
This is a rooftop room,
the symbol of dreams.
You know, young adults
who have dreams and passions
all live in rooftop rooms like this one.
- I've always wanted to do it.
- You're exaggerating.
I knew you'd react this way,
which was why I couldn't confess to you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize how you felt.
No, it's fine. I'm sorry.
When we were pretending to date
I shouldn't have developed
those one-sided feelings.
I want to return the clothes
you bought me.
But why?
Take it.
It's really over now.
But we didn't even start.
Even though it was fake
I was thankful to you.
I confessed,
and now I have no feelings left.
Get home safely.
Last time, Hwan Ki took all my dishes
and today, it's you?
I'm not here to see you,
so don't worry about it.
I'm here to volunteer too.
Thanks to someone,
I feel very ill inside!
- It's cold.
- I'm sorry. I didn't see you there.
I'm worried about how Hwan Ki is doing.
I'm sure he's fine.
He has someone who's always
knocking and dragging him outside.
But even if that's true,
it won't be easy.
We were all stupid.
Not one of us truly told anyone
how we really felt.
I know.
- But you're something else, Kang Woo Il.
- "Kang Woo Il"?
You don't see me as older anymore?
No, I just thought about it.
Three years ago, Secretary Chae
was actually interested in someone else
but you misunderstood
and pursued her all by yourself.
Hey.
I don't know if I should say this...
but it serves you right!
Wow, you're not afraid to say anything
anymore. You're starting to scare me.
I know, right?
Why did you have to open me up?
The same goes for Hwan Ki.
After his doors open,
they won't close so easily.
You're so dumb.
Why don't you keep going? Try me.
This is Reporter Woo,
who's been attacking you all this time.
He used to be a reporter
at a major newspaper company.
He was a close friend of the secretary
who killed herself three years ago.
And I found out something
while I was digging for information.
The late Secretary Chae's sister
is working at Brain PR.
What?
Since the news broke out
about CEO Eun's entitlement
it seems she's been giving
information to Reporter Woo.
Please stop doing that.
We don't have the space for them.
Even if you do all this
Ro Woon won't budge.
Come inside.
I thought I should tell you
that there is no point in
you coming by from now on.
I'm closing the shop soon.
Pardon? Why so suddenly?
The owner of the building has changed.
They raised the rent ridiculously high.
He's getting fewer customers, gosh.
He's been here for the last 30 years.
How could this happen overnight?
I don't know why Ro Woon
locked herself in again.
It looks as if you two are
not meant to be together.
Just let it go.
Now I can see it was
all about that girl, huh?
Did she talk you into throwing Woo Il out
since he made her sister kill herself?
She didn't talk me into doing that.
You sure need a lot of care.
Did you do something to
New York Barber, by any chance?
Why did you do that?
They have nothing left.
Did you really have to do that to them?
You saw how troubled Yi Soo became.
True. What happened to Yi Soo
made me realize something.
I have to find your match myself.
- Pardon?
- Wow!
Right on time.
- Yeon Jung.
- Hello, I'm Seo Yeon Jung.
Thank you for making
the time to come out.
I have no patience and
wanted to meet you quickly.
Please have a seat.
What brings you here?
You didn't know I was coming?
Hey, if you were seeing her,
you should've told me sooner.
Why did you make me get involved?
You know how shy Hwan Ki is.
I should've come to see you first.
I heard you two knew
each other in college, huh?
We're not in such a relationship.
Yes, I tried to go out with him
back then and I'm still trying now.
I really like him.
I like how straightforward you are.
I want to make you my
daughter-in-law as soon as possible.
What do you say?
Would you marry Hwan Ki?
Marry Hwan Ki?
Just the thought makes me happy.
Excuse me, but...
But what can I say?
I wouldn't like my future father-in-law.
What?
I like how careful Hwan Ki is.
He's a bit slow,
but he's considerate of others.
That's just because...
But you're very different from him.
You're more vigorous and impatient
with an impelling drive.
Since I'm more like that,
I wouldn't like someone similar.
I appreciate you thinking highly of me
and asking me out here.
But I thought you'd talk to him first.
Seeing you push forward this urgently...
I assume you already looked into me.
Well...
Since we're talking about it,
I'll be upfront.
Can we not live with you guys
after we get married?
We will come over
on major holidays and such.
Does your family hold memorial
services for your ancestors?
I'm not good at making such dishes.
I admit that I was too hasty.
I was too rude, wasn't I?
But I really don't think this is the way.
I'm sorry I made you uncomfortable.
Is this the start of my sad love story
where I go against
my family's wishes?
[NEW YORK BARBER]
What's all that?
We have to keep this place alive.
Actually, I have
experience in promotions.
Maybe it's time to get out
of this tiny barbershop.
You've also felt suffocated.
This is where your whole
life story is written.
We should protect our memories
with Mom and my sister.
[NEW YORK BARBER]
[30 YEARS OF TRADITION]
Hello, I'm from New York Barber.
Hello. Thank you.
Hello. Please take this.
This is New York Barber.
Please come.
Thank you.
- Aw, so cute.
- How cute.
Boss?
- Aw, so cute.
- How cute.
Boss?
What is he thinking?
Please leave.
Don't do that.
Boss.
What? You're not Boss?
Are you Jang Se Jong then?
No way. You're Boss. Let me see then.
What's going on?
Seeing how cute he is and all...
is it really Jang Se Jong?
Fine, I'm Jang Se Jong today.
In order to be with you,
I can lose myself and be anybody else.
So cute.
So cute!
Include this sign please.
It's New York Barber, people!
Please come by!
Honestly...
I'm getting...
too old for this.
Here, drink this.
"Drink this"?
You're Jang Se Jong.
I can't talk to you that way?
That's enough, Boss.
It must be hard, so take it off, okay?
Seriously, hold still.
Now reveal yourself!
Seriously.
What are you doing?
Let me go, Boss.
I'm sorry.
Can you just think this isn't me?
I just want to see your face once.
Can I see your face
even if it's like this?
I've missed you so much.
Mommy, if a bear and
a human fall in love...
will Dangun be born?
(FOUNDER OF GOJEOSEON, "SON OF A BEAR")
What are you saying?
No Ah, let's go.
After this, just go.
You said you missed me.
Missing you is one thing.
But the fact we can't be together
is an entirely different matter.
Here. Since I have a very low
budget for this promotion
this is all I can afford.
Thank you for coming though.
No need to thank me.
It was my father who made
things difficult for the barbershop.
What? How could he?
I'm sorry.
Now there is one more
reason it can't be me.
But I still came.
Even if I shouldn't,
I decided to do it anyway.
Even if you come this way, I can't...
All this time, it was you who came to me.
You believed in me
without knowing what I was up to.
After you learned the truth,
you easily forgave me.
It's okay to lock yourself in.
All the things you did for me,
such as knocking on my door...
making sure I was okay,
and taking me out of my room.
I will do all that from now on.
How am I supposed to face my late sister?
I can't do that.
I will do what you can't do.
I will be indecent enough to stay
with you when you tell me not to.
I will do it all.
Even if you do all that, I still can't.
It's the job of the special forces
to make the impossible possible.
Special forces.
So let me help with the barbershop, okay?
Because my father is responsible. Okay?
Please let me do it.
I don't know.
It's the same as what
happened three years ago.
Even if you scream,
people don't hear you out.
Something is different now.
What is?
You're not alone now.
Gosh, you're so cheesy now.
I'm about to have one more reason
why you shouldn't be...
I wasn't talking about me.
Gosh.
I knew you'd do promotions
at this elementary level.
Don't you dare tell people
you work at Silent Monster!
Sun Bong.
Agreed. You have a lot to learn.
Who said you could quit?
Yoo Hee.
You should've called me about this.
We all came to help, Ro Woon.
You all seriously... thank you all.
As you already know,
going to a hair salon is trendy.
If we beg you to come to
an almost-forgotten barbershop...
we will only sound pathetic.
Then what?
Rather than complaining about
the changes of the world...
it's easier, faster, and
more effective to change myself.
Do you like red ginseng?
Take one.
And then can you fill out this survey?
Hello, could you fill out this survey?
- Hello.
- Take this red ginseng.
- Can you take this survey?
Feel free to answer the questions.
Take this red ginseng as a reward.
Take one survey sheet.
- Yoo Hee, you take one, too.
- One for me?
We have do thorough market
research first for renovation.
You look like an actor.
Wow, you look cool.
It looks good on you.
It makes you look 10 years younger.
Are you my dad?
You look cool. You look so different.
Why don't you replace
the towels altogether?
To match the theme of the interior
and even the sign outside.
You can also change the name
of the shop to match the theme.
It would be nice to change
the floor, ceiling, and wall this way.
I... don't know how to
thank you for all this.
But I'm uncomfortable
with this whole idea.
Change is the only way to survive.
If I want to change everything
what's the point of
staying at that location?
I'm sorry that you
put a lot of work into this.
- It's okay.
- Not at all.
- You're entitled to feel that way.
- Not at all, sir.
Dad...
Then... I will go home first.
Please get home safely.
Why doesn't he want to
come out of his comfort zone?
It was our fault for pushing him to
change without asking him first.
We have to find a way to get through
to him that won't change him.
Does such a thing exist?
I only heard someone say that.
There has to be a way of
communicating that works for you.
Try to find it.
Don't try to change.
I will find a way, so don't worry.
Go home.
- I will go home then.
- Go ahead.
Suk Joon?
Please do me this favor.
He's a very famous anchor...
I can't guarantee if he'll do it or not.
- You know that, right?
- Sure. Thank you.
Just ask him to take
a look at the proposal.
[NEW YORK BARBER]
In return, I also have
a favor to ask of you.
Can you pretend to be
my boyfriend just once?
What?
You know he's my first crush
from my church, right?
I was a kid at that time who wore braces.
I want to show him
that I'm totally different now.
Of all people, why me?
I played a rude bride-to-be
in front of your father.
You can put on a show for me, can't you?
- I still find it hard to do...
- Ah, you don't want to?
When did I say I didn't want to?
Let's do it.
You will do it then, right?
I like the idea.
I can just say hi and leave, right?
- Correct. Kiss me before you leave.
- Okay... what?
To be honest, I also have
a painful past involving him.
He was sort of seeing me
and I ended up witnessing
him kiss my best friend.
I want my trauma treated.
But still, a kiss isn't right...
Just a light kiss to say bye.
Can't you do that much?
I can't do it.
Then I can't do it either.
Wait. Then I will kiss you on the cheek.
- On my lips.
- On your cheek.
Fine. On the cheek.
Let's go in.
The cheek, okay?
- Suk Joon, long time no see.
- Hi, Yeon Jung. How have you been?
Who is he?
This is CEO Eun Hwan Ki
of Silent Monster.
He's my boyfriend.
- Oh, hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- He wanted to say hi.
- I see.
Honey, you can go now.
Go? Now?
Thanks. See you.
- You're all set.
- Thank you.
Because I kept adopting trendy
hairstyles that didn't look good on me...
I heard my hair stylist doesn't like me.
But in New York Barber...
I can feel the weight of
a tradition spanning 30 years.
Thank you, Yeon Jung.
Thank Hwan Ki instead.
I only introduced them.
Most of all, I liked the idea.
The production crew liked it, too.
I'm leaving for America tonight.
What? America?
I'll be gone for a while, this time.
But don't be too happy about that.
Why so suddenly?
Well, I suppose I'll
linger in his thoughts?
I haven't told Hwan Ki that I'm leaving.
I was hoping that I'd
linger painfully in his mind.
But you still need to say goodbye...
Well, we kind of said goodbye.
Please take care of him.
I...
I know, but I'm asking you.
Have a safe flight, Yeon Jung.
Come see me in America.
Please get in line!
Don't cut the line!
What's happening?
Wow, take a photo here.
There you go. Here it is.
I'm a friend of his.
- Wow, there are a lot of customers.
- Hello.
Please have seat here and wait.
People wait in line for this place.
Bring them in.
What's going on here?
Don't worry about the monthly rent.
At this rate, you can buy this building.
It's just temporary.
Don't change anything.
Just stay the same.
Of course.
[YOO HEE]
Hi, Yoo Hee.
What?
At the end of last year
when a corruption case involving major
construction companies came about
a scandal involving a well-known
actor happened to break out.
The one who knew about
the scandal was Silent Monster.
CEO Eun Hwan Ki, who was
involved in his own scandal
helped President Park of
Rose Airlines to regain his status.
This means more than
"Birds of a feather flock together."
Assemblyman Eun's winning
of the mayoral election
heavily relies on
President Park's in-laws.
Assemblyman Eun has a strong network
in the press and his political circle.
He's quite a master
in dealing with such matters.
When someone jumped off
his company building and died
he covered it up
so there would be no reports on it.
I'm the secretary of CEO Eun.
When his authority issues broke out
he wiggled his way out, showing his
impressive crisis management skills.
Assemblyman Eun gets
rid of uncomfortable truth.
And he lies to put more spotlight
on the convenient issues.
It was Brain PR and Silent Monster
who did all the work for him.
Reporter Woo, how could you
do this without asking me first?
Did you even know that Eun Bok Dong
was involved in the barbershop ordeal?
I know that, but there is
something you're mistaken about.
Boss... Silent Monster...
Ultimately, truth is a
very relative concept.
I'm sorry.
Why can't you go?
What was the call about?
Ji Hye...
she liked that man.
What?
What troubled her the most was...
she didn't think he knew
what she was feeling.
How...
am I supposed to let him in?
There is one way out of this.
Tell them Kang Woo Il did all that
out of extreme loyalty.
- Father...
- He left the company anyway.
Tell them we let him go
after we figured everything out.
That's enough!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
There is only one I want to be with.
I was always in the same place.
She made me run.
She came running towards me.
How long will you stay
by yourself like this?
- I can't sleep...
- Want to watch porn?
That's really sexy.
- Go wash up.
- Want me to wash up?
From head to toe?
Tell me now.
Tell me what you don't like.
Just don't look at what you
don't like or ask about it.
Or don't be curious.
I'm alone again.
Whoever loses should do
what the winner wants.
My wish is complete.
What is your wish?