(FLOWER BOSS, FLOWER DELIVERY SERVICE)
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
(EPISODE 2: I'M SORRY, I APOLOGIZE)
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry!
- What are you so sorry for?
(EPISODE 2: I'M SORRY, I APOLOGIZE)
(EPISODE 2: I'M SORRY, I CANNOT APOLOGIZE)
I should have mustered up my courage earlier.
I hesitated for too long and lost my chance.
Where is she now?
Why did she quit all of a sudden?
- My goodness.
- What about Mr. Smith?
You reek of alcohol.
Why are you here? Did you get fired already?
I did see this coming.
Did Mr. Smith come here or not?
He just left. Didn't you see him?
Ro Woon!
Are you Mr. Smith?
I'm Chae Ro Woon.
These flowers are for me, right?
Yes. Well, it's...
I'm... I'm your...
Where is Mr. Smith?
- Who?
- Mr. Smith.
The person who sent me this bouquet.
- Who is it?
- Well, the thing is...
Actually, I...
I know you can't tell me even if I ask. I know that.
However, I must find out today.
What kind of person is he? Tell me.
Who is he?
Move the bouquet.
What is he like?
I said, what is he like?
Won't you tell me?
You can't go until you tell me.
I'm sorry.
Stop!
I want to meet him!
It's because today's the last day.
I want to meet him since today's the final show.
Please take me to Mr. Smith. Please?
Please?
If you can't take me to him,
at least give him this message.
Tell him that I thank him so much for everything.
Thanks to Mr. Smith, I was able to go through hard times.
Got it?
Please forward my message.
I'll get going then.
Can I ask you one thing?
How did you know I didn't leave?
Go ahead.
Why are you suddenly leaving the stage?
That's a secret...
even for Mr. Smith.
Why do you keep calling him Mr. Smith?
My goodness.
- We weren't eavesdropping.
- Let's go.
That's the alias Daddy-long-legs used.
John Smith.
My older sister...
committed suicide three years ago.
My sister used to always send me...
bouquets whenever I performed.
Although...
she was no longer in this world,
I kept getting flowers.
I felt like she was still alive.
Mr. Smith...
must be my sister's friend...
or her past lover.
Or perhaps...
Are you still there?
Do you really want to know who he is?
Don't tell me.
Actually, I want to know,
but I also don't.
I want to remain curious and let it make my heart flutter.
I can imagine all I want.
Even if my sister isn't around, I'll act like she is.
I never told this anyone.
How did I end up telling it in a smelly washroom?
And the men's washroom at that.
On top of that, I told someone that's super quiet.
"Are you all right?"
"It must have been tough."
You don't even know how to console someone like that.
My sister was just like you.
She had her mouth shut like a clam.
Sir,
is there something you want to say to me?
She should have said so if she was suffering.
She was hurting so much,
yet I didn't hear a peep from her.
In the last three years,
that was the hardest part of all.
Not knowing...
why my sister died.
I was right beside her.
We even shared a room.
Why didn't she tell me?
I wish she had just said...
something.
I must tell her...
so that the tragedy doesn't repeat itself.
- Put pressure on it.
- Okay.
All done.
Thank you.
Excuse me, where is patient Kim Gyo Ri?
Over here.
Mr. Eun?
Am I hearing things now?
Ms. Kim.
It's me, Eun Hwan Gi.
Just listen as you are.
Actually,
I...
I have a small problem.
Well...
I have a disorder that prevents me from interacting...
I mean,
I have extreme difficulty interacting with people.
If people find out, I might get in trouble.
Please keep it to yourself.
Well...
What I'm saying is...
I'm...
really sorry...
for giving you a hard time.
I'll give you paid leave, so take a rest.
Make sure you get treated.
I'll of course pay the medical fees.
Also, if you'd like,
I'll introduce you to a psychotherapist as well.
I can't guarantee her competence, though.
She...
failed to fix me.
I'm...
so sorry...
for giving you a hard time.
- The bike has started.
- What are you talking about?
I got rid of my constipation.
What I mean is...
Mr. Eun.
Relax. Breathe.
There you go. Start talking again.
I finally...
I finally told her.
I told her.
Mr. Eun. Mr. Eun?
Nice shot!
The CEO of Brain is the most searched name on the web right now.
What?
Really? Let me see.
- What is this?
- What is all that?
Let me see.
(UNDER THE VEIL WAS A CRUEL BOSS)
- Good shot.
He's great.
This article is about Mr. Eun's son.
- It is.
- My goodness.
- He abused his power?
- Are you talking about my son?
(CONGRESSMAN'S SON ABUSES HIS POWER)
(THE CEO OF BRAIN HAS BEEN TREATING HIS SECRETARY CRUELLY.)
(HIS SECRETARY HAS ENDED UP GETTING HOSPITALIZED.)
That brat.
We can't reach him at the moment.
Please wait.
- Here.
- We're preparing a statement.
We cannot tell you anything yet.
My goodness.
Here. Gosh.
- Where's Mr. Kang?
- Yes? Hello?
- He's not picking up.
- He's been out of reach.
- Hello?
We're preparing a statement.
- That's not true.
- We'll reveal everything.
We're not really sure.
Where is he at a time like this?
- He must be here.
- Where is he?
Please say something.
I told you. The CEO is not here.
Please go back.
That's him.
Did you treat your secretary cruelly?
- Did you not feed her?
- Is it true?
- How much of it is true?
- Please say something.
- Is she hospitalized?
- Mr. Eun.
- Please say something.
Please explain.
Did Mr. Eun treat his secretary cruelly?
She's hospitalized. Did he hit her?
Are there any other victims?
Did he really not feed her?
Has he visited her at the hospital? Has he apologized?
Why did he treat her cruelly?
Did he abuse his power?
I'm the co-CEO, Kang Woo Il.
You've come all the way here,
but I'm afraid I can't tell you anything for now.
We'll prepare an official statement as soon as possible.
Please come back then.
- He's such a good speaker.
- My goodness.
- He's the best.
- He's amazing.
Please explain what happened.
Do you admit it?
Where is Mr. Eun now?
Did he hit her?
Did he treat her cruelly?
Is Mr. Eun's father aware of this?
What will happen to Mr. Eun's father?
What's going to happen? Please say something.
- Will he run for the election?
- Will he remain as a candidate?
- Please say something.
- Will he run for the election?
- Will it get in his way?
- Please say something.
Please tell us the truth.
Brain never hides or avoids anything.
We won't make any superficial apology.
That's why we need time.
If we did anything wrong, we'll admit it...
and come up with a plan to improve.
I beg you to give us some time.
So many of you came despite the cold.
Wasn't it cold on the way here?
- It was really cold.
- We waited so long.
- I apologize.
- Look at him.
He's so handsome.
We'll look into what happened and come up with an official statement.
Please wait.
Mr. Eun.
- Why is she here?
- Don't you recognize me?
We've met before.
Well technically, I didn't see your face,
so I guess I can't say that we've properly met.
Still, I saw a lot of you apart from your face.
She followed me all the way to my office.
Did it all start from there?
You're Mr. Eun Hwan Gi, aren't you?
Let go of me.
Are you crazy?
Ms. Kim couldn't have done this all by herself.
You seem perplexed.
Could she be involved in this?
Are you okay?
Wait.
I'm sorry, but could you use another elevator?
I'm sorry.
You should keep low. I'll take care of...
- Do you know her?
- Who do you mean?
Do you mean Ms. Chae?
She works here. She's our new employee.
A new employee?
Why? Did she say something to you?
No, it's nothing.
Did she quit musicals all of a sudden...
to get a job at my company?
What is she trying...
to do here?
What about the article? Did you read it?
(BRAIN'S CO-CEO ILL-TREATED HIS SECRETARY)
(IS HIS FATHER A CONGRESSMAN?)
(BRAIN'S CEO, MR. EUN HWAN GI, TREATED HIS SECRETARY CRUELLY.)
I still can't get a hold of Ms. Kim.
She disappeared after she got discharged.
The hospital staff told me that a man came to see her before she left.
Ms. Kim.
It's me, Eun Hwan Gi.
It must be because of money. She has to support her entire family.
She's not that kind of person.
You don't even know her well.
I know her better than you do.
It's okay.
I'll sort everything out so that there's no problem, so don't worry.
I shouldn't have given her money when she's so hungry for it.
Anyway, she'll get in touch with us soon.
If she wants more money, that is.
Hey. See?
Kang Woo Il speaking.
Ms. Kim?
No, it's totally fine.
Thank you for calling.
Where are you now? I'll pick you up.
Stay right there. I'll be there shortly.
She's in front of our building now.
- I'll go with you, then.
- No, Hwan Gi.
You don't need to get involved.
Reporters might swarm in again, so you should lay low.
I'll be back soon.
What if Chae Ro Woon has something to do with this incident?
It's only a matter of time before Ms. Kim talks about Chae Ro Woon.
She's in danger.
Ji Hye.
I'll make him...
fall all the way down to the bottom.
I'll show you.
- Hello, Sir.
- Where is Hwan Gi?
Please calm down. Let me explain...
He must be shuddering in fear in that penthouse of this.
You lead the way.
It's my fault. I should've sorted out the situation sooner.
But the word didn't leak out because of...
Where's that secretary?
I was just about to try contacting her.
Go bring her right now!
That blabbing mouth of hers.
I'll cut it all up...
and thinly slice her tongue,
and store it in a jar with brine.
Gosh, what should I do?
The former CEO looks like a scary man.
I bet he can fire me without even blinking an eye.
I'm so dead.
Where did he go?
Please let me handle it. You should just head home now, Sir.
"Eun Hwan Gi is apparently Congressman Eun Bok Dong's son."
Reporters are excited about their newly-found prey.
You should avoid running into them at all costs.
Please don't worry.
I have a plan that can turn this crisis into an opportunity.
That project you told me about the other day?
Yes. The only challenge I'd have is persuading Hwan Gi.
Let me handle him.
Sir... Sir.
Don't be surprised. Just listen.
It's not me. I didn't do it. Please believe me.
Please lower your voice.
I swear I've never told any of my family or friends about you.
I've let my guard down just once. I told just one person.
I had no idea that would explode like this.
Is it really her, then?
- Please forgive me, Sir.
- Lower your voice, please.
I'll tell you everything.
I'll tell you with whom I chatted to.
Please let me live.
- It was...
- Shut it if you want to live.
Ms. Kim, you didn't do anything wrong.
You didn't disclose anything to anyone.
Pardon me?
You didn't say anything to anybody. Do you understand?
That means... So you're saying...
No matter what anyone does to persuade you, keep playing innocent.
Only then, you can get out of this.
Sir.
So you're worried about me.
Ms. Kim.
What took you so long?
I was really worried about you.
I'm saying it because I feel so bad that you have to go through this.
I wish you reached out to me sooner.
It would've been great if you hadn't signed...
the confidentiality agreement when you joined the company.
If you leave like this, you'll be known as a whistle-blower...
and won't be able to get another job.
I... I never said...
anything to anyone.
I already know everything. You can be open with me.
That man who came to see you at the hospital. Who is he?
It was Mr. Eun.
Mr. Eun visited me at the hospital.
- You mean Hwan Gi?
- Yes.
You find it hard to believe, right? I was so surprised, too.
He even brought me flowers. Why would I do such a thing to him?
I really didn't do it.
Please believe me.
Goodness.
(FLOWER BOSS, FLOWER DELIVERY SERVICE)
(SECRETARY CHAE JI HYE)
(3 YEARS AGO)
I'm sorry to interrupt, Sir.
If there's nothing else you'd like me to take care of, I'll get...
Come in.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Excuse me, Sir.
Is there something you want to say to me?
You seem to be in a bad mood today.
If you could tell me what I did wrong, I'll...
I lost a cuff link.
Now I only have one.
Can you find me the same one?
- Right now?
- Right now.
You hardly wear dress shirts.
If you tell me when you plan on wearing it...
I thought...
I said right now.
Yes. Right now.
Right away, Sir.
Yes. I'm sorry, Ro Woon.
I don't think I can make it tonight.
I hope you do well even if I'm not there.
I know. I do.
You work for the best PR company in Korea.
You serve the CEO of the best company in the country.
Are you trying to make that obvious?
Mom and Dad only care about you, and they don't care about my shows.
I don't need flowers. I want you to come.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
(FLOWER BOSS, FLOWER DELIVERY SERVICE)
Yes. Is this the florist?
I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry!
- What are you so sorry for?
Are you all right?
That was dangerous. What were you doing?
Don't tell me you were thinking of jumping.
Don't ever do that again, okay?
Are you hurt?
My arm...
My arm.
My goodness.
You dropped this.
"Flower delivery service"?
Let's do as she wants.
Then things will go back to the way it was.
Regardless of my intention,
I ended up...
hurting someone.
I admit it is something I cannot deny.
I'm reflecting upon it.
I apologize.
- Hello, Ms. Park.
- Hello.
- Are you well?
- Yes.
How are you?
Will he come?
- No way.
- Who?
The penthouse ghost.
The hidden monster that's hiding behind a veil.
Of course he should be here.
The person responsible should apologize himself.
Otherwise, it's not sincere.
To be an heir of the owner...
allows you never to be sorry.
It's always the weak that have to be sorry.
Thanks to the mess a higher-up made,
look at how many staff have to pick up afterwards.
These days, it's a trend for the CEO to be apologetic...
even when a small problem arises.
He's old-fashioned.
He doesn't know what trend is.
No way.
He'll show up if he's human.
Hey.
- He's not human.
- He's a zombie.
Regardless... Regardless of my intention,
I ended up...
hurting someone.
I admit it is something I cannot deny...
I can do it. I have to.
I can do it.
Why did you come down here?
I'll apologize to everyone myself.
What?
Come with me.
I said I'll take care of it.
You can just hide behind me.
I know you cover for me a lot. So this time, I'll do it myself.
In that condition?
What are you thinking?
I'll admit my fault honestly.
It might bring what happened three years ago to light.
Will you be honest about that, too?
Is that what you're scared of?
Have you ever been in my office before?
Compared to your penthouse,
it looks like a doghouse.
- Woo Il.
- But I don't care.
People tell me...
that I struggle to benefit from my rich friend...
and that I shouldn't work too hard...
because the money will never be mine.
The money will go to the ghost CEO.
No matter what they say,
I've always tried to...
make things easier for you...
and cover up your weaknesses.
Just like you covered up my secret.
Don't worry. What happened three years ago...
will remain hidden.
So please let me talk to the people.
This is not like you.
- Are you really Hwan Gi?
- I have to do it for it to end.
Nothing will end. I'll make sure nothing ends.
Just trust me.
- This time, I...
- Can you...
really stand before all those people?
Can you really express your opinions correctly in front of everyone?
If you're confident that you won't make a fool of yourself, do it.
Hey.
Hwan Gi, I'm sorry for being harsh.
I'm getting impatient because the reporters are waiting.
I'll keep it short.
Will you step down from your position for the time being?
It's just a formality, you know.
All right. I should. I was going to.
Instead,
take charge of a new project.
Your father will tell you the details.
He's waiting for you.
You two decided on what I should do?
He must have calmed down by now.
I had a hard time calming him down.
I have to go now.
Can you really stand before all those people?
We're sorry for making you wait.
We have someone here who can clear up all the misunderstanding.
Please sit there.
See?
I'm...
Mr. Eun Hwan Gi's secretary.
The article is...
completely false.
What?
I was hospitalized...
because of my chronic disease.
Mr. Eun even visited me at the hospital with flowers...
and cheered me up.
I'm very perplexed...
that false things about me have been published against my will.
Mr. Eun and my colleagues,
I'm really sorry for the trouble I caused the company.
- I have a question.
You seem to be in a bad condition. Did you come here voluntarily?
As you just said,
was there no cruel treatment?
Have you met Mr. Eun?
Were you put under coercion?
Please explain.
Hold on.
I'm the CEO of Brain, Kang Woo Il.
I'll answer your questions, considering my employee's condition.
Where's Mr. Eun?
He couldn't adjust his plans abroad,
so he's still outside of Korea.
That's all a lie.
You're stuck in your room every day.
Do you call yourself a man?
Can't you do any better?
I thought you said you're quite good when you play against a wall.
Golf and tennis.
Real sports let you mingle with other people.
Why do you make a fool of yourself whenever people look at you?
Why do you always get so timid in front of people?
Gosh.
Why does Mr. Eun never show up in front of people?
We just divided our work efficiently.
Mr. Eun takes care of the internal matters of the company,
and I undertake all the external businesses.
Three years ago, Mr. Eun's secretary jumped from the office rooftop.
- Is that...
- That's not related to this at all.
There's a rumor that Mr. Eun is impossible to communicate with.
That's exaggerated.
But I humbly admit that there was not enough communication.
To prevent any further misunderstandings,
we've come up with an improvement plan.
Mr. Eun...
will be resigning...
from his position.
I can't believe this.
What?
You didn't win that position because you deserved it.
We're starting a venture in the company.
And you'll take charge of the team.
- Sorry?
- Break out of the egg.
Be reborn.
I can't.
This is your last chance.
If you don't pull yourself together, I'll give the company to Woo Il.
I'm not interested in taking over the company.
What? How dare you say that?
My goodness.
Gosh.
I'd rather start something alone.
Alone? What nonsense!
You can't do anything alone from now on.
Come in.
Stay seated.
You should learn to mingle with people.
An in-house venture doesn't have the customary corporate structure.
Neither does it have rigid hierarchy...
nor unnecessary formalities that can hinder the organization's growth.
In that new horizontal structure, Mr. Eun Hwan Gi will become...
a leader with communicative leadership who can have...
flourishing relationships with our employees.
In-house venture? What is going on?
My gosh, that's so clever.
They'll avoid the blame...
and pretend that he's giving up his CEO position when he's actually not.
My goodness.
I have a question.
This decision will shock many people considering that Mr. Eun...
is the heir of the company.
Has the founder of the company, Congressman Eun, agreed to it?
Of course.
Many second-generation conglomerates have been involved in scandals.
Even though the article is false,
he is deeply distressed because it may have hurt some people.
He asked us to fundamentally revamp our corporate system.
I promise that we will change.
I sincerely apologize...
for causing you concern.
Mr. Kang never disappoints me.
He's so good at everything,
but his crisis management skills are truly outstanding.
From planning to execution, he gets everything done like a thunderbolt.
I can't believe this.
What about Eun Hwan Gi?
He didn't even show up here.
Why did you do that?
Look who's talking. Why are you doing this to me?
Did Mr. Kang make you lie?
It's true that Mr. Eun visited me at the hospital...
with flowers.
That psychopath didn't even step out of his office when you were...
almost dying right in front of his door.
The article came out regardless of my intent.
Keep your lips sealed unless you want both of us to be doomed.
We don't know each other.
We've never even seen or talked to each other.
You got money from them, didn't you?
What do you...
How much did they give you?
It must've been quite a bit.
That must be why you gave up on your conscience...
Yes, I sold my conscience.
What was I supposed to do?
Because of some missionary of justice,
I lost my job. My conscience was the only thing I could sell!
You can get another job.
I mean, this isn't the only company...
Who'd want to hire a whistle-blower?
Well...
I just wanted to help you.
You couldn't even raise your head up...
or look at him when you were talking to him.
But in return for putting up with all of that,
I was able to buy food for my family and pay the utility bills.
I shouldn't have told you anything.
Ji Hye.
You must've been this distressed, too.
You were in so much pain,
yet you couldn't even let out a squeal.
Lie face down.
I said, face down. Lie face down completely.
Lie on your stomach.
The scrubbing towel feels so rough on my skin.
It looks like he pulled out a new one for me, so I should be thankful.
There must be a reason why it hurts so much.
He's a specialist. He must know the most ideal scrubbing intensity...
for removing dead skin.
My gosh, look at how much he's sweating.
He's trying to do his very best to fulfill his given task.
I'll be letting him down if I complain and ask him to be gentle.
I feel as if my skin is on fire.
He might actually be trying...
to relieve his own stress by scrubbing me as hard as he can.
What kinds of things has he been through in life? He's so aggressive.
Is one of his family members ill?
Is he desperate for the hospital fee?
I'm sure that he's trying so hard to forget pain.
I'm just lying down.
I can't... I cannot complain.
(MOANING IN PAIN)
My goodness. You should've told me if it hurt that much.
- You've been enduring it all?
- Sorry?
Lie down on your back again.
I want to scrub the parts I missed.
You little...
They completely got me this time.
Kang Woo Il was the dark horse.
He was prepared for every single possible scenario.
I bet everyone in the company was expecting a scandal like that.
Exactly.
They probably started working on the plans three years ago.
People are calling it the most ideal crisis management strategy...
and highly praising Brain's competency.
We ended up benefiting them.
Eun Hwan Gi's dad, Congressman Eun Bok Dong.
He founded Brain with nothing,
and he's now aiming to get elected as the mayor of Seoul.
It won't be easy to take them down.
I'll take all of them down,
including that psychopath's dad who put a silver spoon in his mouth.
Forget being a mayor. He'll be too humiliated to even leave the house.
You should leave that company.
You've done enough.
What are you talking about?
They completely destroyed my family.
You might end up in danger...
Do you know what infuriates me the most?
It's the fact that the psychopath did not show up.
He put Kang Woo Il on the frontline and made him apologize.
He hid behind him and didn't even lift a finger.
(CALL FOR APPLICATIONS: IN-HOUSE VENTURE PROJECT)
Hye Young, have a look at this.
(OBJECTIVES, CRITERIA, REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS, PROCEDURE, SCHEDULE)
It looks like it's really happening.
The ghost of the penthouse, Eun Hwan Gi.
He does pique my curiosity.
Then go ahead and apply.
Do you think I'm crazy?
Shall I apply?
- You?
It'll be such an easy job.
I'll just have to make sure not to get on his nerves...
and flatter him as much as possible.
Do you want to be unemployed for the rest of your life or what?
I'm telling you. It's all for a show.
The project itself will be cancelled in no time.
No way. I mean, he's the founder's son.
Kang Woo Il is obviously doing it to demote Eun Hwan Gi.
Being cutthroat about it will look bad,
so he's trying to be a little polite.
I guess you're right.
Joining that team means death. Who'd want to apply for it?
Me!
I think it'll be fun.
Kid, come here.
- Me?
- Come here.
Yes?
You keep getting distracted as you have too much time on your hands.
Let's get some work done, okay?
Yes. You know what to do, right? Everything here.
How dare you!
If you misplace any of them, you'll receive a death sentence.
Send them to the photoshoot locations via express courier,
but make sure all the handmade decorations don't get damaged.
Handle them gently as you'd treat babies.
You have to be very careful.
Also, you must be punctual and meet all the deadlines.
Those in fashion are known for their impatience.
Okay!
Because I'm fond of you,
I'm giving you a chance to be the boss.
A chance to be the boss?
When you work at a PR agency,
you have to put up with the media and clients without losing a smile.
The only people we can boss around are those express couriers.
I'm sorry.
Keep them on a tight leash, okay?
Yes! Of course.
All right, let's do this.
Hey, I saw you on the rooftop.
Are you not the guy?
Am I mistaken?
Where are you going?
You're the guy.
Why are you trying to run away?
Why can't you look at me in the eye?
Are you...
a newbie?
You must be a newbie express courier.
I'm not picking on you, so don't be scared. Everyone starts somewhere.
I'm new, too.
Here's another weird guy.
He walks around with his head down and can't even make eye contact.
Gosh, my eye...
What's wrong?
What happened to your eye?
I like that you're looking at me in the eye now.
What scares you? Do you think I'll shoot laser beams out of my eyes?
There's a photo shoot taking place in Ilsan Lake Park.
You just have to get there in one hour.
You have plenty of time, so please ride your motorcycle safely.
- Pardon?
- We'll see each other often.
Wait...
Let's not run into each other again on the rooftop, though.
I believe in you!
Why do I have to do this? It's her fault for jumping to conclusions.
I never said that I work for an express courier service.
If these things disappear into thin air,
the photoshoot will be affected, and she'll get in trouble.
It may be enough reason to fire her.
I do feel bad, but I have to straighten things out.
Yes, I shouldn't go. Get off the car now.
Pardon? The courier didn't arrive yet?
That's strange. We sent them via courier before we left the office.
- You sent them out, right?
- Yes. I sent them.
We're ready to roll.
- Call the courier guy.
- Okay.
I don't have his phone number.
- What?
- Who was it?
Which company?
He's new. He came to our office to promote the company.
Well... He's not bad looking and...
Is that why you forgot to ask him for his business card?
I got his business card on the rooftop...
I can't really say I got it. I found the one he dropped, but I...
Call the courier companies and locate the order.
- Hurry up!
- Okay.
Right. I just...
I would've already called the police.
It actually turned out for the best. I mean, this is what I wanted.
I'll be late anyway.
The photoshoot will have to be rescheduled, and they'll complain.
But it's none of my business since I'm no longer the CEO of Brain.
Yes. I should turn my car around.
- What is going on?
- Gosh.
What should we do? What a disaster!
No one has received the order. Are you sure he's a courier guy?
Yes, he is. I'm certain.
Why else do you think he took them?
It's obviously because they're very expensive designer stuff.
We have no time to waste like this. Call the police now.
Just a moment.
- Let's wait just a bit more.
- He obviously stole them.
- He'll never do such a thing.
- You've never even seen him before.
You said you don't know his name or his phone number.
That's true, but...
Are you two a team? Is that it?
- Are you two splitting them?
- Pardon me?
- Gosh, no way.
- This is why.
This is precisely why you have to be careful when hiring new employees.
All right. It's all my fault. I actually...
asked Ro Woon to take care of arranging the courier delivery.
Why? What were you doing? Tell me.
You don't even do that much.
There're so many people here. Don't get so worked up. Go easy on me.
Can you talk politely to me since there are so many people here?
We did go to the same school, but I can't go easy on you all the time.
- Do you understand, Ms. Dang?
- Yes.
I'm sorry, Ms. Park.
Can you still not figure out what's going on?
I'm sorry. I'm...
I'm... I'm sorry.
It's always the weak that have to be sorry.
I beg you.
I implore you,
so please trust him.
Are you really going to be this bull-headed?
I promise you that I'll find them.
So please don't call the police yet.
Please give me some time. Just a little bit of time.
Please wait just a little bit.
Hey, get yourself back...
What is going on?
Even Mr. Kang is here now.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Kang.
The thing that I've been worried about finally happened.
Where on earth is he?
Did he get into an accident?
Where is he?
Where is he now?
Where did he go?
I knew it!
Look at that.
I knew he would come.
He even gave up his motorbike...
and ran all the way here.
Here!
I've been waiting for you!
I shouldn't have come here.
Thank you for coming!
I shouldn't have gone near her in the first place.
There we go.
Thank you so much for all of your support.
I shouldn't have hovered around her.
I had faith in you!
What if she finds out who I am?
If I told her then...
I knew you'd come!
No, before that...
Is there something you want to say to me?
If only I had told her...
If only I had said anything to her...
If I tell her now,
will I be able to make things right?
Move!
What did you say?
- Move!
- I can't hear you.
I can't hear you.
Or is it...
too late now?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(MY SHY BOSS)
This is a new beginning and a new challenge.
Did you hear?
The penthouse will be opened.
- That's unbelievable.
- Why here, of all places?
She might get hurt if my cover gets blown.
- Did you eat?
- Yes.
Don't worry.
This is only the beginning of my revenge.
I've picked out members for the venture.
Forget it. I have a few on my mind.
There's one more.
- Trust me.
- Have you two already become close?
She's cheerful and energetic just like I used to be.
I like her.
We'll soon find out...
who he really is.
Meet the leader of Silent Monster,
Eun Hwan Gi.