She left without her shoes.
She wasn't even wearing any shoes...
when she was...
going...
so far away.
(Episode 4: I Won't Meet Anyone)
It's still dark outside because the sun isn't up yet.
Where does he wander at this early hour?
He rarely leaves the penthouse,
but it looks like he goes somewhere every morning.
I think he's obsessive about repeating his morning routine.
He takes a shower,
cleans,
sharpens his pencils,
puts on some music,
and dances.
What?
He dances?
What was that? Was that a hallucination?
Am I still half asleep?
Good morning.
Gosh.
There's no way he was dancing.
That cold psychopath never even says hi back.
Did she see it?
Let's have lunch.
What will we be having today? Will it be pork cutlets?
- Hurry. - Let's go.
It's yukgaejang today.
- It's yukgaejang every day. - I had it yesterday.
Should we eat out?
He never eats with his employees.
It seems like he does eat by himself.
Whatever he eats, the kitchen is always cleaned up.
There's no smell, either.
There must be some traces left.
I found it.
Does it smell like kimchi?
- Good work today. - Good work, everyone.
- See you tomorrow. - See you.
It's so cold these days.
Wait for me.
After everyone leaves,
what does he do here all alone?
Tomorrow morning, he'll sneak out again...
like a cockroach.
Here we go.
He exercises?
He's surprisingly good.
I thought he was a loner who never gets out.
Nice.
What a surprise!
You're very good.
It's so unexpected.
Why are you here?
I'm here to work out.
Are you a member here, too?
It's so nice to see you here.
Are you leaving?
I actually want to learn how to play squash. Can you teach me?
Why are you ignoring me?
I'm just happy to run into you.
Isn't it about time we became closer?
Let's work out together...
and drink something cold together later.
I work out alone.
Of course you do.
Is it about Ms. Chae again?
If she makes you that uncomfortable, she'll have to go.
- I'll take her then. - What?
I want to teach her a lot.
- I'll keep her near me and... - You can't do that.
Why not?
I'd like to...
kick her out of the company for good.
- If she stays here, she'll... - What?
She'll get on my nerves.
You can't fire someone because of that.
You know we can't fire people that easily.
The ministry is keeping an eye on us after the power abuse issue.
I'm sorry, Hwan Gi.
I'm sure she's been sticking around you because of me.
I told her to do that.
It was an assignment regarding the PI project.
I told her to analyze what kind of person you are.
She's observing whatever you do with affection.
Stop being so cold and treat her nicely.
With affection?
Why is this so funny to me?
She's giving you such a hard time.
Eun Hwan Gi has met his perfect match.
It all starts from hating each other.
Give it some time, and tell me if it's still too hard for you.
I'll be more than happy to take her.
No. She can stay with me.
What I mean is...
What you mean is...
We have no choice. Just let her stay.
Mr. Kang.
I'm here.
I've been waiting for you. Let's go.
They're together again.
Where are they going together?
I've finished my assignment.
You have?
Where's your report paper?
I didn't have much to write about.
Mr. Eun can be...
defined with one word.
I'm all ears.
A cockroach.
A cockroach?
Late at night, when everyone's asleep and no one is watching,
he becomes active.
He's always dressed in back, too.
He's just like a cockroach.
He never gives any instructions,
or hold any meetings.
He only spends the hard earned money his employees make.
Silent Monster is like an empty shell.
It's all just a show to pretend the abusive boss has changed.
That's harsh.
All his employees are anxious.
They wonder if it's really okay to be doing nothing.
At least, you're working hard.
I don't do much.
I just follow you around, have good food,
and meet people.
Do you think we meet people just to have fun?
Giving presentations is a big part of PR agencies' jobs.
It's, in essence, meeting people and persuading them...
to get on our side.
I believe knowing a good person is a lot more important than...
reading a book both for your work and for your life.
Today, an executive of a major food company will be here.
For the 30th anniversary project of Yong Ramyeon,
there will be a bidding soon.
Do you understand what I mean?
Are we bribing him?
We're just asking him to let us enter the competition.
You'll soon figure it out,
but they're not corrupt people.
Mr. Kang, you're already here.
Hello, Managing Director Jin.
Hello.
Who is this beauty? Is she your girlfriend?
She's an employee I think very highly of.
She's my secret weapon.
I'm Chae Ro Woon.
Nice to meet you.
Please take a seat.
Sure. Let's sit down.
He was supposed to pass the ball to his team,
but he ended up scoring an own goal.
That's so funny.
We haven't even had any drink,
but this is so much fun.
Is it?
Do you know what the secret to my success is?
Your insight into the future?
A global mindset?
You're going too far.
The right answer is health.
Around my age,
many of the competitors fall down...
because of health issues.
In addition to being competent,
you're modest, too. My goodness.
She's an employee I think very highly of.
I'm being recognized.
(New York Barbershop)
She's my secret weapon.
Secret?
My sister ended up dead...
at that company.
(New York Barbershop)
What will Dad say if he finds out?
(Three years ago)
- Gosh, it's so cold. - Be careful, Mom.
Gosh, why are you wearing those heels?
What happened to the pair I bought at the department store?
Those are too expensive.
Who cares if they get a bit dirty?
Your father used half of the shoe polish on them yesterday.
Even dirt will slide right off.
Is your eldest...
going to work at this hour?
Yes, hello.
She works for the best company there is in the industry.
She serves the big boss...
at that amazing company.
Of course she is busy.
Just leave.
My life alone.
Do not.
- Get in my way - That little...
- Mom. - Anymore.
- I will live my way - Gosh.
Your youngest is just getting home.
Are you all out waiting for me?
I'm so touched.
- You punk. Look at the time. - Mom.
Today,
I...
Wait, it was yesterday.
I passed the audition yesterday.
I was so happy.
Guys, I'm going to be on a musical.
Will you come watch?
Are you the lead this time?
I'll be a scene stealer...
that walks all over the lead character.
I'll be playing 18 roles.
That means I'll play 18 different characters.
You will be running in and out of the stage.
It must be very hectic.
That won't be all.
She will be talking a lot. It'll be so noisy.
It's not just one or two.
I'll play 18 roles.
Transformation complete.
Gosh.
It's hard to believe these two are sisters.
My goodness.
Oh, gosh.
Chae Ro Woon, those shoes...
Aren't those your sister's?
She lent them to me for good luck.
Thank you, Ji Hye.
After giving me great luck,
these shoes have died.
Ro Woon, come over here.
- Mom. - Come over here.
- Come right here. - Calm down.
I'll buy her another pair.
I'll make money and then buy her new ones.
I'll buy her nicer and prettier ones.
- Look at her yapping. - Mom.
- You better come over here. - No.
- She's going to get it today. - Mom.
(New York Barbershop)
I wonder...
if Mom is watching me.
(New York Barbershop)
- Did you eat? - Yes.
It was great.
It was really delicious.
What's gotten into her? Her answer got longer.
Did something good happen?
I bet she's drunk again.
She looks fine to me.
Gosh.
Ever since her sister died,
the cheerfulness in her also died. She hardly talks now.
Do you think she'll start talking again?
In one's life,
some encounters are imperatively necessary.
On the other hand, some are unnecessary,
I have an instruction...
to give.
- What's gotten into him? - Are we getting yelled at?
We're done for.
I hope it's not a hassle.
What is it? Tell us, Boss.
Do not meet anyone.
- Pardon? - Pardon?
What is he...
Is this a series?
It's the sequel to "We won't say anything."
"Do not meet anyone."
Could it be directed at me?
Does he think I'll meet with the press?
Is he suspicious of me?
Did he find out that I applied for a different position?
Is he telling me to focus on work instead of my family?
My goodness.
I'm not allowed to date someone at the office?
But I barely got started.
(Managing Director Jin)
Mr. Jin,
did you get in all right last night?
Yes.
Of course. I'll run over if you ask for me.
Yes, sure. I'll see you tomorrow then.
Bye.
- My goodness. - Who was that?
The person I met yesterday.
Exactly who are you meeting all the time?
There will be a bidding for Yong Ramyeon's anniversary project.
The person in charge of PR...
Mr. Kang made you do things like that?
It wasn't anything weird.
We had a 30-dollar-dinner.
We paid our own bills.
Managing Director Jin loves sports, so he doesn't even drink.
I noticed last time that you play sports, too.
Why don't you two play together?
Instead of chasing people around, do your work at your place.
That way, you'll have 100 people that know you,
instead of you knowing 100 people.
But...
I don't know where my place is.
I don't even know what I should be doing.
You never taught me anything.
You'll come with me tomorrow, right?
No. You shouldn't go either.
Don't be like that.
- It's for the team. As a boss... - Never.
I don't want to go.
I guess he really doesn't want to.
If he hates it so much...
Yes, Mr. Jin.
About the meeting tomorrow...
What do you think about going early in the morning?
Boss, you're here.
Managing Director Jin is a member here as well.
It looks like Silent Monster...
is fated to work with Yong Ramyeon. Don't you think?
What do you think you're...
I always wondered who came here earlier than me.
It was you.
Let me introduce you.
This is Managing Director Jin of Yong Ramyeon.
This is Silent Monster's boss, Eun Hwan Gi.
Say hello.
There you go.
You should greet each other.
Hello.
Mr. Kang told me about you.
It's nice and cool. Drink up.
Okay, thank you. Right.
I heard you're pretty good at squash.
No, not really. I'm not good.
He's seriously so good.
He's a pro.
Really?
Let's play a game.
I'm sorry. I like to exercise alone.
Gosh, why? There's no fun in playing against a wall by yourself.
She's saying you're good. Teach me.
When someone's looking at me...
I always make mistakes.
Mistakes? That's totally fine.
Mistakes are what makes us human.
All right. Come on. Let's play a game, okay?
I'll take this.
Good.
Here. Take this.
I clearly said I don't want to do this.
I'll be a referee.
All right.
Allow me to serve since I'm older than you.
What are you doing? Why aren't you playing?
It's 1 to 0!
Yes. Right.
Here we go.
It's 2 to 0!
What are you doing right now? Do you think I'm a joke?
You don't even want to deal with me?
I think my staff was a bit overly driven...
to get Yong Ramyeon's 30th anniversary project.
This is not how I get things done.
What did you just say?
I'll see you at the bidding with our proposal.
Just a second.
I see that you're good at making a fool out of people.
Tell me. Did I ask you to dance around in underwear for me?
Or did I ask you for money?
I just wanted to play a game of squash with you.
Definitely. My boss must've misunderstood something.
Did you misunderstand my intentions, Ms. Chae?
You asked me to come here at this early hour.
And why did you show up with your boss?
- Do you have a hidden agenda? - Not at all.
Then you hold this racquet...
and tell this guy to leave!
Me?
Let's go.
I've always wanted to learn how to play squash.
Will you teach me?
I'm a fast learner.
Please give it to me. Thank you.
- Like this? - All right. Yes.
Don't move your whole upper body when you swing the racquet.
Hold it like this...
- and do this. That's it. - Like this?
All right. Let's play a game.
What? You're still here?
Ro Woon, get out. I'll do it.
Swing the racquet like this.
You're so stiff. Relax your shoulders, okay? Good.
All right, give it a try.
You're so tense.
You'll get hurt like this.
All right. Relax your body first.
My gosh, why is your upper body so mushy?
I guess you don't exercise your upper body.
I mean, I saw how flexible your legs are.
- Gosh, your body is so mushy... - Please, Mr. Jin...
I told you.
I make mistakes when someone is looking at me.
Boss.
My gosh. I'm so sorry. This might help relieve the pain...
I sincerely apologize. Are you...
I'm going to sue him.
He obviously did it intentionally to hurt me.
I absolutely won't settle.
Things just got a little intense while you were exercising.
What?
Take a look at my CT and MRI scans when they're out.
It was definitely more than "a little intense".
Please don't get so worked up.
While collecting statements about the incident,
the fact that you were hitting on our employee will be revealed.
What?
My apologies. I got a little worked up there.
She's an employee I think very highly of.
I take it that you don't want to work with me.
What are you talking about?
This is for your hospital expenses.
Please forgive him, and don't turn it into a big deal...
for my sake.
What did he say?
Does he not want us to participate in the bidding?
I managed to get his permission for the presentation.
You didn't even do anything wrong,
but you had to apologize to him.
This is nothing.
Let's go.
I don't want to.
Hey, how can you say that when I did all that work to sort it out?
I don't want to work with someone like that.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but you're not in any position to be picky at the moment.
You should be asking companies to work with you.
He's obviously expecting something more than that.
He won't evaluate our presentation fairly.
Let's just give it a try.
For our employees' sake. No.
For my sake.
There you go again.
Cut him some slack for my sake.
Ms. Kim, please hang in there for my sake.
Please forgive him, and don't turn it into a big deal...
for my sake.
"For my sake."
He makes it sound like he's sacrificing himself.
Mr. Kang, please look at this camera.
But he's also unwittingly expressing his desire for attention.
The right side of my face looks better on camera.
Please take photos of my better side.
I'm not saying enjoying attention is bad.
- What does Silent Monster mean? - It's just that I'm not like him.
I've been wholeheartedly thankful that he always...
volunteers to be in the spotlight on my behalf.
- We just took the first step, - But...
so please show us your support and look forward to it.
You once said that Mr. Eun stays behind the scenes...
because you're more handsome than him. Is that true?
You haven't met Mr. Eun in person, have you?
- No. - No.
If that's the case, I can tell you in full confidence.
I'm about 20 times more handsome than him.
So you're admitting that you're better looking than him, right?
The problem is that he overly attracts attention...
to the point that it's dangerous.
Did you get any plastic surgery done?
- Pardon? - Did you get any plastic surgery?
Hey, what are you trying to say?
Do you think I'm doing these things because I want the attention?
You're too greedy.
That's hurtful and discouraging.
I'm putting off what I have to do...
to do my best to help Silent Monster.
I respect the way you do things,
but I'm the one who's in charge of Silent Monster.
Take your hands off of this project.
Hey, then what about our employees?
I'll protect my own staff.
How are you going to do that?
By blowing our chance to participate in the bidding?
By wasting their time...
when they should be learning and building up experience?
Listen up.
If you don't do this, no one will give Silent Monster any work.
I know how competent you are, but no one else does.
You don't want to play dirty, petty tricks?
I said I'll do them for you.
I'll do anything it takes to get the ball rolling,
so just do it your way...
and show people what you can do.
Does that sound good enough?
Do you actually want to protect your staff?
Or are you just trying to protect your pride?
(Eun Hwan Gi)
I'll protect my own staff.
How are you going to do that?
By wasting their time...
when they should be learning and building up experience?
Taking the bus and getting a ride from me...
- They're the same thing. - Stop it.
Are you late as well, Sun Bong?
Yes.
I went to a job interview this morning.
There is nothing to do even if we come in early, anyway.
I'll say.
That's true.
Yong Ramyeon's bidding is tomorrow.
Everyone is busy finishing up the presentation,
- except for us. - I'll say.
There is nothing we can do.
He doesn't share anything with us.
I'll say.
Let's go.
Wait for me!
Good morning.
Am I not that late today?
Or is everyone late?
I'm on a diet.
(The Korean ramyeon market...)
(Spot the differences between the old and new packagings)
Are you late, too?
I was on time, but...
I had to go somewhere urgently.
Do you have enteritis again?
Oh, no. Are you all right?
- Hey... - What is this?
Are all five of us late then?
Sorry we're late.
See? He couldn't care less.
We should have come after lunch.
I have an instruction to give.
Prepare for the presentation.
Who are you referring to, Boss?
Me?
That will be all.
Sir, I'm not ready at all.
- I do not have any materials. - Check your email.
I can't go tomorrow.
I haven't presented in a while.
I had two maternity leaves,
and took a long time off.
- I haven't presented once since... - Still, you've done it before.
Gosh.
It's so warm.
You have to line up for these...
I'm all right.
Couldn't you present just this once?
You prepared everything,
so you must know best about what to focus on.
What I mean is...
It must have been a lot of work to prepare alone.
Everyone, let's give the CEO a round of applause.
Gosh. You must be stressed out.
It's employees I need.
Pardon?
Not a mother.
He's abusing his power.
He didn't say a thing until now,
and now he wants you to do the presentation?
I better do as I'm told.
Mr. Kang said that Silent Monster...
won't have rigid hierarchy.
He hardly communicates with us.
He's a tyrant just doing whatever he wants.
If I were him, I would have gone.
He should set an example if employees is what he needs.
Will you go instead?
My mother is always looking after my kids,
but she's planning a trip...
Unfortunately, I'm taking tomorrow off.
I have a job interview.
It's with a major company this time.
I'll do it.
Have you presented before?
We've all done it at school, haven't we?
No. What if things go wrong?
We should do as he says.
She's right. He even warned me.
When he told us not to meet anyone, he was talking to me.
He's telling me to focus on work instead of my family.
I'll try to do this myself.
Tell me if you need anything.
- I'll help if I can. - Me too.
Thank you.
You have bad knees, anyway.
Can you go on a trip another time?
I'll send you somewhere nice next time.
When? When your knees are better.
I know. I know it's because you...
Sorry, Mom.
I'm really sorry. Yes.
Mom, I will...
wire you some money.
Instead of chasing people around, do your work at your place.
Does he think it's fine as long as he works at his place?
What a joke.
(Three years ago)
Our deepest condolences.
This isn't even close to the gravity of your loss, but...
I knew it.
Are you trying fob us off with that money?
So something really did happen at her work, didn't it?
The company also looked into it, but we did not find...
That's why it's more suspicious.
Someone died,
but there is no reason. There is no explanation.
She killed herself at work, but not a single news article got written.
After that, all they say...
is that she had depression.
How does this make sense?
Keep it down.
Take it and leave.
We can't just let him go.
No one from her work came, and they won't meet with us.
They finally came to us. Why would you send him back?
Take it and leave.
What are you doing, Dad?
Are you just going to sit there?
Social life is hard for everyone.
What did you say?
Everyone struggles, but they continue to power through.
She should have done the same.
Dad.
If you won't do it, I will.
I will go and get at least Ji Hye's shoes back.
Stop making a scene and sit down.
I can't do that!
My heart is about to burst.
(I'll wait for your return to the stage.)
Mom.
Mom. He's here.
What? He's here? What's gotten into him?
Mother, I'm here.
It's you, Woo Il.
I thought it was Hwan Gi.
Shouldn't you change the way you call Woo Il?
We didn't even get married yet.
Although you haven't had a wedding yet,
you're living together.
I'll call you Mother after we get married, too.
That will be confusing.
When you have kids, things will become even more complicated.
I was worried it might give you a headache, so I got you something.
Oh, my. Woo Il.
You're the best.
You've been whining all day. Now you smile.
That's because Woo Il is here.
Mother, aren't you tired? Let me give you a massage.
- Are you sure? - Can you lift your legs?
You're the best.
Did you have dinner?
No, I didn't.
Why not?
Hwan Gi hasn't come home for days. I'm on a strike.
I'll tell him to come home.
- Really? - Yes.
It feels so nice.
We're in trouble.
Yoo Hee just called, and she's still home.
She woke up late.
Let me call her.
Why isn't there anything else to wear?
It's suffocating.
Is this not going to fit?
(Ro Woon)
Hi, Ro Woon.
This is an unexpected chance to take revenge.
I don't think she'll get here in time.
Do you want to talk to her?
I just gave my kids their pills.
Hey!
Why are you throwing it back up?
It's too bitter.
Wait. Don't throw up.
Swallow it. There you go.
Wait. Where are you going?
Where are you going?
You should give the presentation.
Me?
Do you expect us to do it?
You're the only one who can do it.
Silent Monster, everyone is waiting. Please hurry.
The thing is...
I'm not dressed properly.
- Also... - No.
Your progressive style makes you look creative.
It's perfect.
The hidden emperor under the veil.
The glorious debut of the mysterious Eun Hwan Gi.
This is a perfect opportunity to make a name for yourself.
Let's go.
Show them what you've got.
Neat hands.
Stylish hair.
There you go.
Let's go.
We should go, too.
Sorry. Sorry, we're late.
My gosh.
Here.
Good luck.
Now, Silent Monster will...
give a presentation.
Please start the presentation.
What if he does a good job?
Excuse me, please start.
- What's going on? - What is he doing?
Excuse me, what are you waiting for?
Well...
I'm...
Silent...
- What's wrong with him? - We don't have much time.
Please get started.
Well, I'm...
- I'm... - Speak!
Speak! Come on!
Speak!
Just do whatever you want.
Is that all you can say?
Why do you let others decide how your hair should look?
You can't even express your opinions clearly.
Why are you so shy?
Fine.
If you can't say anything, I'll speak for you.
- Hey, Curly. - Curly.
- Where are you going, Curly? - Where are you going?
- Are you an old lady? - It looks ridiculous.
Silent...
Excuse me, the judges' time is precious.
- Please get started. - I'm...
I'm...
Everyone fears being stared at to some extent.
My father wanted me to become a leader.
A global leader.
He did not allow me to have even a tiny bit of fear.
He even went as far as...
bribing my teacher...
so that I could...
be at the center of attention.
What if I miss the beat?
What if I forget the lyrics?
It'll be fine. I practiced a lot.
What if my voice has become hoarse from all the practice?
I don't deserve to sing a solo part in the first place.
It's not like I got the solo part because I'm a good singer.
On the day they chose who'll sing the solo part,
Yeong Sik, the best singer in class,
buried his head to his desk and cried.
I feel so bad for him.
Start singing.
Glad tidings I bring.
To you and your kin.
Glad tidings for Christmas.
- What is he doing? - Say something!
Let's just move on.
It looks like he came here with no preparation.
It looks like you're feeling a bit nervous.
Please try to relax...
and start the presentation.
I'm...
(Judges)
I'm sure I at least...
satisfied one person.
- Is this a joke or what? - What does he think he's doing?
Gosh.
Did my revenge...
succeed?
But why is it not gratifying at all?
This is not what I wanted.
Hwan Gi.
Open the door. Please?
I think...
we should give him some alone time.
There will be other opportunities, so don't be too disappointed.
Good work, everyone.
You can leave early today.
Are your kids okay?
The fever went down.
My husband took a day off from work, and he's with them now.
We could use something to cheer us up.
Let's go grab a drink.
Yes, let's go.
Let's go.
Shall we?
I'll protect my own staff.
How are you going to do that?
That presentation was an eye-opener for me.
The person whom I was so scared of...
was actually a huge coward.
How disheartening.
Gosh.
Are you sure you can drink more?
Of course.
For goodness's sake.
Do I work for Brain...
or not?
What a mess.
Sun Bong, what's the matter?
Did the job interview...
not go well?
Because I technically work for Silent Monster now,
no one wants to hire me.
I'm sorry, everyone.
It's my fault for not doing the presentation.
It's not your fault, Yoo Hee.
It's not.
I...
I thought...
that Mr. Eun should do the presentation himself...
instead of dumping it on one of us.
But he even wrote a detailed script for me.
I just had to memorize it and do the presentation.
It also had a surprisingly heart-warming theme.
To celebrate Yong Ramyeon's 30th anniversary,
Silent Monster prepared...
a social media photo contest.
"Ramyeon That Doesn't Change".
Yong Ramyeon has been there for us for 30 years.
Share the moments you spent with Yong Ramyeon...
with us.
Mom.
I feel sick.
Mom, my nose is runny.
You can post a photo...
- from your old photo album. - Mom...
Or you can reenact the moment...
captured in one of your old photos.
- Mom, I'm sick. - Get some sleep now.
Prepare for the presentation.
Who are you referring to, Boss?
Warm family affection.
(AE Dang Yoo Hee)
That strand of noodle must be from her kid.
Whenever she picks up snacks for the team,
she buys those old-school pastries that we all used to eat growing up.
She's the perfect person to express the old-school sentimentality...
this project is seeking.
Me?
It'd been long since I got actual work done.
It made me think of when I was single, and I was all excited.
After all,
I'm just a mom who picks up snacks for the team.
No, I shouldn't even call myself a mom.
I didn't even take my kids to get the flu shot on time,
and I yelled at them knowing that they're sick.
I'm neither an employee...
nor a mom.
What am I?
(Kang Woo Il)
(Chae Ro Woon)
(11 Missed Calls)
Do you actually want to protect your staff?
(12 Missed Calls)
(Chae Ro Woon)
Or are you just trying to protect your pride?
- Hello? - Are you...
the boss?
I have your staff members here.
Get cash ready.
It's cold.
It's 101 dollars.
I'm sorry.
The card reader is broken. Please give me 101 dollars in cash.
Another bottle of soju, please.
I'm sorry.
I want to drink more.
I don't want to go home.
It hurts.
I don't want to get in.
- I don't want to go home. - Please go to Heukseok-dong.
Areum Villa, Room 203.
I don't want to go.
Mister, drink with me.
It's nice to meet you.
What?
When did you get all so grown up, Son?
Room 907, Jinsang Apartment, Myeonmok-dong.
Come here! Where are you going?
Son!
Room 203, Secret Villa, Bulgwang-dong.
- Please drive carefully. - Have a drink with me.
- Bye. - I can drink more.
Let's drink.
Drink with me.
- I can still drink. - Sir, excuse me.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Get up. Let's start walking.
There you go.
Here. Take it.
Sir, please go to Hannam-dong.
You're my girl.
You said you're not an easygoing person.
What are you doing at this shabby bar?
You know all your employees' addresses.
Have you been watching us the whole time?
Why?
Why do you secretly observe people from behind?
Why are you never in front of people?
Is it because you can't?
I thought you looked down on people.
Are you...
scared of people?
When people stare at you,
do you make mistakes or something?
I know people like you very well.
You hide where there's no one else.
You quietly keep your place.
Someone in my family is like that.
No.
Apart from me,
everyone in my family is like that.
Dad,
Mom,
and my sister.
But let alone a hundred people,
not a single person noticed.
If you just stand there and watch,
nothing will happen.
Just by watching,
you can't protect anyone.
(My Shy Boss)
It felt warm.
I said I'm sorry.
- I'm the one who should say that. - He held you in his arms?
I just vaguely remember the smell.
It smelled like peppermint candy.
What Silent Monster needs right now is not work, but teamwork.
Why don't we have a workshop to build up teamwork?
Will it be an overnight trip?
Why doesn't he tell people that he's engaged?
Are you stopping him from doing that, too?
I can never lie to you.
A video clip?
I really don't understand what you're talking about.
- What are you watching? - He's not saying anything.
Is that Mr. Eun?
I'll try to make Mr. Eun become like Mr. Kang.
That's absurd. It'll be impossible.
I'm sure Hwan Gi will change.
He's capable of doing that.
I hope this workshop will help Hwan Gi change.