This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
All right, then.
How about you two start talking now?
All you two have been doing is
glaring at each other.
What? Are you going to say that
I'm petty again if I don't talk?
Hmph.
Did that hurt your feelings?
And you've been mad about that
this whole time, too? How petty.
The thing about being a man
of few words, you see...
It's a courtesy I extend to others.
A courtesy. All right?
It's a courtesy.
Are you familiar with that concept? Huh?
That a person must have
a reason for what he does.
And I'm sure he'll stop
acting like that after a while.
I held back, and held back,
and endured, and waited
but I'm mustering up all
of my will to speak right now.
Do you know how hard
this is for me? Huh?
I'd appreciate it if you
recognized that fact.
Hey, you think I just go around saying
whatever I please, because I'm me?
Don't you?
- No.
- No?
- No!
- Psh.
Oh really, now?
Listen, the reason I talk a lot is
because I have a lot I need to say!
But I can't even say a fraction of
the things I really want to say!
I hold back too, you know!
I have my own worries...
and I hold back a lot too!
Do you know that?
No, you don't know.
So you hold back?
And you have worries?
I understand how both of you must feel.
So how about you two say
what you really want to say now...
- Oh, I'll go first.
- Hey.
Wait your turn. Who said
that you could go first, huh?
Where did my liquor go?
It's gone. Where did it go?
Wait.
There's no liquor now.
- I'll get some.
- I'm fine...
I'll get some.
And don't you dare run away.
Oh no...
Loser! I win! I win!
We're here! We're here.
You're almost there.
All you need to do is walk there.
- Okay?
- Ugh.
Go? Go where?
- Um...
- Go where?
We're here!
Take this off for me.
You want me to take it off?
Is it bothering you?
- Yes, it is.
- All right.
There you go. All done!
- Thank you.
- Sure.
But there's one more.
Are you crying?
Wow, you look so ugly!
Wow! Wow!
- Oh my gosh. What to do?
- Gosh, this is scary-looking.
I can't breathe! Wow.
I won. I won!
I may have gotten a bit hurt,
but that doesn't matter!
I won.
Are you still in pain?
That... that photo...
Yes, laugh to your heart's content!
You didn't laugh when I told you to!
Oh, man.
We're here!
All right, just a bit more.
You really are ugly.
I never you were capable
of smiling this much.
It looks nice.
[EPISODE 9: IF YOU LISTEN CAREFULLY]
Where did Chae Ro Woon go?
Where could she have gone?
Chae Ro Woon!
Ms. Ro Woon!
Ugh, move your leg!
Oh, my bad.
Move your head.
Stop using my arm as a pillow.
- I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
I told you to move your leg,
already. It's heavy!
I did!
Whose leg is this, then?
Ugh, get off me!
What in the world are
you talking about...
Get her off me.
- Me?
- Gently.
How about we get a cup of coffee?
Ms. Chae Ro Woon really
is a peculiar woman.
I feel like I can go back to the way
things were if I stay by her side.
And thanks to her, I fought
with you for the first time in a while
and had petty spats with you,
and laughed with you.
I'd like for us to continue doing that.
But in order for us to do that...
I can't... marry Yi Soo.
The reason I'm saying this to you now...
is that I don't want to lose you too,
even if it comes to that.
I want you to be understanding,
even if I may be acting selfishly.
We've never once properly discussed
what happened three years ago.
How could someone like me...
How could someone like me ever...
How can I be with you, CEO Kang?
It was a ridiculous mistake.
I may have done something
I shouldn't have.
Please don't say that.
If I stay by her side just because
of the guilt I feel toward that person...
it's not fair to Yi Soo to stay
with her when I feel like this.
I only realized after sending
that person off like that
that the true mistake I'd made
was not choosing her.
I don't want to make
the same mistake again.
I won't make the same mistake
I made last time, either.
I won't hesitate anymore.
What do you mean by that?
The person you're trying to "choose"
is Secretary Chae's younger sister.
What?
Chae Ro Woon is Chae Ji Hye's
younger sister. Do you understand?
What? What kind of...
You're sure about this?
Why didn't you say anything, then?
I told you to kick her out, didn't I?
Then, you knew from the very beginning?
If you knew all this time,
why didn't you...
Wait a second.
Why... did Chae Ro Woon come
to work at our company, then?
Just... leave her alone.
What?
Don't do anything to her.
What are you...
I'm the one...
who can't let her go anymore.
Why are you coming out of Boss's room?
Um, I'm not.
I came here to look for him.
No, it's clear that you're just making
your way out of there! I saw you!
No... I told you, it's not like that!
I came here to look for him!
Why would you need to
so early in the morning?
I was... going to ask him
to eat breakfast with me.
So you ran over here
as soon as you woke up
just to ask him that?
Without even washing your face first?
And without even
combing your hair?
Stop it!
Gyo Ri, you shared a room
with Chae Ro Woon, right?
Hey, hey!
I was just curious about whether
or not you got a good night's sleep.
Gyo Ri. Gyo Ri!
Where are you now?
All right, I'll be right there.
Wait, hey! Wait up!
Hey, wait!
Wait!
I can't understand a thing
you're saying to me right now.
She came to the company to get revenge.
She's the one who leaked the
information to the media back then.
Is that really true?
So why in the world did you
keep that information to yourself...
Because I was afraid
she'd get hurt if I didn't.
That's why I didn't tell you.
- Hey, if Father finds out...
- So let's keep it a secret from him.
Don't let Chae Ro Woon find out
that you know about this.
She doesn't know that I know.
Hey, wait! I'll explain, okay?
Come on, Se Jong! Please? Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
That hurts!
Hey, Se Jong!
You know, the fact that you're trying
to stop me make you more suspicious.
I'm telling you, it's nothing fishy,
so what are you even talking about?
Oh, yeah?
Wait, wait. Wait, wait.
Stop it! Damn it, you're fast!
Hey! Stop right there!
I want to protect her this time around.
If you harbor any guilt regarding
what happened to Secretary Chae...
make sure to protect her.
Very good. Cat pose.
Come down.
Breathe.
Breathe out.
And come back up.
And up. Namaste.
- Namaste.
Gyo Ri! Gyo Ri!
Chae Ro Woon didn't go back
to her room last night, right?
I don't know. I was tired yesterday,
so I went to bed early...
There's no way you weren't aware
if you really were with her.
Chae Ro Woon snores so loudly
when she sleeps!
Oh... Gyo Ri...
Man, you...
Tell me the truth.
Who did you sleep with last night?
Boss? CEO Kang?
Or both of them?
Wow, you sure are skilled!
Fine! I did sleep with him!
I slept with Boss! Happy?
See? I told you.
You do like the boss.
All we did was sleep.
I was dropping him off at his room
after he got too drunk
but I passed out because I was so tired.
And you expect me to believe that?
Yeah! Fine, then! Don't believe me!
This is great, then! So stop messing
around and flirting with me, already!
You thought that I was
messing around this whole time?
You're always messing around and making
people around you feel uncomfortable.
You call that being genuine?
What?
You have no idea how I was
out all night looking for you
so that I could take you
on the tour of the garden.
I didn't get a wink of sleep
because I was waiting for you.
So don't you think it's a bit harsh
to belittle my actions like that?
Hey, Jang Se Jong.
Boss.
Where did CEO Kang go?
He returned to Seoul.
Oh, was it something urgent?
I'm sorry. I ended up
falling asleep on your bed.
And to top it all off, I got caught.
By that big-mouthed
Jang Se Jong, of all people.
I should've denied it until the end,
but he was coming on too strong, so...
And to be honest...
I shouldn't be telling you this...
but you're not the type to go
around blabbing to everyone.
So keep this to yourself, okay?
The truth is...
Gyo Ri likes Se Jong.
So I wanted to take this chance
to finally get him off my back.
And he keeps telling me
that he likes me all the time
which makes me feel
sorry toward Gyo Ri.
You were smiling so much
last night, and yet...
you became a brooding loner
of a teenage boy overnight.
I just don't get it.
That's why I thought of the best way
to communicate with you, and...
What is this?
Just stay still!
Ta-da!
There we go.
- It's a traffic light.
- Pardon?
You can show how you feel
by using colors.
When you really want to be left alone,
use red to say, "Don't approach me."
When I can approach you with a
document to be signed, use yellow.
And when you feel good
enough to allow me to ask you
to sign off on trivial things,
or talk to you about anything
use green.
It's fine.
There's no need for this.
It may be awkward in the beginning
but it'll be more convenient
for you as you get used to it.
Here.
Right now, you have a
red light on, right?
I'll shut my mouth now.
Enjoy yourself.
Why is she belittling me like this?
How dare you?
Just what am I lacking, exactly?
Why is she belittling me like this?
Man, these are the
limited-edition sneakers
I got yesterday
so I could impress Chae Ro Woon.
Maybe it's just that I'm too fashionable?
Yeah, that must be it!
It's because of my
brilliant, shining looks
that she thinks I'm shallow
and is belittling me like this.
Damn you, shoes!
This is all because of you!
All because of my damned good looks!
Wait... oh! My shoes!
Oh, my shoes! My shoes!
What is he doing?
To go so far just because of Ro Woon...
Se Jong! Se Jong!
Oh no! Oh no!
- Se Jong!
- Let go of me!
Don't go! It's dangerous!
How could I just let them go? No!
Stop acting like this!
It's not even worth that much!
Please, just let it go now!
No! My limited-edition sneakers!
It was so hard to get those!
Damn it, my shoes!
I thought you'd grown to hate me, Gyo Ri.
Why would I?
You've been acting distant ever since
you found out who my grandpa is.
Oh, that's...
It's fine. That's what usually happens.
Everyone treats me a bit differently
once they find out the truth about me.
They treat me better,
or end up hating me more.
At any rate, they treat me
differently than they did before.
It's not like that...
But there's just one person who's
treated me the same through it all.
Is it Ro Woon?
That's right!
Even though it's a bit annoying
that it's her looking down on me.
That has remained constant.
Thank you for this.
Oh, it was nothing.
Can I ask you just one thing, though?
Why did CEO Kang leave first?
Oh, fine, then!
I'll shut my mouth.
- But, um...
- Red light.
What purpose does this system
even have if you're ignoring it?
Just one question!
Did I...
snore?
I did, didn't I?
You got all sensitive because you didn't
get any sleep because of me, right?
Was my snoring that bad?
Bad enough for you two to
leave me behind and leave the room?
Bad enough that CEO Kang
hates me now and left for Seoul?
Oh, no way!
It's not like that, right?
Right? It's not that bad, right?
But you know, Boss, that flower
looks really nice on you.
- I want to go there again.
- Let's go again, then.
[WELCOME YEON JUNG]
[10 YEARS AGO]
[WELCOME, YEON JUNG]
Hwan Ki!
Hwan Ki... Hwan Ki!
How long has that been
your outfit of choice, though?
Oh, this?
Since college.
Why, did something happen?
Was it because of a woman, by any chance?
Because of pain you experienced
due to your first love?
Looks like I hit the mark!
What kind of woman was she?
Are there some painful memories
you have related to that, or something?
You don't need to know.
It definitely seems like him.
Hello.
Looks like the barber's daughter
still hasn't come home yet.
It's been a couple of days since she
left without even leaving a note behind!
Geez, he must really be upset.
She's finally back! She's back!
Oh, yeah. She's back.
I bet he'll really give her
an earful this time!
He's been too soft on her.
He needs to teach her a lesson.
- You're right.
- Yep, yep!
Go ahead and yell with some
"oomph" to your heart's content!
Did you eat?
Um, yes. I did.
- What did he say?
- He asked her if she's eaten.
Of course she's eaten.
Looking at you reminds me
of someone I used to know.
Even though there aren't that many
similarities between you two.
Yes, Chief Park?
[A LETTER TO BRAIN PR
TO WELCOME THE NEW YEAR.]
[CEO KANG HAS PROMISED TO SPEND
THE REST OF HIS LIFE WITH MY DAUGHTER.]
[PLEASE CONGRATULATE HIM...]
To think that he's off the market now...
He wasn't mine to begin with, though.
But why, all of the sudden?
It feels like this must be a lie!
But this is a letter that the
previous CEO himself sent out.
There's no way that this isn't true.
So he went ahead and made
an announcement like that.
I thought you were aware
of this already, sir.
CEO Kang!
Congratulations on
your upcoming nuptials.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, CEO Kang!
Yes, thank you.
Oh, you're here.
You announced that
we're getting married.
Yeah, I got busy
while waiting for you.
But you did that without telling me,
and while I wasn't even here.
- Can you step out for a bit?
- Yes, sir.
I've been inattentive toward you.
It wasn't because I hated you.
It was because I trust you,
and I feel comfortable with you.
Because I rely on you more
than I rely on my own son.
My son may have
done well this time around
but he still has a ways to go.
Put some more effort in so that Hwan Ki
can lead the company from the forefront.
The weight of the burdens you carried
alone until now must've been quite heavy.
Isn't that right?
So basically, you want Hwan Ki to be
in the spotlight more than me, right?
Look at you, acting all miffed
just because you got slapped once.
I find myself wishing that you were
my son dozens of times per day.
That's why I'm even
giving you my daughter.
Father. Thank you for
your sentiments, but...
But in exchange, you can't
get greedy and want the company
or run for office just because
you're marrying into our family.
We still haven't figured out
who the whistleblower was
for the article about
Hwan Ki mistreating his employees.
Wool Il!
You were quite taken aback, weren't you?
Mom was saying things like, "What if
he has no intention of marrying you?"
And she kept acting
super sensitive about it
so I wanted to offer up an excuse,
but things ended up coming to this.
- I'm sorry, but...
- No, I'm more sorry.
This is the best I can do regarding
pushing our marriage back.
Yi Soo.
Stay with me.
Just do this one thing for me.
I've really been had by Father.
I was fully aware that he did whatever
he pleased with people's lives, but...
My mind's a mess because
of Chae Ro Woon as it is.
And he announced my
marriage on top of all that.
Let's fire Chae Ro Woon.
Doing that is in her best interest, too.
Don't rush into things, and...
You should've done
something sooner, then.
If she does something like
leak intel to the press again...
She won't do anything else.
Why is she still here, then?
She might be trying to figure out
what happened three years ago!
If she finds out, then I...
Is that what you wanted
this whole time, by any chance?
Are you keeping her by your side
because that's my greatest weakness...
Do you really think it'd be for that...
Why are you keeping her by your side
if you need to protect her, then?
That just doesn't make any sense!
Give me some time, too.
Why? What are you thinking
about all by yourself now?
Hey, come on. It's me.
You can tell me, can't you?
Isn't it bad enough that you backstabbed
me by keeping her identity a secret?
I'm always being exposed by you.
Why is it that you see right through me,
but I can't see through you?
Can't I be allowed a glimpse
into your mind, too?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Yoo Hee told me to find you, Boss.
We're having a meeting.
- It... was a mistake.
- A mistake?
Guys have one-night-stands by accident.
Why are you two...
CEO Kang!
Did something happen, Boss?
So a war has finally broken out,
is what it is.
What war?
With that surprise announcement
about CEO Kang's wedding
he's now the ex-CEO's son-in-law.
A bloody battle for power
between the son and the son-in-law.
Thus begins the first act.
With tons of bloodshed.
- Oh my.
- Here you go, drink up.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thanks.
This tastes great!
Yeah.
But those two wouldn't normally be
fighting over something like that.
You never know with these things.
Even my mom argues with her sisters
over things like that all the time.
That's how it is.
It's not like it'd be
much of a battle, though.
Exactly.
CEO Kang has achieved quite a lot.
CEO Eun Hwan Ki doesn't
have many people by his side.
- How pitiful.
- How pitiful, indeed.
It's not like CEO Eun could
do anything without CEO Kang.
Sun Bong. Get back here right now.
No, I think it's about time
that I picked a side.
Keep up the good work, then.
- Toodles.
- Excuse me!
Sun Bong! Where are you going?
We must help him.
This is an old theater.
We've been asked to revamp it
as a theater that calls for movie mania.
It also happens that CEO Kang's team
is working on a theater project.
This is a chance to show
the ability of Silent Monster.
By the way, do we have to decide
on a concept for the revamping?
If you just sit at your desk and write
some articles using your fingers...
you think that's promoting, huh?
If you work from planning
all the way through marketing...
that's when you can say,
"Now I know how to promote."
Ro Woon, go with
CEO Eun to the site first.
May I go with her?
- I think Ro Woon should go.
- Sure, I'm on it.
Can't I be allowed a glimpse
into your mind, too?
You fell for someone
you shouldn't have, didn't you?
Your employee.
And someone already loves her.
Red means "Don't come near." Got it?
Yellow means "Only for emergencies."
- Green...
- Does he ever have green on?
Gosh, seriously.
I will go over to the theater site first.
Ah, I will come with you.
No, you seem to have
the red light on right now.
Do some thinking on your own.
When it turns to green, come.
Go.
Take your time.
- Go.
- I'm going.
Red light...
I've realized that I have to stop.
Even though I knew that...
I wonder if the green light
has come up yet...
I'm sorry.
Hey, Eun Hwan Ki.
Did you really not see me?
Or were you pretending?
I was watching you the
whole time from the other side.
Yeon Jung.
It's always a "long time no see,"
every time we see each other.
Your call is being redirected...
Can't he at least answer the call?
Come to think of it,
I haven't talked to him on the phone.
That's right. He has a phone phobia.
Ah, I recently saw you at the airport.
- It was you, right?
- Ah, at the airport?
You didn't seem to notice me
and passed by me then, too.
Well, I bet you don't
have the guts to face me.
After you stood me up
like that three years ago...
I was traumatized on Christmas.
- I'm sorry. At that time...
- It's okay.
When the article about you being
bossy and entitled went viral
I wrote so many
hateful comments about you.
So we're even.
No way. It's not enough.
- Take me out for coffee.
- Coffee?
But I need to be somewhere right now.
What can I say?
You might not be able to run this time.
You happen to have coffee right here.
It's for somebody else.
Sorry. I already drank it.
I was going to give it to Chae Ro Woon.
I will stop by your office
one of these days.
I'm trying to consult you
for the exhibition I'm planning.
You're not going to stand me up
when it's a client meeting.
I had my reasons three years ago.
Yeah. And I know you
can't tell me the reasons.
If you could, you would've
told me three years ago.
By the way, I was serious about work.
I've been looking for a PR firm.
So I'd appreciate it.
Sure.
I will boss you around, so get ready.
This is me, here.
Should I take you home again?
Is it still a red light?
Chae Ryung.
- This...
- Thank you.
You really don't remember?
I... remember everything.
That's a lie.
Hey!
I'd like to stay next to her
like this a little longer.
Wouldn't it be okay to stay near her
while keeping this much distance?
[MOVIE TICKET FOR "DON'T FORGET ME"]
He didn't come to the theater?
He said he'd definitely
go over there yesterday.
Did you have something else to attend to?
He must have been with some other woman.
He's been smiling,
so he's in a good mood.
Then do you have
the green light on today, Boss?
Then can you take a look at my report?
According to the trend
I decided the concept
to be a virtual reality theater.
I've read it, but the thing is...
I'd understand if it were a game
but there aren't many
of those movies out.
It seems too early for it.
He's right.
Sun Bong is on a
rampage of cynicism again.
As for virtual reality headsets
they can cause headaches and nausea
if people wear them for long.
How would you address that?
If people complain about lazy eyes
and fatigue, what will you do?
Do you have a solution
to those side effects?
That can't be overlooked, either.
Then do you have any other ideas?
A unique concept that will start a mania?
- I have none.
- See?
What was that about?
Sun Bong, you have no ideas, either.
Boss, can you say something?
I need to think about it.
We need to hurry up and set
the place up as the first and best.
Yeah, that would be nice.
Gosh, all the "best," "most," "first"...
Koreans go crazy if a place
doesn't include those words.
They think they're done promoting
if it has those words.
They are so simple-minded.
I don't like how he describes it,
but he's not wrong.
I will take my time
and think more about it.
He really likes taking his time, huh?
I guess he's a red light again today.
As for that traffic light metaphor...
don't you think it's a bit childish?
An adult man has stickers all over him.
What is he, a pervert? It's embarrassing.
Plus, he's the leader...
but he communicates with us
only when he wants to.
Does that make sense?
Stop putting a damper on us.
I was going to stop anyway.
Gyo Ri, why are you fixing your makeup?
Are you meeting someone?
You're not, are you?
- Want to go out to dinner with me?
- Gyo Ri.
- Shall we go on a date?
- What?
- Me?
- Yes.
I want to take you out to a good dinner.
You look especially pretty today.
[VR MOVIE]
What's up with this sudden act?
- Just the two of you?
- Yes.
I have something to discuss,
just between us two.
- Let's go, Gyo Ri.
- Sure.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Let's go!
What do you like for dinner?
Anything is good.
Yoo Hee, care for soju
and something spicy?
I have to go feed my kids.
Your sons will become someone
else's after they get married.
You should live your life.
You shouldn't watch and laugh at others.
And live your life, okay?
Gosh, you still haven't moved on
from VR movie theater idea yet?
Well, if I give you advice,
will you buy me dinner?
No.
I will go do more research on VR movies.
I'll be leaving, then.
- Well...
- Sorry.
I'm leaving. Bye!
Why am I feeling a chill
on the back of my neck?
He seems to want to
eat dinner with someone.
Should I ask him to have dinner
with me, if he's okay with the idea?
No, he will be
uncomfortable alone with me.
Because I'm his boss,
he can't comfortably say no.
Then should I put on the green light on?
To signal that I'm willing,
if you want to.
But Sun Bong said
the traffic light idea was childish.
He's not wrong about that.
An adult man with colorful
stickers on is embarrassing.
But a childish approach can
sometimes improve a relationship.
Chae Ro Woon came up with this idea,
so I will gather my courage.
Uhm Sun Bong?
Uhm Sun Bong? Uhm Sun Bong.
Uhm Sun Bong.
Uhm Sun Bong. Uhm Sun Bong.
How can he not ever
take us out to dinner?
We went through life and death together.
It was all useless.
Hot! Damn it!
I will still eat it though.
In today's market...
VR movies bring you an experience,
regardless of limitation of space.
VR movies will change the paradigm that
the movie industry's had for 120 years.
Wow.
That first step to the innovation
towards a new generation...
we'll be the first in
the country to take it.
I'm CEO Kang Woo Il
of Brain PR. Thank you.
I knew it.
They took the title of "first" away
right before our eyes.
You said it was so old-fashioned
to hang on to being a "first."
If the people on top made decisions,
we could proceed and work smoothly.
But our boss takes his time
to just come up with an idea.
The power struggle
between the son and son-in-law.
For the first round,
the victory goes to CEO Kang.
I liked Ro Woon's idea.
You put a lot of work into it.
You must be sad.
Thank you.
Our boss should have some kind of idea.
He should definitely have a counter-plan.
You have no idea at all?
You've been thinking all this time.
You had the red light on
because you were thinking.
Let's all think about it together
starting from this moment.
It's spooky, like a ghost might appear.
It's so vintage in here, huh?
What's with this old smell?
My back and butt will feel stiff in here.
The space between
these chairs is so narrow.
I like it because I can
sit close to my girl.
Here.
When did they become that cozy?
When one born
with a silver spoon gets mad
the clueless one snatches the bait.
What's going on?
Have you decided to
go out with Jang Se Jong?
The truth is...
he asked me to pretend
to go out with him.
What?
He wants to make you jealous.
He wants to show you
how he makes a woman happy
and how endlessly nice
he can be to a woman.
Well, why don't you tell him
honestly how you feel?
Not everybody can be honest
with their feelings, like you.
People tell me so easily to
be confident and courageous.
That's only possible
if there is someone to hear you out.
No one is willing to hear me out.
Why do you say that...
Can you just pretend not to know?
If Se Jong wants to
make me happy this way...
Who else would want
to be that nice to me?
Gyo Ri...
It'll be hard to attract customers
without a unique idea
like the VR theater.
I agree. It still bothers me
that our idea was stolen.
It would've made news
as the first in the country.
Although we lost
"first," "most," and "best"
I was just reminded of
the perfect keyword.
What is it?
The worst.
- Gosh, what is that?
- Why are you starting again?
Since we can't provide
the best service and facility
why don't we give them the worst impact?
Let's not spend
unnecessarily for remodeling.
Why not a theater
specializing in horror films?
In the worst movie theater...
experience an
unforgettable night of horror.
- Horror?
- Coming soon...
That's good.
- Pardon?
I said, I liked it.
We will proceed
according to Sun Bong's idea.
What idea? The one I just came up with?
I was just saying that to be sarcastic...
It's a brilliant idea to twist
the obvious promotional strategy.
- No, we were just being funny...
- We were being funny...
We can't do that.
You were being funny. It was funny.
Uhm Sun Bong is a man of wit.
Am I?
What was that?
He took Sun Bong's idea seriously?
- Oh my.
- I'm shocked.
Sun Bong, what did you just say?
Finally, the light's turned green.
I created the promotion phrases.
Women might hate going to the "worst"
kind of movie theater on a date night
so I thought how we could test the
strength of the seat backs for the guys.
I see.
We should appeal to the female customers.
- That sounds good.
- Okay.
There is something else.
It would be a design that would prevent
the men from spreading their legs.
He finally smiled.
I have others too.
- I have a different version.
- Ah, do you?
Since we're trying to
stick with the "worst" idea...
People tell me so easily
to be confident and courageous.
That's only possible
if someone can hear you out.
Who knew?
Did he eat something weird?
He's been at his desk for hours now.
He looks cool though.
Boss is someone
who is willing to hear you out.
The worst movie theater...
I can disappoint you more
than you can even imagine.
You can kick someone
in the row in front of you.
It's okay to leave your phone on.
You can drink and even dance, too.
If a scary monster appears on the screen
you can throw your popcorn at it.
- Good work.
- You're doing well.
How long do we have to fit into
the mold others set for us?
We can have one "worst day,"
other than a "best day."
- That's right.
- There you go!
William Shakespeare said this.
"If you have the presence of mind
to say, 'This is the worst'"
"then its not the worst yet."
The worst is when you
can't even say that word.
You still have the energy
to overcome the worst!
So enjoy being the worst.
The worst horror movie theater,
Horror Shakill!
Awesome!
- You did it!
The reason why he was quiet...
maybe it wasn't because he didn't
want to talk, but wanted to hear us out.
What was that?
- High five.
- High five?
- On my back?
- Then, with my hand?
Help me clean up.
- You scared me.
- Did you come to steal our idea again?
What do you mean?
We were already working on a VR theater.
Our boss took his time,
not approving it!
We still don't have
enough movies for a VR theater.
This single movie theater
can't support it financially.
CEO Eun made the right decision.
He's not paying attention
to work because of Ro Woon.
What did you just say?
Haven't you noticed
how happy he is lately?
I guess you didn't know there was
something going on between them.
Do you have anything to say?
Hurry up and finish.
"Wow, you're good.
Where did you learn how to do this?"
"Thank you for saving the expense."
Others say that to me.
I just want you to know.
I agree, it's the minimum.
I don't want to scare other people.
You're scary people enough
with your black hoodie.
I will look in the mirror.
I'm too nervous.
- Let me look in the mirror.
- Close your eyes.
Now I will work on your eyes.
A bit of this.
Close your eyes so I can get them.
How shocking that you
willingly took off your hood.
Why are you not avoiding eye contact?
I'm avoiding it.
You're not going to close your eyes?
I'm avoiding it with all my might.
This feels like we're
fighting in a weird way.
If one of us looks the other way
it means we lose,
so we can't do anything now?
Can you just close them?
The brush could poke them.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
- Boss.
- Don't stay with me.
You once thanked me for staying near you.
Wait! Did I do something bad?
One of my employees is bothering me.
- Bring her to me again.
- Run, run.
Chae Ro Woon isn't the one.
Where there is no Chae Ro Woon...
- Boss?
- Chae Ro Woon. Chae Ro Woon.
If you can't get over her,
bring her back.
Or don't show it.
Yi Soo needs you.
Get away from me.
Excuse me.
Can you really do a presentation?
- I am doing it.
- No, you can't do it.
If I do it, return Chae Ro Woon to me.