(Episode 15)
BioskopKeren
Oh, you again.
I'll say.
"I'll say"?
Is that what I just said?
Wait!
Lady.
- Me? - It's good to see you here.
- Do you know me? - No.
But that necklace you're wearing.
- This? - I made that.
A man asked me to design it.
Must have been 10 years ago.
10 years? What man?
You should know better.
You're the owner of the necklace.
Do you know what it means?
- No. - It means...
"a match made in Heaven" in French.
Destiny made outside of man's boundary.
Are you living happily with the man who gave you that necklace?
Will you stop? You're out of places to try.
There's one place I haven't tried.
The place she's at.
Then go. I give my permission.
Can I go?
Would it be okay to cause her confusion?
Is it okay to confuse me? I'm on edge because of you.
I feel so empty inside.
Are you crazy?
He lived for a long time, too.
Put that back before you cause an international dispute.
He wants us gone.
He's scary when he's angry.
Gosh, this is just so weird.
How could we meet here?
I'm on a business trip. I'm here to research...
designs to put on the corners of our furniture.
- What are you on about? - I don't know.
How have you been?
Are you following me?
Is that a crime?
- What should I do? - I'm not a bad man.
How would I know that?
By spending time with me.
I have no reason to do that.
My company sponsored your radio show.
You offered to buy me a meal.
Is this your first time in Canada?
Let's go this way.
Did I tell you I'd be in Canada?
- Didn't I just say I'd go abroad? - I think you mentioned Canada.
You said something about maple leaves.
Maple leaves?
I remember that.
Let's go this way.
Is this enough?
It's fine.
It's nice like we're on a picnic.
Not for you, for me.
Is this enough for me?
Remember how much I sponsored your show with?
The thing is,
this trip was sudden, not planned.
I didn't bring that much money.
- What do you like? - Beef.
I'm not much of a meat-eater.
You love it.
How do you know that?
Well... Who doesn't like meat?
Don't avoid my question.
Did you have someone dig up my information?
To find out if my family...
is on par with yours?
Who said I'd date you?
You're not a catch at all.
You need to buy me meat.
That should taste lovely.
I'll call you later. Bye.
There's nothing much this way. Go that way.
I'll show you around.
Can you do that?
I don't want to be a nuisance.
It's okay. I'm sure you did it out of excitement.
You seem to know Quebec well.
Were you here before?
Yes. I was here with my first love.
We came here four times.
You have a girlfriend, then.
Not anymore.
Why did you break up?
I was very far away for a very long time.
It took a toll on her.
She'd forgotten all about me.
First loves never work out.
You must've loved her a lot.
I guess I did, considering I can't hold back.
What are you holding back?
I want to hold her hand...
and hold her close.
The woman forgot about you...
but you didn't forget her.
No.
Never for a second or a day.
What a lucky woman.
Have you heard?
If you catch a falling maple leaf,
you fall in love with the person you're with.
Is that what your first love said?
Yes, and I caught a leaf.
Do you still believe that? It didn't work out for you.
You're here with me because it didn't work out.
And you have a thing for me.
Men can be really silly. They tell the woman they like...
about their exes.
- Is that so? - Isn't it?
Are you an idiot? A teenager?
Do you believe catching a leaf makes you fall in love?
He fell for that woman's tricks.
He's such an idiot.
(You are his bride.)
Who are you?
Are you living happily with the man who gave you that necklace?
I don't remember anything.
I don't even know which chunk of my memories I lost.
My goodness.
I don't remember anything.
Nothing at all.
Let's just go and ask.
That should be quicker.
Why are you here?
Are you staying here?
- Yes. - I see.
I have a question.
Did we...
meet somewhere before?
About 10 years ago?
Mister.
It's a bit weird but I'm not hitting on you.
I keep having this weird feeling.
Do you like me?
No. I said I'm not hitting on you.
Yes.
You're my type.
For your information,
I don't have a boyfriend.
I'm not very lucky with men in this life.
I'm just saying.
I'll get going then.
Have a nice walk.
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
You go first.
You were right.
A sandwich wasn't enough.
Why don't we have early dinner? Aren't you hungry?
It will be my treat.
I was going to ask you out for dinner too.
I know a restaurant that serves good beef.
Beef.
I was thoughtless.
My feet hurt like crazy because I didn't bring my sneakers.
Your feet might hurt, but you must look beautiful.
It's okay.
At least you now know that you have to take sneakers with you next time.
I know. It's not like I've been abroad before.
I know.
Why would you go there now when you're just about to turn 30?
When I was 29, I didn't even travel as far as to the corner store.
Really? Thank you.
I didn't have any appointments.
I've been traveling around just fine...
for someone who's never been abroad before.
I rarely get lost and I never miss a meal.
Now, I'm going to have a big chunk of beef.
I'm at a nice restaurant with some man.
It's the man that has to be nice, not the restaurant.
I have to go. I'm sleepy.
Okay. Have a good night.
The future I saw was right.
Over here, Sir.
You ended up meeting this guy.
I'm embarrassed that I can't stop smiling.
Did you come here...
with your first love too?
You fed her a really expensive meal.
It was useless though. She forgot all about it.
Did you see her even after breaking up?
Yes.
I heard that the memory about first love often gets glamorized...
and you get disappointed when you meet again.
No, it's not true. She's still beautiful.
Excuse me.
I'm going to order. Are you ready to order?
Yes.
- I will... - What do you think about...
a girl who just became quite beautiful?
I recently became quite beautiful. Of course that's what I think.
Can we meet again tomorrow?
I'm flying out tomorrow afternoon.
Before you go.
And also in Korea.
Welcome.
She won't be here today, either.
Just give her this.
No wonder I wanted to go to work all of a sudden.
Are you...
Goodness.
Are you the one who's been looking for me?
Yes. You are Yu Deok Hwa, right?
The previous owner of the building.
Do you remember the chicken restaurant on the first floor?
Nine years ago.
I remember of course. You never paid rent on time.
Why were you looking for me?
You sent me a letter through this person, didn't you?
Can I...
get his contact number?
Do you want his number, not mine?
I'm a little busy, you see.
(Sunny not Sun Hee)
Let's see.
Where is a nice and remote place...
for the people who just started dating?
There's nothing much here. Let's go that way.
Is this...
you?
Are you...
a ghost?
Did you die this time?
Is that why I kept seeing you?
Do you...
still see ghosts?
Still?
How do you know that I can see ghosts?
Who are you?
Are you really a ghost?
How do you know that I used to see ghosts?
Is your name...
Kim Shin by any chance?
You came here 10 years ago with me. Is that correct?
Why don't I remember it at all?
Please answer me.
Who are you?
Why did I write not to forget you?
Why did I write that I am your bride?
You are Kim Shin, right?
You are, aren't you?
I'm not.
It's late. You should go back to the hotel.
Why aren't you surprised?
- What? - I sat here all of a sudden.
Do you know who I am?
You look like you do.
No. It's my first time seeing you.
I looked at you because you sat down.
You came to my shop, didn't you?
You brought Producer Ji's letter.
Yes.
You cried on the street.
On a cold day, you were walking...
in the street while crying, so I remembered you.
Did you cry because of me?
Many people get surprised, but not many people cry.
You look...
very similar to one woman I know.
Not too many people look like me though.
Anyway, let's introduce each other.
What's your name?
I'm Wang Yeo.
It sounds like a king's name.
My name is Sunny. S, U, N, N, Y.
I wanted to see you.
I saw you on surveillance camera.
You were so handsome that...
I was curious about how much more handsome you'd be in person.
It turns out you look better on screen.
Thank you for delivering the letter.
Thanks to you, Eun Tak got to travel abroad.
Now that I saw you in person, I will get going now.
I have to run the shop.
It's cold, so don't cry while walking.
Your face will freeze.
It was...
nice seeing you.
Same here.
BioskopKeren.ORG
It was nice seeing you, too.
Mr. Kim Woo Bin.
It was...
nice seeing you.
It was nice seeing you, too.
Mr. Kim Woo Bin.
Remember.
You must remember.
His name is Kim Shin.
Why is it raining so much?
Why isn't the part-timer coming?
The number you have dialed is not available.
Please leave a message after the tone.
What is going on?
Gosh, you startled me.
Kid, what are you doing there?
My grandma didn't come home yet.
At least you should be home, then.
You're Eun Tak's friend, aren't you? Come inside for now.
Eun Tak isn't here today. She skipped work.
Come in.
My goodness.
There you go. It's hot so blow on it before you drink.
When is your grandma coming?
Later at night when she's made money.
You're pretty unfortunate yourself, aren't you?
Grandma said there are many people who are more unfortunate than me.
Good boy.
It's all the deity's fault.
He should distribute more evenly. Only the unfortunate gets the worst.
Don't you think so? He's such a jerk.
You'll get punished if you say things like that.
It's okay.
I've been through a lot starting with the goblin couple...
and the Grim Reaper. I can speak ill of him.
He made me remember my past life and then tried to erase it again.
I wonder just how many people suffered because of him.
Don't you think oblivion is the deity's way of showing grace?
It's so you won't fall in agony.
Who does he think he is? What gives him the right?
Do you see that?
At my restaurant, even the deity has to fetch his own water.
Just like how I decide my own life.
It's my life and my memory.
He didn't even ask for my opinion. I didn't ask for it.
I'll take care of my own life.
I really wish he stays out of it.
Okay. I understand.
Who are you to say that?
(5 years ago)
- All right. A bit more to go. - Thank you.
- Watch your step. - Thank you.
Are you moving?
Yes. I've been saving up.
I'll still go to your restaurant to have chicken.
You should come. I'll give you a discount.
It's hard labour what you do.
- I'll move this one. - Okay.
Hello, I just moved in today. I live on the rooftop.
It's nice to meet you.
Then...
Today is our first day.
Sure.
Excuse me.
Just a minute.
I'm sorry. Sorry about that.
Brother?
To the one who thought...
that oblivion would bring me peace of mind.
The moment our eyes met, I knew...
that you too retained your memories.
Hence, in this life, we'll have to...
I hope...
at least you get this happy ending.
Live in each of our happy endings...
and ignore this tragedy.
I pray that in our next life...
The meeting with you is short and the wait is long.
The wait will be short and the meeting shall be long.
I don't have a religion.
You called 10 times just to tell me that?
That we won't need an excuse to see each other.
Entitled with our own dearest names.
What is this?
Is this a coincidence?
So we could greet each other when we accidentally run into each other.
Every clumsy thing...
that I do is incorrect.
With our love always being the solution.
I pray that we can meet like that.
It was nice seeing you.
I'm just happy that I saw your face.
Same here.
Kim Woo Bin.
Sometimes, you're Kim Woo Bin.
Wang Yeo.
And sometimes, you're Wang Yeo.
Please live a long and happy life.
Goodbye.
Why did that chicken restaurant owner ask for his number?
Who is Ji Eun Tak that was written on that letter?
Why do I feel like I'm the only one that doesn't know?
Of course, a rich heir...
should experience amnesia at least once in his life.
Although...
I feel like I could be someone important to them.
I didn't think it through.
If she forgot about me,
then I'm probably worth being forgotten.
I just...
miss her a lot.
Mister.
If you catch a leaf falling,
- your love will come true. - Your love will come true.
No matter how I think about it, I think you're a goblin.
I love you.
There is no sadness that lasts for eternity.
There is no love that lasts for eternity either.
I'm going to vote that there is.
Which one are you voting for?
Love or sadness?
Sad love.
I missed you.
I won't leave you behind.
Why not? Because I'm the goblin's bride?
I miss you.
Where are you?
It's really amazing now that I think about it.
You said you'd come back as rain...
and as snow.
You kept your promise.
You came on the day of the first snowfall.
"On the day of the first snowfall every year,"
"the goblin agrees to be summoned by me."
"I will be waiting for you."
Was it really because of the agreement?
I begged you not to go.
How could you leave me?
Even if that was for the best,
you took my hands to...
I'm sorry.
It's okay, you kept your promise.
What was the meaning of returning to nothingness?
That I wouldn't be able to see you.
I didn't know why,
but I turned insane whenever it rained.
It hurt and I cried.
I even mumbled to myself.
No pills could help me.
I should have lived well...
in return for all the love you gave to me.
I'm sorry.
I'll make you happy from now on.
I'm saying this because I think you haven't noticed,
but you've been touching me for a while.
You're making me feel embarrassed.
I'm checking...
because I still can't believe it.
I'm not sure if this is a dream.
It's not a dream.
I had too many...
dreams like this.
It's not a dream.
I still can't believe it.
I'm too surprised.
My heart is still racing.
Do you want me to surprise you even more?
I can buy you the whole row...
in one transaction.
Then I want a drink.
What about you?
That sounds good.
By the way, I don't think...
I should call you Mister any more.
"Honey" is a bit too much.
In 10 years, we'll be the same age.
Why don't we just call each other by names starting now?
No way.
Right.
What about my boss? Did you see her?
Just from afar. She didn't see me.
She earned a lot of money,
so she's a landlord now.
Could it be thanks to her brother who brings wealth?
Anyway, she's well.
What about the Grim Reaper? Did you see him?
He's still living at my house.
I'm not sure if he's well.
We really found friendship in each other now.
Actually, it's been a while.
What fates the two have.
Me too.
I missed you, too.
A lot.
I love you.
You're leaving again.
I want to stay with you longer too,
but I only took a few days off from work.
Since I'm a human,
I have to take a taxi to the airport...
and leave a record with immigration.
Otherwise, I'll be arrested.
- I'll visit you at jail. - Come on.
Or do you want to take the plane with me?
I've never thought about that.
Don't you want to take it with me?
I do, but I don't have a passport.
I came in a rush, so I didn't get a chance to.
Then I'll see you in Korea in about 17 hours.
It's going to take so long.
You'll be late, let's go.
Just one more minute.
Just one more time.
Did you wait long?
For 17 hours. I thought I was going to die.
When the gate opened and I saw you walk out...
You saw an angel, right?
You're not an angel.
Let go of my hand. Let go.
Never.
Did you forget your boyfriend is a goblin?
This is cheating.
I'm so excited.
I forget there are cool things behind your doors.
Hello.
Ms. Ji.
Where's Ms. Kim?
You should've called.
She didn't come in today.
I guess she made enough money.
Okay. Thanks.
Where did she go?
Is she busy?
I'm a little nervous.
I'm old enough to know better.
It's a long trip.
He'll be here soon.
This feels...
longer...
than 70 years.
Sorry.
I'm very late.
How many years has it been since we saw each other?
It's been 73 years.
It was my first birthday after we got married.
You said you'd be back after training.
You said you'd be right back.
But they created the DMZ.
I thought...
they would remove it soon.
It took long to finally give you this.
I'm too old...
to even put it on.
You are still...
just as pretty.
I've aged, waiting for you. How am I pretty?
If you were going to make me wait this long,
you shouldn't have said you'd be back soon.
Why don't you sit and talk?
The tea's gone cold, so I'll have to reheat it.
It's chilly out.
Thank you.
I'm so glad I can see you like this before I go.
I have no regrets now.
So where are you buried?
Were you buried somewhere warm?
I was buried in the North,
so azaleas will bloom on that mountain in the spring.
You're late.
Yes. I had an unexpected deceased soul.
You have an unexpected guest, too.
Hi, Mr. Grim Reaper.
May I just call you "Grim Reaper" now?
Missing Soul.
She really is an unexpected guest.
She remembered everything.
She recognized me.
"Missing Soul".
I haven't heard that in so long.
I heard everything.
How could you not come once when you remembered everything?
What good could seeing a grim reaper bring to a human?
It's been a while.
I've been enjoying your radio show.
It's been way too long to say it's been a while.
I'm already 29 years old.
29.
I see.
Let's eat. Wash your hands.
Shall I tell you a secret?
Yes.
You will meet a grim reaper when you are 29.
Even if it's not me.
That's the fate of a missing soul.
This world requires order...
and nine...
is the closest lower number to 10,
a perfect number that symbolizes the almighty.
I wish you luck then...
as well.
You met me...
at the age of 29 as well.
You met a grim reaper.
Eun Tak, it hasn't been a month yet.
Are the symptoms...
No. I came to say bye...
and to thank you for everything.
Thank you...
for keeping me alive.
Otherwise, I would've been very miserable.
I finally remembered how to be happy.
That's great.
But...
what is that method?
I smell meat.
Your taste hasn't changed.
I have the pan on the stove.
Hold on. Oh, did you eat yet?
If not, eat with me.
You're holding the same book you were holding nine years ago.
When will you finish reading that?
A man reads and writes the same book 100 times.
Look at you lie.
How cute.
- Is it obvious? - Yes.
What is this? Where am I?
Under the blanket.
You're really vulgar.
Leave if you don't feel like it.
It's so warm.
What are you doing?
Now that I'm warm I feel sleepy.
One, two, three...
Four, five...
What's wrong?
I was so scared.
Scared that it's a dream.
That I'm still dreaming.
It's not a dream.
You scared me.
From now on, show up before I count to three.
Don't go anywhere, okay?
Okay, I won't go anywhere.
Get in bed.
You left me once.
I'm sorry.
You, over there.
Why did you leave Eun Tak's room to stare into mine?
Are you Mr. Restaurant?
Mr. Restaurant?
So that's what happens.
You choose that path in the end.
It is good to see you smile.
Who's smiling? Should I smile right now?
Your temperament has not changed at all.
Maybe not now, but you smile in the end, so all is well.
Where are you going dressed like that?
Are you actually leaving? Hey.
Make my part-timer...
a happy woman.
Your foolish little sister...
will be happy as well.
Where did he go so early in the morning? Scalpel.
Uncle Tenant.
What's that watch? I want it.
Time is everything in my line of work.
A grim reaper prefers black.
I like it. This is your breakfast. Do you like it?
There you go again.
You're still so careless.
Do you even know what you're saying?
He just found you out.
I found out about you first.
You had blue flames all over you when you came over.
I thought it was spontaneous combustion.
You careless goblin.
Deok Hwa, it'll be hard to believe, but you should know the truth.
About what?
That he's a goblin and you're a grim reaper?
- How do you know that? - We just told him.
Oh, right.
I don't understand why you aren't shocked.
Grandpa told me ever since I turned six.
That I have an uncle who's a goblin.
That our family served that goblin for generations.
I thought it was some kind of odd religion.
I never imagined he meant a literal goblin.
I understand. It would be hard to imagine.
Prove it.
Prove it if you can. Both of you, if you please.
How was that?
Ever seen psychokinesis at work? What do you think?
Even humans can do that.
Don't you know David Copperfield?
Get out.
- That's all you have. - You need to come with me.
You'll find out we aren't going anywhere nice.
Uncle.
If that is your fate, so be it.
He was such a good boy.
I will get revenge.
It must be done before we become close.
(NASA phone number)
Uncles, you got it all wrong.
I wanted to ask if I can set up a branch here in Seoul.
Uncles.
Uncles?
Uncle.
Aunt?
Why do you look so surprised? I'm not banned from visiting.
Do you have any food?
No? I knew it.
I bet you order in all the time because you're rich now.
Come inside. I'll cook you something.
I'm not a picky eater. I wouldn't mind something grilled.
How are Gyeong Mi and Gyeong Sik?
- Have you seen them? - I don't care about them.
No news is good news.
Good riddance, I say. I'm better off without them.
Is this where you live? You make money, don't you?
I guess good grades get you nowhere.
Is it a monthly rent?
Get me something to eat. I'm sure you're busy.
Next week, we'll look into a few cases everyone can relate to.
Thank you. Giving us some valuable legal advice...
was lawyer Kim Yoo Na.
I hope you have a weekend ruled by common sense.
I'll play you a song and after the commercial break,
we'll come back with part three.
How was that?
You should switch jobs. You were awesome.
You didn't even listen.
You look upset. Shall we have a drink?
No. I have to go and see the chicken lady...
and I have plans. Maybe next time.
See you around.
Bye.
I'll be packed and gone by the weekend.
Very well. I'll inform your landlord.
Okay.
What got into you? One trip abroad...
and you're acting like a foreigner?
I missed you, Boss.
You're never at work or at home.
Where were you?
Packing up to move.
You're moving? Your home or business?
Both.
To overcome my new house phobia.
There's no such thing.
I got this for you from Canada.
I've been carrying it around hoping to meet you.
Did you find what you went to look for?
Everything. I found everything.
You won't believe me even if I told you.
I found everything and a boyfriend.
In Quebec of all places. It was destiny.
Is your destiny handsome?
Incredibly.
He has large, clear eyes and he served his country.
He must be so stubborn.
He is.
- What? - I know you have low standards.
Did you have fun with Mr. Restaurant?
I'll introduce him to you one day.
I really want you to meet him.
Forget it.
- Why? - I saw him leave your room.
Do what you want.
What is it?
Just. I was thinking of old times.
Okay. You do as you want with that, too.
Take care of yourself, okay?
What's wrong?
You sound like we'll never see each other again.
Goodbye, then. I have to meet someone.
Okay.
Oh, you again.
I'll say.
He's a Canadian ghost.
That man...
was a ghost.
I didn't see them for a while.
Why have I started seeing them again?
Why are you so deep in thought?
Hi.
I was thinking about Canada.
Not about me?
I was thinking about Canada,
and naturally, I started thinking about you.
You said you went there four times with your first love,
that you fed your first love beef,
and that your first love is still just as pretty.
And?
So I was thinking...
maybe I am that first love.
And?
And something is off.
Then who was that first love that you said you met...
during late Joseon?
You.
Liar.
Before we even met...
Before I even knew,
you had come by.
I saw you on the 12th year of King Chuljong's reign.
You in the far future.
- Liar. - It almost seems like a lie.
That's so cool. I'm so excited.
It really seems like a lie...
that the first love was me.
That's right. Then back then...
when I made a wish during the first snowfall,
was that...
how the warrior Kim Shin looked?
Yes.
I see.
I was really curious...
about your past that I didn't know.
But I got to see you.
- Did I look strange? - No. You looked cool.
A man from Goryeo.
Yes. That's why I'm saying this.
I'm saying this because today is just about right.
I'm saying this because you are still shining.
I'm saying this because...
you were that first love.
On another day that is just about right,
will you be my bride?
(Goblin)
For a long, long time...
Goodbye.
Is this our happy ending?
That is...
the instincts of that moment...
and completely...
one human being's choice.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.