BioskopKeren.ORG
Yes. That's why I'm saying this.
(Episode 16)
I'm saying this because today is just about right.
I'm saying this because you are still shining.
I'm saying this because you were that first love.
On another day that is just about right,
will you be my bride?
I will.
I will be the bride of this lonely man.
I will be...
the first and the last bride of this beautiful man.
I most definitely will be.
Mom.
I'm getting married.
I'll be happy.
I see you met the goblin.
And you're getting married.
Good for you.
Why am I tearing up?
Hey!
- Do you see us? - Yes.
How long has it been? How have you been?
You finally see us again.
You startled me.
Have you been doing okay?
We were lonely, that's all.
Come with me.
I'll treat you better than the goblin does.
Wait here. I have a sack of salt somewhere to...
You still have the same fiery temper.
Congratulations.
- You're getting married. - Congratulations.
Drink it.
It'll remove your memories from your life.
Thank you.
What kind of nonsense is this?
I won't share a table with my driver.
Or drink the same tea.
Here, everyone gets the same cup of tea.
What logic is that? I'm upset as it is to be dead.
Why should I be treated the same as...
the likes of a man whose whole life isn't worth the watch on my wrist?
I will tell you again.
Here, everyone gets the same cup of tea.
Your watch has already stopped ticking.
Nothing you have with you...
can pass that threshold.
Were you a powerful man in this life?
As soon as you go through that door, you'll realize that...
the crimes you committed with your eyes, your mouth,
your hands and feet...
and heart are much more powerful than anything you knew.
See how deep in Hades they drag you down.
Don't you want to go on a blind date?
I don't like chefs.
He isn't a chef.
He's a client of mine.
He's rich, owns a company,
is handsome and the crucial part is that...
he's young.
He likes older women.
I consult him about inheritance issues,
not anything shady. What do you think?
A blind date?
Oh no. These are new.
What just happened?
I shouldn't be waiting here.
Ji Eun Tak!
What should we listen to? A new singer's song?
Sure.
How can I help you?
I'm Producer Ji's boyfriend.
- What? - Her fiance, to be exact.
Shall we get hitched this weekend?
- What? - What?
Shall we get some lunch first? Let's get out of here.
Is someone joining us?
Deok Hwa. You should say hi.
I guess.
What if he doesn't recognize me because I look so old?
That will never happen.
Can I have some soup, please?
- Sure. - He's here.
An official-looking feast in front of...
a couple sitting side-by-side.
- I got what's going on. - Yes.
We're engaged.
- What? - What?
Saturday or Sunday?
What got into you today?
Lunchtime or dinnertime?
I prefer Sunday evening. Saturday's my night out.
What's this about?
Can't you tell? It's to stop you from going on blind dates.
With a handsome rich guy...
who is younger than you.
What are you talking about?
I'm the only one in Korea who fits that description.
Don't worry. You aren't my type.
Nice to meet you. I am Yu Deok Hwa.
Hello, I heard a lot about you.
I am Ji Eun Tak.
He got promoted to manager.
Ji Eun Tak?
The Ji Eun Tak of that old letter?
The Ji Eun Tak who knows my tenant?
There's still a lot you don't know.
- Enjoy your soup. - Thanks, I will.
So,
do you know what my uncle is?
He's a goblin. Doesn't everyone know one of those?
- Correct. - No way.
You know about my building and my uncle.
What's going on? Why am I the only one in the dark?
Let's eat.
Eat up and grow up.
You'll find out in due time.
Me, too.
Don't you dare go on a blind date.
Why would I? I'll be a married woman soon.
She said "married woman".
Where do you live?
I said you aren't my type.
Do you like your job?
My uncle's getting married.
That's great news.
It is. I want to get married before he does.
That's even greater news.
Isn't it? I'll have lots of kids...
so that no one's lonely.
I could wish for nothing more.
But Deok Hwa.
You need a partner to get married.
I have lots of women.
Yes, and that's the problem. You can't have many women.
Was there anyone who made your heart pound?
Anyone you missed to the point of wanting to cry?
Was there anyone who made you think you'd be willing to...
die for that person?
Not yet.
Don't you want to get married?
- I don't. - Why not?
I'm already married with three kids.
I married such a person.
No way. Did you really?
- Why didn't I know that? - I never told you.
- Why didn't you tell me? - You never asked.
You don't care much about...
the people around you or how the world works.
That's why I'm waiting for you to ask questions.
Questions that an adult would ask.
About the world...
and about the joy and sorrows of those around you.
Thank you.
Give me a little more time.
I'll try my best to grow up.
You do that.
How could you just come out and tell everyone...
without my permission?
Eyes on the road. A car's coming.
Watch out.
Are you afraid?
No. Watching you drive makes me think...
you're all grown up. Stay in your lane.
- Keep your hands on the wheel. - I am.
I know you are, I just find it fascinating, that's all.
I've never been a passenger before.
- Turn left here. - Left?
Not right, left, left!
Stop yelling. Where are we going anyway?
Turn on the blinkers before you make a turn!
You look so pretty.
You look pretty nice yourself.
I always do.
Let's get married with a bowl of water.
Keep it mysterious.
Okay.
Is it a gift?
A wedding gift.
He has pretty wrists.
I'll take this one.
I love all the roads we will walk together.
I love all the sceneries we will see together.
I love all the questions we will shyly ask each other...
and all the answers to those questions.
I love you...
in all those moments. From your bride.
After we listen to a song, we will come back with a listener's story.
Cue.
What is this letter?
It's so poorly written.
Was this written at night?
What is it? I love love letters.
I'm sure you do.
"To the one who thought..."
"that oblivion would bring me peace of mind."
"The moment our eyes met, I knew..."
"that you too retained your memories."
Pick this story. It's my right as the producer.
I'll be back soon.
Eun Tak! Hey!
This is a live show!
"I pray that in our next life..."
"The wait will be short and the meeting shall be long."
"That we won't need an excuse to see each other."
"Entitled with our own dearest names."
"So we could greet each other..."
"when we accidentally run into each other."
With our love always being the solution.
I pray that we can meet like that.
I'm just happy that I saw your face.
Sometimes, you're Kim Woo Bin.
And sometimes, you're Wang Yeo.
Please live a long...
and happy life.
Goodbye.
Did she really sell the building? Didn't she just move?
No. She sold the building last week. You live on the rooftop, right?
You're my tenant now.
I heard you work for a radio station.
Yes.
I'm in a little bit of a hurry right now. I'll see you later.
(The rooftop unit)
Eun Tak.
I'm leaving.
Take care. Don't cry.
Get something to eat.
You were all alone without a family.
I hope I provided you a little bit of comfort.
Please take good care of my stubborn brother.
Stay happy together.
Goodbye.
She remembered everything.
Sunny...
left.
She remembered everything.
She kept the memory alone.
She took care of me when I didn't remember anything.
She missed her brother who disappeared.
She must've been so lonely.
Why did she leave now?
It's because she can't forgive him.
She made the choice...
not to see him again in this life.
There's no bigger punishment...
for the Grim Reaper.
I should count to 50 and leave.
One.
Two.
47.
48.
49.
One.
Two.
Three.
You will...
not hear from me.
In this life,
we will never meet again.
Can I...
hug you just once?
Take care.
Like that,
we parted in this life.
It was...
much later...
when I heard from her.
I touched this vulgar thing for you.
Why don't you try it?
The apples look like bunnies.
Sunny...
left.
She is...
always...
so good...
at leaving.
After what happened to you,
I didn't know what to do, so I kept it.
I meant to return it to you much sooner.
I'm sorry it's late.
It wasn't mine from the start.
It was your resentment, sin, and longing.
I think you should keep it.
Can I keep it?
Yes.
If you eat this.
And thank you.
I heard you lit the candles...
at the temple while I was gone for the past nine years.
I don't know if I had the rights to pay respects to them.
But I wanted to face my sins.
I wish someone could tell us.
"You've done enough."
"It's time to end it all."
I'd like that.
I heard you wanted to see me.
Yes.
I want...
to tell you a secret.
A secret?
You become a grim reaper if you commit a sin in your past life.
I wanted to tell you what your sin was.
The big sin we committed...
was taking our own lives.
Those who took their own lives...
are born again as grim reapers,
made to guide many deaths,
and live as a being that's in between the living and the dead.
What do you think is the reason for this?
Why do you think someone without a name...
or any memories...
needs a house...
and food?
What do you think is the reason?
While looking for the answer to those questions,
I realized one day...
that maybe it makes us...
yearn for a name...
and the life...
we had once abandoned.
Maybe this punishment ends...
when we become desperate for life.
I know why you avoided me.
I assume...
you met Park Joong Heon nine years ago.
That means you know...
who you are and who I am.
That's why...
I wanted to apologize.
I should not have chosen death...
by borrowing your hands as I did.
I regret it.
Also,
I beg for your forgiveness.
So forget everything.
Forget from now on.
Send off the deceased souls during their final moments.
Make penance like that.
I hope you will...
come to forgive yourself as well.
What the deity wants of us...
is probably to forgive ourselves and realize the earnestness of life.
Come eat.
Where are you going so late at night?
The soup will get cold. Eat.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I hope you don't end up being a single mom like your mom.
Why must you always...
How long are you staying?
I gave you enough memorial foods.
You're a ghost. It isn't good to roam for too long.
How dare you talk to me like that?
Hey.
I can't just go like this. It's not fair.
If only I had those bank books. If only you hadn't stolen them,
I wouldn't have died on the streets!
What's wrong with you?
Must you do this even after you die?
You're talking back because you haven't been hit in a while.
Why I...
Hey, lady. Whom do you think you're trying to touch?
She's someone I cherish dearly. Shall I break your wrist?
What's your problem? Who is this psycho?
I'm your senior by years, and what? A psycho?
You know what? You need to come with me.
Go with me. It's because I'm lonely.
I tend to get along well with evil witches.
Let go. Let go of me!
- Do you know her? - Hey!
I think I've finally found my companion.
She'll be a good sparring partner for the lonely afterlife.
You're leaving?
It's time.
Thanks for everything.
Live happily ever after with the goblin.
Come on. Let's go.
Hold on.
Auntie. Thank you for raising me.
In our next lifetime, let's meet on good terms.
Don't make me laugh! Why would I meet you again?
Let go! Let go!
Let go.
Hi.
You're still doing that alone. Where's the goblin?
I don't know. He said something about drawing fresh water.
I'm the one who wanted to see you.
I have something for you.
Did you get...
my name card?
No, it's not like that.
I see. You scared me.
Are you worried that your name will come up?
Not really worried. I'm curious...
about how my fate has changed.
Your fate has so many variables.
Exactly.
The birthmark is gone and I pulled out the sword.
So I've been living without problems for the past nine years.
But it doesn't change the fact that I'm a missing soul.
I was almost never born.
I drove the person I love to death.
And...
the person before me is a grim reaper.
Above all else, every human dies at some point.
That's why life is even more beautiful.
That's why...
the first thought I had once I got my memory back...
was to live each day as if it were my last.
If today is my last day, this will be...
my final memory of the person I love.
So I'd better...
live hard and love.
That's what I told myself.
Your life is already beautiful. Just know that.
What did you want to give me?
Here.
Congratulations on your wedding, Goblin's bride.
Thank you.
Until death parts us,
every word that you say,
whatever it may be,
me too.
Until death parts us,
every word that you say, whatever it may be,
me too.
- That looks good. - This?
Should we make more?
Champagne is best between 7 and 8ºC.
Uncle Tenant.
I feel drunk already, and I haven't even drunk yet.
You can't get drunk already.
- Bottoms up. - Not you, too.
Are you okay?
- You don't look well. - I'm fine.
Okay. I made it 7ºC.
Would you like a glass?
Yes, thank you...
- Oh no. - Mr. Kim.
Seriously.
Can't you guys be more careful?
Both of you are too careless and relaxed.
What was that? How did that come out so naturally?
Sing. Sing.
Sing.
No, no. I can't sing.
I can't sing.
Meeting you.
Among all these people.
Was.
Really lucky.
Meeting you.
In this big world.
All together, now.
Meeting you was happiness for me.
Meeting you among all these people
I'm sleepy.
Goodnight.
I love you.
This is our last song. I wish you happiness.
Okay, good job.
Good work.
Today's show was so great.
You were right on time and the set list was perfect.
Our bulletin board is receiving a lot of good feedback.
It's rare to have such a perfect show.
Stop flattering me.
Then I'm going to go meet with a guest,
then go straight home from there.
All right.
- Goodnight. - See you tomorrow.
It seems like a day care bus is going to get in an accident.
This looks like the driver.
Now,
I really feel like this is a punishment.
I'll be back after this call.
Mister.
Sir. I just got a call from the head office.
They told us to discard the list we received today.
The children's fates have changed.
Really?
Why would it change, though?
Because of a death...
where a list cannot be made.
Can there be a death without a name list?
What do you mean?
A death that cannot be predicted.
(Goblin)
A sacrifice.
Where are you? It's a scary world out there.
Do you know what time it is?
It's 4pm. I'm on my way to a meeting.
Hold on. Let me turn right first.
You have to turn your handle right, okay?
Come on.
Hello? Eun Tak.
Ji Eun Tak.
The day care bus...
If I dodge, those kids...
What? I can't hear you. What did you say?
I must be crazy. What am I doing?
What's going on?
Now that I think about it,
it was such a perfect day.
When I woke up, I was in his arms.
Then I made perfect eggs.
The show today was perfect, too.
Everything went perfectly...
to bring me to this moment.
So that I won't be late.
Hello? Where are you?
Eun Tak, where are you?
I couldn't be late,
not even for a second.
This was my fate.
Goodnight.
I love you.
Me too.
A human's sacrifice...
is something the almighty cannot predict.
It wasn't a part of his plan.
That's because it's a momentary instinct...
and a choice...
solely made by that human.
It's a choice...
only humans can make.
(Ji Eun Tak, 29 years old, car accident)
We received...
a late...
name list.
She gave a sad answer...
to his wicked question.
Missing soul...
Move back, please.
Move back.
You were born on 1998,
July 23.
You are 29 years old.
Ji Eun Tak.
Can you...
confirm?
I questioned myself,
but I was already...
doing it.
I was...
really scared.
This afternoon, a truck that was parked on the curve...
had its brake come loose and rolled down,
taking the life of a woman in her 20s.
That car must have taken all the shock.
My goodness.
She must've been an angel.
I believe that she's not an ordinary person.
Had it not been for her,
a lot more people would have died.
Is this the place...
you work at?
It's really nice.
Mister, there is something I'm curious about.
I heard...
humans have four lives.
How many lives have I had?
Can't you tell...
a dead person?
This was...
your first.
Thank goodness.
I still have three more.
I'll go get the tea.
You two can talk.
Do you...
remember what I said before?
The person left behind...
has to live to the full.
You'll cry sometimes,
but you'll also laugh a lot...
and live bravely.
That's the proper response to the love you were given.
How can it be like this?
How can you do this?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Look at me. Let me...
see your face. Please?
Mister.
You forgot to grant...
one of my three wishes.
Can you grant me that wish now?
Don't be heartbroken for too long.
I'll come see you again.
Wait for me...
and don't make it rain too much.
It'll cause trouble.
That's three wishes, not one.
How am I supposed to live without you?
I'll be gone for just a while.
I promise.
This time,
I'll come to you.
I will...
come looking for you.
In our next life, I will make sure to be born with a long life...
and stay by your side for a long while.
I will beg the divinity...
to let me do just that.
When everyone else leaves...
Please...
take care of this man.
This is the tea of oblivion.
It'll remove...
your memories from your life.
I won't...
drink the tea.
I think...
I have to go now.
I'll be back soon.
I'll go running...
and come back running.
You have to come.
Even if it takes 100 years or 200 years.
I'll wait for you.
So...
See you...
again.
(Goblin)
(Bride)
In loving memory of...
beloved goblin's bride.
May she rest in peace.
(In loving memory of beloved goblin's bride.)
(May she rest in peace.)
(Beloved, bride, rest in peace)
That day,
Missing Soul walked through...
the tears of someone.
Tides of time got carried away...
by the rainfall.
It was...
a very long rain.
Missing Soul...
left this world without a guardian...
after leaving one behind.
A very lonely and beautiful guardian.
She must have...
met her mom by now.
What is that hairpin?
You didn't pay for that, did you?
No, this is of my dad's taste.
Then wear it when he's around. Why do you have it on now?
I love my dad whether he's around or not.
So mind your own business and shut your mouth.
I don't even have a dad who can buy me one of those.
I don't get it.
Gosh, why do you have to get all serious?
What are you looking at, Lady?
Kids these days are scary.
Whatever.
Sweetheart.
I know you can be like that at your age,
but you don't have to be.
I was only looking at you...
because I couldn't believe how precious you are.
I'm sorry.
Do you want more fish cake?
- Yes. - Yes.
First loves never work out.
You must've loved her a lot.
I guess I did,
considering I can't hold back.
I mean...
I missed you so much that I couldn't breathe.
It was too dangerous.
The woman forgot about you,
but you didn't forget her.
No.
Never for a second or a day.
By the way,
you're not supposed to press my head like that.
You're supposed to pat it like this.
(30 years later)
It's your final name card.
Your long punishment has come to an end.
Is it just one?
Yes.
Finally, it's the end of my long punishment.
Congratulations.
Please...
go in peace.
You've helped me a lot.
Thank you.
I won't need to dry clean this anymore.
You said...
I wouldn't hear from you.
Your news came anyway.
It's my last job.
Take care.
You too.
Regardless of the time or the appearance you wear,
be happy.
I've had a good life until now.
- Don't make it rain. - Don't worry.
This has been my job for a long while.
Once the washing is done, make sure to hang the laundry.
When you're done with that, come to the tea house.
I plan to break the rules just one more time.
I'm leaving anyway.
You haven't aged at all.
You're still just as handsome.
Have you been well?
You said I wouldn't hear from you.
I had forgotten...
that the man I was seeing was a grim reaper.
I forgot that you would find out.
I've missed you.
I knew you would.
I've always wanted to put it on you properly, at least once.
I'm sorry I forced it on you so meanly that time.
I've missed you a lot.
I knew you would.
You are the last deceased soul...
that I am leading.
I see.
Then what's next?
What happens to us?
Is this our happy ending?
This was your third life.
What about you?
I don't know.
I guess...
this may be the last time.
Your brother is here.
Outside.
You still don't care about your brother.
I am happy I get to see you at least like this...
before I go.
It is because I made a good friend.
I'm sorry for going first and leaving you behind.
Please take care of yourself.
Let's meet again someday.
Be happy,
my ugly sister.
My sister,
my friend,
and my bride...
have all left.
And as always,
I am left all alone.
Cheer up.
Do you know why sandwiches come in pairs?
To share with someone else.
Take it.
There are lots of jobs in this world. We'll find one.
Eat up.
You're young.
I know you're frustrated.
Try to cheer up, though.
Some people shine...
later on in life.
Every life is touched...
by a deity at least once.
Just when you're drifting away from the world,
if someone nudged you back in the right direction,
that would be...
when the deity chose to visit you.
I have to go.
Mr. Kim.
Go this way instead.
You will meet someone who needs your help.
Thanks for the sandwich.
Do you know anything about cars?
Yes.
I can tell that this one's not running.
Can I help you?
Do you know about cars?
I've been fixing them for about 20 years.
Let's have a look.
Why didn't you call your insurance company?
They'd sort things out for you.
Did you call the insurance company?
I got distracted when you opened the hood.
I'll call right away.
I believe...
I was meant to meet you.
Were we?
That's a romantic thought, Sir.
Yes. I'm a bit of a romantic.
There we go.
As I sent the lantern flying that night,
I prayed that my sister, in her future...
and my master, in his future...
would meet again one day.
And when they meet again,
that they be happy.
That had been my wish.
What's this?
I arrest people right away,
handcuff them without hesitation...
and read them their rights.
You have the right to remain silent,
the right to refuse to testify...
I asked what this is about. Is that a hard question to ask?
You asked me to show you how I act out an arrest.
I just... I asked you to show me,
not actually handcuff me.
Your criminal's over there.
Oh, is she the criminal?
You looked more like one. Sorry.
Don't I look like a detective?
At 1st glance, 2nd glance and 3rd glance,
you look like a criminal.
How dare you. What makes you think I'm a criminal?
Did I steal your heart or something?
You look like the hostess of a gambling den.
From head to toe.
I just look like one.
I'm working undercover. Undercover.
We're pretending this is 2016.
Forget it.
Director, who is this guy?
Why is he so rude?
Didn't I introduce you two?
He's our consultant, a detective from a violent crimes unit.
I'm Lee Hyuk from Gangnam Police Station.
Lee Hyuk? No way.
I heard that.
Don't get any ideas.
I'm an actress...
and we're filming nearby.
The crew didn't book a hotel...
so I'm here because I don't have a choice.
I'm her stylist.
I have only one free room.
I can't believe...
why there's always only one free room.
That's too bad. We'll take it.
Quickly, please.
We could try looking for another hotel...
but we'd only get sore legs.
Sore legs become swollen.
The more sleep I get the nicer my skin will be tomorrow.
Why didn't they book a room for the actress?
I never wanted to know.
Here's the key.
Lead the way, stylist.
Do you have a room?
Sorry, I only have one left.
Pretend you didn't hear that.
I didn't hear anything.
So what will we do now?
- What do you mean? - Like...
"Should we date? Meet up regularly?"
"I like you." When will you say things like that?
Aren't you going to?
Should I say that first?
Should I, then? I'm an actress.
I'm already annoyed that I liked you first.
Who said you liked me first?
Everyone does. Are they all wrong?
- Yes. - How?
I liked you first.
That's my state...
No, that's my confession.
My goodness.
Just a step too late...
and I might have liked you first.
Give me your hand.
- What's this? - Consider it like a handcuff.
You just stole my heart.
Do you see this?
They call you the Grim Reaper.
Isn't this a bribe?
Arrest me, then.
Is this our first day together?
Are you going somewhere, Sir?
I'd like to go for a walk.
Avoid the main street if you can.
Some Korean students are visiting and they're noisy.
- I shouldn't be long. - Of course, Sir.
I found him.
There is no sadness that lasts for eternity.
There is no love that lasts for eternity either.
I'm going to vote that there is.
Which one are you voting for? Love or sadness?
Sad love.
Mister.
You know who I am, right?
The first and the last...
goblin's bride.
Bioskop Keren
(Goblin)
(Thank you for watching Goblin.)