Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(GOBLIN)
At a moment of life and death,
make a wish with a powerful desire.
A soft-hearted creator might grant you that wish.
You punk. Drive properly!
- Hey. Look.
- What?
What's going on?
(EPISODE 3)
Who are those punks?
Are they from "Men in Black" or what?
Who are they?
Hey.
Go. Go.
Step on it.
Now!
Daddy! Daddy!
Mommy...
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Get out.
Get your things.
Were you hurt?
Where?
"Are you hurt?"
What?
How could you ask that...
after cutting the car in half like that?
Wait here.
What do you plan to do?
Will you kill them?
You won't kill them, right?
- No.
- You always said, "No."
The Grim Reaper came too.
It's not like he came to save me.
That would make more sense.
Don't worry. I won't kill them.
I simply wanted to show them that I was angry...
so that they'd wish they were dead.
Help.
- Help!
- Don't kill us!
- Please don't kill us.
- Please.
Please don't kill us! Please!
- Are you okay?
- Help us.
This road will disappear from the map for two days.
As in, you won't be lucky enough to have someone find you for two days.
It'll be so painful that you'll think you're dying, but you won't.
You'll be found by the police two days from now.
You can pay for your sins once you get to the police station.
You should be grateful I'm not the one making you pay.
Mercy is often hidden among the victims that you harass.
She's the one you should thank.
The two of you fought. That's all.
You did not see anything.
You will never make up for the rest of your lives.
Did you...
not bring a car?
We don't take cars often.
Did I...
I'm asking this just in case.
Did I die?
Is this the road to the afterlife?
It's a country road.
And we just saved you.
Then will you kill me now?
Was I captured alive?
I'm curious.
When will we hear her thank us for saving her life?
Calm down.
We're with a 19-year-old girl who is still angry.
I never imagined the two of you would be this close.
How could you bring the Grim Reaper...
to the person who asked you to save her life?
I'm curious.
When will we hear her thank us...
Quiet already!
Why are you yelling at me?
Why is there not a single car on this stupid road?
Someone made sure there will be no cars on this road for two days.
I said to stop talking.
Why didn't you leave yet?
You said you were leaving.
I will soon.
Don't mind me. It's not like I'm all that curious.
I know.
How did you come?
I couldn't blow out the flame from the lighter.
I don't know.
I just heard your saying "Save me," or something like that.
But I only thought it in my head.
You must think very loudly.
You didn't have to come.
I had no reason not to.
I'm sorry.
You came in the middle of the night to save me who isn't your bride.
I thought about it,
and you were right when you said...
I was living on bonus time.
I heard you saved my mom and me 19 years ago.
That's why I don't mind that it's bonus time...
since I got to meet Mom because I was born. So...
I won't hate you anymore.
- You seem to hate me.
- I do not.
I wanted to tell you this if we ever met again...
although you probably hoped we wouldn't.
- You do seem to hate me.
- I do not.
From now on,
I won't make wishes, think,
or do anything,
so you can relax and leave.
I hope you have a safe trip...
and meet someone nice.
Someone pretty and nice, who will discover your true self.
Not her face, but her heart.
Since you don't care about looks.
It's all cooked now. Go ahead and eat it.
I'll get going then.
Wait.
Do I have to pay for it when I didn't eat it?
You're the one who wanted to eat this.
I didn't have any, either.
Besides, I don't have money.
I will pay for it then. Just make some time for me.
Go after you're done.
Are you...
trying to feed me dinner?
Yes.
I don't think they fed you before kidnapping you.
No. I don't want to eat dinner with you.
Or I'll take it home. I'll thankfully eat it.
You do hate me.
Listen carefully.
Eun Tak lost her parents when she was little.
She was maltreated by her aunt and her cousins.
Oh, poor little Eun Tak. She must've cried a lot.
Here's the list of people who made her cry.
Her aunt and her cousins.
We don't even have to dig deep.
Everyone in the town knows about it.
Eun Tak's mother left her about 150,000 dollars of insurance money.
They're abusing her now because they can't do anything when she turns 18.
That the type of person she is.
Why?
I'm surprised that you're actually useful.
If you're a rich person, you have...
to use money and power to dig into someone's background at least once.
Where did you get these pictures?
I followed them and took them.
But I didn't see Eun Tak. I think she's busy.
What's that?
It's me. I look nice in it.
By the way, why did you ask me to do this?
To punish them.
How?
Are you not well?
That's not a punishment. That's gold.
How can you punish someone by giving them gold?
- How about me?
- Good job.
How about me?
Why don't I get a gold bar?
Didn't I commit a lot of sins?
Don't I deserve to receive divine punishment?
Did they kidnap her or what?
Why aren't they calling?
Be quiet, you morons.
Don't you see that your mother is in pain?
Idiots.
My money is about to get in the hands of those punks.
You borrowed it anyway.
Yes, I should've starved both of you to death.
Our life now is not any better anyway.
Yes. I'm the idiot.
Why did I have children one year after another?
- What is this?
- It's gold, you idiot.
Eun Tak changed all the money into these gold bars.
This is why she kept saying she didn't have a bankbook.
This is why she doesn't have a bankbook.
Let's go to the jeweler's as soon as the day breaks.
As we promised, we will divide it evenly among us.
Do any funny business, and I will...
I'm your mother, you moron.
- Give it to me.
- Let it go.
- Let it go!
- No!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Mom, get up! Gyeong Mi took the gold!
That wench!
Her phone's busy.
I know. She's talking to someone.
Whom is she talking to?
It's you, you moron.
Hang up!
Get the taxi.
- Taxi!
- I'm in a hurry!
- Move!
- Let's go.
- Go.
Yes, Grandpa. Uncle's eating now.
No, he just had a bite.
I even put kimchi on his plate.
He's eating seolleongtang.
Okay. Okay.
By the way, my credit card...
Hello?
Actually, this problem will be solved if you say just a word...
Uncle, did you hear what I said?
What are you watching?
I'm watching the television.
He's a pitiful man.
I should pity him, not get angry at him.
He was just about that age.
Who?
The King I used to guard.
He was 17 years old.
You used to guard a king?
That's crazy.
Were you a eunuch?
I was his clothes.
Pity him, Deok Hwa.
He needs your help.
It was the brightest time of the day.
My eyes hurt,
so I constantly resented someone.
I'm not sure if it was the King, the divinity,
or me.
I forgot.
Is it him?
Who is?
The person who caused my 1,000 years of rage.
The reincarnation of the King who slew me.
Look carefully.
Did he reincarnate?
I don't know, either. He'd be that age if he reincarnated.
He was a eunuch. "Your Highness."
Forget.
The resentment and the desire for revenge are making you miserable.
Are you happy because you don't remember anything?
I can't tell by just looking.
- I have to touch him to know.
- What?
You are completely useless.
What will you know when you touch him?
By the way, why are you so sure that he reincarnated as a man?
- Is it her?
- I can't tell by just looking.
I have to touch them to know.
What happens when you touch someone?
It's her, right? Tell me that it's her.
I think I'm ready to forgive her.
You said it was your 1,000 years of rage.
I'm sure he had his reasons.
As you know, rage is found everywhere and nowhere.
What is it? What will he know when he touches them?
Why are you leaving me hanging?
Gosh.
Hello, Sir! I'm Kim from Batch 21.
Hello, Sir! I'm Kim from Batch 23.
Nice to meet you, too. Take a seat.
- Yes, we will work hard, Sir!
They are so young and fresh.
We were once like them, too.
I am Kim from Batch 21.
At ease.
- Yes, we will work hard, Sir!
You're here.
By the way, why don't you check your work email?
About the missing ones...
A new team has been formed to take charge of them.
Please submit a list before the year-end.
I don't have any.
You have two, don't you?
Who says I have two missing ones?
Everyone says that you have two missing ones.
- I'll submit it right away.
- That will be much appreciated.
I have business to take care of, so I will get going now.
I'll see you at the winter workshop.
Take care.
It's her.
Hello.
I'm Kim from Batch 23.
- I'll get going.
- Go ahead.
She's beautiful.
She should be an angel. Why is she a grim reaper?
Her batch mates are thrilled because of her.
You look very thrilled about her, too.
Clear the way.
- Move.
- Honey.
- This way.
Come on.
Honey...
Well, then.
Okay. Oh, right.
There's a welcoming party for Batch 23 at the end of this month.
There's a penalty for not showing up. Make sure not to show up.
I'm Kim from Batch 21.
Did you book an OR?
We don't have time. Hurry up.
Mr. Choi Yeong Jae.
I am sorry, but I'm occupied at the moment. Stay outside.
You're 33 years old.
You die on October 4, 2016.
Time of death is 5:41pm.
Cause of death is overworking.
It's you, isn't it?
Did I...
die?
Yeong Jae!
- Yeong Jae!
Yeong Jae.
Please open your eyes.
Thanks to your first aid,
the patient made it.
His vitals are stable. He made it.
That's good.
(FORM FOR MISSING SOULS)
(THE GOBLIN EXHIBITION)
(GOBLIN SNACKS)
(GOBLIN STATIONERY)
(NIGHT GOBLIN TOURS)
I'll marry you.
I really think you're the goblin.
I love you.
I found him.
Close your eyes. Don't make eye contact.
He's the Grim Reaper.
I don't care.
He can leave if he wants.
Is it sold already?
Why can't I get a refund?
Like I told you already, Sir, you need to bring the receipt.
I wanted to buy a book, not someone's memory.
What am I to do with this thing I found in the book?
- I want a refund.
- Even if you do,
without the receipt...
I'll buy that book.
Does this memory belong to you?
Well... Yes, it does. It's mine. I'll buy that book.
There's no evidence that it's yours.
- Guess where this leaf is from.
- Que...
You wouldn't know the answer even if I were to tell you.
That's correct.
I thought I'd lost it forever. Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're too old to read that.
It's for research.
What about you? Why did you buy it?
- I know a goblin.
- What?
What? Doesn't everyone know a goblin or two?
- Really?
- Of course not, you silly.
If someone asks you to vouch for them, say no.
If someone suggests you to buy something, say no.
If someone offers you a snack?
"Get lost."
Give me 10 dollars for the book. How long must I sit here?
Sorry about that.
Hang on.
Isn't this book second-hand now?
No. No.
- Just this once.
- Get lost.
Uncle.
Hello... Grandpa.
Hi.
I came by to drop off the dry-cleaning and say hello.
You seem to have a guest.
Oh, right. A guest.
Who would you be, Sir?
What are you doing in my uncle's house?
I am... I am his friend.
- I'm visiting.
- Oh, you're visiting a friend.
You must be my uncle's best friend.
Are you throwing him a party before he goes abroad?
Goodbye.
Take care. Never come back.
Be happy for a long time. Stay until you die.
You can leave instead. We aren't friends.
Get out of my house. Never come back.
Uncle, you can't say that to your best friend.
Do you think you're an exception? Get out as fast as you can.
How could he do that?
- Wasn't that just too mean?
- It was.
Right? How could he kick me out as well?
Would a real relative have done that?
- He won't stay for long.
- I hope so.
Or you'll have to come with me.
To some place.
A nice place, I hope? It wouldn't be nice, would it?
- Come in.
- No thanks.
- Even if you beg me to...
- Not you.
Go home and get yelled at.
One-nil to me.
- Bye.
- I'll get yelled at?
What for?
Did you tell my grandpa everything?
How could you do that?
How much did you tell him? Tell me so I can make an excuse.
Did you tell me before you rented out my house?
I won't go.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll stay and haunt this house.
Oh, yes.
What's this?
Goodnight. It's a tie now.
Is that... Is that horse blood?
Grim Reaper! Get this out of here!
I'm sorry so get rid of this. Hey!
Yes?
You.
Do you sleep here?
Well...
I'm sorry. I've been meaning to tell you,
but I couldn't find the right timing.
I'm really sorry.
How did you know?
I don't brush my teeth at the store.
I have another evidence.
Ms. Kim,
I've actually been sleeping at the restaurant...
would it be all right if I stayed here for a while?
(WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT IF I STAYED HERE FOR A WHILE?)
Ms. Kim,
I have been sleeping here for a couple of days...
Thank you for letting me stay.
I've been kicked out from home.
Please help me.
Help me with what?
I'm sorry.
Is it because of your aunt?
Kind of.
I had a few things happen to me.
Okay.
Aren't you going to ask me more questions?
Why should I? It's not like I'll solve it for you.
I should only do things I can help.
Here's your week's worth of work.
I'll give it to you week by week. Why?
If I give it to you monthly, you might never get anything.
Even if you sleep here, go to the public bath to shower.
Get yourself a snack there.
Thank you.
You earned it. There's no need to...
thank me like that. People will think you're easy.
I'm not thanking you about the money.
I'm thanking you for being so admirable.
That's because money is admirable.
Go get a shower. Before you go, roast a squid for me.
Are you going to drink?
No, just the squid.
I don't drink.
I get drunk when I drink.
Pardon?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
No, no, no. It was a mistake.
No!
Were you reading?
I always have a book by my side.
I have much interest in music and arts as well.
I'm sorry to have bothered you when you were reading.
Exactly.
Why are you bothering me?
I didn't call you. It was a mistake.
I was grilling squid when it caught on fire, so I had to blow it out.
Was it tasty?
Why are you here? I thought you were leaving.
I was packing my books.
Books come first.
- I better go and pack.
- Hey...
You always talk to me when I try to leave.
It's the other way around. You always leave when I talk.
- I have something to ask.
- I'm not giving you 5,000 dollars.
You surprised me.
I thought you said you won't profess to me.
It's because you just assumed and said something so random.
Since when is it all my fault?
Since when you told me I should be seeing something.
So what exactly is it that I should be seeing...
to become useful to you?
If I tell you, are you going to tell me you can see it?
No. I'd tell you I can't see it even if I can.
What if you start being nice to me because I can see it?
You might suddenly give me 5,000 dollars and buy me steak.
You might even ask me if I want anything.
Then I'd be so tired since you're so annoying.
I've never heard such a thing.
I swear. I've never heard it before.
Hey, I'm talking. What are you looking at?
Don't answer me if you don't want to.
Don't you see something special?
It should look painful.
That?
- Can you see it?
- I get it now.
Bye. I'm busy, so I have to go.
Hey, do you want to eat steak? Do you want anything?
- I want 5,000 dollars.
- I thought you were busy.
- Go.
- Then I want meat.
Come on.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
That was the last piece.
Can you see it?
Yes.
It looks delicious.
Thank you for the food.
I asked if you can see it. You can't, can you?
Are you snapping at me?
Did it sound like that?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I was just going to ask if you want freshly squeezed juice after this.
Sorry if my voice got too sharp.
Freshly squeezed juice?
Which one do you want? You can get an expensive one.
I'm full.
I'll get a large one of that.
You're not full.
Me, too. Get me the same one.
I'll help you with the payment.
She'll help you over there.
I'm not paying for him.
What's gotten into you?
I thought you hated fruits.
What about you?
Are you killing someone in the area?
I'm a regular here.
Is it me?
Am I dying here today?
Did I...
get lured in by meat...
and then get caught in the trap with this juice?
Are you two really a team?
No, it's a misunderstanding.
I'm actually on your side.
You can see the sword.
Pull out the sword.
What are you doing?
What are you talking about? Why are you on my side?
What's with her? Why can't I control her?
She's not someone you can predict.
That means I'll have a lot of supplementary documents to hand in.
Have a good time.
I have a meeting to go to.
Did he really come to drink juice?
That's interesting.
By the way, why is he saying that he's on my side?
It's none of your business.
Hey, don't you think he's handsome for no use?
Is it because people tend to follow a handsome grim reaper?
Maybe they only hire handsome ones.
Are all grim reapers handsome?
Do you call that handsome?
Yes. He's handsome.
What about me?
You're...
just looking.
Stop drinking.
You're full.
That guy is handsome, too.
I guess only good looking people come here.
I'll be right there. See you soon.
I love you.
Yes, Honey. I'll be there soon. I miss you.
What are you doing?
Something everyone hopes to happen to them.
Are you all right?
Magic.
I'm sorry.
- I'll untie it.
- Pardon? Oh, gosh.
Well...
What is this?
Excuse me. Okay...
I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Well...
It's untied now.
Are you all right?
Yes.
This is a very strange day.
I feel like I'm enchanted.
Speaking of which,
do you...
have a boyfriend?
No. My parents are very strict.
- I see.
- Do you...
have a girlfriend?
Never in my life.
I've been waiting for you all this time.
Kiss. Kiss. Kiss.
Do you have a second job as Cupid?
That was you being their guardian, wasn't it?
One or two in a century...
are reincarnated with the same faces from their previous lives.
I know that man from his previous life.
He can't afford to lose that woman.
What was his previous life like?
Did he save our nation when it was in crisis?
In his previous life,
he was a farm owner...
who used to leach off of impoverished peasants.
Then why help him?
Are you a guardian for bad people as well?
That's not fair.
The good people are the ones who need your help.
I'm not their guardian.
I'm the guardian of the man and woman they just lost.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I miss you. I'm on my way.
You don't need to rush. I don't want you to trip.
Okay?
The man is a liar and a coward.
The woman is vain and ungrateful.
Those two will become each other's nightmares.
You're cool.
From time to time, I meddle...
with the lives of mortals by enchanting them.
By the way,
can I ask why you're talking like an actor in a historical drama?
I don't know why.
That being said,
is it because I sinned greatly...
in my previous life and I'm being punished for it now?
Is it my punishment...
that I was born as the goblin's bride?
I am not acquainted with your previous life.
You're too young to evaluate your life.
And you're not the goblin's bride.
I thought I could fool you.
I know I had my ups and downs, but I like the life I'm living.
I was greatly loved by my mom.
I even found myself an umbrella.
I'm pleased to have met you.
Was. Was pleased.
You hold grudges.
And you haven't answered me on whether or not you see it.
Do you see it or not?
This is what my mom said.
"We should watch where we place our feet before we take a step..."
"and always know where we're headed."
You know what that means, right?
No. I don't.
It means this is where we part ways.
I'm going that way.
Goodbye.
You're cool.
You look cool.
Just now, you looked like a part of a painting.
Where's the other uncle?
- He's not home.
- He must be working late.
Uncle, I had a thought.
I think I should become a grim reaper when I die.
At the end of the hallway of life,
death awaits me.
I'll be welcomed by Grim Reaper himself.
In your dreams.
You're short of million sins.
I don't want to break it to you,
but only those who sinned greatly can become...
What kind of great sins?
How did you know?
My gosh. Did he kill someone?
You can never judge a book by its cover.
Not that. How did you know he's a grim reaper?
Uncle.
Don't you think it's too late for you to ask me that?
Remember when you made the room cloudy and thunder,
I got nervous when I saw him come out of his room.
But he didn't even flinch by the slightest.
- What's wrong with him?
- And I heard you talking about...
how a grim reaper like him can foresee the future and everything.
Watch your mouth, Grim Reaper.
Don't underestimate my power to foresee the future.
That's not all. Just look at his pale skin and bloody red lips.
And why does he only wear black?
I thought he looked dashing.
I'll be going now.
You.
How did you know that I'm a grim reaper?
How can I not know when you do things like that?
You just teleported here.
You guys should really be more cautious.
You guys are so carefree.
You blew my cover.
You talked about me behind my back, Goblin.
How can you blame me with the way you behave?
You could've been a murderer in your previous life for all I know.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
It's not like you're being punished for not sinning at all.
Gosh.
You must've hurt him.
What do we do?
Can't you see that I have no clue?
Great sin, is it?
Disobedience.
Disloyalty.
Insolence.
Immorality.
Infidelity.
Let's not go there.
- It's probably not the case.
- No, it's not.
What is it? What are you going to do now?
Act of responsibility.
Willingness to become better.
People call it, "apology".
I apologize for the slip of my tongue.
What did I not do among these?
- Disobedience?
- Get out.
I did it again. I thought you'd laugh.
- Your previous life doesn't matter.
I don't care what you did or who you were in your previous life.
- Really?
- Yes.
No matter what you did, I'll hate you just the same.
I shouldn't laugh.
When they first met,
I thought Uncle would kick him out in an instance.
But they're strangely good together.
One is suffering from losing the memory of the previous life.
The other is suffering because he can't forget.
The two are depending on each other.
You and I...
are rest stops they dwell with...
in their long, long lives.
I see.
Wait, you knew about it as well?
My gosh.
I'm worried they might blow their covers out there.
You just worry about yourself.
Raise your arms straight.
Straighten your back.
I can't be your grandson.
You couldn't do this to your blood-related grandson.
- I'll have my revenge.
- Punk!
As you know, Mr. Kim,
this building was a present for my eighth birthday.
I know. What did you get when you turned nine?
A lot of hate. Not for long, though.
Now that I'm a grown adult...
You know they still hate you, right?
You spend so much money like a grown up.
So you canceled my credit cards.
That's why I plan on making some cash with this building.
Have the tenants move out. The less trouble the better.
Start with the out-of-business fried chicken restaurant.
There are a few things you must know.
First, do you see the sign that says "closed"?
The store isn't open yet. It's not out of business.
Second, I'm not here to do your bidding.
I'm tailing you because the chairman ordered me to.
You tailed me in the open?
I thought you were with me.
Let's do this, then. You will soon get a call.
A woman will ask if I work there.
You just have to say that I do. That's all you need to do.
You don't work there.
Come on, Mr. Kim. You're way too honest.
My grandpa must be pleased you work for him.
I need to make a new credit card.
Please? Just this once.
Going somewhere?
- To the store.
- The store?
Your excuses are getting lamer.
Don't you see the Eco bag?
I didn't know the purpose of it.
I can't believe you tagged along. Don't you trust me?
Could I?
You were going to see her but came here when I tagged along.
You went to the cafe to get her, but I got you first.
I won't take her.
I'm actually rooting for her.
Why would you root for her?
I'm on her side. You die when the bride takes the sword out.
It'd be better for you to disappear forever...
instead of taking a trip abroad.
She can't see the sword yet,
but I'm hoping for a miracle that she might notice it later.
I'm betting all I have on that day.
There are people watching.
Fine, then. Make a promise.
What promise?
That you won't harm her if I leave.
Are you serious?
- Are you really leaving?
- However,
if you try to take her, I'll come right back.
Leave her alone.
When will you leave?
In two days. Happy now?
Did someone see you?
You can't come to where I live.
My aunt will kill us both. Did she see you?
Is she asleep?
- I don't know.
- You scared me.
What were you doing outside my house?
Are you here to see me?
Maybe.
What?
I must have thought of you for a while.
I guess that's why I ended up here.
Why?
I'm not your bride and I'm not pretty.
I'm just a load of trouble. You always have to save me.
Why did you come to see me?
I guess I missed that about you.
I saw you, so I can go now. Your aunt disappeared.
The house is empty. Go on inside.
My aunt disappeared?
Really? When?
Why did you come here if you didn't know?
I came to get something I left behind.
What?
It's just a thing.
You don't need to know.
Okay.
Bye.
Hello, Mr. Man in Black.
Don't you need a hairpin?
Hairpins aren't my thing.
Get one for your girlfriend.
I don't have one.
Girlfriends come and go, you know.
Once you buy one, it's yours forever.
Have a look in the mirror.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
How much is this?
I picked it up first.
Are you crying?
Do you want it?
It's not for free.
Give me your number.
- I don't have one.
- You don't have a phone?
- Are you poor?
- I don't need a phone.
You just don't want to give me your number.
The ring is mine, then.
Give me your number. Write it down...
and leave it here with the ring.
Let's exchange names first.
You need to know my name if you want to call me.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sunny.
Sun Hee?
You can call me that if you want.
It's a fake name anyway, so anything goes.
Credit card?
Or cash?
Who's going to pay for the ring?
It doesn't matter who pays.
You'll both pay a heavy price for it anyway.
I...
must be too late.
I am...
fine.
If this is the end,
then it shall be my destiny.
You should go.
Do not stop.
Take your steps toward His Majesty.
Are you really going to be like this?
I hear you're not the goblin's bride.
Just come with me.
I hate you.
Are you ignoring me?
Fine. I'll just keep on talking. Let's see if you last.
I'm going to harass everyone around you.
I'll kill that woman first.
That piece of... That Jerk. That son of a gun.
I should just murder him.
She's so scary. Hey, why is she so scary?
Ms. Kim, are you all right?
Tell me the truth.
Is my face having a bad season?
I had it all figured out.
They never take this long to call me.
Why hasn't he called me yet?
The ring guy? That man?
- Calm down for...
- I can't calm down.
He's the most handsome man I have ever seen.
Can you see how hard I'm trying? I drink this every day for my skin.
Why hasn't he called me?
Handsome guys are always difficult.
- Just forget about him.
- How can I?
He was the only guy I've met that wasn't considerate.
That ring was so pretty.
It was supposed to be mine.
Do you have a pen?
No. You can just tell me.
That was funny.
Are you good at memorizing numbers?
One should always seal it with a kiss.
Be careful.
Hello.
What is all this? Is my family moving?
Didn't your aunt get in touch?
She put the place back on the market.
We have someone moving in.
They didn't clean up, so I'm going through this trouble.
Gosh.
The place is up for lease?
What do I do?
What should I do?
Why are you asking me? Ask your aunt.
She took her deposit.
If you need anything, take it.
"Lover".
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(STORAGE)
Ji Eun Tak.
Empty out your bag and your pockets.
Go on.
That's...
Be quiet.
You carry everything that can make a fire.
Where are your cigarettes? Aren't you going to take them out?
Are you protecting the last bit of your conscience?
No, I actually have a reason.
I don't smoke.
Other kids told me they saw you smoking.
Let's make it quick.
Okay?
Give me your hands.
Hurry up.
Both hands.
You're so thorough.
This is why smart kids are scary.
Eun Tak.
I'm scared when kids like you do well in school.
You act like you're kind and you make us feel sorry for you.
However, it's all an act.
It's people like you who taint our society.
That's how good people end up getting wronged.
Okay?
Thank you.
Why are you drinking all of a sudden?
What about you?
It's never too sudden to drink.
It's always better to have more alcohol, women, and meat.
I was noble enough when I was a general.
You were a general?
Back in the days, you wouldn't dare talk to me.
Come on, you don't even know who I was.
Who were you?
Well...
What? Were you a king?
Did you finish packing?
That's what you meant?
Well, I don't have much to pack.
Have a safe trip.
- I'll call you.
- I don't have a phone.
That's why I said it.
What are you doing? You're bothering me.
Was a can of beer really enough for you to be like this?
I don't know where she is.
- Where who is?
- She won't summon me.
She won't summon me, so I can't find her.
I'm not the all-mighty, but there wasn't anything I couldn't do.
I can't find that girl.
All of my possessions are of no value to me.
That's the truth.
Your powers are only good for enjoying yourself.
How did you find her before?
I just did. Like this.
Just call her.
She must have a phone, right?
Right.
But I don't have her number.
And I shouldn't anymore.
There you go.
Mom.
How are you?
Are you resting in peace?
How is it like up there?
Is it better than here?
Mom, I'm...
I'm...
I'm not well.
Nobody asks me how I am.
Again.
I'm sick of it.
My life is rainy.
It's because I'm feeling down.
What is?
The rain.
It'll stop soon.
Does it rain when you feel down?
Yes.
How down do you have to be to make a typhoon?
That's not me. It's the planet.
How have you been?
The rain is stopping.
I just started to feel better.
I didn't summon you this time.
No, you didn't.
I've been busy, too. Doing this and that.
I've been pretty occupied.
This isn't good.
Why?
Whenever it rains,
I'll think you're feeling down from now on.
It's not like I have anyone to rely on.
I'll have to worry about you on top of that.
Aren't you cold? What are you doing out here?
Because I'm not happy.
It feels more like a cold now.
- What does?
- My series of misfortunes.
It comes back when I think I have forgotten about it.
When the time comes, I catch it again.
I'm not saying this to make you feel bad.
You didn't mean anything specific by that, did you?
Did I catch you off guard?
Don't say that.
That's the phrase I hate the most.
I picked the words correctly, then.
Continue your story.
It'll make you weep tears of sorrow.
I'll try to hold it in.
Have you heard the story?
Humans have four lives.
A life of planting seeds,
a life of watering the seeds,
a life of harvesting,
and a life of cherishing the harvests.
How do you know that?
That's what grim reapers say to the deceased.
I've been the goblin's bride for 19 years.
I've heard stories told by the ghosts.
I think it's unfair.
Why don't I get to...
the harvesting part in my life?
There's no progress.
My condolences.
- That's so formal.
- How should I do it, then?
There are so many choices.
You could pat my shoulder, brush my hair,
or give me 5,000 dollars.
Gosh. What about your hand?
My hands...
need to rest from working part-time too much.
I'm saving them for later...
in case someone hands me a handful of something.
Like what?
Forget it.
My present for you.
It's pretty, isn't it?
- It's pretty.
- I know, right?
What was that?
I brushed your hair.
It was a farewell.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Did you pack your things?
You asked me that already.
I want to keep reminding myself.
It makes me feel happy.
You got a text.
No. It was the bell.
That's the first time it rang in 60 years.
I see.
What?
What did I just say?
The bell.
Nobody rings the bell.
Cut it out. You're scaring me.
- See through the wall.
- I can't do that.
What kind of grim reaper can't even see through walls?
You're one to talk.
Is this Mr. Goblin's house?
It's my house.
Did you come looking for me at my doorsteps?
Did you make an appointment with me?
I think I came to the wrong house.
Did you even tell her where you live?
Why are you here? How did you find this place?
I asked the ghosts where the goblin lives.
What's he doing here?
Your love spat's still ongoing. I hope you reach a happy conclusion.
I feel very uncomfortable.
- Do you live together?
- Just until today.
Why are you here?
To tell you something I didn't get to earlier.
You keep asking if I see something.
What if I see it?
- Why ask? You don't see it.
- Who says I don't?
One, if I see it, do we have to get married right away?
Two, if I see it, will you lend me 5,000 dollars?
Three, if I see it,
will you stay?
Don't go.
Stay here in Korea.
Can't you?
Do you...
really see it?
- What if I do?
- Prove it.
I want an answer first.
Pick 1 of the 3 options.
You don't see it.
I really see it. I really do.
That sword.
(GOBLIN)
She sees the sword. She's my bride. I'm going to die.
Is she really my uncle's bride?
Why is she his bride?
It's a trick of fate.
It's a perfect house to raise a kid in.
Let's have a few kids and live happily.
Is this why they say marriage is a disaster?
Mister, is this our honeymoon?
Hello, how have you been?
I made up my mind.
I must disappear...
before I want to live for longer.
Before I feel happier.
This is something I must do for you.
I must end this life.
You're the goblin's bride.