Here I go.
(Episode 7)
Why can't I grab it?
I can see it, but I can't pull it out.
Did you put enough pressure?
Here, let me try again.
You said earlier that it's not my fault...
no matter what happens,
- so don't take it back. - Hey.
- How can the goblin's bride... - I said, don't take it back.
Just stand still. I'm more surprised than you.
I'm standing still. How can I get more still than this?
Give me that agreement. I'm going to burn it.
Wait.
I know what it is. This must be it. I get it now.
- What is it? - The cursed prince.
You know, the ones in fairy tales?
What about them?
A kiss.
I was just in a rush. Please understand.
Open your eyes.
They are open.
What did you...
Are you insane?
Insane?
I tried my best to make you pretty.
Do you think I wanted to do it? It was a sacrifice on my part.
You must have done it lots of times, but for me...
Forget it.
- For you, what? - It was my first kiss!
I shouldn't have wasted it like that.
- Get back here. Let me try again. - No, no.
Talk from there.
I can't see straight right now.
If I can't even touch it, you'll tell me to give everything back.
There's nothing I wouldn't do in this desperate situation.
What is with this attitude?
What if it doesn't work again?
If it doesn't work again, there's only one answer.
- What? - True love.
I'll have to do that too, if necessary!
I'd rather love you than lose this bag!
I'm sorry.
You put in all that effort and made it snow, too.
- Cool. - "Cool"?
What should I do now?
About what?
- Will you kick me out? - I won't kick you out!
Really?
Don't forget what you signed.
They say, a man's word is worth his weight in gold.
Don't be cheap and take it back.
My uncle isn't coming back?
Wait.
Are you saying my uncle left this world?
(Registration Certificate)
He led an immortal life and is finally perishing.
Do not miss him for too long.
Death is but a different world on the other side of the door.
You will also open that door...
No, Uncle. My poor uncle.
My poor uncle.
I don't need my credit card.
I don't need this stupid credit card.
Please, come back. Please.
What's this?
Why is he coming through that door?
Uncle! Uncle. Uncle.
Deok Hwa.
Uncle.
Are you back? Did you come back?
I love you, Uncle.
Okay, okay.
So I was thinking,
can I get my credit card back?
What?
You heard me. Why are you pretending you didn't?
Uncle.
It's merely a new world on the other side of the door.
You've already started the journey. You should just keep going.
Deok Hwa is very worried about his uncle.
He's right. Don't worry about us.
May I get the deed back?
What did you do?
Eun Tak.
- Yes? - Please return the 5,000 dollars,
perfume, and bag first.
Uncle. You gave her that much?
No. I will not. You said you wouldn't kick me out.
I asked for the 5,000 dollars, perfume, and bag.
I didn't say I'm kicking you out.
Mister.
I love you.
No?
I love you, too.
- Mister. - Shut it!
- I love you. - How dare you?
Did you burn the scroll by any chance?
- I did. - You are such the jokester.
Are you anxious?
That's your punishment for being so thorough with your goodbyes.
I shall accept it gladly.
I shall send the scroll...
through Deok Hwa in the morning,
so do not worry.
Thank you, and I'm sorry.
Then Sir,
if I dare make a suggestion,
could you give up trying to die...
and consider living instead?
Because of you, some people in the past...
were able to turn a new leaf.
Wouldn't it be nice if they were to benefit from...
a strange but beautiful...
stroke of luck or a miracle?
A man who never ages...
At the age of 29,
you're still shining.
But I'm not...
by your side.
Why can't I grab it?
I can see it but I can't pull it out.
Has the future changed...
or has the oracle?
Whatever the case,
it is good to be back.
I'm so shameless.
Missing soul.
Tell me in detail what happened.
It started off really well.
We were in a moonlit buckwheat field...
with the first snow falling.
Anyway, I tried to hold the sword.
However,
I couldn't touch it although I could see it.
He came back alive.
I thought one of you wouldn't.
I know. I thought he'd leave me in the field.
He brought me back.
The missing soul does not know yet...
about what will happen when she pulls out his sword.
Should I tell her what will happen?
The goblin might die of fury.
Then this house will be mine.
What are you thinking?
When you look at me like that,
it gives me the chills.
Why can't you touch the sword...
although you can see it?
I was trying to figure it out.
You, too? So was I.
Why is that?
Is the goblin right?
Am I really not his bride?
Is there another bride who can touch the sword...
and will she be pretty?
Anyone could do the deed.
Exactly.
Do you think he'd go back to being mean to me?
We're pretty close now.
One extra mouth to feed is really taxing our expenses.
We're out of meat already.
Should I start keeping track of receipts?
I'm in too rotten a mood to do the dishes.
I'll do the dishes.
I really want to do the dishes.
Do you?
I guess you are at the age where you'd love to do the dishes.
There's so much washing to do.
I can't afford to send everything to the dry cleaner's.
Should I throw out all my dirty clothes?
You have me. As soon as I'm done with the dishes,
I could do the laundry.
Will you do that? If you insist,
I prefer them to be hand-washed.
I bet students find it easier to concentrate in a clean home.
When will I clean all these rooms?
I feel bad for the student in the house.
Was that deliberate?
No.
I'm wet. You must see that.
I wonder if they'll dry by this evening.
You are doing that deliberately.
Do you hate doing the washing? Tell me what's bothering you.
I'm glad you brought that up.
You must think I'm not your bride.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
You might seriously regret giving me a hard time.
Do you mean you are my bride but you can only see my sword?
You said every moment you spent with me shined.
Because the weather was good, bad,
- or good enough. - Yes.
- Today as well. - See?
- What? - Even now.
You shine brilliantly.
So why are you...
- giving me a hard time? - That's different.
How are they different issues? You said everything shines.
Can't we stop doing this?
Let's find another value.
If I can't be your bride, since you're my boyfriend,
I'll be your girlfriend.
No, thanks.
- How about acquaintances? - No.
Then a lodger?
Then pay 500 dollars a month in rent.
Water and gas bills are separate.
Did he demand you give him money?
Yes. We're at loggerheads now.
We're bound to clash sooner or later.
Why can't I touch the stupid sword?
Maybe you need something more powerful than the curse.
Something like true love, for example.
I tried that already.
What did you do?
A kiss.
My goodness.
You shouldn't talk about that.
Do you usually go around telling people whom you kissed?
I didn't say anything. You did.
- Weren't you going to? - I wasn't.
They...
- kissed? - It's about me.
Why do you care?
We're talking about my kiss.
Hey. No one person can claim a kiss.
Half of it is mine.
Fine, take half.
No, I don't want it.
Then I'll keep it all.
You do that, greedy bugger.
Someone...
can't make a call because he doesn't have a business card.
These two are just...
What?
I guess I should be glad you're back,
but shouldn't we send the girl packing?
- What? - Don't you want to?
Can't we send her away and be happy together like we used to be?
Whom were you living with?
She's not the goblin's bride. I'm going to kick her out.
She knows who we are.
We can't cut her loose and let her talk.
She won't talk if you give her 5,000 dollars.
Don't you watch TV dramas?
Once you start paying people off, there's no end to it.
Maybe you want her to stay.
I want her gone.
I want to send her away more than anything.
- What? - She couldn't touch the sword.
You're actually pleased about it, aren't you?
Because you can live.
Why would that be pleasing? Are you crazy?
I've been waiting for this moment for over 900 years.
Okay, then. I'll take her out of my friendship for you.
She must bother you. She kissed you without permission.
There is no friendship between us!
What kind of a friend would want another friend to die?
See? You're glad you aren't dead.
I am not. I just have a promise that I must keep.
I signed a contract.
A man's word is worth his weight in gold.
I made a promise and I will keep it because I'm a man.
Were you not a man when you gave me the deeds to the house?
When a goblin becomes angry...
Hey, come back. Reaper. Reaper?
Reaper.
On the day of the first snowfall every year,
the goblin agrees to be summoned by me.
I will be waiting for you.
Why are you here and not in your own room?
Are you protesting?
I want to stay close to where the snacks are.
The snacks stopped coming after you stopped trying to impress me.
You're so cheap.
Our family fortune is going downhill.
It's a luxury we can't afford right now.
Can you not get on my nerves?
I'm in a very sensitive state right now...
since I'm preparing for the exam.
Are you being cranky right now?
What kind of a guardian are you? I have exams coming up.
What? What is it?
Do you by any chance...
know the answers to the college entrance exam?
I do. When is the exam?
You don't know when it is, but you know the answers?
Yes. Do you want me to tell you?
- Yes. - First, do the practice questions.
Okay.
For your information, it's next Thursday.
By the way,
on that day of the first snowfall...
Oh, right.
I wanted to bring it up first.
Don't feel pressured.
That was my first kiss, of course.
I was going to talk about the snow. The snowfall.
Oh, the first snowfall.
Don't say it.
Don't talk about anything related to being the first one.
- You got the first question wrong. - I said don't.
- Aren't you hungry? - I said stop it.
It's so noisy from all the traffic. It's not good for you.
Do you like your bed?
It'll fill you up. It's mostly meat.
Do you think what I want is a lunch box?
Do you think you can memorize them all?
These are the answers in order. Listen carefully.
- First, the language section. - I hate you.
Go home.
I'm tempted to memorize them.
The bus is coming.
You need to respect the absolute power.
- But if you really want to know... - I'll pass.
I'm going to know all the answers anyway.
Will it be less awkward if I pat you on the shoulders?
I'll casually look at the time.
Did you...
stop the time just now?
No.
Oh, no. I'm done for.
Almost 30 minutes went by.
Don't worry. Did you forget that your boyfriend is a goblin?
You said you don't want to be my boyfriend.
I was lying. Follow me.
Good luck on your exam.
Gosh, are you crazy? Do you want to die?
Where did he go?
Watch where you're going.
(Language Section)
(2017 College Entrance Exam)
Over here.
I bombed it.
Mom!
How did it go?
I'm home.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired from using my brain so much.
How did the exam go?
It was my idea. He paid for it. Deok Hwa bought it.
It's a cake.
Why are you crying? Did you not do well on the exam?
It's not that.
I'm just happy.
What?
She's happy.
I should make a wish since I'm so happy.
I have a free pass on anywhere I go today.
Let me watch a movie with Mr. Goblin later.
I want popcorn, too.
What about me?
Thanks for the cake.
I can get a maximum of 50 percent discount.
It's something that we do. You don't want to know.
- Why are you still doing there? - What?
You want to watch a movie, right? With some popcorn.
Let's go. Your wish has been granted.
Really? Give me 10 seconds. I'll go leave the bag in my room.
You should go, too. Go to your rooms.
Why? I want to watch a movie and have some popcorn.
No.
Why did he call me over, then?
The college entrance exam is just an excuse, isn't it?
If he made the exam just for this, we have to give it to him.
You.
I need to talk to you.
What?
But why?
I'm curious about something.
Not as much as me, I don't think.
You.
Where did you get your business card?
What?
Business cards. They're rectangular and mostly white in color.
They're sharp around the edges.
I get mine from the company since I'm the corporate heir.
Why are you asking me that?
- I want one. - What?
And there's another thing I want to ask you about.
From this up close?
If he really is Yu Deok Hwa of Chunwoo Group,
he is my lord. My landlord.
She said you're some kind of a lord. A landlord.
Yes, I do have a small building under my name.
Why do you ask?
How can people... I...
Where are you going? Did you close?
I was on my way to your store.
Yes, we're closed. My boyfriend is waiting for me.
Come next time.
Open it.
How about just one more drink?
Gosh. Hold on.
Did you just fly?
Just like that?
What are you? A bird?
What's wrong with me?
Why am I in here?
That's what I'm saying.
This is crazy. Why do I keep seeing things these days?
Take care.
A peace like the river
Do you know how to do this?
There isn't a thing I can't do.
Which one do you want? The rabbit or the raccoon?
Lighter. I want the lighter.
- What? I couldn't hear you. - I didn't say anything.
I was so close, right?
Let's stop. You can make gold appear,
but you can't get a lighter out.
- Get out of my way. - I didn't get in your way.
Also, it's time for our movie.
Step back. Here I go. I'm going.
Don't scream and embarrass me. Just tell me when you get scared.
I've lived 19 years in horror.
This should be a piece of cake.
It's starting.
- What is he doing? - What's going on?
No! I want to go! I want to leave!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Look.
It's the first snowfall in a theater.
I'm sorry.
I didn't get to watch a single scene thanks to you.
I don't even know what the movie was about.
Aren't zombies so scary?
The future of Korean film industry seems bright.
Just order.
You must be hungry from screaming and crying.
I'm not hungry from eating the popcorn. Don't mind me.
I won't, then.
I'd like a large sub of that one.
Okay.
For question number seven on the mathematical section,
I applied the equation and used...
lettuce as X...
I mean, I was almost caught in the trap there.
- Is it delicious? - Yes.
Their large is really huge.
It's not healthy for you to eat so much.
You had a large juice before, too.
You ate countless cows before that. Are you unhealthy?
It's delicious. You should've gotten some.
It's expensive. How can we buy two?
How long are you going to nag at me?
You gave me gifts and then took them back. I liked that bag.
I've never seen 5,000 dollars in real life.
You should've never given it to me to begin with.
I'll make sure I don't next time.
You were so strange when you gave them to me...
as if you were going to leave.
You told me to use them when I got older.
You gave Deok Hwa a credit card, then the house to Grim Reaper.
It's what everyone wanted.
They were like goodbye gifts.
Am I right? Were they goodbye gifts?
Were you going to leave...
after I pulled out the sword?
I'm right.
Why?
I thought I told you already.
I have to prepare to leave once my bride shows up.
To where?
Europe? Canada?
Even now?
Do you still want to leave?
No. I don't want to leave.
However, if the bride really shows up,
the choice won't be up to me.
I see.
Are you going to leave with the real bride?
- Will you let me go? - No.
I won't let you go, so you should just leave me.
When the real bride shows up... No.
I'll leave before she shows up.
You can go when I'm not around...
so that I don't find out.
- Did Uncle buy you food yesterday? - No.
Why not? Are you still Cinderella at home?
Yes. The goblin is my stepmother.
I have too many step-moms in my life.
That's strange.
My uncle gets soft just looking at girl groups.
- And? - Ever since he met you,
all he does is get angry.
You must not be his type.
Girl groups?
Everyone told me I'd get pretty once I get into college.
You'll see when I get admitted.
(2017 Communications Major Essay Entrance Exam)
Wow, college boys?
Are you all right?
Is that you, Tae Hee?
Ji Eun Tak?
It's been so long. I hardly recognized you.
Right? I changed a lot, didn't I?
I went through a lot so...
You got prettier.
You're taller, too.
Do you go to this school?
I took the entrance test today.
Over here, Sir.
Is that the guy?
You have to get up and eat.
He was touching her hair.
I almost broke his wrist.
- Who? - She was twisting her body.
I thought she was Twizzlers.
Who are you talking about?
I should've let him play the piano.
Then they wouldn't have met.
Who met who?
I'm home.
No!
My spring.
Who is that idiot?
I'm so annoyed.
I hit it.
Tae Hee really became a baseball player.
He's amazing.
Are you eating ice cream?
I'm not sharing. I paid for it.
I didn't say anything.
It was raining, so I'm craving ice cream.
I said, I didn't say anything.
I know. Why are you holding that without saying anything?
Put that marbly thing down before I get really upset.
This Bluetooth speaker...
Get your hands off it.
Do you even know how to use that?
You can take a picture with that, too.
I'm going to take a picture of myself eating this ice cream.
So don't touch it.
What? Why?
You're so cheap.
Why did it rain?
Why did you feel sad?
Don't you already know why?
Is it because I can't draw the sword?
Is that my fault?
I did my best.
Are you sure that sword was meant to be drawn?
We kissed, but it didn't work.
We loved each other, but it still didn't work. What more can we do?
You didn't mean it.
You said "I love you" in such a secular way.
Did you mean it, then?
You said "I love you" with a crystal clear intention.
- You're such a peculiar man. - Do you think you're any better?
I am young.
What about being young?
I don't age, but you will age.
I will always be young and beautiful.
You are not so young, Mister.
I met my first love again,
so you don't look beautiful to me at all.
- What love? - Do you play baseball well?
Tae Hee plays baseball really well.
Did you see me play baseball? You will be shocked when you do.
Is this how you're going to treat me now?
I will go to my room, then.
I hope you take the best photo of your life with this.
Don't ask me to take a picture of you.
She fooled me.
Who's Tae Hee? Show yourself.
Tae Hee, someone's looking for you.
I am Choi Tae Hee. Who are you?
How can you...
look like this?
- Pardon me? - You're the handsomest here.
Well, you're right.
But...
- we've met before, haven't we? - We met just now.
No. Look at me.
Have we really never met before?
Didn't we meet when I was this small?
How can you be so bad?
Why don't you move your waist a little?
Don't mind me. Mind your own business.
It's just that I'm better than you.
You shouldn't hold the bat like that.
Hey, little boy.
I've been living as an upright general...
Never mind. You will be shocked when you find out who I am.
- So mind your own business. - Then...
do you want to make a bet with me?
I can't believe this. Do you know who you are dealing with?
- Don't regret it. - You shouldn't regret it.
Let's hit 10 balls, and the loser will grant 1 wish to the winner.
All right.
A thief!
A thief broke in and took the piano.
It really disappeared.
How can nobody spot him taking that big thing?
It's as if he's a ghost.
I won the bet,
and I asked you to get rid of the piano.
I was really bad, but my mom couldn't give up.
I said I wanted to become a baseball player.
The piano really disappeared.
So?
Aren't you...
- the guy I met? - No, I'm not.
I don't think you're him,
but if you are that person,
you didn't age at all.
What?
Like that, that kid recognized me.
So what?
Is that all you can say?
Do you think I'm doing this indecent thing to hear that?
If you don't erase his memory, he'll spread a rumor about me.
Then I'd have to leave here.
You wanted to live happily with me.
I thought you never said it.
You shouldn't live like that. You have to help others.
Why would I help the goblin who can't even erase memories?
All right. We'll see.
Let's see.
- Hey! - You were going to cook it anyway.
All right. It's perfect.
What brings you here?
I was...
- I was just cleaning. - The vacuum's outside.
Give me what you're sitting on.
One more.
I think I signed only once.
Really? Then why are there two copies here? Goodness.
You've committed forgery of documents, trespass,
- and theft. - Gosh, you're so cheap.
Girl groups make you forget about the thousand years of rage.
I apologize for not knowing that you're one of those people.
This is mine, so give it back to me.
I came here to get this back. You have no idea.
I told you to read it. I never said you could keep it.
Goodness. Look at that girl.
I knew it.
I can't tell which is the original and which is a copy.
I can't compliment her for being talented at this.
What will she become when she grows up?
Was he careless with it because it wasn't his?
I'm so annoyed. I'd better not find anything.
Look at this.
He wrote in it because it wasn't his.
Seriously. "First love"?
Sure.
I'm sure he had one.
That broom did everything there is to do.
It was my first kiss.
He has an ugly handwriting.
(Tae Hee)
Hi, Tae Hee.
It's okay.
What about it?
The phone's ringing.
(Sunny not Sun Hee)
So what about it?
Answer it for me.
If I avoid her again, she may really kill me.
But I don't have a business card yet, so I can't pick up.
I have nothing to say.
Just this once.
Why don't you have anything to say?
"Don't you know my voice? My voice isn't easy to forget."
Do that.
You said let's not help each other. You said you don't need me.
You, Grim Reaper, with zero foresight.
Forget it.
Where did that missing soul go?
She can't help you, either.
She's too busy giggling in front of the ice cream place.
Don't bother.
Giggling?
Why is she outside...
Shut it! I don't want to explain.
I was thinking about it and it was just so cool.
How could I run into you like that there?
Me, too.
How have you been?
I don't know.
Thinking about you now and then?
You're so funny.
Missing soul.
Take this call.
Are you insane?
How could you follow me here?
Who is he?
Is he your father?
You are...
careless with your words.
And what is your name, careless one?
No! Don't tell him your name. Don't look him in the eye. Look down.
I cannot take this call...
so take the call for me.
Otherwise, I shall ask his name...
and write it down carefully.
Take care of it.
Fine.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Careless one, sit down.
So you used to play the piano and now, you play baseball?
How did you know that?
She'll get the wrong idea if a woman picks up.
Whatever.
Hello?
Isn't this Kim Woo Bin's phone?
It is.
Manager Kim Woo Bin stepped away for a moment.
He's a manager?
He's a director.
What kind of a company promotes employees in a second?
Whatever. I know he's there. Tell him tomorrow, 1pm at the same cafe.
He may come as a manager or a director.
If he's late, I will kill him. Please tell him so.
(Sunny not Sun Hee)
Goodness.
How did it go? What did she say?
Talk in person. Tomorrow at 1pm. The same cafe.
But her voice sounded very familiar.
- Is she... - Stop.
My question first.
What's your question?
Phone number, name, then age.
Blood type. Single? Married? Wealth.
Past relationships. Ideal woman. And so on.
You don't know what she'll ask. Prepare answers for them all.
Aquarius... No, no.
Sagittarius. Sagittarius.
I'm 34 years old. My birthday is November 5th.
Sagittarius. Blood type AB. Single.
I live in a rental. I can get a car if needed.
My past is clean. I don't have a business card yet.
I've missed you.
Goodness. Me, too.
You're so strange.
Do you like me? Although you kept avoiding my calls?
I thought...
you wouldn't like someone who didn't have a business card.
You could've answered my call and said you didn't have one.
You could've texted, too.
From now on, I will.
Do you have a business card?
Why do you ask?
I wonder what you do.
My face is my business card.
It says right here, doesn't it? "Pretty person".
Yes.
You're right.
I wish...
I could take one.
See? It's so much fun when we meet in person.
You get to learn more about me and we can get closer.
What do you like?
You.
You're driving me crazy.
Not that. Like hobbies and things like that.
You.
I understand.
Your unpredictable acts...
draw me in more than a drama does.
Your unpredictability...
incites my imagination.
I am clueless...
and keep giving the wrong answer.
My new hobby I found in you seems like...
the deity's plan...
or perhaps,
the deity's mistake.
You speak so well.
Do you have a religion?
Do I need to have something else again?
I'll call you when I have it.
No! You don't need one.
Sit back down before I kill you.
What is with this man?
I'm 34 years old. My birthday is November 5th.
No, no! You don't need to tell me.
Just sit there.
I'll pretend I'm looking at a magazine.
What do you like?
Vegetables. Okay, then.
What?
I have to go that way.
What about me?
Weren't we going to eat?
You won't even feed me?
You ate an entire hotdog.
Overeating is the source of all illnesses.
You're the one who gets me ill more than anything else.
Forget it. Where are you going?
I have a company outing.
I have to pay a fine if I skip it.
What's wrong with you?
You're so clueless, and everything you do is wrong.
It's all wrong.
The questions are too difficult.
Let's drink to the death!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Don't drink too much.
Watch where you're going, will you?
Use your eyes.
Does he have a death wish?
Do you think he knows what he just did?
He'll do something to anger the spirits in less than a month.
What should we do?
That's his fate. Let's go, I need to use the restroom.
Me, too.
- Cheers! - Cheers, cheers.
The treasurer's here. It's time to wind down.
- Pay the bill. - Okay.
That's a lot.
Is something wrong?
- Is something missing? - The money.
Watch where you're going, will you?
He was a pickpocket. The man I bumped into.
No wonder. What should we do now?
He stole from the wrong guy.
This won't do. Put your hats on one at a time.
Move slowly and take turns so that no one notices.
Are we allowed to do this?
We have to write up a formal apology...
if we use our powers for anything other than work.
Don't worry. I'll make sure you don't have to.
Year of 23, you guys can leave first.
I know of a way.
What is it? Can you get us off the hook?
You'll see.
Why you...
I need your help.
Will you be his guarantor?
That's the only way I can release him.
There's a misunderstanding.
I'm here because he called me, but I don't know him.
He never was of any help to me.
I'm not entirely sure how I can help him.
Didn't you receive his call?
Let's agree to say you know me. I'll help you out.
I'll erase Tae Hee's memories.
I just remembered who he is.
Eating without paying?
That's such a crass crime that I've never heard of.
Where do I sign?
This is who I am.
You have...
a business card?
What's going on? Why do you have a business card?
Uncle.
- Have some tofu. - Did you know?
He has a business card.
A business card? Of course he does.
He owns the whole company.
Hotel, trading, ship-building, oil, construction, and furniture.
- Didn't you know? - Stop it. I didn't tell him.
That's how rich I am.
Here, have some tofu.
I've always wanted to do this.
Like uncle, like nephew. Get out of my way.
Why does he always walk like that?
I got it. I finally figured it out.
He sees something when he touches someone.
The person's previous life.
He can see someone's past life?
What about you? What kind of power do you have?
My power is staying alive.
You can't do anything but make it rain, can you?
You forgot your tofu.
I guess the missing soul isn't back yet.
Is she out with him?
- Hello? - Where are you?
Why aren't you back yet? It's scary out there at night.
It's only 7pm, and I'm busy right now.
Hello?
The phone has been turned off.
Please leave a message...
Unbelievable.
Which of you saw the goblin's bride?
Where?
Uncle!
Uncle.
He's not in. He went out.
Did he?
Then can you pass this to him?
I forgot that it was in my car.
Why give him this when he took your credit card?
My grandpa said he'd give me an allowance if I deliver this.
- You humans... - That's how scary...
and convenient capitalism is.
He gave you a credit card and me the deed to the house.
He must've given your grandfather something more valuable.
Do you think so?
I don't know what this is. Shall we have a look?
He isn't here.
She's really pretty.
Who is she? Is she his ex-girlfriend?
This looks really old.
Doesn't it?
What's wrong?
It was the beginning of a terribly sad love story.
This thing called destiny is so sad.
It's not a sin to fall in love.
Maybe they didn't deserve what they got.
What did I do to deserve a sudden raise in rent?
I can't afford to pay an extra 100 dollars a month.
Ever since you moved in,
I keep dreaming of grim reapers.
I see.
The tap in my bathroom is leaking. When will you fix it?
Is it leaking? Then don't shower.
You'll still be pretty.
You can sing.
I know.
How did you know I'd be here?
You can run but you can't hide.
What about the chicken place? Did you get fired?
I'm working multiple jobs now.
Singing at weddings pays well.
But...
watching wedding ceremonies...
makes me feel strange.
Why do you feel strange?
Just...
"I won't have a mom to light the candles..."
"or a dad to hold my hand."
"I won't have friends to take pictures of me."
"Without any friends, there won't be any congratulatory money."
Such thoughts come to my mind.
It's funny, right?
That's probably why...
I was obsessed with being your bride.
It felt like we were becoming family.
I thought I could have what I never had.
I thought it came to me like fate.
Why... Why are you crying?
Are you trying to make me feel sorry?
No.
In the end,
I should be the one who's sorry.
You know what?
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't draw the sword.
I've been meaning to tell you,
but every time we met, we got into an argument.
I know this isn't the perfect timing,
but I should say it now that we're talking about it.
I'm working more jobs...
and steadily preparing myself.
So can you wait a little longer until I leave the house?
Stop being mean to me.
Until I'm ready to leave,
can you give me a 50 percent discount...
when you're being mean to me? Please?
I don't think I can do that.
Not the 50 percent discount.
45 percent?
What is it? Are you hurt?
Is it the sword?
Mister.
I can grab the sword.
Hold on.
Hold on. I'll pull it out for you.
It's moving.
The oracle was real.
The future I foresaw was correct.
With this girl's help,
I'll be able to end this curse of eternity...
and return to ashes.
A mortal soul can only live up to 100 years.
Is what I'm looking for...
my life as an immortal soul...
or your face?
I think it's your face.
(Goblin)
I told you. I really am your bride.
This was destined to happen.
It was destiny.
It's nice.
Who on earth are you?
Why are you making me feel smoldered?
I think I saw her from somewhere.
How did you remember your past life?
One day after 100 years...
When the weather is good enough...
When the weather is good enough,
I wish I could tell her that she was my first love.
I ask for permission to be granted.