BioskopKeren
What is it? Are you hurt?
Is it the sword?
Mister.
I can grab the sword.
Wait.
Hold on. I'll pull it out for you.
It's moving.
The oracle was real.
The future I foresaw was correct.
With this girl's help,
I'll be able to end this curse of eternity...
and return to ashes.
A mortal soul can only live up to 100 years.
Is what I'm looking for...
my life as an immortal soul...
or your face?
I think it's your face.
(Episode 8)
Are you all right?
I should be the one asking that.
Is that right?
Goodness.
I'm sorry. You must've been really startled.
You didn't know it would hurt this much.
Nobody had ever grabbed it before.
By the way,
you can really fly.
I wasn't asking to show it to me like this.
It's...
a piece of cake.
We have to toughen up.
This isn't a simple task.
By the way, I was more surprised that I could move the sword.
Aren't you really glad?
It's now proven that I am really the goblin's bride.
I'm glad.
Aren't you...
glad?
I'm glad.
See? I'm really the bride.
This was my destiny.
Destiny.
It's nice.
Why isn't he coming home?
I'm getting paid only if I complete the job.
Let's see what happened today.
It happened.
Were you on the second floor the whole time?
Hurry up and look at this.
Is this you, by any chance?
Why aren't you doing anything? Go deal with it.
Is it really you?
I don't have the energy to explain. Don't ask.
We don't have time. Hurry.
What on earth did you do?
Grandpa, listen carefully.
Uncle... No, not me. It's Uncle.
Mr. Kim, listen carefully.
Use the entire computer room of Chunwoo Group...
No, not me.
It's not about me.
We have to go somewhere.
Where?
My uncle lacks social skills, so he shattered the society.
Starting now, go to all the portal sites and...
social media that have the ability to upload this video and...
ask them to delete the video.
You have to stop it from spreading before it becomes a bigger issue.
You may use the big data, and when you contact them,
the work will be easier if you say you'd stop advertising...
Chunwoo Group and its subsidiaries.
All right.
Let's begin.
- Okay, Sir. - Okay, Sir.
All right, everybody.
First, if your car or property got damaged, please stand here.
If you saw something disturbing and got disturbed,
please line up over there.
The car was damaged by unexpectedly strong wind.
The money fell from the sky. That's it.
You did not see me today.
Next.
It's me. By the way, isn't it too dark here?
I don't feel too good.
Would you please look at my eyes?
The car was damaged by unexpectedly strong wind.
The money fell from the sky. That's it.
You did not see me today.
Next. Next.
Come on. Hurry up.
Look at my eyes. Look.
Next.
What's the model of your car?
We'll be done once we delete these files.
Will you look at my eyes?
How badly do a couple have to fight to break 30 cars?
Do you know how hard we had to work?
Good job.
- Thank you. - Don't thank us.
I just don't have the energy to fight.
Let's delay the fight. I feel depressed enough.
You still won't be as depressed as me.
How do you know if you're worse than me?
Hey.
This thing was stuck about...
Never mind.
Forget it.
Did you almost die or what?
What's wrong with you?
Mr. Buckwheat. We don't have to leave anymore.
I am surely the goblin's bride.
Gosh, my body aches.
What's wrong with him?
Is he... Is he dead?
It's the medication.
Let him sleep.
He'll wake up with an ache if he sleeps on the floor.
You should carry him to...
Yes, do that.
If you can, that is.
What's wrong?
Why did you take the pills?
Are you still in pain?
Who are you?
Why does my heart ache so?
Our pickled radishes taste good.
37.
38.
I will go home once number 50 goes by.
I'll be nice.
He doesn't have a fever.
You're an adult.
You shouldn't fall asleep in random places.
I'm sick, that's why.
Are you awake?
I smelled your muscle patch.
My body aches.
Does yours hurt, too?
You said you were okay before.
I lied.
You always lie.
Get well soon.
You don't know where it hurts.
Where does it hurt?
My first love hurt me really badly.
She must've been really pretty.
You even wrote something about her.
She's very pretty.
Every day.
She's pretty.
You're very sick.
You're in a critical condition.
Sleep well so that your body aches really badly.
Don't go.
Why not? I don't care about someone who isn't over his first love.
What a thing to say to your bride.
She's pretty if you look hard enough.
So stay here.
I told you not to use words that start with a certain letter.
You're so mean.
Stop it.
I want all the vegetables and toast the bread.
Okay.
Here's the bribe you ordered.
Where's the item?
Can you really interpret this?
Any rich heir should memorize the 1,000 basic characters at age 3.
What's this?
Something about your uncle and his first love.
It's our secret.
Listen, little girl. I love looking into someone's background.
Let me see.
This character means "to hear", just in case you didn't know.
Don't say you can't read it after you ate that sandwich.
It's a love letter.
- A love letter? - Yes.
It's a sad confession of love.
"After 100 years..."
"On a good-enough day..."
My worst fear came true.
That'll do. I know who it's about.
- Who? - I heard all about her.
It's totally understandable. In his 900-year life,
he could have met someone unforgettable.
- Just one? - Is it not?
- I don't know. - You scared me.
Anyway, about Mr. Kim Shin.
Who's that?
Your uncle.
Is he Kim Shin? He's Yu Shin Jae.
Well... It's a long story.
Anyway, about the sword that's stuck in his chest...
There's a sword in his chest?
- What do you know? - What sword is it?
If you don't tell me everything, I'll end up with a complex.
Tell me what you know or I won't tell you what only I know.
What is it that only you know?
He saw her portrait and cried?
- The Grim Reaper did? - Yes, he sobbed.
I tried to talk him out of it but he insisted we take a look.
Did he really cry?
- Why? - I don't know.
Let's be angry at him and ask why.
Why did you look at my painting? He said he tried to stop you.
I heard you cried. Why? Even I don't cry.
I was so confused that I thought about it long and hard.
I think it was something like Stendhal syndrome.
I felt so moved and almost stopped breathing.
Who is the woman in the painting by the way?
- Why do you care? - I think...
she looks familiar.
Who do you think she is?
This woman is my sister.
You have a big sister?
Have you seen my little sister?
Think about it. Where was it?
Little sister...
I think she may be one of my deceased souls,
but I'm not positive.
She was reincarnated? When?
I said I wasn't sure.
I can't remember everyone I took away.
She seems familiar, so I'm guessing.
I don't remember. I just feel.
I was just extremely sad.
My heart felt like it was breaking.
Uncles, I know.
I think I know.
Maybe the Grim Reaper is your sister's reincarnation.
Try calling him your brother.
- Do you want to die? - Do you want to die?
Bro...
Broth...
Have you heard the news?
About Messenger Kim from Janghang-dong.
What about him?
He went to pick up a soul,
and it was his wife in a previous life.
So he put her name on the missing soul's list and ran off with her.
- So? - That is all.
I don't know the rest.
I'm sure they were caught.
How did he remember his past life?
Who knows?
That's why everyone's nervous. I've been drinking every day, too.
I keep thinking.
They say you become a grim reaper if you commit a great sin.
I wonder how bad a sin it was.
Maybe they erased our memory so that we wouldn't be tormented by it.
So that we can repent while doing this work?
It must be the deity's consideration.
If you remember, you remember. If not, you don't.
It is all the deity's will.
However, I wonder why he returned the memories...
that he had forgotten.
I wonder.
Jin Young!
Let's go.
- Did you have fun? - Yes.
What should we eat?
I need to go.
Don't drink too much.
Have a nice day.
Mom, where are we?
I think it's a tea shop.
What are we drinking? What are you going to order?
I ordered paradise...
to give it to you.
Paradise?
Here is paradise that you ordered.
Thank you.
Mom, why are you crying?
- What are you doing? - Oh my gosh.
What are you doing there?
I was going to the library.
What about you? Do you know them?
Who are you?
Step aside.
Open the window, air out the room, and button up.
You'll need this.
Let's go.
Daddy.
Hi. How did you get here?
I got in a taxi and showed her the address.
It was five dollars.
- I'm going here. - I know where that is.
Buckle up.
Daddy, I'm hungry.
What?
Okay. Here.
Daddy, I've missed you.
Me too.
You were pretty cool again today.
At times, a parent, a child, or a sibling...
becomes each other's guardian spirit.
I merely gave him a sandwich.
I did not save that man. His daughter did.
That's cool too.
The sandwich costs a lot.
It's a good thing Chairman Yu makes a lot of money.
But you know, about the sword...
Why do you think it suddenly moved?
I couldn't even grab it. Right?
Maybe you need something more powerful than a curse.
For example, true love. Something like that.
Don't you have something to say to me?
- No, I don't. - I'm sure you do.
Oh, that?
- There is one thing. - See? You do.
Don't hold it in. You're totally obvious.
Tell me. It's okay.
Whatever you say, I'll accept it without judgment.
I know you have a lot of money,
but is it okay to just stay home?
Is that what you wanted to tell me?
You worked for the country during the Goryeo Era, but that's it.
Hey. Are you done? I had a career, too.
It won't make you immortal, but you won't get drunk for a while.
It won't make you immortal, but you'll smell nice for a while.
It won't make you immortal, but you'll be happy for a while.
Why are you talking down to me?
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
- Yu Jae Shin. - My apologies.
My apologies for that, as well.
That's why you just stay home.
- Because you are lacking. - What do you mean, I'm lacking?
What do you think? You're lacking brain cells.
Seriously, I've never heard that before.
Ever. Seriously. Never.
I guess your first love never told you that.
Are you jealous?
What? Why would I be jealous?
I don't know when she lived or anything.
When did you meet? Goryeo? Joseon?
Mid Joseon? Late Joseon?
I'm sure she must have been pretty.
But you know, first loves never work out.
Go home. Don't wait for me.
I'll be late.
Who says first loves don't work out?
I don't like that.
- Hey. - Ho.
What?
What's "Hey, ho"?
Wasn't that funny? Everyone else thought it was funny.
It's lame.
You know, your birthmark faded a lot.
Really? Maybe it's because I'm getting older.
Why do you always waste money on this when I can't drink it?
It's such a waste.
Who would get you coffee other than me?
How did the exams go?
Good, of course.
That's why you should tell me your story before it's too late.
Other ghosts are busy...
telling me their stories and begging me to help them.
Why haven't you said anything to me?
Once I go to college, I won't be able to come here often.
Then...
will you come visit me?
I'd love some nice flowers.
I'm in Paju.
Okay. I'll come.
By the way,
how did you die?
It was on my graduation day.
There was a car accident.
I'll be waiting, then.
What happened to her?
- Welcome. - Hello.
How did you know I was here?
I'm even more surprised. Why did it have to be here?
There are more chicken restaurants in Korea than the total number...
of McDonald's in the world.
Why did it have to be this one?
Because this is the one Mr. Goblin put me in.
He's such a hindrance to my life.
What is it today?
You're giving me heart attacks. Are you going to keep this up?
Why do you think I'm here?
I'm here to get chicken. Give me one.
Don't lie.
I know you're a vegetarian.
Even if you know, give me one.
I want that one with extra radishes.
Really?
Were you supposed to meet him?
Did I just walk in at the scene by coincidence?
What are you doing? You can't touch that.
You're not supposed to be seen by humans, either.
Just go sit in the corner.
If you stay quiet, I'll give you an extra drumstick.
Welcome.
Have you been well?
Please take a seat.
Sit down. What would you like?
I thought about it, and what do you think about...
chicken for dinner?
Aren't you craving...
I guess we have no choice.
Tonight's dinner will have to be chicken.
I'm sorry for being selfish,
but tonight's dinner is...
Shut it.
Grim Reaper, I need to talk to you.
You can start without me. I'll be back before it's cold.
I'd rather just die...
Why do you keep coming to our store?
It can't be because of me.
Are you after my boss?
It's not like that.
I only go there to see her.
As long as you keep quiet,
everything will be peaceful.
It's you who should keep quiet.
Don't mention about Tae Hee's visiting me...
and that he smiled at me.
He also bought two more chickens on his way out.
It's our secret.
A secret?
He came to visit you at work? He smiled at you?
Sure, you might want to keep his smile a secret,
but why the take out?
Tell me the truth. How many coupons did you give him?
Be quiet. How many times did he visit you?
Let's say he came five times. How many coupons should he have?
I said, be quiet!
Hey. Do you know who allowed him to play baseball?
I used to be his guardian,
so I taught him everything. You're clueless.
Let's say what you claim is true. However, it can't be all you.
My first love Tae Hee's will played a big part.
Don't you know about the human will? Just look at me.
I ended up grabbing your sword.
I won't let you get pretty.
Hey, wait.
What is the process for an unnatural death?
Tell me the basics, and I'll try to do it myself.
I'll also help you with the chicken coupons.
I know a faster way. Why should I ask you for help?
Eun Tak.
- Hey. - Ji Eun Tak.
It somehow reappeared out of nowhere.
Not a single soul saw it when this huge thing was put back.
It's unfathomable, isn't it?
Eun Tak.
Do you have a minute? I have to ask you something.
Did you do well on your exams?
You could say that. Why?
You must have done really well.
You're conceited.
I bet you did well, too.
You're really smart.
I know you don't get any tutoring.
That's pretty amazing.
- Are you being sarcastic? - No, I mean it.
Which schools did you apply for?
I don't want to overlap.
We probably applied for the same schools,
but I won't overlap with you.
I'm considered as an underprivileged student.
So... Are you getting accepted?
What are you talking about?
I heard you see ghosts.
Don't they tell you things like that?
I'm curious if I'll get accepted.
That's what you wanted to know, isn't it?
At least you're being fair.
You're not talking behind my back.
I can't stand being curious about something.
That must be why you're so good at studying.
I can see them,
but they don't tell me anything.
I have to go.
We were in the same class for three years,
but we talked the most today.
You have the interview tomorrow at Seoun University, right?
Good luck.
You too.
You didn't care earlier whether I left or not.
Why are you here?
- Didn't you forget something? - What?
My scarf!
It's because you ignored me and got me irritated.
Don't get cold feet...
and don't get nervous.
Do you want me to come with you?
I'm not a kid.
Why isn't the bus coming?
- Are you still mad at me? - I was planning to,
but I failed because of the scarf.
- I was right. You're jealous. - So what?
- Are you happy I'm jealous? - Yes. I was happy the whole day.
You should go home.
I'll do well on my interview.
Thank you for the scarf.
Watch out behind you.
I'm sorry.
I was going to dodge her.
Your eyes are so huge and clear that everything reflects on it.
All right. Just get on the bus.
Thief! It's a pickpocket!
Bye.
But why?
You're not in the scene.
What's that?
My mom will kill me if I fail another interview.
I wish I got into a car accident.
Don't say that.
You should be careful what you wish for.
Death by Mom or traffic accident. What's the difference?
Everyone dies at some point.
Gosh.
I'm so tired.
Have some coffee, Sir.
I was the one who said I was tired. Why don't you have one for me?
I told him not to bring you one.
Are you still sullen about last time?
Who says I'm sullen?
Everyone says that.
It's good that you know.
Who are the new faces?
They came to back us up from Hannam-dong.
It must be a serious accident.
I heard everyone from the support team got five each.
You have way more than that.
It's because this is my jurisdiction.
Kim Hyun Jeong, age 34.
Park Soo Bin.
Age two. Death by accident.
They must be mother and baby.
I should prepare another paradise.
What?
You should call it a day and head home early.
I didn't even get started and you want me to call it a day?
What are you talking about?
It means I'll buy everything you have.
Why are you so impatient? Aren't you too young for that?
- Do you even know what's in there? - Socks.
What do you say? Will you do as I say?
Are you crazy?
You.
You're the one from the bus stop.
Why do you keep following me?
Make a guess.
The cash you stole was merely 23 dollars, 32 dollars,
10 dollars, and 3 meal coupons.
Do you know how many people could've died because of that?
What are you?
- Are you a cop? - The person you stole from...
gets diagnosed with fracture that takes three weeks to recover from.
She'd lose her job if she rests that long...
so she works without wearing a cast for three weeks because of you.
What on earth are you on about?
Does this wallet belong to you?
The monthly pay goes into medical expenses.
You make her go into shock from the untreated fracture.
Shut your mouth or you'll regret it.
I asked you who you are.
It's not to my liking that I have to save someone like you,
but it'll have to be a side effect from meddling with human lives.
But don't think your punishment is over.
You will be punished even after your death.
However...
An eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth.
This is my way of doing things.
It'll hurt a little.
Bear with it if you'd like.
Oh, my hand!
Get on stand by. It's time for work soon.
Okay.
The bus is approaching.
It's Mr. Grim Reaper.
Did she just look at you?
Can she see us right now?
There are some who become like that before they die.
Poor girl. She's still young.
Why is she...
Who has a name of Ji Eun Tak on the list?
Who are you talking about?
Wait, you're right. There is an extra person on the bus.
I thought everyone died.
Hold on. What happens when there's an extra?
There isn't going to be an accident today.
It's a bust.
What? Why?
That bus can't go like that.
It's not supposed to. It should get in an accident now.
Now should be the time.
What do we do? Shouldn't we cause one?
The bus just left. Nobody died.
This has never happened to me in my 300 years of career.
What do we do?
This is the first time I witnessed the occurrence of missing souls.
This has to be a miracle.
So miracles do happen.
Do you know how much paperwork this miracle is worth of?
Watch your mouth.
I'm sorry. It's just so astonishing.
But how did you know?
Oh, gosh.
I think it's a goblin.
What? Don't I look like one?
I need to talk to you.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why do you keep meddling with human lives?
Eun Tak almost died today.
If that is her destiny, it can't be avoided.
Says who?
The only thing I can't grant myself is my own death.
Do I have to meddle with every single human life for her?
You...That was my workplace.
But...
No matter how I look at it, today's accident was strange.
I foresaw the accident a few days ago,
but Eun Tak wasn't there.
Besides, I saw her future of 10 years from now.
And this accident would've definitely killed her.
It's because the accident you foresaw wasn't part of her destiny.
She became the variable of the accident.
Because you were going to save her.
Thanks to the missing soul who has a goblin boyfriend,
everyone who was meant to die ended up staying alive.
You made me work overtime.
Do you want some fried chicken?
Will you please consider returning to ashes?
It was a joke. No need to take it so seriously.
What does it mean to return to ashes?
Is it like becoming dust, wind, or rain?
And being scattered?
Why do you even wonder?
The missing soul can't even touch your sword.
Eun Tak grabbed the hilt.
It even moved, so I...
I almost killed her.
It hurt so much.
I'd never felt so much pain before.
Don't you think you should tell her the truth?
- About what will happen? - No.
I want to hide it if possible.
For about 80 more years.
- What? - That's a human's lifespan.
It's the maximum age a 19-year-old girl can live to be.
I want to keep it from her.
But can I?
No?
(Communication Sciences)
Did you come to pick me up? What a surprise.
I'm out because I felt a little stuffy.
I know. There's no way you'd care about my welfare.
What's all this?
Socks?
It signifies the next 10, 20 years of someone I saved today.
Did you decide to sell socks...
to support me for the next 10, 20 years?
Because I asked why you don't work?
- Do you want to help out? - Sure.
My interviews are over so I'm free now.
I'll take better care of you from now on.
How do you mean?
What are you doing?
Exercising.
To make sure I pull out the sword in one go next time.
I realized last time that I need strong arms for the job.
Don't overdo it.
Why do you sound so reluctant?
Can you excuse me? I need to talk to someone.
- To whom? - I won't be long. Go inside.
Come over here. Come down to my level.
Don't you think you punished me enough?
Did you hate the idea of my enjoying something that much?
Did you show me that in advance to stop me from doing something?
Do you think I'll make that decision?
I won't. Never.
Come down here.
Let's talk face-to-face. Why won't you?
Do you think I'm afraid of you? Come down.
Why don't you ever face me?
Is he still sick?
I didn't look. I swear.
I really don't like this.
Having to like you...
I couldn't be more foolish.
What...
did you just say to me?
- It's fine if you missed it. - I heard everything.
Then good.
Does that mean...
he actually confessed his love for me?
What's wrong with him?
48.
49.
50.
(10 missed calls)
You never call so I didn't bother to check my phone.
You startled me.
I was surprised that you called me first.
10 missed calls?
I was working late when I thought of something to say.
It must've been really important.
It is.
I don't have a religion.
You speak so well. Do you have a religion?
Do I need to have something else again?
I'll call you when I have it.
Did you call me 10 times just to tell me that?
I thought I should tell you as soon as possible.
You're cute.
Am I...
- cute? - Didn't you know?
Didn't any of the other women tell you so?
I didn't have any other women...
That's a good thing. Not having other women.
Don't go looking for any.
You're perfect as you are, okay?
Is he a player?
Tell me this and be very honest.
I will tell you, too.
Tell me what?
My real first name has only one syllable.
Kim Sun.
My parents were poor,
but they still paid someone...
to come up with a good name.
The fortune-teller said I had to have this name.
But I prefer Sunny.
I think I shine brighter when I'm Sunny.
I really hated that name.
It sounds sad like something happened in the past.
Kim Sun.
Our master...
goes there around this time every year...
and launches a sky lantern.
Woo Bin.
What's your real name?
I know your name is fake.
Even if it's weird or doesn't suit you,
I won't tease you, so can't you tell me?
I give you the sword with rage and concern.
Go as far as you can, as if possible,
do not return.
Your Majesty, do you mean...
How could you...
Goryeo is your nation.
You ordered me to guard the border, so I did.
You ordered me to kill the enemy, so I did.
My sister is here and so are the people...
You now understand...
the concerns of the King.
Notify me of your death,
and I shall notify you of my sorrow.
It is my royal decree.
Is something wrong?
Is it your chest? Your stomach? What did you eat for dinner?
Are your hands cold? Give me your hand.
If you massage your hand, it'll help blood flow and...
I'm sorry,
but please look into my eyes.
What?
You did not see me today.
I'm sorry I can't take you home.
Turn around and go home.
Where did he go?
From now on,
you'll have to serve Master Kim,
so you must remember this day clearly.
Why is he launching lanterns?
Who are they?
They are people...
to whom he owed a debt in his heart for a very long time.
I heard there is a sword stuck in Uncle's chest. Do you know about it?
How did you know that?
You cannot let our master know that you know about it.
Why not?
That sword...
is his prize and punishment.
It is his reason for existing,
and the clue to his extinction.
You are my life...
and my death.
And I...
like you.
Thus, I keep this secret...
and ask above for permission.
May you not know for one more day.
May you not know for 100 years more.
You know me, right?
I need to talk to you.
Do you have time?
Will you please get right to it?
I don't feel like speaking with a deity right now.
Something went wrong.
I think...
it starts with you.
Where did he go?
This is why...
I said even if he doesn't say he's coming,
I want him to say if he's leaving.
What do you want to know?
Well, so...
I told you before.
Once my bride appears, I must prepare to go farther away.
Something seemed strange.
You know the sword in the goblin's chest.
What happens exactly...
if I remove it?
He kept saying he's going somewhere.
Does that mean you're not leaving?
For now.
I may have to prepare to go farther away.
Where is that?
Remove that sword quickly.
Remove the sword and return to ashes.
You show up out of the blue and tell me to die.
Shouldn't you tell me why...
You've lived long enough,
but not her.
I was truly happy when I created her,
so decide now.
How ironic.
I don't know what decision you want me to make.
When I was first born as Kim Shin,
you must have created me.
Am I not your child?
That's why I'm telling you.
For my child, Kim Shin, for whom I wished happiness.
Because it is what you want the most.
- What do I want? - You want her to live.
If you don't return to ashes,
Eun Tak will die.
So...
he wanted to die.
That's why he wanted me to be his bride...
and remove that sword?
So...
if I remove that sword,
he will die?
So...
if I remove that sword,
he will disappear...
from this world? For good?
She was born to pull out your sword. That's her fate.
No, you gave her that fate.
She'll become useless if she doesn't do what she was born to do.
There will be no reason for her existence.
Hence, if she fails to pull out the sword,
she'll continue to face death.
I'm sure it happened numerous times already.
- No. - You little.
Bye.
Yes, that's right.
There will be worse accidents.
It'll be more frequent and more severe than before.
You almost killed her once...
with your own hands.
It's moving.
One day after 100 years...
When the weather is good enough,
I hope I'll be able to...
tell her she was my first love.
I ask...
above for permission.
(Goblin)