Episode 21
What brings you here—?
Jin Eon needs you right now, Dokgo Yong Gi.
Pardon?
This was found amongst Hae Gang's possessions.
Shin Yang Bank - Check Card
Dokgo Yong Gi
On the day of Hae Gang's accident, it appears that you were with her, Dokgo Yong Gi.
What did you say?
If we want to find out how and why Hae Gang died,
then we definitely need your help.
Please help Jin Eon.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
the Forgotten Love Team at Viki
What! The urn is gone?
In order to work at daybreak, I sent someone to do a preliminary check but it was completely empty.
Wh-What could have happened?
Just be alive.
Just please be alive, Do Hae Gang!
Hae Gang isn't here.
Excuse me?
There's no way—you're saying that it's empty?
Where could my wife be right now?
Could you please take a look at this picture of my wife?
No. I don't want to see it.
Where I'm at right now with my feelings, I don't think I can bring myself to look at your late wife.
She's alive.
Like you.
But... Why hasn't she appeared? And for four years?
I suppose she's lost her memory, too—like you.
I came because I was told that
I was with your wife on the day of the accident.
Because my card wallet was found with Hae Gang's possessions.
I'll help you.
I'm scared, but I also want to know
the reason why I was with your wife that day.
This is why he left it empty.
So that Brother-in-law could find it,
so that he can strangle me any time.
That's why he said you couldn't put someone else's remains in there.
An urn with Lawyer Do's name written on it can't ever be filled with a stranger's ashes.
That's why that old geezer was being so stubborn about it!
I didn't know his intention but I thought it's his affection for Lawyer Do.
That sneaky bastard.
You said it was a suicide, but the urn is empty.
How should we block this?
Just come up with a witness for the suicide. Since there's no evidence, all that's needed is a witness.
There's only suspicion but no evidence. Don't you think?
There's no record of the accident, no videos, absolutely nothing. How are they going to prove anything.
Unless Do Hae Gang comes back alive, unless Dokgo Yong Gi's memory returns,
it will be impossible to track.
What if he asks why there isn't any record of the accident, when there was even a witness?
The record was removed.
To protect Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals, the Chairman covered up his daughter-in-law's suicide.
It's okay.
There's nothing to block, and we can block it.
It's up to Jin Eon to prove it, not me.
We just need to get rid of Dokgo Yong Gi.
As long as that woman, Dokgo Yong Gi, is gone...
On September 27, 2011,
it's showing that I scrapped my car.
That's the very next day after you were scheduled to go to China.
Then, the accident was the day before.
Do Hae Gang's rental car was returned just fine,
but my car was scrapped, and my card wallet was with Do Hae Gang's possessions.
How in the world are we going to figure this out?
If there's a possibility...
If there's a chance I'm your wife...
I'll make sure to find out and prove that's not the case.
I'll make sure to find out what happened and by whom, so until then,
please wait.
There is something called an Accident Verification Certificate.
If you get one, you can check more details of the accident under my name.
I'll check tomorrow.
I'll try—to remember.
I'll try my best to get my memory back.
It seems that's the way we can end this.
It seems that's the way I'll be able to end it with you.
Who is this?
Aren't you Dokgo Yong Gi?
What brings you to President Choi's office at this hour?
Is he inside?
Yes.
It seems like you're on your way out, so why don't we head out together?
Yes, okay.
Did you bring your car?
No.
Then we can take you to where you need to go.
No, thank you. I'll just take the bus.
Why don't you just ride in my car? I have something to say to you, Dokgo Yong Gi.
Excuse me? Something to say?
You're working hard this late at night.
Yeah. You too, Brother-in-law.
So it's understood? No more picketing until Moon Tae Joon recovers.
Yes.
And once he regains consciousness, it's agreed that the lawsuit will be dropped.
You heard from his family, right?
Yes.
Brother-in-law, I received Dokgo Yong Gi's promise that she'll let go of the Pudoxin lawsuit.
Is that right?
Thorough epidemiologic investigation and debunking false charges are promises I received from Choi Jin Eon.
Why don't you leave Pudoxin up to me from now on?
Both of you, Brother-in-law and Dokgo Yong Gi.
I'll handle it. I'll take care of it myself.
Okay. Let's do that.
This is the first floor, you can get off.
♫ My heart is closed and I'm living like a fool ♫
♫ Memories of when I loved you ♫
♫ Are locked deep within the corners of my heart ♫
♫ Countless days have passed us by ♫
♫ Just like that day ♫
♫ You are here looking at me  ♫
♫ Even if we are far apart ♫
♫ Even if everything changes ♫
♫ My heart will withstand time ♫
♫ And it will stay right here  ♫
♫ Even if we can never meet again ♫
♫ Even if everything changes ♫
♫ My heart won't ever forget your smile ♫
Come in.
♫ And it will remain the same ♫
- Your balance is insufficient.
- Wait a minute, stop there please!
- Ah, yes.
I don't have a change—only a ₩10,000 ($10) bill.
Ay, you don't have any change? Hurry up and put it in.
I'm sorry.
It's dangerous! Hurry up and take a seat!
Thank you, thank you.
Ah, thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
the Forgotten Love Team at Viki
All the objects in this world are holding one another.
I, you. You, me.
Even if you don't believe me, you believe Newton, right? Isaac Newton.
But the father of modern science lived from 1642 to 1727.
- You want to get hit?
- Yeah, I want to get hit.
It's time for us to have skinship. Here, hit me, hit me, hit me. Hit me with your lips, your lips!
Do Hae Gang! Make me yours. I'm yours. Hae Gang!
Hae Gang! Hae Gang! Hae Gang!
Hae Gang. Hae Gang! Hae Gang!
Do Hae Gang!
Be careful!
I'm going, now! Hae Gang! Hae Gang!
Hae Gang!
He said it might get too stuffy for her, so he wanted to move her to a place that was sunny and breezy,
so I agreed to it.
I see.
She'll be moving to where Eun Sol is, tomorrow morning.
And the urn, Brother-in-law—
How did you know?
Pardon? Ah, I was working and suddenly
Director Do came to mind, so I stopped by and was surprised to find it was completely empty.
I am filled with gratitude as it could be difficult for you.
Did Brother-in-law say anything in particular?
Like what?
Hyung!
Gyu Seok!
Why are you so surprised?
Surprised, who's surprised? Man, it's because I'm glad to see you.
Aigoo ya! I didn't come to see you, so you can stop frowning.
That's a relief. I'm back now.
Yeah, okay. Sit down, Professor Min. Should I get you some tea?
No, thank you. I came to get some water.
Please continue with your conversation.
See you later.
This punk, as soon as he sees me, he says "see you later."
Aigoo, seriously, who's going to take that guy.
Why? Besides being a bit mean, he doesn't have any faults.
The woman who takes our Professor Min will be winning the lotto. The lotto!
So then, where is that lucky lady?
Aigoo, really.
Waiting for him, I've developed hwa-byung and it's killing me.
(emotional disorder from repressed anger or stress)
Everyone has their other half. Just wait, she'll appear.
I see.
Professor Min, I heard that you're so renowned that patients come from abroad to see you.
They struggled to come here from such a long distance,
so you should take extra special care of them,
and make sure they get better, in a kind manner, okay?
I know how to take care of my own patients. Please stop worrying.
You're not cold?
And if I'm cold, what?
Then you have to run.
Should we run? You look cold.
You tend to get cold easily, but you're not sensitive to the heat, right?
No.
That's not the case.
Who were you thinking I was when you followed me here?
I was thinking it'd be nice if Dokgo Yong Gi was my wife. If you were my wife, Yong Gi.
Because when I see you, I feel nervous.
Because when I look into your eyes, I feel pain.
At one point in time, this charcoal was
once a tree branch laced with white snow.
Such a beautiful saying...
I guess it's not just anyone who can be a poet.
When she was young, even the spot where a flea had bitten her was beautiful.
This is my story. This is my story to a T.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
the Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Hello?
Yes, Mother, it's me.
Did you get some sleep?
Of course.
Please go with me to the hospital today.
Mother, you definitely have to go.
The medicine for it is under the way being developed.
Sunbae was also researching Dementia.
If you get diagnosed it early,
You have to be taking good care of yourself to be able to take the medication that Sunbae is developing.
Okay. Okay, let's go.
Let's go and receive testing to see if I have it or not.
Yes. Yes, Mother.
No, it's fine. I'll go get ready and then I'll come by to pick you up.
Okay. I'm hanging up now.
Do you know anything about Han Gang Group's youngest daughter?
Why?
I try to make my brother-in-law and her a couple.
Her family is probably the 20th wealth among Chaebols?
You think you can control a person's fate, that if you stick people together or pull them apart, it ends up how you want?
Just let him date a woman he likes so he doesn't get old and regret it.
Where is there a marriage that a person doesn't regret when they get old?
One way or another, there's regret. One way or another, it ends up broken.
If that's going to happen, then you might as well look at wealth, family, and education.
That way you end up having much less regret when you get older.
Please find out for me, since that side has shown interest in my brother-in-law.
Okay.
And make sure to check whether she is doing drugs or not. That's the scariest.
Our Jin Eon needs to hurry up and get married too.
I need to at least see that. I need to at least see our Jin Eon get married.
See it and then what?
Why'd you stop in the middle of talking? It's making my imagination run wild.
I wonder what that secret is that you can't say out loud.
Oh, yeah. I heard Do Hae Gang's imitation has amnesia.
What? Amnesia?
Yes. I heard she lost her entire memory.
- How?
- I don't know how.
I thought maybe her liver had fallen out of her insides,
(due to being so swollen; "swollen liver" = to be overly bold/shameless)
but it was her memory that had fallen out of her brain.
I wonder what it would feel like to have your memory disappear.
I wonder what it would feel like to live without being able to remember anything.
Well, I guess your thoughts of revenge would disappear, your anger would go away,
and so would any hatred and resentment,
I suppose you'd live peacefully, with a kind and loving heart.
Why?
You're the one who needs to have amnesia. You're the one who needs to lose her memory, seriously.
What did you say?
It'd be nice to deposit memories into a bank.
If my memories were deposited into a savings account,
then it'd be nice to just be able to withdraw and use them whenever I needed.
I have a long way to go if I want to follow in your footsteps, Father-in-law.
I couldn't foresee a second ahead of time like a fool so I believed and thought you were my side.
I felt guilty and sorry without knowing you sit there and think only about getting rid of me everyday.
I don't know about anyone else, but I suppose you'd be the one to know about the anxiety I'm feeling that's driving me crazy...
I was foolish. I guess I've always been a bit foolish.
I understand. Yes, I get it now, Father-in-law. Now that I've completely grasped your true intention,
it's war from now on, Father-in-law.
If you wave a knife at me, then I'll shoot you with a gun.
But rather than it hitting you, I think it'll be your son, who's cluelessly running wild, ending up taking the bullet—
That's my worry.
Don't worry. Because my son can just shoot you first.
Because, even if I forgive you, that guy will never be able to forgive you.
I may not be able to punish you, but that guy,
when it comes to him, he can definitely punish you.
You talk as if I'm the one who's done something wrong.
There is a difference.
The statute of limitations has expired for me. But it hasn't expired for you.
I may not have a lot of time left to live, but you
have many years ahead of you.
Let's have breakfast together, Brother-in-law.
- I don't really feel like it today.
- Then come sit for a little while before you leave.
Alright, I guess.
Whenever it's possible, let's all make sure to have breakfast together.
It's my wish, so everyone please stick to it. Choi Jin Eon, especially you.
Okay.
Are you doing better now?
Yes.
You see, because in Hae Gang's urn—Hae Gang isn't there.
Wh-What did you say?
What isn't there?
That's absurd! How can you say something so outrageous!
You mean there aren't any remains? Why is it? How can there not be any?
I guess Brother-in-law would know that. Why is Hae Gang's urn empty?
We never ended up finding her body.
If you never found a body, but you confirmed her death,
I suppose there's a witness who's able to provide even more guarantee than Hae Gang's own body.
Someone who was there with Hae Gang at the scene.
That's right. There's a witness who saw her fall into the dam.
And Father-in-law is the one who had the police report removed.
Since we can't let the whole world know about his daughter-in-law's suicide.
I saw Hae Gang yesterday. A Hae Gang who's very much alive.
What'd you say? She's alive?
I'm sure you saw it wrong. Attorney Do is dead.
Last time, you confused another person for Attorney Do too, remember?
I suppose. Whether I'm confused,
or whether Hae Gang is still alive. I'll check and find out.
I thought—
Jin Eon. Jin Eon! Pull yourself together.
That's a disease. I'm telling you, it's not love, but a mental disease!
All this really is, is that everyone looks like Do Hae Gang to you right now.
I understand. The pain of losing your spouse.
You just don't want to admit it. You want to deny it.
But your the one who abandoned her. You were the one who asked Father to get rid of her.
Omo, hey, hey!
Just stay still, please.
Whether it was suicide or not, whether there are remains or not, however she died,
you're the one who made it end up like this.
I'm saying this all happened because of you. Even if your wife came back alive,
with her personality, she would never forgive you.
Only you miss her to death, Do Hae Gang hates you to death.
If she saw you, she'd want to take revenge on you.
How could you expect her to love you?
It's your sin. The original sin you started. It's the seed you sowed.
This is all a punishment. So quit obsessing over Do Hae Gang, and just receive your punishment, okay?
When you planted hatred, how can you expect to sprout love?
What is this like salted vegetables? Head up and look at me.
Whenever you eat or you fight, you need to look at each other and do it.
I'm telling to you guys to look at each other, instead of looking away from each other.
If you keep turning away from each other during tough times,
when the time comes that you want to look to each other, you won't be able to anymore. It'll be too late.
Did you get disappointed by Yong Gi?
It's a given for family to disappoint each other.
One minute it's disappointment, the next it's hope, then desire.
That's family.
Don't hold a grudge but believe each other and speak out honestly when you fight.
If you hold a grudge and not speak out, you will really get narrow-minded.
People's hearts, too.
She's not family, yet.
Don't trap Yong Gi by calling her family, Father.
You were always honest.
You always looked directly into my eyes and told me honestly.
The one who can't do it is me.
I'm in the middle of thinking things through and agonizing over them.
Just give me a little more time. Then,
I will look at your eyes and honestly fight with you.
Mom. Am I getting a shot today?
Today, just an exam.
Should we play that?
Ms. Zhang Ming!
Oh yes, I'm right here, Zhang Ming.
- Please come in.
- Yes.
Let's go in, Woo Joo.
This way, please.
Come on, let's sit you down. Thank you.
Aren't you going to greet the doctor?
Ni hao! ("Hello!" in Chinese)
Welcome, Dokgo Woo Joo.
I already told you her name isn't Dokgo Woo Joo,
so why do you keep—
I'll sit down.
Why don't you start by telling me her symptoms—in Korean.
Pardon?
Ah, that's—
My child was falling down all the time, so I took her to the local hospital— (spoken in dialect)
-  Next patient.
- Excuse me?
What are you doing? See these people out, and bring in the next patients.
The relationship between the doctor and the patient starts with respect.
If the basics are wrong, rarities can't be cured.
Korean—
I can just speak Korean, then.
Okay, then. Please tell me Woo Joo's symptoms.
She falls down easily and has anemia.
She was being treated for leukemia but it didn't seem right.
Strange cells were seen in her bone marrow.
Looked like it may be Gaucher's disease.
Since you are the expert in this field, I came to Korea because of you.
Let's have a basic examination and an enzyme analysis right away.
It's difficult to determine by bone marrow tests alone.
Gaucher cells are not always found in the bone marrow.
Since there are many similar cells, though it may be more costly, you must get an enzyme analysis.
Hong Se Hee!
You're so pretty. What's your name?
Zhang Ling.
Zhang Ling? You must have come from China, is that right?
What's the matter? Is there something on my face?
Dokgo Yong Gi.
I swear, really!
Passport.
Instead, please pay me back 57,520 won.
Are you not going to pay me?
I'm going to find some work today, okay?
I'm planning to do whatever work comes my way as soon as I can, without being picky whatsoever, so
please just give me a few days.
I'll give you three days. In three days,
by 2:47pm, please pay me back by then.
Fine.
Your name is Dokgo Yong Gi?
Pardon?
No, it's not! The doctor got it wrong.
My name is Zhang Ming! Zhang Ming.
But—why are you staring at me like that?
I've never seen you before.
Female Plaintiff in Lawsuit for Damages from Medication Side Effects, Jumps Off Court Building
That woman is on a different level from Yong Gi Unni.
She's cold-hearted and cruel.
Pharmaceutical Chemist Loses Patent Infringement Lawsuit, Murders Opposing Attorney's Daughter in Retaliation
Her daughter died.
Because of his wife.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
the Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Accident Verification Certificate
Name: Dokgo Yong Gi, Accident Date/Time: 8-3-2011 2:10 pm, Accident Location: City of Guri, Degree of Accident: Injury
...victim suffered threat with a deadly weapon and attempted kidnapping by an unidentified assailant.
8-14-2011...in Cheon Nyeon underground parking lot, victim suffered threat with a deadly weapon and attempted kidnapping by suspect Lee Jung Man.
It pops up as an assault.
Since a deadly weapon was used, even if it was attempted, an aggravated assault charge should have been issued.
Special robbery is a crime that shall be punished by imprison at least five years.
How can the culprit who was apprehended red-handed
be free of all charges?
I wouldn't know. Why don't you ask the prosecutor that was in charge then?
Why are you acting like this now?
Let go of the past and stay careful.
And the same incident two separate times!
And please don't take revenge.
What was the date, the day you found Dokgo Yong Gi?
September 26, 2011.
I did a search on the car.
On September 27, it's listed that Dokgo Yong Gi
went in person to go scrap her car.
She was in the hospital, until the 28th.
Hae Gang's urn is empty.
She's alive. I'm going to find her.
This time, properly, without fail, for sure,
I'm going to find Hae Gang.
I'm still certain that Dokgo Yong Gi
is my wife.
I will find out for sure and then act accordingly.
I can't afford to just believe what you tell me,
and then lose her while she's right in front of me.
This one woman.
The woman who you and I both love.
Let's just focus on that woman, and go from there.
Let's throw away our greed, let's throw away our regret.
Let's both just focus on her happiness,
and go from there.
Chun Nyeon Pharmaceuticals broke all the rules. What are you going to tell her?
Fake urn, fake columbarium, questionable accident.
I'm telling you your family did that, Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals did that.
Are you going to tell her the truth?
Once you find her and bring her back,
when her memory returns, what are you going to do?
When she remembers you, when she remembers everything,
when that time comes, what is that woman supposed to do?
Have you thought about the shock that she'll experience?
Choi Jin Eon, this time too,
you won't be able to find your wife properly.
And you shouldn't look for her either.
Can you please excuse me?
Hello?
Hello? It's me, Dokgo Yong Gi!
Don't hang up, just give me a minute.
I'll be back after I take this call.
2970.
Did you write it down?
Read it back to me, starting with the address here.
It's not 46. It's 465.
You're probably going to get a call.
Sorry. I really have to work,
You are the only one I can ask as my reference.
What kind of work are you planning to do?
I'll just do whatever job the staffing agency can find.
I don't have a lot of options.
I'll come by after I get off of work. Maybe we can have dinner. I'll see you later.
Ah, hey! You don't have to come.
Seok, I'm really okay.
I even lived in China. This is nothing.
I feel so strange.
I feel like I came out from my own coffin, not the MRI Machine.
I'm not very good at offering words of comfort, Mother.
I don't think I can bear to tell you to have strength either.
Nor do I have anything particular to say.
Instead, I'll come with you to the hospital.
Without Jin Eon being involved, if that's what you want.
So that you don't have to feel scared or lonely, all by yourself.
Thank you. More than any words of comfort,
that gives me strength and comforts me.
Do you want to go watch a movie?
I want to be alone. I want to go alone, just today.
That's right. I'll just be by myself for now.
That's just how I'm feeling.
Yes, okay.
I'll be leaving first, then.
Okay.
Okay, then. See you later.
Let's go.
It'll be dangerous if we leave her like this.
As long as she's living as Dokgo Yong Gi, she's at risk of falling into danger again.
I came here to ask that you pay attention to her safety.
I'll look after Yong Gi, you just look after Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals.
I'm not just saying to be careful, I'm asking you to stop them.
So that they don't do anything, to stop them from doing the same thing twice.
Your family, your people, I'm telling you to stop them.
Stealing a person's life, stepping on and twisting their life...
I have no idea what in the world they're trying to hide to keep doing such filthy things,
I will reveal it, end it, clean it up, fight it,
and I will not forgive it.
The most immediate work is housekeeping, but you probably won't want to do that because you're young, right?
I'll do it! Housekeeping? I'll do it.
Then you should get a phone as soon as possible.
I can have you working right away today,
but it's more difficult to contact you.
Then I'll be back in 2 hours.
You can't give work to someone else. Okay, Head Manager?
I heard about your tough circumstances. I understand so come back in 2 hours.
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Employment Agency
What brings you—? You don't seem like someone who would need to come here.
The lady who just left, her Chinese name in Zhang Ming,
what kind of work did she come here to find?
Do you know her?
I just met her a little while ago at the hospital.
Because I feel bad for her being in such a tough situation.
I want to help her, with her kid being sick and all.
She got robbed and lost all her money.
She asked for the most immediate work available, so I'm planning to connect her to some housekeeping work.
Then, please direct her to my place.
Oh my, would you like to do that?
Yes.
Then, please fill this out.
Housekeeper Request Application Form
Kang Seol Ri
Here you go.
I gathered everything from her vanity, desk, and bathroom, so look through them.
I couldn't bring myself to throw anything away,
not even an eraser.
But what are you looking for?
I'll tell you later when I'm certain.
I'm the housekeeper who's been sent here by Manager Lee—
Huh?
At the hospital earlier—right?
Yes, please come in. Zhang Ling, let's go sit down.
Please have a seat.
Okay.
I'm Baek Seok Oppa's younger sister.
Yong Gi Unni.
Pardon?
I saw your face in my brother's middle school graduation album.
That's why at the hospital earlier...
Ay, and I thought—!
Nice to meet you, Yong Gi Unni.
My car was scrapped, I'm alive, that woman is dead,
something of mine was found amongst that woman's possessions...
Choi Jin Eon's wife, what if I was the one who was responsible for it?
It wasn't you. You didn't do it.
Didn't you say there was no body found? But that family,
with a fake urn and a fake columbarium...
It's something Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals did,
I'm sure of it. Believe me.
I was a whistleblower,
I almost died twice and the culprit was let go.
then, while trying to kill me...
Do you think that might've been what happened, Seok?
Both of us look alike, enough to confuse Choi Jin Eon!
They tried to kill me, but
they ended up killing Choi Jin Eon's wife instead.
You know, that woman,
would she be able to cope with all of this?
Just like he said, if she's alive,
if she returns, would she be able to cope with all of this?
Her in-laws and her husband who did all of this to her,
would she be able to forgive them?
If you were that woman,
would you be able to forgive them?
I think it would be difficult for me.
I don't think I could forgive. It's not a matter where I can just forgive,
and how could that be forgiven?
That woman will probably not forgive either,
if she finds out that Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals,
where she devoted her life, did that to her.
Please check to see if it's the same person.
How would you like to receive the results, by email, mail, or fax?
Through fax.
Alright.
8am to 12pm, Monday, Wednesday, Friday. How does that sound?
Three times? It doesn't even look like there'd be much to clean.
You're doing this on purpose to help me out, aren't you?
Don't be like that, there's no need. I can just work multiple jobs.
Manager told me she'd connect me to five or six more places.
What was my brother like in middle school?
Did you two really date each other? Or did my brother just like to think of it as that?
We really did date each other, from 9th to 12th grade.
During class he would always read fiction or poetry.
Your brother's nickname was "ground beetle".
That's also the name for "bookworm".
It's the perfect name for your brother, right? I still can't kill ground beetles because of your brother.
Abracadabra, Hakuna Matata Poly Poly, Andantaespraesebo, Aeiherumuh,
All day, he memorized and cast spells.
Not everyone can be a doctor or lawyer, but you can be a magician.
If you open your heart, magic is everywhere.
The spells I memorized then have helped me out greatly, when life was hard.
If I didn't meet your brother, I would've lived not even knowing I was Dokgo Yong Gi.
Ah, and in 12th grade, we watched "Before Sunrise" and got the feels, so your Oppa played Ethan Hawke and I played Julie Delpy,
and we acted out those scenes taking the train to Jeongdongjin.
But you know, I noticed that Julie Delpy's aged a lot since.
Oh my, are you crying?
Why are you crying?
Oh my! Omo, hey, Seol Ri!
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
the Forgotten Love Team at Viki
You think everything's over? You think you won?
It's not over yet.
Excuse me?
Protect it well. Don't get it stolen like me.
The stealer is bad, but it's worse to get stolen from.
Don't you think?
Seol Ri...
You must hate me,
but I also hate you too.
I'm scared of you. The way you eat away at me...
You are still...destroying me.
Why again? Why are you doing this again?
You're the one who started it first.
You insulted me and scorned me first.
You act like you're the absolute, you act like you're so perfect.
You stepped on my heart and tried to get rid of me.
I want you to disappear from this world the most.
I really wish you could disappear!
I wish you were dead!
She's still at the office.
Alone?
Yes. Gi Moon is watching her.
What about Moon Tae Joon?
No one else has tried to access him besides his family,
and there aren't any unusual signs as of yet.
Alright.
Accident Verification Certificate
8-3-2011...victim suffered threat with a deadly weapon and attempted kidnapping by an unidentified assailant.
8-14-2011
...in Cheon Nyeon underground parking lot, victim suffered threat with a deadly weapon and attempted kidnapping...
Chun Nyeon Pharmaceuticals broke all the rules.
What are you going to tell her?
My resident card?
Yeah.
Have some coffee first.
Okay.
At the Wonjoo rest area,
I gave it to this woman, along with my cell phone.
You see, I took that woman's car and escaped.
I kept speeding and driving like crazy, and I finally lost the guy who was trying to kill me.
I kept calling her with my cell phone so I could return her car back, but she never picked up.
So I went back to the rest area,
that woman was gone, and my car was gone, too.
Do Hae Gang. That woman's name was Do Hae Gang.
There was a name card in the card and a Divorce Certificate, too.
But you know, I saw that she was the director of our company's legal team.
I need to find that woman.
I need to find her to find out if she's safe and apologize to her.
I need to tell her how grateful I am, because thanks to her, I'm alive.
But I can't gather enough nerve to do it.
If there's a chance, if there's a possibility that because of me,
instead of me...
Meeting Report
Dokgo Yong Gi
Female Plaintiff in Lawsuit for Damages from Medication Side Effects, Jumps Off Court Building
Pharmaceutical Chemist Loses Patent Infringement Lawsuit, Murders Opposing Attorney's Daughter in Retaliation
What was it that you were doing?
You knew something you weren't supposed to know,
and you had something you weren't supposed to have,
am I right?
So you kept being watched and followed.
You were rubbed the house and threatened as well.
What was that? I need to know in order to help you.
How long are you going keep running and living so precariously? Plus—
it's not just you who's in danger.
It's not that I can't trust you.
I just need to protect my child.
No, fine. To be honest, I can't trust anything.
I forgot. I forgot everything.
As soon as Woo Joo gets better, I'm going to leave once and for all, and not ever look back.
So stop asking me.
Hey kid.
Dad.
What are you doing here?
I came to see the family, but I can't bring myself to go in.
Now, there's no place for me there,
and I feel like everyone will feel uncomfortable.
Why wouldn't there be a place for you? Come on.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
the Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Let's go. It's cold.
I stopped by after an appointment I had nearby...
is a lie. I came by because I was worried after I got your fax.
I'll just take you home.
Just think of it as riding a taxi...
is also a lie.
I know I totally sound crazy with all the things I just said, so let's just get in the car and go.
Go to Seol Ri.
Pardon?
I briefly saw her earlier, and she didn't seem well.
I'll be going.
♫ I was really okay  ♫
Thank you for worrying.
♫ I came all this way sort of with a smile  ♫
I'll go home carefully and safely, so don't worry.
♫ But now I’m filled with lies  ♫
Drive safely.
♫ What can I do? ♫
♫ My heart that hated you so much  ♫
Just one more time.
♫ My bad greed  ♫
♫ It was all love  ♫
♫ It was a dazzling love  ♫
Can you just say it one more time?
♫ The only ones who can believe it  ♫
Excuse me? Say what?
♫ The only ones who know  ♫
When you told me to drive safely.
♫ It’s just you and me in this world ♫
Drive safely.
Preview
Yong Gi. Yong Gi! Yong Gi!
It's my fault. I'm the one who said she was Yong Gi,
I told her she was Yong Gi.
She looks like you, Mom.
Do Hae Gang? Do Hae Gang...
Someone sent this to you. It appears that the dump truck right there crashed into Dokgo Yong Gi's car.
I love you! As much as the universe!
Dokgo Yong Gi, where are you right now?
What are you saying right now?
I'll let you go when I can. I'll let you go when I'm able to.
Wait for me, Sunbae.
What do you mean she's dead?