Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
That is a wall. While we feel that it's a wall which can't be moved past,
at that time, a climber quietly starts climbing that wall.
It's a poem that Do Hae Gang liked the most.
Without a drop of water,
a place where even a seed can't survive,
when people say that it's a wall of hopelessness,
a climber, without hurrying, goes forward.
It's me, Seok.
I said it's me. It's On Gi.
It's my birthday. Congratulate me.
All of my memories came back.
The memories that I had spent with you for four years as well.
Like a lighthouse, you always protect Do Hae Gang, night and day.
The past me and the present me are fighting right now. Did you see me a little while ago?
Sometimes, I feel a surge of anger I can't control. I hate, reproach and dislike him.
I really want to reveal everything and I can't forgive him.
Then, I feel I don't have any right to forgive someone or not.
Why...
Is it September 25, 2011?
The day of the accident, when we met, was September 26,
and the day you woke up in my house was September 29.
Why did you even pretend forgetting about me?
It's not only to remove Choi Jin Eon from your life,
but it's also to erase me.
You tried to make me give up hope on you by hurting me.
You tried to cut me off.
Yes.
I didn't expect you would act this way.
I didn't really expect you'd offer to be friends with me after being humiliated so much.
I lost to you, Baek Seok.
So, what is your plan?
After you cut me off, cut Choi Jin Eon off, and cut everything off, what are you going to do?
I will return to the past me.
I will return to the Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals.
What?
To catch a tiger, you have to go into the tiger's den.
To protect Yong Gi, I have to be in the tiger's den.
About Pudoxin, the murder instigation,
and the death of the researcher, Kim Sun Yong,
if I don't have solid proof, I can't reveal anything.
If I act hastily and unwisely, he will be released with no suspicion again.
All I know are the circumstances of four years ago. That is also only a part of the information.
I will ally with Min Tae Seok.
After allying with him, I must put the handcuffs on his hands.
Even so, why Choi Jin Eon? He is on your side.
It's possible to put one handcuff on Min Tae Seok's hand and
the other handcuff on my hand.
I want to fight with the past me, by myself.
I don't want to drag him into this and cause him pain again,
revealing all those sides of me.
I am ashamed of myself.
I've finally come to know how much he had to endure.
Because of you, I got to know it.
Help me so I can correct my life, even now, Seok.
I can wash away the sins I've committed, one by one,
so that I can protect my poor sister,
and I can part from him. Help me Seok.
Hae GangConnecting...
Since there is no answer, this call will be connected...
Hae GangDialing...
Hae GangConnecting...
Yes. It's me, Hae Gang.
Where are you?
Excuse me, Choi Jin Eon. It's me, Baek Seok.
Right now, this is not your deed. Is it Hae Gang's idea?
Yes. Stop calling her. You have called her too many times even just today.
Don't think about only your feelings. Think about the feelings of the other side that doesn't want to answer your calls.
Where are you now? What are you two doing, where—
What time is it now? Where are you?
Tell me quickly where you are.
That's Do Hae Gang's decision, what she is does, with whom, where.
Do Hae Gang is not your wife nor your date any more.
Hae Gang and I will decide whether she is or not.
Don't recklessly come between us. Don't carelessly act as if you know. You don't know about Hae Gang and I!
Hae Gang is my wife, and also because she is my lover,
Don't carelessly go near her.
I'm telling you not to go near that woman. Don't go near her, understand?
No. Right now, to Do Hae Gang,
you're her ex-husband—no more, no less.
Moreover, she wants to put an end even to that relationship.
Please wait until Do Hae Gang calls you. Then.
Sorry.
Don't be sorry.
"Between Calmness and Passion"
The music Jerk Do Hae Gang heard when she had a headache.
Although people can't remember everything that happens in their lives,
I believe that they will never forget what is precious to them.
The dialog in the movie Jerk Do Hae Gang liked.
The volume please.
Why aren't you drinking? Let's drink together.
It's still today, even if there are only a few minutes left.
Why can't you just say happy birthday once for me?
I want to hear that from you before today passes.
I waited all day.
I've waited days before. No— I waited four years to hear those words.
There are three minutes left. Can't you say it?
Is it your birthday?
Hae Gang. Do Hae Gang!
What are you doing here now?
Why are you being here like this?
You're acting very strange. This is going overboard. This is an overreaction!
In my eyes, you're purposely trying to avoid me.
You desperately avoid my birthday and avoid me. You seem hiding from me.
If you want to fall into expansive delusion, do so within the reasonable bounds.
So what if it's your birthday? So what about you?
Wake up. You still don't get it?
I came because I am curious about him.
I came because I was curious about the past four years after this man's tears stuck in my head.
I haven't thought of you once.
Because this person's eyes were so warm, and because his words were so comforting,
I just didn't want to go back to the hotel.
There's one minute left. Happy birthday. Happy?
I'll be going. Thank you for today.
It's late, I'll take you home.
- Would you?- Let's go.
She said she's going with me.
I'm warning you. Don't try to get between us.
I'm asking you a favor.
Don't ever lay a hand on Do Hae Gang that easily.
♫  Even though I love you and love you more  ♫
♫  my love doesn't go well like someone else ♫
♫  Even though I hate you and hate you more  ♫
♫ for me, all I need is only your love ♫
♫  Even though I love you and love you more  ♫
♫  my love doesn't go well like someone else  ♫
♫  Even though I hate you and hate you more  ♫
♫  for me, all I need is only your love  ♫
It's my birthday. Wish me Happy Birthday.
♫  If you want,  ♫
It's my birthday. Tell me happy birthday.
What about my birthday?
Spit out those words. Those are mine, so spit them out. Hurry.
What are you going to do for me? How?
On your birthday, I'll...
properly give you a birthday punch. Refreshingly.
I better learn how to fight like a boxer. Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee. Whoo, one shot!
Should I change ties? I'll change it.
♫  all I need is only your love.  ♫
Do you like it?
Yeah. Totally.
♫  My love I can't erase  ♫
♫ Only with a name called love  ♫
♫ I made you hard  ♫
It's my birthday. Wish me happy birthday.♫  I did to her  ♫
You can't delete everything.DELETE
Why is it Hae Gang?
Why are you thinking of leaving Cheon Nyeon Parmaceuticals, that's like your other self, to someone who doesn't share a drop of blood with you?
Tell me honestly because I need to see the end of this with you today.
Sit down.
Hae Gang is my friend's daughter.
What? Your friend? What friend?
Ji Hoon.
The one who died in the mountains?
The one who keeps on following you in your dreams?
Yes.
And?
Ssanghwasan was Ji Hoon's.
Ji Hoon had developed it.
And?
After he died, that Ssanghwasan,
I took it from him, claiming that I developed it first.
Like fate, Hae Gang comes to me as my daughter-in-law, and by night, that guy comes to find me.
I accepted Hae Gang as my destiny.
I was finally able to sleep again.
Jin Eon can develop medicine with Hae Gang running Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals. They can live together like that—
They already divorced. They are not related any more.
What do you mean live like that? How would they?
If Jin Eon finds out, he'll go crazy.
Why are you passing your sins onto your son?
You stretch out your legs and sleep while my son lives as a sinner beside Hae Gang forever?
No, I won't allow that.
I can't leave her by Jin Eon.
While she lives and even when she dies or returns from the dead,
she'll grab, shake, dig into, and scratch my son.
Jin Eon can't win her.
With her coldness and noxiousness, Jin Eon will get hurt again.
Even now, he's covered in scars. And Ssanghwasan on top of it?
He said that they had started over.
Since they lost each other, they would change.
Let's believe in both Jin Eon and Hae Gang.
The scar just means that the pain has passed.
It means they were healed. It means they overcame it.
Forget everything and make a decision.
Is it me or is it Hae Gang?
What?
Answer me. Is it me or is it Hae Gang?
Se Hee.
I hope my last memory
is my son's happy face.
You got rejected?
You were kicked to the curb? Right?
What kind of love is this? It's not even a roller coaster. It's already over after a few shouts.
How long had you waited in line all this time? But you're told to get off as soon as you got on.
Aren't you dizzy? And you feel like throwing up?
It's written all over your face. You look way older than me.
This is what I think, Jin Eon.
Your wife is normal and you're the one who's abnormal.
Cheating is vengeance. How is it love?
You sure do dream big. Who would understand why you are making such a fuss?
You shot the poisonous arrow first. Then you are waiting a cupid arrow in return. Does it make sense?
You're the one who's strange. Do Hae Gang is the completely normal one.
You've erred and failed.
I guess all that's left is for you to lose your mind.
I'm just saying this because I'm worried about you.
I am afraid you are jumping around like a crazy person without knowing if you are in heaven or on the earth.
Think about it. You wife is foaming at the mouth to exact revenge.
Dad tries to hand over Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals to your ex-wife who looks like a dog bone. Moreover, you are enemy—
Of course, you'd go crazy. Why wouldn't you? Why wouldn't you lose your mind?
This sister is truly worried about you, Jin Eon.
No matter how hard I think about it, Hae Gang is a swamp, where you sink down to die or become prey for a alligator.
What should we do with you?
If you've said everything you wanted to say, then leave.
As you can see, today I can't go any further.
If you stay by me, you may get struck by my wrath. So leave.
Haven't you seen this coming? You really didn't see this coming?
Of course I did. I really did.
I expected this, prepared myself, and steeled my mind, but
now that I've confronted this, right in front of my eyes, I don't know what to do at all.
So don't bother me, Noona.
So you're just going to sit there and take it?
You're going to let your position and Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals be taken away from you?
Let's join forces. Be on my side.
Let's block her from getting the company, together.
You must hate it as much as me.
Is she a salmon? Why does she come back? Who is waiting for her?
You should have just left her to become the daughter-in-law of the dumpling family. Why poke at someone who was living happily and cause this mess?
You're the stupid one.
You're the one who dug this all up.
When she was with the dumpling house family, she looked happy. She looked human.
If you had left her to get married to Kang Seol Ri's brother, she'd have been happy and we'd have been happy.
It wasn't going to work out anyway.
You ruined it all. Your selfish love for her is ruining you both. Do you know that, Jin Eon?
Get out.
I said get out.
Noona!
Didn't you hear me?
Get out. Get out!
I-I hear you.
I'll leave. I'm leaving right now.
But you know what?
Do Hae Gang threw you away to Seol Ri.
Since she threw you away, she told me to come clear you away from her sight.
It's not like you're garbage, to pick up or clear away. That girl, sheesh!
Let's meet today. I got what you asked for.
Wow... Already?
How? It hasn't been very long since we last met.
I don't think Dokgo Yong Gi would have given it to you easily.
You're not a close family, you're practically strangers.
Did your sister really give it to you? What does she trust about you?
I stole it without her knowing.
Her luggage's passcode was pathetically her birthday. She doesn't know.
Wow. Of course!
You did well.
Choi Jin Eon's position... I mean get my position ready immediately.
I always keep the bullets loaded in the gun. So don't worry about it.
Aren't you going to regret this?
Are you sure you won't regret this later, Lawyer Do?
I feel like I throw the naive and innocent brother-in-law into the dirty and sinful bog.
I already regret too much.
Okay. I'll be at the office after 2, so I"ll see you there.
I will meet with you later.
Daily Notes for Research of Developing a New DrugNew Drug: PudoxinResercher: Kim Sun Yong
I will trust her for now and suspect her later.
I will be able to see her next move only if I trust her for now.
I will find out if she's fake or real along the way.
You're saying that she really asked for that position, kicking out Jin Eon?
Yes, she even said to make up some wrongdoing to kick out...
She is sinister and cruel.
How do you try to hand over Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals to such a vicious and dirty devil person?
It doesn't make sense. It makes no sense, Dad.
I will confirm with Hae Gang.
You do that for sure.
Do Hae Gang is coming to take revenge on Jin Eon.
Jin Eon is getting much more of punishment from her than what he gave to her.
She's not someone who would do that. Even when they separated, she said they were not over.
She said Jin Eon would return to her and that she would wait.
I trust Hae Gang.
Father and son are the same. How don't you have any keen eye for a woman?
You are being deceived by her. Both you and Jin Eon are being deceived by Do Hae Gang. Ahh, it's so frustrating.
What she does as soon as she's alive, as soon as she comes back?
She's a monster, Dad. She's the devil, Satan.
Please get a hold of yourself!
Ah, seriously! Why isn't it here? Why?
No. Come out. Come out. Hurry, please come out!
Woo Joo, haven't you seen the yellow envelope in my bag?
Come and eat! Woo Joo, hold your mom's hand and come out quickly!
Excuse me, excuse me. Did you touch my belongings by any chance?
What do you mean?
My luggage! Did you go through it?
What? No, I didn't. Why would I go through your things without your permission?
Because... Because...
Why? What disappeared?
- You really didn't go through my things, right?  - No.
Then who would have?
Eesh!
Woo Joo, why is your mom like that?
What on earth did she lose so she is restless and so irritated?
Can't you knock?
My mind is in hurry. My mind is burning fully like a live volcano right now. The moment you flashed on my head,
my mind is boiling like the hot lava.
That's none of my business. As what you said, I am just a yellowish flesh.
Forget it. You must forget about it quickly, Miss Dokgo Yong Gi.
What is none of my business? You told me to trust you. You said "Let's live together"!
You told me to stay next to that yellowish flesh.
What's your reason? What's your motive? What are you plotting?
Tell me honestly!
I am worried about you, Miss Dokgo Yong Gi.
I got to like Dokgo Woo Joo. Yong Gi and Woo Joo are the words I think about the most,
with a bad feeling toward the former (Yong Gi) and with a good feeling toward the latter (Woo Joo).
That's my reason, my motive, and my plot, Miss Dokgo Yong Gi.
Didn't you take an international airmailed envelope from my luggage?
With what motive would I take that?
That's because... Because—
Because... Follow that line of thought to the end.
Your brother! To bring it to Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals.
So you're saying the contents of that envelope is related to Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals?
Such as the whistle blowing contents, right? Didn't you lock the trunk?
Of course I locked it.
Then someone unlocked the passcode and took it. What's your passcode?
My birthday.
Then the culprit must be someone who knows your birthday.
Well, if someone wants to know my birthday, isn't it easy to find out? Especially if I'm being played with?
I will meet with my brother.
Woo Joo, your mom will be in danger if she has this.
Will bad guys come looking for us again?
That's why your aunt needs to take it.
Can you keep this a secret from your mom?
And from other people, too.
You have to keep this secret.
Promise.
Check it.
We could make the video clip be copied. But the daily notes were hand-written.
It explains why you risk your life for Kim Sun Yong's daily notes.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Does your sister also know that the lawyer who represented our company for Kim Sun Yong's suit was you, Lawyer Do?
That's why she loathes me. She said she would pay back.
To catch me and President Min Tae Seok.
So how are you thinking of blocking your sister this time?
Let's first hear how you plan to get rid of Choi Jin Eon.
This device of blocking wiretap costs ₩ 30 million. At time like this, I realize you are really a Chaebol (tycoon).
I am overawed by you as much as I can't stand this punk.
Did you receive several billion won worth of stocks since 6 or 7 years old and
make them swell out to the several ten billion won in 10 years?
Probably.
Ah, Damn!
Hey, Chaebol (rich kid), what do you guys live for?
What do you pour yourself into, when you already have and have gained everything?
We live by pouring ourselves into fighting each other.
Looking at each other's weaknesses, we live leaning on one another's weaknesses.
What?
This is my brother-in-law's paper company that is in Cayman Islands.
Let's hit him with this. He has several tens of the borrowed-name bank accounts.
Wow, he sure did put away a lot. It's a good thing we did this hacking.
All of President Min Tae Seok's weaknesses are now in your hands, how can he get rid of you?
He's the one about to go, and Hae Gang has no clue whatsoever.
But isn't Hae Gang going overboard?
Even reporting you to the police. It appears she's determined to humiliate you.
It looks like a dog fight here on out between you two.
Let's just brush ourselves off and leave them to go after each other.
Let's pack our things and just go to the research department.
You and Hae Gang have seen all each other, but this kind of dog fight,
this really isn't right, Jin Eon.
It's not just your love, but your souls that can be ruined.
Even if people can't remember everything that happens in their lives,
I believe that they will never forget what is truly precious.
What?
This is the dialog in the movie we watched together in 2003, Autumn. Our favorite dialog.
Even if she loses her memory, even if the worst of her memories comes back,
I believe that she will never have forgotten what is precious.
Later, after a long time has passed...
In order for this painful period to remain as a precious memory,
I have no choice but to fight now. I just have to win.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
If I win,
I filled some money in brother-in-law account. Tomorrow, the audit will be conducted.
Next week, we will call the board meeting. Within this month we can get rid of him at the extraordinary general meeting.
You well know this isn't even work.
Let's keep this in the rental safety box.
Or we can keep it in a safe where it requires two keys to open.
From my perspective, if this gets incinerated,
I lose my card that guarantees my sister's security.
I can secure it in a safe, but I can't turn it over to you.
Let's prepare a safe, that nobody can't open unless together.
That sounds great.
You can keep the USB. I have a copy.
How do you plan to keep your sister's mouth shut?
Will it suffice to send her abroad?
It'll be difficult for me to do more than that because she is my bloody sister, no matter what.
Make sure to send her away. She must leave, if not,
That's right.
This was with me.
Why does it all rest on my doing?
Why is my name in every place that Min Tae Seok's name should be?
After making me dead, you did posthumous execution with the dead one.
You comforted my mother every year on the anniversary of my death.
How did you come to that?
Even four years ago, you acted humanely even though you were incompetent.
Give me all of the materials you put on my name.
Otherwise, I will make this matter issued.
The fax you asked me to find out,
It's come from a neighborhood stationary store. This is an address and telephone number.
And look into every CCTV within 1 km of radius.
Ah, yes. I got it.
Excuse me, President. Your wife...
Managing Director Do Hae Gang is over in that office.
What is his wife? That person has never lived a minute as his wife.
Let's go.
Let's go eat.
What? Just like that? You don't need to see her? You can't do that?
Let's go.
Okay.
Hae Gang.
Hello.
Jin Eon went over there.
You look better in lab coats than what you're wearing now. Both of you.
Oh, really? I have some things to discuss, would you like to have lunch?
What do you have to discuss with me?
Let's talk while we eat. Let's go.
Multiple... Multiple personality?
Who? Ah, Manager Go?
No.
Do Hae Gang. How many faces does she have?
I'm not sure which direction I'm supposed to dance. It's so hard.
We're having lunch with Hae Gang.
-Did you tell her I was coming too?-No.
Ask her again.
Actually I have him too. Can I bring my attachment?
If you mind at all, like an Arabian,
I'll put a black Keffiyeh and make him sit quietly next to me.
You just think you brought Lawyer Do's horse that you raise at home.
You, two eat together. I'll pass.
No, you can't do that. If you received the birthday present, you have to pay back of it.
Have some conscious, you idiotic rich punk.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
I'll call Japanese restaurant at Hal Ra Hotel and you go there.
You're not going?
No. Eat comfortably.
Can't he be forgiven forever if he made one mistake?
We're not God, we're human.
As humans we should let things slide, and forgive each other by giving a few of hits on the cheeks.
There is no such thing as a perfect person or a perfect love.
People fill each other's hole.
There is a song called "Bridge Over Troubled Water"
♫ My heart is closed and I'm living like a fool ♫
♫ Memories of when I loved you ♫
♫ Are locked deep within the corners of my heart ♫
♫ Countless days have passed us by ♫
♫ Just like that day ♫
♫ You are here looking at me  ♫
♫ Even if we are far apart ♫
♫ Even if everything changes ♫
♫ My heart will withstand time ♫
Go! I said go already!
♫ And it will stay right here  ♫
If while studying, I forget and end up dating someone,
It would probably be you.
If I fail the bar examination in a very rare chance and go crazy,
and end up drinking all night with someone, that would probably be you.
If I end up thinking about someone for just a moment while studying,
it would probably be you.
If I miss a person as staying in this room by any chance,
Because my life, Do Hae Gang's life, is probably all yours, Choi Jin Eon's.
Can you back off from it? Back off while I'm telling you.
I really have to study, Choi Jin Eon.
I trust you. You who had twinkling and blinding eyes.
Our time and our memory,
I trust you, Hae Gang.
That you'll never forget it was precious,
I trust you, Do Hae Gang.
♫ Even if we are far apart ♫
♫ Even if everything changes ♫
♫ My heart will withstand time ♫
♫ And it will stay right here  ♫
I won't forget.
The time we spent together...
Our memories...
I'll forever and preciously hold onto them.
Choi Jin Eon.♫ Even if we can never meet again ♫
♫ Even if everything changes ♫
♫ My heart won't ever forget your smile ♫
♫ And it will remain the same ♫
It'll take about 2 hours and 10 minutes so it'll be best for you to take a nap, Dokgo Woo Joo.
Dokgo Yong Gi, you should go work. I'll bring her when it's finished.
Close your eyes and sleep, Dokgo Woo Joo.
But I don't feel sleepy, Doctor.
My heart won't stop racing.
Can you sing me a lullaby to help me fall asleep, Doctor?
A lullaby?
My heart keeps thumping.
Alright, I'll sing. Close your eyes, Woo Joo.
♫ Everytime I ask you when, how and where
♫ You only answer perhaps, perhaps, perhaps
♫ And days pass like this me, growing desperate
♫ And you, you always answer, perhaps, perhaps, perhaps
♫ You are wasting time thinking, thinking
Did you take Dokgo Yong Gi's belongings, Hyung?
I'm coming to get it, so return it if you took it. I'll be there by 4.
I really, really love you ♡Yong Gi Unni
You can't compare to me, Kang Seol Ri.
Even if I died, even if I became a different person,
even if I lost my memory, you have never once won over me.
Do you know why? It's because you've never had that man.
Because you have never received that man's love even once. You just keep hoping.
You alone call that love. You call that kind of thing, love.
You are just stubbornly insisting it, understand?
Just stop.
I'll clean this room for you so you should stay out.
No. I'll do it.
I will throw it myself. I'll throw it all away.
Why would you throw it away? You can give it to the people who need it.
I don't want that.
I want to burn this, Dad. I have to.
With my own hands, all of this.
Without leaving out a thing, I'm going to burn it all.
Fine, burn it.
Burn it all without leaving a thing. But then it has to be over. Today has to be the end.
Don't only burn the stuff,
but burn that heart, alright?
Seol Ri unni.
Oh, Baek Joo.
Dad said that you would come. You really came.
Are you going to live with us now?
Yeah.
You're not going to go anywhere, right?
You're not going to leave us, right?
Yeah.
Who needs Yong Gi unni?
We also don't need someone like her.
She said she forgot us. She forgot everything.
She said she doesn't even know who we are.
Does that make any sense? I've forgotten her, too.
We, too, have forgotten Yong Gi Unnie.
Seol Ri unni, really. I'm being honest.
Unni.
Yong Gi unni.
Unni!
Unni, unni!
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
CN-B12Kang Seol Ri (870406)
Clinical Study of CN-B12Kang Seol Ri (870406)Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals
List of Pudoxin Clinical Study Participants.Cheon Nyeon
List of 3rd Phase Clinical Trial Contributors for Pudoxin.F-1444/ Kang Seol Ri / 25 yrs old
Yes, Fath— Chairman.
Let's have dinner. Come to the house. I also have something to confirm.
I'm uncomfortable going to the house, Chairman. Let's eat out.
I'm telling you to come to the house to make you uncomfortable, so don't say anything and come.
I'll see you at the house.
I just heard my embezzlement from the audit department, Brother-in-law.
You know it isn't what I want.
At my position, it's hard to reject Lawyer Do's request.
I have to survive, too.
Even right now, if you're willing to accept the Chief Researcher position at the Central Research Department, I'll let the audit stop.
Even though you lose your face a little bit, you won't lose your face completely.
Let's try to make you retire from this position gracefully.
I think you and Hae Gang both think of me as too easy.
Why do you think I'll just sit by and take it?
Why don't you think I might strike you first?
Strike me? You, Brother-in-law?
How? What can you do?
TY Resourse & Investment
I'm not going to the auditors, I'm going straight to the prosecutors.
Foreign Remittance Bank Accounts Inquiry
How did you... How did you get this?!
I was behind the hacking.
What?
I am holding your lifeline, not Hae Gang.
My hands, these hands, can do everything.
And on top of it, it's too easy.
If I press a mouse, it'll be over.
I'm going to keep my position. I'm not going anywhere.
Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals isn't going to you or Hae Gang. I'm going to do it. I will get it.
So don't bring Hae Gang into the company.
Having her re-enter the company, you block it from happening. You have to without fail.
Then I'll keep you from crying in embarrassment before the prosecutors.
I'll allow you to keep your face and sitting in this position. I will.
Since I have a lot of hidden cards, I can get rid of you at any time.
Well, how may we help you today?
I'm here to see President Min Tae Seok.
Ah, you're the younger brother? I received word from downstairs.
Please wait a moment.
Yes, President, your younger brother is here.
Please stop.
Yes.
He said to come in.
My younger brother is here.
Please leave us.
I'll be awaiting your reply.
Pororo Ahjussi.
Woo Joo, Woo Joo.
It's been long.
Yes.
I'll keep Woo Joo while your speaking with your brother.
Please call me when you're finished talking.
Will Miss Dokgo Woo Joo play with Mr. Pororo for a little while?
Do you remember this Ahjussi?
It's Hyung.
My Hyung.
He's a good brother.
Like your mother did, he raised me.
If I didn't have my brother, I wouldn't be here either.
Please greet my brother before you go.
Hello.
Goodbye.
This is really good, but why aren't you eating?
Just watching you eat is much more enjoyable.
It's so sweet just watching you.
This is a secret that I'm only telling you,
but lately I've been so sad. And I got the horns grown (get angry).
But, when I see you, my horns melt away in my eyes
and the sadness in my heart has melted. It's all gone, because you're so lovely.
My mom says that too.
Just watching me, she says she melts.
It all melts away.
Did you meet your aunt?
Oh, the really pretty lady who looks just like your mom.
Did you speak with her, too?
She doesn't like me.
What?
"Aren't you going away? Get out, now!"
That's what she shouted to me.
Do you know who that Ahjumma is?
I know her better than anyone in the world.
Then, is she a good lady or bad lady?
Of course, she's a very good lady.
She is Mom's sister and your aunt.
Then does she keep promises well?
Did you make a promise with your aunt?
What kind of promise?
It's not me, it's really not me.
Then who is it?
You know. That's why you're not surprised or curious.
Who is it, tell me.
Her twin sister.
Who?
Do Hae Gang.
Her birthday
What kind of promise did you make with your aunt? You're not going to tell me?
She must have told you not to tell anyone.
Please tell her to quietly return the property Do Hae Gang took from Dokgo Yong Gi without her knowing.
Pardon?
Property taken without her knowledge?
Doctor, you know, too?
Oh, but it was a secret?
Please tell me in detail what she has to return,
that's how even I can return it.
Do Hae Gang took the whistle-blowing video clip and the daily notes of Kim Sun Yong's Pudoxin research secretly.
Pardon? What did you say?
- This is for you.- Thank you.
Thank you for the flowers.
Did you tell me to buy them on purpose for Choi Jin Eon to see?
Yeah.
If he sees you coming here, we should appear as if we're dating.
I'm okay with dating.
To appear real, it's better to do a real date.
Was Mon Tae Joon's lawsuit turned over his mother?
Yeah.
Here. These are the documents on the people who participated in the Pudoxin clinical trials.
Let's divide and meet these people on this list and check their side effects shown.
Let's warn them the possibility of danger and lead them to the class action suit.
Wow, how did these documents...?
4 years ago, I save this document because of Kang Seol Ri.
What?
Kang Seol Ri also participated in the clinical trials of Pudoxin.
What did you say?
Keep our names out of it and take her to the hospital to get tested for the bone density.
It might be nothing, but just in case.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Preview
I have another man, Mother-in-law.
-What?-Your son is like a leech.
Really?
I'm going to go crazy because of you!
You have no shame, just what are you doing?
Do you really want to see me go insane?
We decided to start from today.
What?
Not Hae Gang, give your seat to me. I'll do it, Father.
It isn't Jin Eon, it's you I'm throwing away. There's no need to return to the company.
You say you'll win over me?
Yeah, I'm going to win over you, Hae Gang.
Okay, let's see.