Episode 36
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Why aren't you asking why I came here?
Because it appears you aren't here to see me.
Then, whom do you think I came here to meet?
I don't care, so there's no need to tell me.
It doesn't matter whomever I meet?
As long as it isn't me.
I sent Mido's CEO to you.
I even went to see him at the prison the day he was released.
And I sent the fax to Jin Eon.
Because I thought he should know those awful things that you did.
The counteracting strategy against the lawsuit of the patient infringement of Mi Do Pharmaceuticals,
do you remember now?
That horrible document that you created.
You did unnecessary work again.
He already knows about it.
He had already known about it.
I think we'll have to wait and see if it was unnecessary work or not.
I turned it over to Shin Il Sang, you see.
-What?-This time I'll become the thorn in your side.
I'll become a useless stone that rolls around in those expensive shoes.
I let everything go.
I let Sunbae go, I let myself go, completely.
Since I have nothing to guard, it's freeing and nice.
Like you said, the two of us aren't finished yet.
I'm not trying to see the end where I get Sunbae.
The end of you and me, whether your wrongdoing or my wrongdoing is bigger.
That's the end that I want to see.
Do Hae Gang, based on how much wrong we did,
let's receive our punishment, okay?
Knock, knock.
I saw you leaving for the day, did you come back?
Yeah, I had a guest.
-Your guest?-Just left now.
-Please give it to me-No, no, no.
Today accept from me first.
Why? What is it, Brother-in-law?
My father. What is my father
hiding from me, Brother-in-law?
That climbing accident where two went and only one returned,
is what my father saying all there is?
Brother-in-law,
Only Father-in-law knows the truth.
If he killed his friend,
or if he watched his friend die.
Only Father-in-law knows the truth, Brother-in-law.
However, there is a certain truth that I know.
It's that Father-in-law stole Ssanghwasan that his friend had developed.
The very next day after his friend died.
Whether he really killed Vice Chairman Do Hae Gang's father in the mountain without anyone knowing or not,
he did steal and start Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals with Ssanghwasan that Attorney Do's father developed with blood and sweat.
That's how our company started.
Although it is terribly painful, we have to know that way, Brother-in-law.
Did you know about the falsified reports? Did you know but keep your ears and mouth shut?
That's right.
I knew, but kept my ears and mouth shut.
For the company's sake. Because it was for your father's company.
From the opening day of the new year, President Min's subordinates,
cut them out one by one.
So, you want to become a hunting dog at Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals, again?
The sin that becomes a part of daily life.
The sin, that you choose and commit on purpose,
is the heaviest.
Who is it?
Come out. Come out I said.
I'll go up against you if you want, so come out. Come out I said!
Even knowing everything,
you were still thinking of starting over with me?
There is nothing I can't do for you.
Whether you permit me to or not,
there is only your decision left.
How is that possible?
What is this, without any notice?
I needed a drinking buddy.
Really? There's a drinker here, so have a seat.
Is your forehead okay?
You weren't worried about me, but you came because you were worried about him, didn't you?
-Sorry-You're not sorry.
Just hand over the beer. I was in the middle of thinking if I needed to go buy some when it's so cold out.
Here.
Since we don't talk about work, there's nothing to talk about, right?
If there's nothing to say, then let's just drink beer. Here, cheers.
Why don't you ask me what I did today?
What did you do today?
I went to get some air at Imjingang Station.
Yeah?
If you get frustrated, go there, too. It helps clear your eyes and head.
I was getting frustrated myself, that's good. I'll make sure to go tomorrow.
Don't just drink, eat something, too.
I'm fine.
If you eat that, I'll return the Pancillate Monodiplan to you.
What did you just say?
I said if you deliciously eat a piece of pufferfish I gave you, I'll return the medicine that Cheon Nyeon took from you.
Why?
Are you trying to kill me with the pufferfish poison?
It's said that the Tetrodotoxin from one pufferfish can kill more than 30 people.
Do you know one of the pharmaceuticals in Japan is developing the pain medicine from this pufferfish poison?
If you use the poison well, you can turn it to the medicine.
Have some. It'll make the pain, you are suffering right now, disappear.
Don't beat around the bush. Just get to your point.
What do you want from me?
I have to know what game this is, to decide if I'm in or out.
Please put Do Hae Gang and Chairman Choi Man Ho in jail.
Someone, that is holding my flaw, asked me to ruin Do Hae Gang.
When I thought about it, if I held hands with you,
I realized I could get Chairman Choi Man Ho as well at the same time.
Do Hae Gang is just a hunting dog.
It was Do Hae Gang who grabbed Mi Do Pharmaceuticals but the person who swallowed it was Chairman Choi Man Ho.
On the outside, it looks like Do Hae Gang did, but isn't Chairman the one who orchestrated it from behind?
Is there a prosecutor you know? I'll go to the prosecutor tomorrow.
It's useless you send the anonymous letters even 100 times.
I can introduce you to a prosecutor anytime. Just start by getting evidence that Choi Man Ho was behind it.
From the Mi Do Pharmaceuticals researchers who took money from Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals,
or from the patient examiners, you try to make any witness.
You also listen to the story of the researcher side, who committed suicide by jumping from the building.
Weren't those employees that you spent decades with, like family?
I'm sure they run out of the money they got. And if they have a conscience, give them a chance to use that conscience.
I will support you more than enough.
Put Do Hae Gang and Choi Man Ho in jail?
I'll get Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals and you'll get your medicine back.
And someone else will get revenge on Do Hae Gang.
And another someone else will self-destruct because of Do Hae Gang and Choi Man Ho.
Cha Do Murder! It means to borrow someone else's sword and kill the enemy. It comes from The Art of War.
Thanks to you, it looks like I'll be wiping my nose without lifting a finger.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Today. Just today.
Because it's Christmas.
I don't like it.
Because Christmas comes every year.
Because they exist until I die.
I don't like being like this only today.
You lost again. How can you lose every day?
Hey, if you lose the lawsuit.
I won't lose. I won't ever lose.
Even if I lose to drinking, I'll never lose the lawsuit.
Why? Because I'm your hope.
Right?
Yeah, you're my hope. Baek Seok is my hope.
My feet are comfortable, my eyes are comfortable, and my heart is comfortable.
It seems your heart is very uncomfortable today.
I'm really comfortable right now.
You're really not comfortable right now.
Why do you think?
It's because you're not doing your punishment.
Stop dragging it out, and hurry up and do it. Quickly.
What's my punishment? Go out like this in the cold?
Well, I'll let it go with a song.
Sing me a song. Here, mic.
♫ I wept tears hanging around beyond eye-shots of others,  ♫
♫  for days gone by pierced me to the heart. ♫
♫ Lights getting turned on under empty sky,  ♫
♫  I try calling charily the name of old love. ♫
♫ While I turn up my collar against cold wind,  ♫
♫  tears of regret and anger flow.  ♫
♫  If anybody asked me, my days gone by  ♫
♫ seemed not to hurt me but that was all lies.  ♫
♫ Now what I've missed,  ♫
♫ I'll let it stay as is in my mind.  ♫
♫ when you come to my mind  ♫
♫  as I let it be  ♫
♫  Wandering on hill as white snow is scattered, ♫
♫  I come to the street by the thought of old love.  ♫
♫  While Kwanghwamun street is being covered by white snow, ♫
♫ white snow is going up to the sky again and again.  ♫
♫  Now what I've missed,  ♫
♫  I'll let it stay as is in my mind.  ♫
♫ when you come to my mind  ♫
♫  as I let it be  ♫
♫ Sometimes love gets me tired,  ♫
♫  for that loneliness is so overflowed in my heart. ♫
Don't come.
Don't come closer.
Hurry up and go inside, Do Hae Gang.
♫ old love - your appearance resides in eternity.  ♫
Don't come?
Who's the one who came? You came here.
This is my house you know.
My house.
♫ street is being covered by white snow,  ♫
♫ and white snow is going up to the sky again and again.  ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Only Father-in-law knows the truth. If he killed his friend,
or if he watched his friend die.
However, there is a certain truth that I know.
It's that Father-in-law stole Ssanghwasan that his friend had developed.
The very next day after his friend died.
♫ My heart is closed and I'm living like a fool ♫
♫ Memories of when I loved you ♫♫ Are locked deep within the corners of my heart ♫
♫ Countless days have passed us by ♫
♫ Just like that day ♫ ♫ You are here looking at me  ♫
♫ Even if we are far apart ♫
♫ Even if everything changes ♫
♫ My heart will withstand time ♫ ♫ And it will stay right here  ♫
Don't come. Don't come closer.
Why is it so quiet? Did everyone go somewhere?
To go sledding.
Huh? By themselves?
There's a tiny one that opened nearby.
To make a little of money from kids, they put a few of red plastic basins as sleds and sell the snacks.
It's break, should we take the kids somewhere nearby?
Even if we can't take them on oversea trips like others, if we let them free in the hot springs, they will have fun playing all day long.
I'll schedule something and take them, you just concentrate on the trial. I can't sleep.
I am disgusted and losing my temper.
It's the <1% that's ruining this world.
They don't have any conscience nor common sense.
They have just a full of greed.
Even though they had 10, they wanted to have 11.
How did they do such a crazy thing? Heavens!
There's no end to a person's greed.
Hey kid, by you acknowledging it like that, they, with the endless greed, don't know how the people are scary.
And also, how can you say they are human beings? They're animals!
No, the animals who hear that would get upset. Animals only take what they need for their existence.
They don't make storage bins or sheds to store the carcass up to rot.
Wow, our father is really angry. I get it, I'll make sure to win.
I have to win, Father. I promised that I would win.
With whom?
Someone. To someone who wants me to win more than anyone.
Are you going to have the first trial, today?
Yeah.
How are you going to win? Do you have a way to win?
Lawsuits involving drug side effects are hard to win even in the U.S. How are you going to prove the side effects?
Even though there are the supporting research papers, those are only a few.
If I go with the legal principle way, I'll lose 100%.
We have to fight using unequivocal witnesses or evidence.
Unequivocal witnesses or evidence?
What are you going to do if Dokgo Yong Gi's memory returns?
Fabricating Pudoxin's clinical test results, Kim Sun Yong's death, and even the video you made! That wench knows everything! She knows about everything!
The last person Do Hae Gang met before she died was that wench, Dokgo Yong Gi!
I'm coming in!
Oh, come in, Oppa!
What did the doctor say about the tests?
"Our bone is composed of cortical bone (compact bone) at the outer surface and cancellous bone (trabecular or spongy bone) at the inner layer, Patient."
" In your situation... Hmm... the cortical bone has dramatically gotten thin compared to the regular people."
"Even if the bone fracture happens at any time,... Hmm, hmm...  we won't consider it's a strange case at all."
It's the first time I realized the word of the regular people is so important.
I have been striving to become a special one for 29 years.
My striving is useless now.
What about medicine?
For now, I just got a prescription for the oral calcium.
Saying they'll prescribe the proper medicine once the cause is discovered.
Although, I already know the cause.
Seol Ri, get treated and be careful,
and confidently take each day by day.
So you don't fall physically or mentally,
I'll always hold onto your hand tightly.
And with your other hand, you'll hold Do Hae Gang's hand?
What?
Between Do Hae Gang and me, if you have to let go of one hand, whose hand will you let go?
Think carefully starting today, if you'll let go of my hand or of Do Hae Gang's hand.
Seol Ri,
If the three of us were standing at the edge of a cliff,
think about whose hand you would let go of to have fall off the cliff.
What nonsense? I wouldn't bring you to a cliff in the first place. I'd take you to the prairie.
Do well today. Don't be pushed down or shoved by Do Hae Gang.
You must get a head start from the beginning. Understand?
What? Jin Eon knew about it?
Yeah, he asked so I told him.
Why is it so quiet then? Is a bomb about to explode or what?
He isn't going to start moving after just my words. He'll probably start by trying to confirm it.
How will he confirm something from over thirty years ago?
I don't know about Do Hae Gang's father's death,
but about Ssanghwasan, if you just check its patent registration through the internet,
you'll be able to know right away that Father-in-law stole it.
He'll probably go crazy. It'll probably make him jump up and down going crazy.
With Brother-in-law's personality, he'll probably want to die.
Or to kill him.
What a life his is! This is not about a suffering life with Do Hae Gang.
A life with full of ups and owns! A life that went until gone! How come his tragedy doesn't end?
That is because he has a good father.
The price he was born with holding several 100 billion won worth of the gold flatware!
You can be happy with a few of tens thousand won but you have a lot of tragedy with several 10 or 100 billion won.
How will Jin Eon act now, Honey?
He'll either destruct himself alone or destruct with Father-in-law together.
Well, it's probably either one of those.
Master Register Issued Patent
Owner of Registration: Dokgo Ji Hoon
Registered May 10, 1981
Transferred to Choi Man Ho on May 16, 1981
It means he stole Ssanghwasan that his friend had developed.
The very next day after his friend died.
Based on a witness statement of the latter climber falling as the rope breaking down, the police is investigating the exact cause...
Gosh, this world, we can buy the tickets just sitting here.
That's right. We can even select our seats.
It's worth living long to see, no matter what.
Let's see.
Oh, how about Himalayas. Hwang Jung Min appears in it.
Let's watch  Inside Men. Lee Byung Hun and Jo Seung Woo appear.
I like Hwang Jung Min better.
What is it about?
What is this? To find his colleague's corpse, who died in an accident during climbing,
they start a new life of journey risking their own life...
That's enough. I don't like it because it reminds me of your close childhood friend.
How does the subject leap to that way?
I want to finally see a movie with you after thirty, forty years.
That's what I mean, we are finally watching a movie after thirty, forty years,
I don't want to watch it thinking of Hae Gang's father.
You say that now, but while watching the movie, I'm sure you'll think of your friend who died in the mountains.
What is that? To go ruin your mood at a theater.
I didn't think about that.
Until you mentioned it,
I didn't think about it.
Watch that movie with me, Father.
And watch a movie that Mom wants to see today.
What? You're going to watch a movie with your dad? You?
I'll check the schedule and buy the tickets.
Oh, okay.
Then, I'll be back.
I'll be back.
Okay, drive carefully.
That's why I told you to use a driver, it worries me.
I'll be careful. I'll call you later, so come out around the time of my getting off work.
Go on a date with your son.
Today? I can't today, the advertiseme... oh.
I have plans.
Really? Then let's go another day.
Okay. Hey, Son. Keep your word.
If you stand me up, you're dead.
Okay, I'll be back. Bye.
The other tires were fine, so i just changed the left front.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Your car key.
-Thank you.-Take care.
Don't put one on my car.
You should greet me.
How can you hold your head upright after seeing a superior?
Of course, I am and it's better we keep business and private matters strictly apart.
Why are you looking agai...
I'll go in first.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Is something the matter?
What's wrong? What is it?
Something bad happened, didn't it?
What is it that... tell me, hurry.
Should we go live abroad?
What did you say?
Far away. As far away as possible, just the two of us.
Galapagos, yeah, let's go live there.
There are many more turtles and iguanas there than people.
We can stay in island and then buy a yacht and go out on the sea sometimes and eat and sleep,
dolphins and sea turtles will pass by in front of us.
Do you want to go?
What's wrong?
What is it? Huh?
I'll make you happy.
Happy every single day, happy every moment.
Let's go, Hae Gang. Let's leave.
Let's first go to work, go up and work.
Let's talk after work whatever it's about.
Let's go upstairs.
♫  Even though you love me and love me more  ♫
♫  my love doesn't go well like someone else ♫
♫  Even though I hate you and hate you more  ♫
♫ for me, all I need is only your love ♫
Which courtroom is it at 3:00?
Oh, courtroom 15.
Are you planning to come?
It'll make you uneasy if you watch, will you be alright?
Why? Because of the other side's attorney?
If nothing else, I want to hear what she has to say,
I want to hear clearly what she has to say, that's why I want to go.
What is she going to flap her lips about with the opened mouth?
Okay, you're going to be a witness anyway, so come watch.
But don't forget that what you see isn't all there is.
I'm going to do whatever it takes
to get the journal and memos from her and give them to you.
If you only had the memos that he left, you'll be able to win this case.
I have the memos and the journal.
What?
I have a copy of the journal and the originals of the memos.
Wait, how did those...?
That's what I mean, how would I have those?
You can't ever say anything about those memos, Yong Gi. Nobody can know about those.
Oh, I understand.
Ong Gi is lonely fighting by herself as a lawyer Do Hae Gang right now.
For your sake. To set things right.
I can't, so come cheer her on.
Why aren't you opening it, I'm freezing to death.
Isn't anyone there? Open up, quickly! Hurry!
Oh my, you came?
I was in the middle of making handcut noodles, so my appearance is a bit...
First, come sit, over here.
Let's sit together, as I have something to say to you.
Then please go to the kitchen.
I have to feed our Kyu Seok at 12:00 so I don't have a moment to sit.
It's his day off so I have to take care of three meals. Really.
Wh-what? Kyu Seok?
Who are you calling your Kyu Seok? Who are you calling Kyu Seok?
Are you out of your mind? Can't you really distinguish between heaven and earth?
By any chance, do you have an anger disorder?
Oh my gosh, why are you so angry?
I see, I'll call him Doctor. Then will that make you feel a little better?
Wh-wh-wh-what?
I'll just go finish what I was doing. Breathe deeply.
Doctor.
Can't we do that date thing again?
Woo Joo, are you being angry with me right now?
Why? What is making you angry?
Doctor is not looking at me and only looking at books,
so it makes me feel mad.
In any case, I can't just look at your face all day long.
Do you like books that much?
That's true. I like books.
Do you like them more than me?
About ten of them.
There are about ten books that I like more than you.
But out of people, I like you the best.
Are you disappointed in me?
If you're that disappointed and angry,
then find ten books that you like more than me.
Then our hearts will become alike in what we like.
Would you go to the bookstore with me?
Let's go. To buy ten books that you like more than me.
So, you don't have any thoughts of ending or breaking up?
No.
But, would you like some handcut noodles before you go?
If you would like to eat, I'll have to make some more dough, you see.
You're a child's mother.
Ah. We'll just eat then.
You're a single mother, you are. Know your place, your place.
Is that all?
Your daughter is an incurable disease patient.
A patient who can't be cured even if she's treated her whole life.
How could you bring such a child to our brother-in-law... Does that make sense to you?
Your daughter's illness, you should know it's genetic.
I don't know if you gave her the illness or her father did, but don't bring it into our house.
Whether it makes sense or not, I'll show you by living it out, Sister-in-law.
Wh-wh-what? Sister-in-law?
How do you get off...
Say it again. Say it again.
Excuse me?
-Sister-in-law!-Ahh!
I'll live nicely, Sister-in-law.
As nicely as you and Brother-in-law worry about it, more nicely and more happily, we'll live.
Sister-in-law, I know I can do it.
As you say,
I'm a child's mother, a single mother, and my child is sick.
But if our Kyu Seok likes me,
how can I refuse him in my situation?
I'll have to make an effort and grab hold of it.
I will really do well, Sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law!
B-b-brother-in-law.
Make the dough again.
Make the dough again so the three of us can eat handcut noodles!
What are you doing? Make the dough again, Sister-in-law.
You can't step one foot outside until you make us new handcut noodles to eat.
Wh-wh-what did you say?
Here's the flour and water. And plastic gloves.
Put the flour and the water and make the dough nice and chewy!
Sister-in-law!
What is this? That person, why is she doing that in my kitchen?
That's what I mean.
She must really be afraid of her younger brother-in-law.
Restructuring?
Are you preparing restructuring without my knowledge?
Chairman ordered it.
He and Vice Chairman, excluding the company representative, only two made a decision that would stir a whole group?
Chairman decided it on his own. I only received the orders.
He tries to alienate you and me to each other.
He is really cunning. He meant to not make you and me the same side.
In any case,
it looks like you're going to hear the weeping sound as soon as you're seated. Will you be okay?
From the beginning of new year, if restructuring is heard, besides the employee will resist, it'll affect the stock price.
Let's hold a funeral (restructuring) when the weather is warm, Vice Chairman Do.
No,
The restructuring isn't of the employees, it's of the management.
What did you say?
Who is getting cut?
When you go to funerals, you don't only hear mourning.
Only the bereaved are sad,
the visitors are laughing and noisy all night. And they relieve stress.
I'm only going to go after the fat pigs that took tons of money for years without doing anything.
So the employees will welcome it.
Fat pigs?
Here is the fat pigs list.
The Subjects of Managements for Restructuring at Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals
List of the subjects of management for restructuring
Kim Hwak Soo, Strategic Deputy Chief Director.
During past 3 years, he paid out ₩ 8 billion and 80 million as a rebate fee to Jae Yee Hospital.
He received ₩ 4 billion back out of that money. Do you know about it?
What is it?
It seems you knew about it.
Did you share it together? Oh.
You should have used some discretion.
There is an information from the prosecutor's office that the scandal-ridden rebate is under investigation.
Cut Strategic Deputy Chief Director Kim Hwak Soo, the tail, quickly.
Pointlessly being connected with him, don't get blown away harshly together.
Then, after taking time to look over it, let's turn it up.
You'd better know I absolutely can't compromise the person who has already been caught of involving in the scandal.
I have a trial, so.
Cheon Nyeon PharmaceuticalsR&D Business Unit President
He's inside. Should I let him know?
No.
Inside and outside, strange.
The two of them are very strange.
They aren't an ordinary couple.
After cutting off my arms and legs, you'll come into power of a whole group.
Absolutely, I will not allow it. A candle light in front of wind is you, not me, Do Hae Gang.
Imjingang Station
This is from May 10, 1981, what is it?
Please have someone look for any witnesses and rescue workers that were on the scene.
Who is it that died?
Hae Gang's father.
Hae Gang's father?
Climbing accident in five days of lifting the ban on access to Bukhansan rock climbing course.
-But why?-I need to know how he died.
So, why do you suddenly need to know that?
Yong Gi
Hello?
What is this? Did you answer?
Yeah, I answered.
Did you eat?
What?
Are you deaf? Lunch.
Did you eat lunch?
No, not yet.
What's to brag about? Hey, what good is it to have all that money of 2 or 3 billion won?
You can't even eat when it's 2:00 already.
Eat. Your mother will get upset.
Why aren't you asking anything?
I was about to ask anyway.
But in return, you have to answer truthfully.
Mm-hmm.
Are you lonely?
What?
Are you really lonely?
Answer truthfully.
Be strong.
What?
I said to be strong.
Even if I hate the sin, I decided not to hate the sinner. Especially my three-minute-older sister, just for you.
Why?
Because you're me.
What?
Because we're twins. Because you're my older sister.
Because you're my older sister.
I'll cheer you on from home, so do well at the trial.
I'm hanging up.
Don't hang up. Don't hang up, Yong Gi.
Why not?
Just... let's just talk some more.
Should we?
Tell me about you.
Me?
Ah, I saw Dad.
What?
In a picture. Your father-in-law showed me a picture they took together.
But he's uglier than I thought.
But, he did look like a good person.
You don't know dad's face either, do you? Ask your father-in-law to show you the picture.
I will.
He said that Dad had cut the rope.
What? It wasn't broken by itself?
It looked like the two of them were going to die together, so I guess Dad cut it first.
Isn't our dad quite amazing?
Our Dokgo Ji Hoon was really a man's man, hmm?
Dokgo Ji Hoon?
Our dad's name was Dokgo Ji Hoon?
Hey, you didn't even know that this whole time?
I suppose, you probably didn't have any opportunity to.
This is the first time hearing it, but why does it sound familiar?
Dokgo Ji Hoon isn't even that common.
It must be because he's our dad.
Your heart must have connected with him before your ears did.
No,
I've heard it before. Definitely.
The two of them are definitely working together.
Lawyer Baek Seok has something. Search and bring it to me while he is on trials.
Yes, sir.
Certification
Research journal
- I'll be back.- Please be back.
At the defendant's company, the sales record for Pudoxin, the treatment for gastritis
is presently in first place, taking 45% of shares in the market.
That's not all. In the first year of sales, in 2010, it reached ₩10 billion in sales.
Just last year, it earned ₩ 95 billion from the domestic sales.
It is in the process of being sold to the Chinese market.
It has been taken by many people already and there will be more people in the future,
who will take this problematic drug without any warning
or caution.
Ah, yes, I understand.
I asked the court to please look at Exhibit P-1,
Exhibit P-2, and Exhibit P-3.
As you can see, these are Moon Tae Joon's X-rays.
Exhibit P-2 is that in May of 2014,
while he was getting off a bus,
falling down suddenly, and being diagnosed that he had fractures, the picture of X-ray he got at that time.
Now, the photo from Exhibit 3 and
the health report he received in July of 2010,
I ask the court to please have a look at them alongside.
Before takng Pudoxin, Mr. Moon Tae Joon's bone density
showed no problems whatsoever. Bone density: Normal
Other than having gastritis, he was in good health.
The PII component that's used in Pudoxin,
if taken long-term, it loses acidity and prevents the absorption of calcium
and raises the thyroid hormone,
and due to osteoclast, the bone density level declines,
and the chances of having bone fracture is elevated.
According to a doctor from Johns Hopkins-
What suddenly brings you to the courthouse?
compared to those who aren't-
Weren't things over between you and Vice Chairman Do Hae Gang?
Brother-in-law, who are you rooting for?
The plaintiff's weight was 102kg.
He's last recorded weight was 61kg.
Rapid weight loss very well can be the cause of bone fracture.
But why did the plaintiff's attorney leave this fact out,
and trying to blame a national pharmaceutical company with side-effects from a drug that can't even be proven,
I don't understand why he's looking for reasons
to pin the blame for the bone fractures.
And that's not all. The plaintiff was not taking only Pudoxin.
But also, he always took Colloid Gelcaps and the similar medicines.
If the deceased's multiple fracture,
If this is the side effects of the medication as the plaintiff's attorney claims,
He should bring up the issue of the other medicines' side effects in the same way, as well.
Please take a look at Exhibit Ds, Judges.
The plaintiff's father, Moon Kyeong Tae
had suffered from Rheumatoid Arthritis and died from complication of the heart failure.
Also, the plaintiff's second older brother is presently
diagnosed with Reumatoid Arthritis and taking the medications.
This rheumatoid arthritis is that the excessive inflammatory mediators produced in the body
affects the metabolism in the bone. So due to pain, an abstacle of body movement and
the reduced activity seriously affect on reducing the bone density.
Moreover, according to the research reports, 60% of the cause of the rheumatoid arthritis developing,
is from a genetic factor.
Therefore, the cause of Moon Tae Joon's multiple fracture is not from Pudoxin.
It's a common sense and a logical and rational thought if we look at the family genetics for the cause of it.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Research Journal2.24.2011, tomorrow, Imjingang Station 19 o'clock.
She gave this to him.
She swallowed ₩ 5 billion and hid this away.
Me! She tries to hunt and kill me!
Sorry.
Seriously.
Go easy now. That competitive nature of yours.
Prepare well for the second trial.
At the second trial, I will bring up Kim Sun Yong's story so I can turn around the situation in my favor.
Anyhow, my winning trial is the second trial so don't mind.
I'm hungry, Seok.
Let's go eat.
I'll go first.
She says she's hungry, so torment her after feeding her.
What are you doing? Not coming?
♫ My heart is closed and I'm living like a fool ♫
♫ Memories of when I loved you ♫
♫ Are locked deep within the corners of my heart ♫
♫ Countless days have passed us by ♫
I'll get audited? How dare you—
You should stop that. Watch yourself.
You're not being like Choi Jin Eon, just say it. Tell me.
-It's about our fathers.-About Father-in-law?
-What is it?-What were my father's last words?
He said to take care of Hae Gang for him.
My father doesn't know my name, Chairman.
-Why are you like that?-I was about to go thud for you, Professor.
-You can do that thud thing.-What?-Let's give it a try.
Are you all right? Are you really okay?
I'm saying this because you don't know it, but I'm embracing you even though it's really difficult for me.
So please stay still.♫ My heart will withstand time ♫
♫ My heart will withstand time ♫