Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Let's go.
What is this about?
I'll cook dinner for you. Let's go.
Huh?
I'll make you breakfast tomorrow, too.
Let's go.
Excuse me, Vice Chairman.
What's the matter?
Excuse me.
Well... Where are you going? I have to know President's whereabouts.
Vice Chairman is going to make a meal in person.
Pardon?
Let's go, Vice Chairman.
Okay.
Then, work hard.
Bye.
What is this? People in high positions are holding hands without dignity.
Isn't it just a show?
Show?
- Ahh. A political show!- Yes.
A rumor spreads that the power struggle has started within the group.
They show their alliance indirectly.
That's right.
In the bright daytime, that is not a walk of love, but a walk of politics.
A proclamation of war that has taken an aim at the opponent.
That means they are allies.
Then, it's time for me to line up in a different line.
Did you see something you were not supposed to see? Why are you freezing up?
I was at a loss when I saw you all of sudden.
I apologize, Chairman.
Are you going out or coming in?
We are going out.
What brings you here?
Why didn't you pick up the phone?
We try to get fresh air and eat dinner out.
Your mom has been pressing me to take you to dinner since she owes you a dinner.
She's waiting for you in the parking lot.
I have a previous engagement.
Just the two of you have dinner today.
A previous engagement? You two?
Yes.
The door's open. Let's get on together and go down.
What are you doing without getting on?
Chairman is waiting. Get on quickly.
Whether it's for business or personal, it's quite reassuring to see you being together and it looks good, too.
Everybody is probably watching you.
Calculate and be careful of your actions.
Ah, he should have picked up the phone. Seriously.
Since the air is cold, why don't you get in the car and wait?
I am fine.
Don't the prosecutor son and the doctor daughter ask you to quit your job?
They did for a while, but they are quiet these days.
Thanks to whom, they can do well?
Tuition, the marriage fund... We shall be eternally grateful to the chairman.
They are doing well because of their smart brains.
The chairman is coming out.
What is this? Why does he bring the attachment without asking me?
Why are you outside? It's cold.
Why are you here? Are you going, too?
Only the two of us are going. Your son has a previous engagement.
With whom?
With her?
It's not a personal matter, but business.
How about Wednesday evening? I don't have anything scheduled on that day.
Anyhow, you are skillful in disappointing me.
If you had picked up the phone, we wouldn't have wasted the trip.
Check your phone and see how many times he tried to call you.
I have worried so much, all the way to here, whether something happened to you or not.
Get on, quickly.
I'm going.
You are full these days even if you don't eat, aren't you?
The position of Vice Chairman, 10.5% of the company shares...
Since things already went this way, you just work hard. Hard, very hard, okay?
Should we use my car?
Yes. You drive it. I had a drink.
Did you have a drink during the daytime? With whom?
Is it correct for the two of them to meet for company business?
It doesn't seem so, does it?
Don't you feel a queer atmosphere?
I feel suspicious no matter what. If it were for business, they should have done it at the company.
Where on earth are they going near the end of the business day?
What were my father's last words?
I heard he cut the rope himself.
Before he cut it, it seems he would have said some final words.
Usually in those circumstances, people leave last words for their family.
What words did he leave?
Yeah,
to take care of you both. He asked me to take care of Yong Gi and Hae Gang.
- Hae Gang?- Yeah.
My father doesn't know my name, Chairman.
The name my father left for me was Ong Gi. Dokgo Ong Gi.
Hae Gang asked about her father,
about what his last words were.
In the mountain? What were his last words?
Why are you stopping in the middle of talking? What did he say before he died?
He said for me to take care of Ssanghwasan well.
Then you didn't take it away. Why did you say you took it away so you made me guilty as well?
If you didn't take it, but you were asked to take care of it, then tell Jin Eon in advance,
so you won't make him suffer, needlessly.
Do you understand?
So, what are you going to make? Do you have a plan?
Monkfish is in season.
I'll make the spicy steamed monkfish, oyster stew, steamed vegetable, and fried tofu.
That much for a dinner.
Why? Shouldn't I hold your arm?
You said you know all of my heart.
I'll make you happy as well.
I love you, Choi Jin Eon.
That's enough. Who didn't love before? Seriously.
I am sorry. My wife is so pretty.
Who is your wife?
Only today. You are my wife only for today.
Hold my arm.
₩9,800 for Monkfish  ₩4,800 for Flounder
They don't have the razor you are using.
Just use this one.
You can use my skin lotion. Let's go buy pajamas now.
Pajamas?
Where am I going to sleep tonight?
Wherever you want to sleep.
Ahh.
Let's go buy pajamas.
Honey.
What, Honey?
Thank you for making me happy.
How can you already be happy? I haven't cooked for you yet.
Seriously. What am I going to do if I'm already this happy?
I wish time would stop right at this moment.
While I'm in the middle of chopping this monkfish and you in the middle of trimming the bean sprouts?
Yeah.
Without eating the food I cook for you?
- Yeah.- Why?
Because it's the last meal you're cooking for me.
You're wrong. I'm going to cook breakfast for you tomorrow, too.
Are you going to leave?
Depends on how you do.
Do you want to get hit with this monkfish?
I better go. I can't stay being treated this way.
I'll wipe off here.
The bean sprouts, it should be enough for you to eat alone.
There's too much monkfish for you to eat by yourself.
Save it to make a stew tomorrow morning and eat it by yourself.
This is exactly the happiness I was wanting,
not too big or not too small,
just this much happiness.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
My face is going to wear out. Stop that and eat some.
Out of all the countless women,
thank you for finding me.
After chasing you to death for a year and seven months,
thank you for agreeing to date me.
Thank you for loving me to overflowing, too.
In the 2002 World Cup, Korea vs. Spain,
in the miraculous 5-3 penalty shootout victory,
That day, thank you for giving me a miracle, too.
After six years, for giving me a blessing.
I thought I'd had entered into Nirvana and produced Buddhist relics in my body. (abstained)
I really should have treated the warriors (Korean soccer players) to a meal.
How for six years,
if I took one step, you'd push me back ten.
If I told you that I loved you, you'd say that it would cool soon.
How didn't you visit me at all during my military duty?
Seriously, I wondered how someone could be like that.
To me who had lost my memory,
for coming back to me,
for loving me again,
for allowing me to love the man Choi Jin Eon again, just like the first time,
Thank you.
Let's eat. Don't make me talk, I have to eat.
It's not because of you, but it's because of me that I'm breaking up with you,
so that I can set my life straight even if it's now,
so that I can forgive myself.
There isn't any part of my heart that hates you.
I'm being sincere. So don't blame yourself.
Our parting ways is entirely because of me.
It isn't because of you.
And also, I've already parted ways with you.
From the moment my memory returned, I said farewell to you.
Yes. When I checked with the floriography (language of flower) that left on memo,
It's a shrub called oleander, and it can be poisonous.
What? That young kid left a poisonous plant at her front door?
Yes. There was an actual case that a murder was committed by using this plant.
What, murder?
So, what you're saying is the same guy you saw in the parking garage, right?
Yes, it's the kid who punctured the tire.
I was in the process of looking for him anyway.
Find out quickly who he is, what relation he has with her, what he is aiming for.
Yes.
It should be on the CCTV.
Check it out immediately.
Oleander?
The shrub?
Do you know?
Since it has 6,000 times stronger toxin than Potassium Cyanide (KCN), it's known as a murder shrub in the foreign countries.
6,000 times?
Because of the poison called Oleandrin, once you ingest it, stomach pain and nervous breakdown occur
and then heart attack occurs.
There were many cases that people died from eating a few of the leaves.
But why suddenly an oleander?
Huh? It's nothing. Finish what you were saying.
According to the documents, someone secretly brought Zolpidem (sleeping pills) to your chief researcher's house.
That was not a thing Do Hae Gang did. That must be done by someone that Chairman ordered.
We have to drag him to our side to be a witness.
I met the mother of the deceased Kim Eun Joo and the Korean Chinese person who worked as a maid.
They don't know anything about it. They surely believe he became addicted and overdosed on the drug, as the prosecutor stated.
Who was the prosecutor leading it?
Yoon Hak Seong.
Prosecutor Yoon Hak Seong? There are many prosecutors who received the Cheon Nyeon scholarships Chairman Choi offered.
If we check the list of scholarship recipients, we can find out whether he was Chairman Choi's line or not.
He drove me out like a mouse, by sticking together with broadcasters, prosecutors, and stockbrokers.
Those bad bastards.
Among those who are in positions of power, there isn't a single person who isn't rotten.
There are only good bastards to me.
Is it your story?
Unfortunately, that's the story for all of us.
Here are your toothbrush, razor, shaving cream and clothes to change into.
I'll get going.
I think it would be better if I just leave.
Why?
Because I won't want to leave you,
because I'll want to hold you again.
Thanks for dinner. Don't come out.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki
Flowers bloom in summer. The floriography is "Danger". Please nurse this healthily and well.
Danger?
What is this?
Oh.
Go inside, I'll go to the police and be back.
The police?
I looked it up and it's a plant that can be really poisonous.
I think someone put it here deliberately to threaten you.
Recently, did something else like this happen?
Tell me the truth.
Hae Gang.
You—
Are you really going to be like this?
Go inside.
Let's go together to the police.
Didn't you hear me? I told you to go inside.
Go inside quickly.
So, Shin Il Sang's son is threatening Do Hae Gang?
Yes. His residency is in Sillim-dong.
It seems as if he is working part-time at the gas station on purpose.
Use this punk.
Pardon me?
Even if he was hiding his face, it was probably caught on CCTV.
If you look, it is probably taken in other places besides the gas station.
Even if we confirm that he was loitering in the proximity of Do Hae Gang,
if something happens to Do Hae Gang, he'll be a prime suspect.
The next trial and even the trial after that,
a way to prevent Attorney Baek Seok from coming to the courthouse comes across my mind.
Let's use Shin Il Sang's son.
Come and put some toner and lotion on.
Well, here.
Hurry up and put it on, your face will dry out.
Okay, I'll put it on for you.
Live how you wish to.
However you want to, do whatever you decide to do.
Whatever you choose, or whatever you do from now on, I'll be on your side, and I'll protect you.
So please, if it's difficult, say that's difficult.
If you're scared, then say that you're scared.
And if something happens, I'm saying for you to tell me that something happened.
That hurts.
Oh.
Let me at least do that much in your life.
Even if I can't be your husband, I'll at least do that much.
Just that much, let me into your life just that much. Hmm?
Okay?
Hurry up and put it on.
But are you really going to sleep on the sofa?
Yeah, I'm going to sleep on the sofa, so you can't curse me out.
But I don't have a blanket.
I can just cover myself with a coat.
I'll just sleep holding your hand, like a dummy.
For real, you better only hold my hand.
♫ My heart is closed and I'm living like a fool ♫
Why aren't you sleeping? Hurry up and sleep.♫ My heart is closed and I'm living like a fool ♫
♫ Memories of when I loved you ♫
I did wrong.♫ Memories of when I loved you ♫
♫ Are locked deep within the corners of my heart ♫
♫ Countless days have passed us by ♫
I did more wrong.♫ Countless days have passed us by ♫
I'm sorry. ♫ Countless days have passed us by ♫
I lived only that way. ♫ Just like that day ♫
Come here. ♫ Just like that day ♫
♫ Even if we are far apart ♫
♫ Even if everything changes ♫
♫ My heart will withstand time ♫
♫ And it will stay right here  ♫
Why don't I see any sight of Dokgo Yong Gi all morning?
"Uh-huh, oof, oof." She keeps sighing,
"Why alcohol, alcohol are you my enemy?"
"My mouth! This mouth behaved in a giddy way!"
She keeps saying that. And she gets up and lies back down. She closes her eyes and opens them.
Mom must be sick, Professor. She says she isn't hungry.
- There isn't any fever.- I said I'm not sick, why do you keep doing that?
Hurry up and go out and eat.
It is not a cold. looking at your sinking down, you might come down with a body ache.
I said it isn't the body ache. It isn't that, okay?
I said that I'm really not sick.
There isn't any benefit from ignoring your sickness.
This won't do, what good is it not to use a perfectly good doctor.
If we ask Professor Min to take a look, he'll be able to know right away where you're sick.
Just wait, I'll go call him.
Oh, no!
Wh-wh-wh-why call him? Wh-wh-who are you going to call now?
What's wrong with you? Did something happen with you and Professor Min?
Wh-wh-what happened? Nothing happened!
I'm coming in.
If you're in a condition where you can't even eat, then you can cancel what you said to me.
Wh-wh-wh-what did I say?
I-I-I don't have any memory, I must have blacked out right then.
Did you? I well understand.
I fully understand that your drunkenness caused you to cross the line, so come out and eat breakfast.
What? Drunkenness, I crossed the line?
Wait, h-h-how did I cross the line?
"You're fascinating, Professor."
"You're amazing, right now." If you weren't sincere, then you've crossed the line with me.
What?
"If only I weren't a mother, I would have gone ker-thump for you."
If you're going to spit out words so sweetly that you aren't going to remember,
then you're definitely crossing the line, Dokgo Yong Gi.
This is why I dislike alcohol. And I dislike people who can't control their alcohol, even more.
People who depend on alcohol, people who run away from things with alcohol, I dislike them all.
So in the end, I dislike Dokgo Yong Gi.
So there isn't any need to cowardly hide from me to avoid me, Dokgo Yong Gi.
Heaven, heaven, my gracious heaven!
Woo Deum Ji Dumplins
I am a victim of Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals Pudoxin's side effects...
What is it now?
Hey, kid, what is that?
I don't know. It was in Seul Ri's room.
I am a victim of Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals Pudoxin's side effects.
Your noona, where is your noona?
In the bathroom.
Give that here.
Hello, I am Kang Seol Ri, majoring in pharmacy. 4 years ago, I started participating in the clinical trials believing no side effect...
What is this?
To support Oppa with his lawsuit.
If we bring the public opinion, the prosecutors will consider it once more time.
So you're going to stand in front of Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals hold this?
Yes.
No way. We can't do this to each other.
We already did too much what we couldn't do to each other.
If you hurt others this way, you'll get hurt, too.
This is not an attack, but a self-injury.
I've already thought it through before doing it, so don't worry.
My background will help to attract the media's interests.
I won't do it for long.
As soon as I get their attention, I'll stop picketing.
I can keep attacking by doing the interviews.
If I stand in front of the company holding this picket sign, will they get hurt like I was, Dad?
Then do it together with me.
You can't do it by yourself, kid.
It has to be a one person protest.
That way I'll be legally protected.
If by chance they try to force me off the property, they will be breaking the law.
I don't know if it will turn out like I planned, but I do have a plan.
A plan? What plan?
I saw the allocation of stock.
How could you not give me even one share?
Did you pick me off of the streets?
Am I a stepchild?
You give half of it to Do Hae Gang who doesn't share a drop of blood with you.
How could you do this to me? How?
10.5% is how much money?
So what are you going to give me?
I want to get it in advance.
Give me something ahead of time.
Did you leave something with him? What do you keep asking him to hand over?
Without any manners, it seems you don't know your place or your ancestry.
My ancestry?
Am I really part of this family's ancestry?
Am I getting treated like this even though I am?
I gave you over 7%, too.
If you include your husband's and your children's, more went to you than to Hae Gang.
If Stepmother and Jin Eon combine theirs, it's over 27%, Dad.
Why didn't you include the money you took from me without my knowing?
Even if I didn't give it to you, I assumed you were taking care of your inheritance on your own.
You didn't raise a child, you raised a thief. A thief.
They say that the wife follows the husband's lead. How dare you two try to take your father's money?
I don't think we're the only thieves.
Dad also stole from his friend to accumulate his wealth, didn't he?
What?
Ssanghwasan. That Ssanghwasan that Do Hae Gang's father developed, you stole it, too, Dad.
Stole? Who says he stole it?
He said he entrusted it to him. He left it to him before he died.
To make sure Ssanghwasan was a success in his place.
Why are you laughing?
Because it's the funniest thing I've heard in a long time.
You're saying he left a will, aren't you? A will that only father-in-law knows of.
Then you didn't steal from your friend, you protected it.
So you brought up Ssanghwasan according to your friend's wishes.
Wow, when did you prepare such a moving story, Father-in-law?
Then you shouldn't have registered for a patent transfer the day after your friend died.
That's why I said I took it from him.
Because it's true that I got greedy after hearing my friend's will.
What do you know?
Don't write a novel using a mere sheet of paper. Were you in that place?
I was there. I was.
How dare you? I'm still living.
I didn't die and I'm still alive like this.
Only the dead would know the truth, right, Father-in-law?
You believe what you want to. Given the same information,
you believe what you want to. People do.
And also, truth belongs to the living.
Going forward, too, it belongs to those who have to live. Since nobody knows the truth of that day except me,
don't carelessly flap your lips as if you know.
Got it?
These are your father's initial examination charts that I received from the attending physician.
Why suddenly this old information, what in the world is it?
A stab wound? A 4 cm wound on the back of the left calf.
If it was a stab wound...
Does it mean that he was stabbed by a knife?
There's no way to say specifically that it was a knife.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Since they call it a stab wound whenever someone has been pierced by anything sharp.
Seeing that your father couldn't remember where he was stabbed, it doesn't seem to be a knife.
Because I didn't do the initial examination of him and he came to me after his surgery,
I only took a look at it after he got stitched up.
A stab wound doesn't appear in an x-ray.
How much must they have struggled to keep from dying?
He was very badly bruised and bleeding.
There was a ton of blood on one of his legs. Not on the dead person but the living one.
Pardon me?
Before deciding that you should live, at least you should live.
They probably said, "You die, I can't die."
So my father had said he couldn't remember how he was stabbed.
Because he was injured badly in several places.
Or maybe he got stabbed with the knife that was used to cut the rope.
He got stabbed and with that knife, he cut the rope.
Thank you for my meal. I will enjoy it.
In prison, I wanted to eat this so badly.
Please have a french fry.
The plan will go into motion very soon.
Rumors will be spread to make the stock prices go down and an attempt will be made to buy up all of Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceutical's stocks.
So you want me to buy up all the stocks one step ahead? Is that what you're asking?
Yes.
But why are you trusting me with that much money?
It isn't you,
but I trust your brilliant criminal records.
Tae Jun stock price manipulation case, OPC stock price manipulation case, and Park End stock price manipulation case.
Those are the ones you got caught because you failed. There must be a lot of others you were successful in doing without getting caught.
So should I make you take over Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals?
I will worry about taking it over,
so you just have to get Cheon Nyeon stocks instead of me.
Hey, what will I get out of it?
I entrusted you with all that money, use your skills and take what you need.
Because it isn't the money but the stocks that I need.
You keep the money that you earn.
Is this for real?
- Yes.- Okay, deal.
Just a moment.
What? Disappeared?
I have a copy, so the trial isn't a problem, but the fact that I have it means that you or Yong Gi gave it to me.
What can I do? You've been found out.
There isn't any word? Any kind of hint that you get?
He didn't tell you to get off this lawsuit?
He said it wasn't suicide, but that it was murder.
He told me to protect him.
That's why he confessed to killing him.
You're in danger. Min Tae Seok isn't one to sit still and just take it.
At the very least, I'm safe until this lawsuit is finished.
The problem is you, Seok. I'm not the one in danger, you are.
He's going to do whatever it takes to stop you. He won't let you stand in that courthouse.
I'll be careful that doesn't happen.
I'll really be careful this time. I'm sorry.
Be careful, Seok. If you get hurt again because of me, then— Then, I'll really—
I won't get hurt. I won't ever get hurt.
No matter what, I'll keep standing in that courthouse.
And then, I'll make sure to win against Attorney Do Hae Gang.
I will make sure I put a dent in your 100 percent win record.
I'm hanging up.
Research Journal
Attorney, he's here to install the backup camera.
Ah, yes.
What location is good—
I think it would be better not to install a camera, Office Manager.
Excuse me? Wh-why?
Then we'll be watching you 24 hours just to catch a thief. We can't do that.
I'm sorry, please just go back.
Then, should we put it outside?
Then do that.
Ah, yes.
Let's go.
Do you know our stock price went up ten times more last year because of a new drug Brother-in-law developed in America?
Well... Since the stock price keeps ups and downs around ₩700 thousand per share,
10.5% is... My goodness!
You've become rich overnight, Vice Chairman.
Secretary Shin, please prepare some tea.
Yes.
Let's go inside.
Please have a seat.
Don't you think the price is absurdly high for the body of hunting dog?
There must be a reason for the absurdly high price, because the money doesn't lie.
Did Brother-in-law not say anything?
He said he had something to say regarding my father and Chairman.
He said to give him two or three days,
and that he'd tell me everything without hiding anything, after he confirmed it.
As expected, Brother-in-law wouldn't hide everything, deceive everyone, and stab others in the back when given the chance. Different from us?
He's a good person, unlike us.
You should become a good person, unlike me, Attorney Do.
If you swallowed my money, ₩5 billion, you should work for me. Isn't it basic manners and business ethics?
If you keep playing dumbfounded games against me, keep in mind I'll also play dumbfounded games against you.
You'd better not act thoughtlessly. Just win the lawsuit.
If you take care of me through this Pudoxin situation, I'll quietly bury it.
Ah-ha. In two or three days, Brother-in-law will shake up this game.
We'll have to set up your opponent again.
Your opponent and your side will change—so will your anger, too,
therefore, hastily making me a target of your enemy.
So let Chairman Choi strut.
Because if Chairman Choi and I become a team, clearing out the likes of you won't take any work.
I've already gotten the experience, too.
What are those pictures you have in your hand? It looks like they were taken by CCTV cameras.
They're nothing much.
Really? Go on in.
Vice Chairman, R&D President Choi Jin Eon is here.
Please send him in.
Yes.
She said to go on in.
How do I look, Secretary Shin?
Excuse me?
Do I look dark? Do I look weighty?
Would you make me laugh?
Excuse me?
Get back to work.
Yes.
You left your watch, did you know?
Ah, really? I'll go to get it.
Did you leave it on purpose?
Yeah.
I was going to leave socks, but with socks,
I didn't think you'd say, did you know you left socks? So I left my watch.
I'm kidding.
I didn't even know I left my watch behind.
I'll bring it to you tomorrow.
Just leave it.
Why? It's a watch you like.
You can have it.
Thanks,
for giving me something so big I can't even wear it.
Why can't you wear it? Wear it on your ankle. Your ankle.
Anyway...
Ah, it's automatic, so you have to feed it every day.
Make sure to feed it well in my place.
I'm going to let it starve.
You can let it starve. All it will do is die.
Anyhow, your time and my time stopped again.
Why did you come here?
Oh, this. These are pictures from the CCTV.
These were taken in front of your house.
And these were taken in and around the office parking garage.
He's still a kid. We're looking into it, so don't be too scared.
But his clothes,
that day in the parking garage, it looks like the kid who was passing out advertisements.
Oh, I'll get going then.
Who are you? Who are you that...
Family informationSon: Shin Kyeong Woo (18 yrs), Preparing GED test, Working part time at Sang Ahm Gas station.
How much should I fill up?
- Full.- Yes.
Oh, it's cold!
If you have anything to throw out, please give it to me.
To throw out?
Nothing in the car, but in here and here. Would you get it out and throw it away for me?
When you're so angry you're going to go crazy, how do you vent?
When you hate someone like crazy, what do I have to do in those cases?
82,000 won.
Kid, don't you have gloves? Work wearing some.
Thank you, go safely.
Where is the car wash?
If you go over that way, there's one.
I see.
Goodbye.
Young man, catch this.
I won't eat this.
I said I wasn't going to eat, seriously!
I'm asking you to open it, kid.
Aren't you going to open it for me? My throat's blocked.
Thanks.
On the way of thanking you for helping me, can you hold this, too?
What are you doing now?
Are you pick a quarrel with me?
I am in the process of trial and error with you.
I want to get closer to you, but I don't know how and what to do,
so I face up to you recklessly with no particular plan in mind.
What?
I'll be back when I need more gasoline.
Work hard in this cold.
Yes!
I am a victim of Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceutical's Pudoxin's side effects.
Hello, I am Kang Seol Ri, majoring in pharmacy. 4 years ago, I started participating in the clinical trials believing no side effect...
You were urgently looking for me?
Kang Seol Ri is striking about Pudoxin side effects in front of company right now.
What did you say?
Do you know the reason Kang Seol Ri is doing this is totally because of you?
If you feel responsible, get rid of her quickly. Quickly!
What are you doing prior to trials?
If she gets attention from the media, what are you going to do?
Drag her right now! Make sure to take necessary action so she won't come again tomorrow, not twice! Surely!
Yes. I'll certainly take action.
Security team, all of you! Dispatch right now!
Kang Seol Ri.
Baek Seok?
Call Baek Seok over here?
You are like this. You are pressing with power, threatening, and frightening.
But what can you do?
This is the picture I wanted.
Vice Chairman, come out of there.
Hurry, Vice Chairman.
I'm YMEJ reporter Kim Seon Young.
You're Vice Chairman Do Hae Gang of Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals, aren't you?
I'm not doing any interviews.
According to Kang Seol Ri, the clinical testing results for Pudoxin were falsified. Is that true?
I said that I wasn't doing any interviews.
- Security Team Leader.- Yes, Vice Chairman.
Delete all the pictures of me from all of these cameras.
I understand.
You're prohibited from taking pictures on this side!
Is Pudoxin really...
Pudoxin clinical trial...
This kid.
Where are you going, Attorney?
Attorney?
I'm YM Media reporter Kim Si Jin. Would you do an interview with me?
Next Thursday is the second trial.
If you come to the courthouse then, I'll give you an interview.
Next Thursday, what time is the trial?
Thursday afternoon at 4:00 in courtroom 25.
If you come, you'll probably get an exclusive.
Where are you?
I'm nearby.
Nearby where?
At the gas station.
Are you getting gasoline?
Yeah, but why?
The manager who worked at Bukhan Mountain athe time of the accident has been identified.
Name: Kim Ki Seong, Age: 58
Occupation: Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals' chauffeur.
I'll put the file on him, on your desk. Come and check it.
What was the name, Hyun Woo?
Name: Kim Ki Seong, Age: 58
Occupation: Cheon Nyeon Pharmaceuticals chauffeur
Why aren't you saying anything?
Hey, Choi Jin Eon
Hey, Choi Jin Eon.
Send me a picture.
Picture?
Okay, I'll send it right away.
It won't be.
No, it can't be.
Hyun Woo
I'm going to kill you.
Yeah, Seok.
Right now, to the parking garage?
Okay, I'll be right down.
Oh, Seok.
Seok!
Seok,
Seok.
Wake up.
Seok,
Seok. Seok!
Wake up. Seok!
Timing and Subtitles brought to you bythe Forgotten Love Team at Viki