Subtitles by DramaFever
[This is a fictional drama
based on historical events.]
[Episode 21]
Baek Dae Gil, what are your
true intentions?
You pushed Yi In Jwa away
and pushed me away.
Are you planning on making him a king?
That is very unjust of you.
Or did you think because we are all
of the same lineage
that I would let you two brothers live?
Did you think I didn't know?
Today... I will end this insufferable
relationship.
Move aside!
The late king had a dying wish.
He said the Noron faction would
not accept you as king.
He said the Soron faction would most
definitely use it to their advantage.
I was told to save Yeoning's life.
I was told to save my brother's life.
So I responded, "Yes, Your Majesty.
I promise to protect Yeoning's life."
"As his older brother,
I will put my life on the line".
That was what I promised him.
Father's dying wish...
was for this traitor to live?
Are you there?
Is he speaking the truth?
Yes, Your Majesty...
Father has saved your life.
However, this will be the last time
I forgive you.
Also, as for the Noron faction's
refusal to accept me as king...
I cannot forgive them.
- They will all be punished by execution.
- Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Also...
Crown Prince, protect yourself.
Do not take part in government affairs.
Do you understand?
What are you doing?
What should I do?
The lives of the Noron ministers...
How do I save them?
I will look for a way. Do not be rash.
Wait here. All right?
Speak!
Tell us what we want to know!
You rascals!
Your Majesty!
Cheers.
Evidence?
[I swear on my blood to help my
brothers in arms to defend the country.]
It's a blood oath between
Yi In Jwa and the rebel Jeong.
Your Majesty, those who committed treason
and got the Noron
to name a successor....
The assassin that came in the night, the
poison in your food, and the gossip.
The ones who disgraced you
and caused trouble in the government.
That was all Yi In Jwa. Please forgive
the Noron faction.
Please execute the rebel Yi In Jwa.
If Yi In Jwa is also a rebel,
I will execute him as well.
It does not excuse the Noron faction
of their crimes.
Your Majesty
naming Yeoning as the successor
and the Crown Prince Regent...
Are you trying to say that it was all
Yi In Jwa?
The Noron faction members are not
the puppets of Yi In Jwa.
Also, it is not important whether there
was an act of treason or not.
What's important is that they had that
feelings in their hearts.
They have never once accepted me as king.
That is the reason why they must die.
- But, Your Majesty...
- I will not say it twice.
The Noron ministers and Yi In Jwa...
I will punish them as I see fit.
What happened?
I could not stop the executions of the
Noron faction ministers.
[Jo Tae Chae, Yi Gun Myung,
Yi Yi Myung, Kim Chang Jib]
[Kim Chae Gun]
Your Majesty!
Please spare their lives.
Punish me instead.
Please take my life.
Save the lives of the ministers,
Your Majesty!
Was it all your doing?
Did you get them to take action to
dethrone me?
Was it you who made them treat me like
a king in title only and insult me?
- Was it all you?
- Your Majesty...
They made an error in judgment out
of loyalty to me.
Then they deserve to die,
so why are you here on their behalf?
Your Majesty, please.
I have no intention of forgiving those
who even think of rebelling.
Even if... it is my brother.
Your Majesty... Your Majesty.
[Kim Chang Jib]
Make way!
Crown Prince.
Step aside!
We did what was best for this nation
and its people.
How could it be treasonous?
Your subject, Kim Chang Jib, will protect
you and keep the promise I made.
Minister.
Your Highness, please trust me.
Minister...
Crown Prince!
You must stand tall until the end!
Your must survive and reform this
nation's government!
Stop...
Stop... stop! Stop!
Stop! I said stop!
Move!
Stop!
Move! Move aside!
Move, move!
You must endure it.
You cannot step in and get injured.
They cannot die.
What have they even done wrong?
What have they done?
I am sorry.
I promise you...
I will get vengeance on your behalf.
Trust me.
And wait for me.
I am sorry.
Leave me alone.
I said leave me alone, please.
Please, leave me alone.
Mother.
Now...
What am I to do?
Father...
I do not want to lose anymore.
I do not want to lose any more
of my people.
Dae Gil.
Are you all right?
How is the Crown Prince?
You should have stayed with him.
Why did you come back?
I'm sure he must be traumatized.
There was nothing that I could do
for him.
You asked to see me, Your Majesty?
Tell me.
What should I do about the Crown Prince?
If you do not pull out the roots
of a rebellion it will rise up again.
You should take his life.
About a hundred Noron were killed.
You were the one to persuade the
Noron ministers.
You instigated this incident and
led them to death.
That's not true, Your Majesty.
What power do I have that I could get
the Noron ministers to take action?
Then what power do you have that you
can get me take action?
Am I a easier person than the ministers
in your eyes?
Eunuch.
Has my time finally come?
Are you going to deny this blood oath,
as well?
Your Majesty.
- Crown Prince.
- You should leave.
Right now...
I do not wish to see anyone.
I do not wish to hear anything.
The king has made a decision.
The king is kicking Yi In Jwa out of
the palace.
Your Majesty, I have never committed any
acts of treason.
Are your going to make denials even
in front of this blood oath?
Your Majesty, it is true that I wrote
this contract.
However, all of this...
I did it for your sake...
to get you on the throne.
Have you already forgotten, Your Majesty?
Don't you recall how the late king and
Noron ministers used to treat you?
Don't you remember how Yeoning behaved?
They were cold and neglected you.
They threatened you.
The promise that I made you,
I held it deep in my heart.
You should sit on the throne,
Crown Prince.
I will just accept your heart.
This was all for you, Your Majesty.
I did it all out of my loyalty to you
and to get you to the throne.
Do you really not know this?
Your loyalty...
I do acknowledge it.
I cannot forget it.
However, just as you said,
rebellion can rise up again.
In return for me sparing your life...
you will not be able to step inside this
palace ever again.
You will lose everything that you own.
Your Majesty, why don't you kill
me instead?
I am asking you.
Do not involve yourself in government
affairs again.
Your Majesty!
The rebel Jeong
will be executed tomorrow.
I endured all that time.
I worked so hard to get this card.
Must I throw it out now?
In such a wasteful way...
We must throw out a sword that has
become dull.
The Noron ministers have all
been purged.
The king's feelings
have changed as well.
We do not need to carry a useless sword.
Are you all planning to turn on me too?
You joined hands with the rebel Jeong.
We have heard about that blood oath!
Leave! We no longer
have any business with you.
You will turn your back on me?
Are you sure you will not regret this?
Are you threatening us?
The king has favored you
because you were his teacher.
How could he continue a relationship with
someone who joined hands with a rebel?
Get out of here!
He will lose everything.
- The king will take everything--
- So what?
Will that change anything?
Yi In Jwa...
I'll get rid of him.
All those people that died because of
schemes will not come back.
[Jeong Hee Ryang]
- It's been a long time, Jeong Hee Ryang.
- Have you had a change of heart?
Well, they do say the soul looks good
if you die while eating.
They say you will be executed tomorrow.
I think you need to die
in order for me to live.
The body may rot for a moment,
but the soul will not leave the body.
What is it?
You need to stand up again.
For all those that died for you,
you must stand up again!
Crown Prince!
The rebel Jeong and his people have taken
their own lives by consuming poison.
I heard that the criminals have all died.
You wanted to keep the rebel Jeong alive.
And dig deeper into his background.
Haven't your plans failed then?
Not yet.
It is win or lose now.
I need you to mobilize the Euigeumbu,
Office of the Inspector General
the police, and the Hansung
Regional District.
We need to tighten the noose around
Yi In Jwa's throat.
Eunuchs.
The king turned his back on you?
- Yes.
- How did that happen?
What is the reason?
The king ended up receiving
the blood oath.
But, I'm sure that...
The contract that Hong Mae burned...
was a fake.
She probably gave the real copy to
Baek Dae Gil.
However, it doesn't matter.
Our plans will have to move forward.
The King was a card we would have
eventually thrown away .
- Take everything!
- Yes, Sir.
What's going on?
Sorry about the interruption.
I'm carrying out a royal command.
Royal command?
You will lose everything you own.
Police Chief, you are making
a big mistake.
I'm from the Hansung Regional Office
to investigate a matter.
It looks like I'm late.
I'm here from the Office of
the Inspector General.
What did you say?
Why don't you turn yourself in to
the Euigeumbu tomorrow?
Before a warrant is released.
My lord, what will you do now?
It seems that the king is out to kill me.
He is already a man headed toward death.
I had planned on using him a
little longer.
If he insists on being this way,
I will have to strike first.
What are you planning to do?
In case something like this happened,
I had a plan in place.
[Park Pil Hyun]
Is it you?
Are you Yi In Jwa's partner,
Park Pil Hyun?
I'm Jeong Hee Ryang from Yongnam.
I have a blood oath with Yi In Jwa.
We cannot lose this opportunity.
Make your decision.
He has finally drawn his sword.
Send a message to our comrades.
Tomorrow, at midday...
I, Park Pil Hyun, will be charging into
the city.
Yes, Sir.
It looks like the city will be turned
upside down tomorrow.
Are you certain Yi In Jwa will
make a move tomorrow?
He will make a move.
Otherwise, he will end up dying.
Crown Prince, you need to eat something.
Crown Prince.
We will kill the King.
Then we will start a new world.
King, all of the things I have done for
you all these years...
I will take it all back today.
Who are you?
- I am Yi In Jwa.
- Yi In Jwa, you say?
What brings you here?
I have waited a very long time for you.
Why is the bell ringing?
I will check on it.
First, the bell rang five times.
The second time, the bell rang
nine times.
The fifth word in the Celestial Stem
is "Mu."
The ninth word in the Earthly Branch is
"Shin."
"Mu Shin."
Just now...
how many times did the bell ring?
Pardon me?
Everyone, rise up!
It is your nation, the people's nation!
It has arrived at your door!
Those that have fallen into ruin...
Those of you whose families have been
killed and have suffered in fear...
Those of you that shed tears because
of this corrupted government....
All of you, stand up!
Let us start a new world together.
It's a royal command.
Arrest all officials in charge
of administrative and executive affairs.
Was this it?
Is this everything?
The rebels that you planted inside
the palace...
How did you know?
I expected that there could be rebels
within the palace.
But I wasn't certain.
I wondered how you would
mobilize them all at once.
But...
I became certain once you rang that bell.
Then are they all...
Go on and arrest them!
Yes, sir!
It's over now.
Yi In Jwa.
I truly wanted it...
I wanted you to become King.
I heard you were a genius
and could see into the future.
You must not have been able to read
my face very well.
How could you think I look like someone
who'd become a king?
Do you really want to die by my sword?
Do you think you can do it?
- Dae Gil!
- Stop.
I saw it, the rebellious nature
in your heart.
Your Majesty, it's a very big
misunderstanding.
What did I even do? There is no evidence.
Evidence!
Why? Will you try denying more?
King, it's not over yet. You will see.
There will be no trial.
Your face will be revealed to
the people.
Once it gets dark,
you will be hanged to death in public
to make sure no one thinks of committing
such acts again.
Rebel? That man is a rebel?
- Oh my! How could he do such a thing?
- So, this is that rebel traitor?
Goodness, he looks like a normal person.
Don't you have anything better to do?
You awful man!
- What kind of a person...
- Just take out his eyeballs now!
He's going to die anyhow.
He deserves to lose them now.
Don't you agree?
- That's right!
- Yeah!
Yes, he also took advantage of
poor people. That guy!
- You bum!
- You bum! Jerk!
Yi In Jwa.
Baek Dae Gil! You should have killed me.
You insult me like this instead?
How dare you.
How dare you do this to me,
Yi In Jwa!
I'm sure it's torturous for you.
Did you think about why the King decided
to punish you like this?
It's to show the rest of your followers
your pathetic last moments.
That way, they won't try another
rebellion.
How much do you know, exactly?
- Park Pil Hyun.
- How do you know about him?
What do you think my father's been up to
after he left me?
What has Baek Man Geum done?
From the beginning, I knew that
Jeong Hee Ryang was not dead.
You likely used a medicine that slowed
down his heartbeat.
I let him go on purpose.
A rat caught in the palace
was looking for a way out.
He won't be able to get into the city,
in the end.
Well, I'll see you when
the sun goes down.
You worked very hard.
The blood will not stop flowing
in the palace.
I do not have much time left.
You're not getting better.
So, I added some medicinal herbs that
should help.
How much time do I have left?
Your Majesty, why would you say such
a thing?
I have been ill a long time.
I am fully aware of my situation.
Tell me.
How much time do I have left?
The King is naturally weak.
In the end, he will end up embracing
Yeoning again.
I suppose he will since he does not
have an heir.
There are no other options.
He cannot get rid of Yeoning.
At this rate, what if we all end up
dead?
We have to do something before then.
Even if that means we shake the stability
of the royal family
I will not stand by and watch the son of
a lowly, water maid become a king.
Let's go.
What happened to Jeong and Park?
It's a relief they have escaped.
Will our great plan fail?
Get a horse.
- Crown Prince.
- Do not worry.
I will not lie down and be weak
like they want me to.
Crown Prince, Crown Prince!
Crown Prince!
It was not poison.
However, if you eat the wrong taproot
of a plant...
it can cause death in serious cases.
I cannot die like this.
Crown Prince, you must lie down.
I need to see the King.
What happened to them?
Park Pil Hyun and Jeong Hee Ryang must
have found out.
They already disappeared.
The royal guards will come after us.
The four gates are shut to us.
I will leave through Naksan.
Yes, they say it is darkest under an
oil lamp.
Be careful out there.
Yi In Jwa's execution has to carried out.
It has to be.
Save me, Your Majesty.
The ministers are plotting to kill me.
I'm sure they are.
The Noron ministers who were loyal
to me tried to get rid of me.
You are only a Crown Prince.
I'm sure they would try to kill you.
Please stop them.
Your Majesty, you are the only one who
can stop the Soron faction.
I have no inclination to stop the
Soron faction.
None whatsoever.
Then...
are you saying I should just accept it?
I refuse... to die like this.
The wind is chilly.
Let's go inside.
What do you think?
It is very beautiful.
Do you think so?
To me, it looks very sad.
Once the sun sets,
it is gone without a trace.
It feels empty and destroyed.
[Queen Seonui]
I am worried about you being left alone
without an heir.
Your Majesty.
How will you protect yourself from harm?
You must stay strong.
As long as I sit on the throne,
I belong to all the people.
My fate is keeping the royal family
stable and serving the people.
However...
I am very sorry.
What do you plan on doing once
Yi In Jwa is dead?
I will decide once he dies.
Stop!
Get him!
Go on without me. I'll stop them.
I will see you again.
So, you're here?
Go on without me.
Stop!
Stop right there! Stop!
My lord.
Over there! There he goes!
Get him! Get him!
Lend me your bow and arrow.
Yi In Jwa, I cannot allow you to live.
No matter how much you fight,
hell will be waiting for you in the end.
Then I'll see you in hell, Kim Chae Gun.
Stop!
Go to hell, Yi In Jwa.
My lord.
- Check the body.
- Yes, sir!
What happened here?
Hwang Jin Ki chose suicide at the end
of a cliff.
Your Majesty...
I have heard that you haven't eaten
in two days.
Bring it in.
Have you made your decision?
I will bring in your court lady to test
your food.
No, don't.
You may leave now.
Yeoning.
I am sorry.
As for forgiveness...
I will plead for forgiveness from you...
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, Your Majesty!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Daebak]
Hide like a rat
and live that way forever.
I will never be insulted as the lowly
son of a water maid again.
I do not want to see your face again.
I order you to be executed.
You want us all to leave together?
You'll see once we get there,
Grandpa.
Are you ready?
We have taken over Cheongju Fortress.
He renounced his nation,
and you want to put him on the throne.
It's as many as 200,000 people.
How can we stop that many people?
We can do it. Our goal is to get Yi
In Jwa in three days.
Slaughter the rebel Yi In Jwa and
all of his followers.