Subtitles by DramaFever
[This is a fictional drama
based on historical events.]
[Episode 22]
He's still somewhere in this forest.
- Find him.
- Yes, sir!
He's had more than
enough time to escape.
No, I know he's here somewhere.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, Your Majesty...
Come back to us, Your Majesty.
Yeoning.
I am sorry.
As for forgiveness...
I will plead for forgiveness from you.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, Your Majesty!
Come back to us, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty...
[Queen Seonui]
Your Majesty.
My lord!
What is it?
The King has died.
We should return now.
Yi In Jwa!
Hide like a rat
and live this way forever.
Do not show that face of yours again.
I do not have much time left.
Will that change anything?
Will it bring back the lives of
all those that died for nothing?
Crown Prince! It wasn't you, was it?
- Let go of me!
- Minister.
I just met with the doctor.
He told me that His Majesty died
after eating raw crab in soy sauce.
What is it that you want to say?
The King has been ill for a long time
and has been coughing up blood.
How could you give him raw crab
in soy sauce and persimmons?
Don't you know that those foods can
cause him harm due to his health?
I am heart-broken to hear
that the King died as well.
I had not heard that he died
from eating the food.
Isn't that right?
But...
Who are you to insult the heir to
the throne for serving the King a meal?
In your eyes, do I not
look like a crown prince?
Leave, right now.
Crown Prince, what happened?
It's just as you heard.
I served the King his favorite food
raw crab in soy sauce
and sweet persimmons.
Please tell me. Did you really...
Are you suggesting that
I poisoned the King?
Can you tell me that you did not?
If you didn't do it,
please tell me that you didn't.
Tell me you have nothing to hide.
Tell me you have nothing
to hide as the next king.
I am your friend, Baek Dae Gil, who
would put his life on the line for you.
Tell me you have nothing to hide.
Please tell me that.
If I tell you that I didn't do it...
would you believe me?
We were once friends.
Do you think it's possible to
have friends in my position?
I can be your friend if you want.
I don't need a friend like you.
We were once brothers too.
Are there younger brothers
who draw swords
against their older brothers?
Are there older brothers
that get in the way of
their younger brother's success?
I trust you, Crown Prince.
However, your heart...
Once you allowed suspicion
into your heart...
you've already thrown me away.
Crown Prince.
I am not the crown prince.
I am the king.
I will never be insulted for being
the lowly son of a water maid again.
Anyone who disobeys me,
scorns me, or disgraces me...
I will not forgive them.
Not my parents or my brothers.
I have nothing more to say to you.
You should leave now.
Crown Prince.
The Crown Prince is not wrong.
This is no longer something
you should get involved in.
He is no longer...
your friend.
Dae Gil, are you really leaving?
Don't bother trying to stop him.
He is as stubborn as his father.
He's already left home a hundred times.
Grandpa.
Who's there?
Who is this?
Man Geum!
Have you been well?
Why you, rascal!
Do you know how much Dae Gil and I
suffered after you died?
Why didn't you just stay dead?
Why did you come back
to this corrupted world?
Did you think I would dance around
happily if I saw you again?
Thank you...
for protecting our Dae Gil.
Man Geum...
Man Geum! Is this a dream or real life?
Oh, Man Geum.
You want all of us to leave together?
Where to?
To a place where we can help people
and live well together.
You'll see once you get there.
Don't worry. It's a good place.
Where is this good place?
You should go if you've made
the decision to go.
What about Yi In Jwa?
You haven't found him yet?
He is long gone now.
Even if he does manage to live...
he won't be able to rise up again.
Goodness, why are you pests
all hanging around here?
Get out of here now!
Deliver this to the shaman.
My lord, you are still alive.
Madam.
A homeless man outside gave me this.
Do not look for me. Just wait.
I will come find you again, someday.
There is no way to express
the grief for the late King.
We must protect the people of this nation
and not leave the throne empty.
For the strength and leadership of Joseon
I declare Crown Prince Yi Geum
as the new king.
Reign forever.
Long live the king!
Long live the king, long live the king!
Do you resent me?
I do not resent you.
We have our own destinies.
We are merely heading down
different paths.
Long live the king!
Long live the king, long live the king!
Just you wait.
I will rise up again.
I will tear down this
corrupt government.
I will turn the government
upside down.
No, no, it can't be.
Dae Gil?
Are you really leaving now?
Take care of yourself.
You too, Master.
Your Majesty, congratulations.
- Kim Il Kyung.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
I no longer want to see your face.
Shall I leave the palace then?
No.
I am ordering you to be executed.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Your joke is too severe.
Joke?
As soon as the late King
ascended to the throne
a hundred of the Noron ministers
that supported me were killed.
Three hundred more ministers
were sent into exile.
Did you really think I did not know
who was behind it all?
Kim Il Kyung will be sentenced to death!
Your Majesty!
Provincial Governor Mok Ho Ryong.
You gave false testimony with your lies.
Innocent people were killed
because of you.
Your Majesty, please spare my life.
- Sentence him to death as well.
- Yes, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, please have mercy!
- Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
If you have anything to say,
say it now.
However...
you will need to put
your life on the line first.
Where has he gone?
I don't know where exactly.
Did he say anything...
before he left?
I understand.
You may leave now.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I can bear the burden of this throne.
However, sitting here
alone in the world...
is not easy to bear.
What is all of this?
It's as if we've come back
to our hometown.
Dae Gil, Dae Gil!
- Have some of this watermelon.
- Okay.
Have this ripe one. Here.
One for you too.
Yeon Hwa!
Have you been well?
Welcome.
Watermelon?
Thank you.
"Hak Yi Bool Sal Jeuk Mang".
[Crown Prince Hyojang]
"Sa Yi Bool Hak Jeuk Tae".
"If you only learn and do not think,
you will fall into ruin."
"If you only think without learning,
it is dangerous."
Is that true?
What is that all about?
What in the world?
"The King poisoned the late King."
"The King is not of royal blood."
Find out who's spreading these lies.
Put them all to death.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[Hwang Jin Ki]
It's been a long time.
My lord!
What have you been doing all this time?
I have been keeping myself very busy.
Did Moo Myung end up dying that day?
He is alive.
[Remove the fake king
and seat the true king]
They will try to use him
to catch me someday.
Or they will use him
as some sort of bait.
So why come look for me now?
It has started.
The great plan that we have been
dreaming of for so long.
If you stop in this condition
the person...
You need to find Park Pil Hyun.
Tell him it's time.
How many years has it been, Yi In Jwa?
Are you ready?
I was getting tired of farming
all day and night.
It's not many, but I have
trained a hundred men.
When is it?
The rebellion?
It has already started.
First, we will start with
my hometown of Cheongju.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir!
We cannot allow Cheongju Fortress
to fall into the hands of the rebels!
Do whatever you must to protect it.
Yi In Jwa!
[March 15, 1728 - Cheongju Fortress]
While I am capturing Cheongju,
you need to take control of Yeongnam.
At the same time...
Park Pil Hyun will be taking over Honam.
They have seized control
of Cheongju Fortress!
We will make a push toward Jeonju now!
Yes, my lord.
The weather is nice today.
Hello, Queen Dowager.
Are you out for a walk?
You are so dignified.
You're looking stronger everyday.
It would have been nice if
the late King had an heir like you.
We will be on our way now.
Come now, Haeng.
Your Majesty.
Yi In Jwa...
Bring me Kim Chae Gun.
I heard there was a big commotion.
There was a battle at Cheongju Fortress.
They took over it all.
Is that true?
- Who did such a thing?
- I don't know.
Move, move!
They've even taken over Goryeong.
What are you going to do?
Yi In Jwa sure has a long life.
Don't think about doing anything.
He has nothing to do with us anymore.
You remember, right?
We said we'd forget it all and move on.
How nice is everything right now?
Still, that's not right.
It's the people who will
end up in the revolt.
Wouldn't it be the people of
this nation who end up hurt?
My dad is right.
Dae Gil.
I'm not a soldier.
I shouldn't get involved.
But, you never know...
I should be prepared.
Oh, look who it is!
It's our Dae Gil's master.
How long has it been?
How many years have passed?
It has been a long time.
Hello, Master!
Hello, Seol Im.
Master.
How have you been?
It's nice here.
Is this about Yi In Jwa?
Dae Gil.
We cannot look the other way on this.
After Cheongju Fortress was seized...
an entire town was massacred
because they supported Yi In Jwa.
The man in charge was
removed from his position.
You cannot undo the blood that was shed.
Was that under the King's orders?
It is not the King's will, however...
the blood that was shed...
don't you want it to end?
This bitter fate with Yi In Jwa?
Yi In Jwa.
My lord, do you hear that?
Yes.
This is the will of the people.
King, wait for me.
I will step on Hanyang land soon.
Yi In Jwa is now an unavoidable force.
Every moment is critical.
Now... it's time for you to meet him.
Your Majesty.
Former Special Military Officer,
Baek Dae Gil, is here.
You may all leave now.
Sit down.
Father, who is this person?
Haeng, why don't you
step outside for a moment?
I feel as though we have
a wide distance between us.
You look so much like King Sukjong.
Do I?
I heard that people who aided the rebels
were massacred by the soldiers.
Some people become rebels.
Some people join hands with those rebels.
And some people help them
from the background.
They are rebels, just the same,
and have paid for their crimes.
And why?
Why did these people start
following those rebels?
Did you not stop to think about that?
All people want is a bit of land
they can farm.
A bit of grain and food to eat.
That is all.
That is all the people want,
Your Majesty.
And so?
The rebels are spreading out.
Are you telling me I should
sit here and just watch?
Your Majesty.
Then what makes you any different
than the rebel Yi In Jwa?
You did not come here to
receive my royal command.
You came here to reproach me.
Please think of the people first,
Your Majesty.
It is a small sacrifice for
the good of the nation.
I must endure and pay for killing my own
people because I sit in this throne.
I will give you a government post
and military soldiers.
No one knows Yi In Jwa better than you.
You can read that animal's mind.
I do not care what must be sacrificed.
Stop him.
If you use your army,
more people will get hurt.
Please reconsider, Your Majesty.
I will give you five days.
If I do not hear from you in five days...
I will use my army.
Try it.
If you care for the people...
there is nothing you cannot do.
What have you decided?
They are all anxious too.
The army will be arriving
in Hanyang in ten days.
The government will be
in a similar state.
We have no time.
At first, they said it was
a disturbance in a small town.
Now, it's one of the rural districts.
Now the islands are involved,
and they're getting very close.
Shouldn't we do something immediately?
Still, we should not act rashly.
[Jo Il Soo]
There is no guarantee that
Yi In Jwa will succeed.
We could get beheaded at any moment.
Also, the King summoned Baek Dae Gil.
I don't know what he is thinking.
I suppose he wants to use Baek Dae Gil
to catch Yi In Jwa one more time.
That will not happen.
This is a letter from Yi In Jwa.
Is everything in this letter true?
Tell him this.
The Soron faction will
side ourselves with Yi In Jwa.
My lord!
However, if this is not true...
our entire faction will oppose him.
Be very clear about that.
I will deliver the message.
My lord, what exactly
was in that letter?
First.
He will install Mil Poong Goon as king.
"Pae Ga Yib Jin".
I am going to dethrone the fake king
and install the real one.
[Mil Poong Goon, grandson of
Crown Prince Sohyeon]
So I am the true king?
The King poisoned the late King
and that's how he's now on the throne.
He was born from a water maid,
so his royal lineage is questionable.
How can we have a ruler like that?
We need you to remove him
from the throne, Your Highness.
You must sit on the throne.
Build a new government.
Pay the gratitude back to the people.
Why don't you show me your strength?
We do not need to go far, Your Highness.
I'm from Jeolla-do.
I'm from Chungcheong-do.
I'm from Gyeongsang-do.
Your Highness,
they are not the only ones.
In all of the eight cities,
we have over 200,000 people.
200,000...
Do you really have an army of 200,000?
Yes, Your Highness.
We have Jeong Hee Ryang in Yeongnam
and Park Pil Hyun
in Honam training fighters.
We have men and women
helping out in all areas of operation.
However, no matter
how many people there are
do you think people who are not
trained can handle soldiers?
Also, we do not have
any allies within the palace.
It will not be so easy
to bring down the King.
What if we do have an ally in the palace?
The Soron faction have no power anymore.
It's someone higher than that.
Higher than that?
The Queen Dowager.
The Queen Dowager?
Are you really telling me that
she is working with Yi In Jwa?
Watch what you say.
I will speak to her myself
and confirm it.
You should all prepare yourself.
"The royal lineage has been broken".
"It must be rectified".
Did the Queen Dowager
really send this letter?
No.
The Queen Dowager gave it
to me herself in person.
I cannot forget the night the late King
was poisoned and killed.
My blood curdles
every time I see the King.
Do you know how that feels?
If you are able to move the hearts
of the people outside the palace...
I will move the hearts of the ministers
and sway their opinion.
If you can end this corrupt nation...
I promise you that I will
end the King's life.
Please, make your plan a success.
The moment you decide to join me
the Queen Dowager will draw her sword.
Have you not seen enough?
With the strength that we have
it will take ten days
to reach the capital.
Ten days is enough.
Your Highness.
Make your decision now.
Yes.
I will join your cause.
There are many who have headed
north to take refuge there.
Master, I'm going to go meet Hong Mae.
You go back to the mountain
and get ready.
All right, but wait a minute here...
Who do you think are
to give orders to your master?
Master, you're going to go regardless.
Why are you complaining?
Why, that rude kid!
What?
You want me to get
some medicine for you?
Yes, right now.
They say you can get
anything here in Hanyang.
You show up here after years.
What is this nonsense?
Look here, Hong Mae.
You've made your living from
the blood and tears of the people.
For once in your life, you can
do something on their behalf.
There's no need to speak like that.
What blood and tears?
It's not hard to get the medicine.
How much do you need?
Are you all ready?
I have thirty horses prepared
and I have food for them too.
This is from Hong Mae.
Seol Im, you take care of it.
Okay, let's see.
This is a peddler's guide map
for the eight cities.
Dae Gil, South Goblin, and Seol Im.
You go here.
Go to Anseong and block Yi In Jwa.
The remaining three will go to Daejeon
and stop Yi In Jwa's people.
Next, we'll each go to
Gyeongsang-do and Jeolla-do.
We will go to the areas they control.
We'll win over the people and take on
Jeong Hee Ryang and Park Pil Hyun.
No, I'm going to Mokcheon.
That's not a strategically
important city.
That's why it's important.
Things have gotten worse.
Yi In Jwa has His Highness,
Mil Poong Goon, with him.
Mil Poong Goon?
Yi In Jwa is pretty smart.
Isn't he going around lying?
He's telling everyone he will
give them grain and land.
Who wouldn't follow him?
If I didn't know what he was like
I would risk my life
to fight for him too.
How are we supposed
to stop all those people?
It's not just one or two people.
It's 100,000 or 200,000 people.
It's better to use a strong army.
It's not possible unless you
can fight them all at once.
It is possible.
If we can just catch Yi In Jwa...
The problem is that
we only have five days.
I will give you five days.
If I do not hear from you in five days...
I will use my army.
Once five days pass
the Special Military and all
five branches of the military
will be mobilized at once.
If that happens...
it's unavoidable that
the people's blood will be shed.
I do not want even
one person to get hurt.
Five days is long.
I know the King promised you five days
but he will not be sitting by
and not take action.
Three days then.
Our goal is to catch
Yi In Jwa in three days.
Chief of the 5th Military Branch.
From this point on, I am allowing
the use of guns and gunpowder.
Hand out these guns to
the soldiers in your unit.
Yes, Your Majesty!
How many men are in the Gyeonggi unit?
There are one leader
and three special officers.
There are 1,350.
Choose 1,000 well-trained men
from them to create an elite troop.
Wait for my orders.
Yes, Your Majesty!
The men in the Soron districts and
at the four gates will be cut in half.
Military trainers and the Forbidden Guard
Division will guard against the rebels.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Baek Dae Gil is heading towards Mokcheon?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I will head there as well.
What do you think?
Do you think it's possible?
Do you think it is possible to stop
Yi In Jwa without an army?
He is traveling with an entire
operation of people helping him.
He has over 200,000 people.
However, I trust in Baek Dae Gil.
Trust me.
It's not for my sake,
but for your sake.
That is my wish.
Baek Dae Gil.
I trust in you too.
However...
As a king that sits on this throne...
I cannot trust you.
It does not allow it.
[Mokcheon]
I cannot trust anything.
What is this?
I would like to meet Yi In Jwa.
Who are you?
I heard that you plan on returning
the land you claimed back to the people.
Is that true?
It is true.
His Highness has allowed it as well.
I am Mil Poong Goon.
Your Highness!
We, the citizens of Mokcheon,
promise to join Yi In Jwa.
They say the will of the people
is the will of the gods.
Unpack your belongings
and allow everyone to rest here.
Feed the horses plenty of food.
Does that mean...
Tomorrow, we will cross over
Jukju Mountain Fortress.
All right.
Let's go.
Feed them a lot, all right?
Did you do what I ordered?
Yes, and you have a visitor.
My lord.
What brings you all the way out here?
Baek Dae Gil.
Yes, the King has summoned Baek Dae Gil.
What? Him again?
Baek Dae Gil...
Yi In Jwa!
Hide like a rat
and live this way forever!
Do not show that face of yours again.
Did you deliver my message
to the Soron ministers?
Yes.
However, the situation in
the palace is very intense.
The King will make his move soon.
The King will use the central army
just to stop me.
You should get to Hanyang quickly.
Keep an eye on the palace.
Baek Dae Gil.
It will cause problems for us
if he makes a move.
That's what fate is.
A destiny that you cannot
escape even if you try.
If we meet again, either I will die
or Baek Dae Gill will die.
It's one or the other.
Where are you, Baek Dae Gil?
He's planning on returning fully
out in the open like this.
They are all being fooled by
that beast's two faces.
I'm going to show everyone what
kind of person Yi In Jwa really is.
Everyone should be okay, right?
[Jeonju Fortress]
Father and Master are more
trustworthy than anyone I know.
[Sangju Fortress]
Who is Yi In Jwa, you ask?
I will tell you about this guy.
Hong Mae and Yeon Hwa too.
"Bad rumors regarding Yi In Jwa
have started to spread in Hanyang".
Hong Mae's mouth is
still alive and well.
Are you all ready now?
Yes!
We must succeed.
If we fail today...
The Special Military is on
standby outside the city.
the army will make their move.
I have said this before.
This group has gathered very quickly,
so they do not know one another well.
We must use that against them.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Oh my...
I was tired, so had a good nap.
Now I feel better.
You both must be tired. Go in and rest.
We'll watch this place for now.
Should we?
Then, thank you.
Don't worry.
You make this much stew?
How can they eat all of this?
Look how many people there are.
You have to make this much
in order for them to eat enough.
This is from Hong Mae.
I'll have one more bowl of rice.
Yes, have some more. It's good.
Have enough so that you get full.
Hey.
Oh, my stomach!
We will cross over Anseong, gather
strength, and go into the capital city.
Are you all ready?
- Yes!
- My lord!
- What is it?
- We have a big problem.
The men have eaten something wrong.
They all have diarrhea.
Sir, the storehouse is on fire.
Hurry, hurry!
Water, water, water!
Bring more!
Sir, the horses are all gone.
Why weren't the horses
being looked after?
A sudden stomach issue,
no provisions, and now the horses.
There's a rat hiding in our midst.
Do you think Dae Gil will be okay?
Do you know what the most
useless thing to worry about is?
It's worrying about Dae Gil.
He has lied to the people.
As for Yi In Jwa and his followers
who have insulted this government...
slaughter them all.
Yes, Your Majesty!
It's been a long time, Yi In Jwa.
Baek Dae Gil!
Subtitles by DramaFever