Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 23]
Baek Dae Gil.
It's been a long time, Yi In Jwa.
Was this your doing?
You should give up now.
You have lost your horses
and provisions in the fire.
Half your troops are down
due to stomach illness.
Advancing is not possible, Yi In Jwa.
No, it's too early to give up.
This is His Highness, Mil Poong Goon.
So, it is you, Baek Dae Gil.
The government will use the
entire military to stop this rebellion.
I hear that the king is gathering
50,000 troops.
All five branches of the military
will join and occupy Anseong.
Isn't that true?
You must have been very scared.
You even got yourself
a spy in the palace.
The cause of the great plan
is still alive and well.
We have over 10,000 men left here.
We also have over 100,000 men in
Gyeongsang-do and Jeolla-do.
So, go ahead and try to stop me.
I'll look forward to seeing you try.
Give up on this now.
Are you planning on
killing everyone here?
Everyone here volunteered to be here
and are my fellow comrades in this fight.
Who do you think you are?
Soon... everyone will find out.
They will know what you're truly like.
You will do whatever it takes
to get the throne.
You're willing to sacrifice
innocent people for your own ambition.
I will stop you.
I will send all of you back into
the arms of your families.
We will advance forward
without the injured and ill.
Instead of using horses,
we will use strong bindings and carts.
Send out messages.
Find out the movements of
Gyeongsang-do and Jeolla-do.
Dae Gil, I was so worried about you.
Let's get things organized.
By the way, there are people watching...
I wouldn't mind having a sword.
Grandpa, stop thinking useless thoughts.
Go help out over there.
So, only you get to have a sword?
Gather around, everyone!
We'll be handing out food to everyone.
Take some and go home, everyone.
Don't go around bleeding,
getting broken bones.
Come on, everyone!
Get up and come get your share.
Everyone, come this way!
Over here! Come over here!
You can take this medicine for that.
You should hurry before it gets worse.
Come this way. Over here, everyone!
Here you go.
Here.
Were you cut?
Oh my... where are you from?
Dae Gil.
We've handled the stomach illness.
We also handed out a lot of food,
but we still have plenty left over.
Oh, that's a relief.
You should head outside.
Everyone is waiting to hear from you.
What is going to happen to us?
We took part in a rebellion.
They say anyone who took part in it
will be put to death.
You have all put down your weapons,
so that will never happen.
Is that really true?
The king has promised it.
Anyone who puts down their weapons
will be forgiven.
He was very clear about this.
You may all return home now
with the food you have received.
Is that true?
Did the king promise that?
The 50,000 men under your command
have just passed Gwacheon.
However, to stop Jeong Hee Ryang and
Park Pil Hyun's 100,000
that will not be nearly enough.
If we cannot stop them at Anseong...
It's only a matter of time
before we lose the capital city.
Your Majesty!
I have message for you from Mokcheon.
Baek Dae Gil has
cut their forces in half.
Yi In Jwa's 30,000 men
are reduced to half
but they are still headed to Anseong.
Although he has only half his men
we will lose Anseong
if we do not get there in time.
It will take the military two days
to get to Anseong.
We cannot waste a single moment.
I must go myself.
Your Majesty!
It is too dangerous for you
to go there directly.
They are coming right at me.
Shall I sit idly by and
give up my palace, as well?
We cannot waste another moment.
Prepare to leave at once.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I'd better send Dae Gil a message.
There is no need.
What do you mean?
No matter what happens in the city,
Dae Gil will follow his plan.
His plan?
The rebels should be approximately here.
However, the men will be suffering from
exhaustion as they have not eaten.
They will stop by this village
before heading to Anseong.
My lord, the men are very tired.
It's hard enough to get there
in two days instead of four.
We have no food or horses.
If we continue on like this
they will all pass out
before we arrive in Anseong.
We will rest in the nearby village.
They may end up looting this village.
You should take the rest of our food
and go to this village.
This is from your Master, Kim Chae Gun.
I have tracked down Jeong Hee Ryang.
I will keep my promise to you.
I will make sure that innocent people
do not get hurt.
I will have to trust Master
to take care of the South.
And now what?
I'll have to move on to
the next part of the plan.
A three part plan?
First, take the horses and provisions
in order to slow down the rebels.
That doesn't sound easy.
The rebels have a weakness.
They've gathered from all eight cities
and do not know one another well.
I recently received a message and
it appears they have succeeded.
Is that true?
Let's stay strong.
We're almost there.
They've lost half of their men.
Then what is the second part?
It will be to stomp out the rebellion
rising up at Cheongju Fortress.
"Yi In Jwa's rebellion has failed."
We will spread that rumor.
Oh, that's a great idea.
No one will be able to verify
the truth of that rumor.
Those who considered taking part in the
rebellion will have to be careful.
Where are all of the soldiers?
There's a rumor that's been going around.
There's a rumor that Yi In Jwa
was defeated at Anseong.
How could you be so stupid?
You don't actually
believe that rumor, do you?
I don't necessarily believe it,
but I cannot ignore it either.
I apologize but I can't help you.
I can't give you what I promised.
What do you think you're doing?
If you pull out on me now,
you will likely betray me.
I can't let you go.
Why, you rascal...
I suppose this is what
I should expect from a rebel.
Arrest them all, right now!
Yes, sir!
Stop them!
You had people hiding?
I never did trust those who make a
living off the government.
Hold on and watch a little longer.
Dae Gil.
The military has left the palace.
I will give you five days.
If I do not hear from you in five days...
I will use my military.
Grandpa, it's become urgent.
I've got to go now.
Take care of the rest for me.
Where are you going by yourself again?
Anseong.
I have to meet the king
before something happens.
My lord, they've been starving all day.
If we keep going like this...
Find a little more strength, everyone.
According to news we received
from Yeongnam and Honam
it will be two days...
just two more days.
We will be joining 100,000
of our men in Anseong.
Then we will accomplish our great plan.
My lord, look at them.
They will not last half a day,
let alone two days.
Look!
- I think you can eat this.
- It's food!
What is it? Let's see.
You can eat it.
What is it? What is it?
Give it to me! Give me some!
Get me 20 of the best men.
What are you doing? Hurry up.
My lord.
Isn't it wrong to steal food
from these villagers?
It is only enough to get us to Anseong.
Do you want to give up on everything
over a few meals?
Let's load it up.
Hey, stop!
Stop!
You can't do this!
Do you know what this food is to us?
Oh my...
You all deserve to die.
Do you have nothing better to steal that
you'd steal from farmers like us?
If you're going to take this,
you're going to have to kill us first!
You're going to have to kill us!
I won't give this up even if I die,
so go ahead and try!
- That's right!
- Just try it!
Then there's nothing I can do.
I want you to lock them all up in here.
The rest of you should start
loading up the food.
What are you planning to do?
Anyone who holds us back from
heading to Anseong...
I will kill them all.
What? What?
No matter who that is.
What did you say?
Do you want to do this?
Do you?
Why are you telling me
to lock them up in here?
It's a sacrifice for our great plan.
That's all you need to know.
Are you crazy?
I will enrich this nation
and make it stronger.
I will repay their souls.
I can't watch innocent people
die like this.
Are you going to destroy our plans?
Do you really not know that all of this
is a sacrifice for our salvation?
[Jukju Mountain Fortress]
How many soldiers have gathered here?
Right now, there are 35,000.
We will be getting 20,000 more
from Suwon and Yongin.
Where are the rebel troops now?
They have not arrived in Anseong yet.
According to our scout, Baek Dae Gil has
taken Yi In Jwa's horses and provisions.
There is a rumor in Jeolla-do that
Yi In Jwa has been defeated.
It seems this is the work
of Baek Dae Gil.
Is there a reason you are confident
you can stop Yi In Jwa?
Do you have a plan?
First, I will use his weakness and
slow down his troop movements.
I will reduce the number
of his men by half.
Second.
What's scarier than
a sword... is a rumor.
Rumor?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I will use rumors to cut off
Yi In Jwa's arms and legs.
What's your next move after that?
My third plan is...
There are 100,000 men coming from
Jeolla-do and Gyeongsang-do.
Everything will be over if we fail.
Oh, I'm so tired. Goodness.
Oh my...
Oh my.
I know you are all tired.
Hang in there a little longer.
You all look terrible.
What don't you give up now?
Why would you say such a weak thing?
This is not the kind of nation I wanted.
I heard that you plundered a village.
It was a choice I had to make.
Do you think it was the right choice?
Follow me.
No one has touched the food.
These men are citizens of this land
before they are your troops.
They wished for a better nation,
a nation that was for the people.
That is why they stepped up.
How could they eat food
plundered from villagers?
It is not plunder. It's a sacrifice.
What meaning would there be to sit on the
throne after sacrificing the people?
Anseong is within our reach,
Your Highness.
The throne will be yours in half a day.
Have you come this far
by treating people this way?
You have plundered a village
and even killed its people.
Why did you do it?
I may be starving...
but w did not want to steal from
innocent people.
I told you all many times
to keep your mouths shut.
I... am here because of His Highness,
Mil Poong Goon.
I am not here because of you.
What did you say?
If you value your lives...
watch your mouths!
You...
How dare you murder someone in front of
me without a second thought!
Your Highness.
Please trust me.
I promise to you that
I will get you on the throne.
You did not need to kill him!
Bury him somewhere nice.
I'd like to be alone.
I am sorry.
Your Majesty, why haven't you
kept your promise to me?
Didn't you promise to give me five days?
It will be five days today.
So, have you brought me Yi In Jwa?
I know you have accomplished a lot.
You have reduced his troops by half.
You slowed his advancement by
taking his horses and provisions.
However... that is all you can do.
Now, I will put an end to this rebellion.
Are you going to draw your sword
against your own people?
They are your people, your children.
They have deserted me.
So, they will be punished by the sword.
Your Majesty, I did not
use my sword even once.
Do you know how I managed to
reduce Yi In Jwa's troops by half?
It was faith.
It was faith in the people.
Thank you.
Go on and live well now.
That's about 15,000 men.
All those men have put down their swords.
What do you think that means?
We can do this.
Without drawing swords
and without drawing blood...
we can end this revolt.
He will arrive here soon.
If we lose control of this place,
it will give them access to the capital.
No matter how many men are in the palace,
it will be difficult to stop them.
So, I am considering
evacuating before then.
It is absolutely imperative...
that we defeat them in this place.
Your Majesty!
The rebels have arrived.
We are finally here in Anseong.
Have we heard anything from
Yeongnam and Honam?
Yeongnam has just left Jincheon.
Honam has passed Pyeongtaek.
It will take half the morning
for them to arrive.
If the soldiers attack us before then...
we are done.
Don't you worry.
I have a hidden card inside.
Look at them.
Those troops...
Do they look like regular people to you?
Kill all the rebels.
Your Majesty!
Yi In Jwa, Mil Poong Goon,
and all the rebels.
Do not leave a single one alive.
Move aside!
You can't do this, Your Majesty.
You dare to disobey me?
They are your people.
They are traitors.
Please be merciful.
They do not know what mercy is.
That is why I fight them with my sword.
What about me?
Will you turn on me, as well?
If you choose to join hands with rebels,
I will cut your throat.
Your Majesty.
I made a promise to the late king
that I would always protect you.
But, from this moment on...
I cannot keep that promise.
What do you think you're doing?
How dare you...
King...
It is time for you to die!
Members of the
defeated party still exist?
The government is so corrupt.
Wouldn't it be more odd
if there weren't any?
Since the Queen Dowager
joined forces with me...
two of the military leaders have
turned their backs on the king.
The naive king has come all the way here.
He will end up losing his life.
Finally... the king is dead.
The fortress doors will open soon.
We will accomplish our dreams.
Now... we will advance to Hanyang!
Are you all ready?
Your Highness, you should enter first.
March forward!
Baek Dae Gil.
Retreat!
From this moment on,
you are no longer rebel troops!
Yi In Jwa had no great plan.
The only thing he had was
self-interest and greed.
Your Highness,
I have been waiting for you.
I heard you were looking for me.
I asked you what the
third part of your plan was.
If the troops in Honam and Yeongnam
are Yi In Jwa's arms
His Highness, Mil Poong Goon,
is the sword in his hand.
The dagger he holds close to his heart
are the spies he's hidden in the palace.
Mil Poong Goon and radicals from the
defeated party are working together.
How will you get them to come out?
I will get the rebels following
Mil Poong Goon to come here.
You will use Mil Poong Goon as bait?
How will you find out who these spies
are from the defeated party?
I...
will draw my sword and
hold it against your throat.
I had my doubts.
But, there are two of you.
I cannot believe the two of you.
Put down your weapons.
If you all surrender, you will live.
The king has promised this.
Put down your weapons
before I change my mind.
Do not be afraid.
The revolt will end soon.
You will all go home soon.
You have saved the people again.
However, your work here is done now.
I will take care of the rest.
- Your Majesty...
- Mil Poong Goon.
I will determine what to do with you
once I deal with this revolt.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, pull back your sword.
Soon, 100,000 rebel troops
will come upon this place.
If I lose this opportunity now,
it will be over for the capital city.
Unless I attack first...
Anseong will be seized
along with the capital city.
I'm sure the second part
of my plan will work.
Have you received word?
Has Park Pil Hyun been stopped?
Have you confirmed that
Jeong Hee Ryang has been stopped?
Tonight is the last night.
We barely made it back to camp.
Mil Poong Goon rejected the throne
when it was handed to him.
My lord, it's going to be hard now.
We only had half the men to begin with.
Now, we have lost another half.
Get all the commanding officers in here.
I have something to discuss.
Your Majesty, please reconsider
one more time.
There is nothing you can get
without sacrifice.
How can you force sacrifice
on your people?
Once the revolt is over...
I will plead for forgiveness.
I will prepare funerals for them
and give relief to the poor.
You say that I am forcing others to
sacrifice themselves?
As for me...
I am prepared for the disgrace of
being labeled a tyrant.
Your Majesty.
- What is it?
- Just stand here.
Stand right there.
Hold that.
You have to stand there.
What do I do?
But, what are we standing here for?
They will all die!
We still have over 8,000 men.
We can hold out.
Park Pil Hyun and Jeong Hee Ryang
will join us soon.
The military will have over
five times as many men.
Do you really not know this?
My lord, this isn't right.
- This isn't right.
- We've come this far!
Do you know what it took to get this far?
Victory is right in front of us.
So many died for this.
Have you forgotten the tens of thousands
who have died to make this happen?
Tonight...
there will be an attack.
I will order an attack myself.
The military is here.
The time has finally come.
Are you ready?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Attack!
Stop!
Your Majesty, please stop.
It is too late.
Those people standing there
are just shields.
They are rebels who have
committed treason.
Kill them all.
Do not leave anyone standing.
Shoot!
Get up.
Wake up and open your eyes.
Hey!
Wake up!
Stop!
Please stop.
Take a good look at what's going on.
Is this... is this the great plan
that you wanted so badly?
You cannot achieve anything great
without making sacrifices.
Stand guard and stop them from entering!
Aim.
Your Majesty!
Stop, stop!
Stop!
Please don't shoot! You can't do this.
Please spare them.
Stop the attack.
Seol Im...
Your Majesty, please trust me.
That is very commendable of you.
However, I have no intention of
protecting those who
took part in the revolt.
Then, I will show you.
I will show you whether they are
really rebels or just good people.
What?
Please just watch.
I will show you.
Attention.
Stop the attack.
Baek Dae Gil.
It is not over yet.
You are finished.
However...
you do have a choice to make.
The lives of everyone here
will depend on the choice that you make.
If we cared about our lives,
we would not have started this at all.
I, Yi In Jwa...
can be buried here,
in this spot, with all of these people.
I will join hands with you.
After all this time,
you say you will join me?
Baek Dae Gil, you?
You have lost many people
that were following you.
Mil Poong Goon has
turned his back on you.
You have no right to the throne.
So, what?
I will promise you
with my life on the line.
If you can prove to me
that you are right...
I will do it.
Prove myself?
How will I prove myself?
Let's leave it to the heavens.
What?
Your Majesty, we should not
sit here and watch.
Your Majesty?
Wait.
Do you remember this coin?
I put my life on the line
for this one coin.
It also saved my life.
This coin changed my life.
So, this will decide our fate
and the fate of Joseon.
Let's put it all on this one round.
All right.
Let's do that.
Let's be clear about this one thing.
Make this promise in front of
all the people here.
If I win...
give up on everything.
If you do end up winning...
I will give up on my plan.
Make your choice.
Front side.
The side with the words
"Sang Pyung Tong Bo."
Then, I choose the back.
I am curious.
Will the heavens choose you?
Or will they choose me, Yi In Jwa?
Do you know what?
I don't make bets
unless I'm sure I'll win.
As you promised, give up
on everything and go to prison.
I'm sorry, but I can't keep my promise.
Yi In Jwa.
After tonight...
a large group of rebel troops from
Yeongnam and Honam will join us.
Do you think 100,000 men won't be able
to take Jukju Mountain Fortress?
Jeong Hee Ryang and Park Pil Hyun
are finished already.
What are you talking about?
They are finished already.
Park Pil Hyun from Honam had been
tied down to begin with.
You were not farmers, after all.
It's the same for
Jeong Hee Ryang in Yeongnam.
I received messages from them.
They told me they would be arriving soon.
Was that you?
You don't think I only
tied them down, do you?
Whether or not you end up dying...
you ought to repent for your crimes.
Then... even Park Pil Hyun?
I heard that Yi In Jwa is
leaving blood wherever he goes.
A great plan that involves the killing
of innocent people.
So, this is the "great plan"
you all talked about?
You shouldn't dare to speak his name.
He is not someone to speak of that way.
I will make sure to see if you're so
talkative once you are beheaded.
Please go on with your work.
There are no support troops coming.
So, give up now.
Your greedy ambition will never happen.
What did you say?
What are you doing? Take him now!
Hwang Jin Ki.
What are you doing?
You said so yourself.
A nation for the people...
You said you'd get a king for the people.
Not only could you not feed the
starving people.
You used the stomachs of the people
as a shield for arrows!
I was very conflicted about it.
Should I let you live?
Or... should I die with you?
You were someone I considered
my master at one time.
It should be me who sends you off.
Let's not make this any worse
than it has to be.
No!
His life belongs to the people.
Now is not the time.
Put down your weapons and surrender!
Put down your weapons!
- Arrest him!
- Yes, sir.
Yi In Jwa.
It is over now.
Dae Gil...
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Daebak]
Don't even think about dying easily.
Apologize to the people before dying.
You will all come to realize that you
needed someone like me!
Are you saying he won't give up,
even after death?
Who could've poisoned the Crown Prince?
I want you to bring
every possible suspect to me.
The people in the eight cities want
Baek Dae Gil to become king.
Can the king return to his old self?
I have come here because they say there
is a man who pretends to be a king.
I have come to kill you today.