Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
I'm here for you,
Ma Ri.
Is it you, Ji Won?
Honey, this is your party.
We can talk after the party.
Ji Won.
Pull yourself together. Everyone is watching you.
(EPISODE 05)
Swan.
Ji Ryoon, who was that?
Who is it?
What is going on?
With Ms Yoon fainting and the lights flickering...
Did you see the man?
Who knew she had a secret lover?
Mother, watch what you say.
I think the party is over, Swan. Let's go.
Okay.
I'm sure it's Cha Ji Won.
So?
Cha Ji Won, the heir of Sunwoo Group, is back.
The heir?
- I believe he is a murderer.
- Well...
You're right.
How could he show up here so confidently?
Do you think he has evidence to clear his name?
Clear his name?
Watch your mouth.
You don't want to die in an accident because of what you say.
What did he say?
That old man acted calm, but I can tell he's on his tiptoes.
How dare he threaten me?
Chairman Cha's son is back!
Father.
What brings you here?
I thought you were busy dating and training.
Training must have been tough.
You've become so dark.
Why don't we go fishing like old times?
Want me to make you spicy fish stew?
Yes, please.
You told me he was dead. Why did you?
How was I supposed to expect anyone to survive that explosion?
I have to meet Ji Won.
What do you have left to say to him?
Did you forget that we're married?
Where are you?
Why did you do it?
- Do what?
- Ma Ri.
How could you marry Ma Ri?
One of the reasons for me to be alive is gone.
You're dead.
- I found your number chain there.
- Why did you find just that?
You should've looked for me.
Stop hiding, and show yourself. Then we'll talk.
Cha Ji Won!
About Ji Won...
I didn't get to meet him.
I think he just left.
Sun Jae, that idiot!
- How could he leave loose ends?
- Should I get rid of Cha Ji Won?
Sun Jae was the last one who shot him.
We shouldn't interfere in a fight between friends.
I was considering giving Sun Jae a chance,
but I don't think we have to.
I'll have to take over Sunwoo Group.
As long as we get the development rights to the casino complex resort,
Sunwoo Distribution will become the holding company.
We'll stick to the original plan,
and I can become the real owner of Sunwoo Group.
We just need one more signature to purchase the land.
(PARK HO SIK IS THE LAST LANDLORD OF BUSINESS CONSTRUCTING SITE.)
- Hello.
- Is this Panda News?
I have a message for Reporter Seo.
It's related to Kim Jung Ho from the Mount Cheonggye incident.
We're not interested.
Hello?
Who was that?
I don't know, he was saying something about Mount Cheonggye.
- Hello.
- Don't hang up and listen.
Are you calling about the Mount Cheonggye incident?
Yes!
If you want to know anything about Kim Jung Ho and the case,
go to the address, 78-2 Jung-gu,
and look for Park Ho Sik.
Can I have the informant's name?
The Mount Cheonggye incident is about the guy that slipped.
Is that right?
- I found Park Ho Sik.
- Let me see.
(PARK HO SIK)
Where do I know that voice from?
The number was 39 Mo 8829.
I know this man. I saw him at Kim Jung Ho's funeral.
Does that mean he's the murderer?
What are you talking about?
- Stop talking about...
- We have to find this man!
I just got a call...
saying he's related to Kim Jung Ho.
So what?
What do you mean what? We have to cover it!
You should fix your face first.
It annoys me. It annoys me a lot.
What's wrong with him these days?
He has an emotion control disorder.
Let's go.
The address is 78-1 Jung-gu. Let's go catch Park Ho Sik ourselves.
If Leech finds out, he will kill us.
- Should I go alone then?
- Please go alone.
I guess I'll be okay by myself. It will be just a little dangerous.
Hey!
This is the right address, but the building looks empty.
No. Look at the rubbish.
An empty building can't have that much rubbish.
I see one gangster.
I think you're right. It must be an illegal VVIP gambling place.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I have to disguise myself.
- I will go bring Park Ho Sik.
- Wait.
Hey! Swan!
Make sure you strengthen the surveillance.
- Keep a close watch on everywhere.
- Yes.
I saw an advertisement that you're looking for a waitress.
Your identification card?
What's this?
Are you a Korean or a foreigner?
I used to live in Thailand, but I came here to earn money.
Please don't report me.
That's good.
Come with me.
I can keep the tip, right?
We confirmed that Cha Ji Won arrived in Korea yesterday...
- as a French national.
- Black.
We don't know what he did in Thailand after the explosion.
He joined the French Foreign Legion and earned the French citizenship.
- Is that all?
- The French army is confidential.
There's no record of him entering Korea in the last five years,
so it's certain that he hasn't been in Korea.
Are you feeling okay? You should take some more rest.
I never got to visit the hospital since it opened.
I have a lot of work to do.
Thank you.
For what?
For everything.
Let's get rid of that scar.
It makes me feel bad whenever I see it.
- I can do it at your hospital.
- Yes.
It will be just a moment. I will give this to her and leave.
I will go.
I just have to give her this.
But Madam doesn't eat things like this.
- Hello, Father.
- Hello, Ma Ri.
I heard this is...
the best for getting girls pregnant.
Yesterday, I took a guest to Gangwon Province.
I went inside a field and caught these myself.
Was it a rice field?
Anyway, I didn't get to work...
all day yesterday to catch these.
Thank you.
Here.
Gosh, you didn't have to do this.
Please cook it well for her.
Don't eat it all while pretending to taste it.
- Father.
- Yes?
Sun Jae is still home.
Is that right?
Then I should leave now.
I'm leaving.
- Take care of yourself. Bye.
- Okay.
What's the use of calling me Father?
She never invites me for a meal.
Gosh, well...
I can't wish my daughter-in-law to treat me well when my son doesn't.
The customer must be near this hotel.
- Did you call the taxi, Sir?
- Yes.
Where are you headed?
Take me to the nearest gukbab restaurant.
Sure.
By the way, why don't you eat at the hotel?
I don't like the hotel food.
Your taste is just like mine.
Are you... Gosh!
Hello, there!
- Come on!
- There you go!
- Yes!
- I got it.
- Gosh...
Hi, there.
Where is Park Ho Sik?
What? What's wrong?
You want me to look there?
Yes, Sir.
Can I take her out?
Do one thing at a time.
It's either gamble or woman.
I always do three things at the same time.
Gambling, woman and booze.
Give me something strong.
Okay.
She's mine.
What a lunatic!
Hello?
Do you deliver jokbal?
What's this now?
If this is a prank call, I will kill you!
I am sorry.
Khaya?
Why is she there?
He's there.
(PROMISSORY NOTE)
Here you go.
No thanks.
Do you want some juice?
You reported to Panda News, right?
Gosh, I don't have money. I can't give you tip.
I am not asking for tip.
Please meet me outside. I'm from Panda News.
Panda what? What about it?
What's wrong with this girl?
Is she crazy? Hey!
Don't bother him today.
Okay.
What do I do?
I never believed it.
You must not have killed...
It doesn't make sense that you are a murderer.
You are the best.
By the way,
is it okay for you to go around in public?
You're a murderer.
You said you didn't believe it.
Of course I don't,
but the world isn't like me.
Eat.
Eat some kimchi, too.
By the way, what will you do next?
- I should turn myself in.
- Turn yourself in?
I haven't done anything wrong, but I need to find Ji Soo.
Only family members can file a missing report, right?
Hey, you can't.
You can't do that.
You know that I'm an expert in that area.
If you get a crime record, your life will be doomed.
You could be locked up in jail for the rest of your life.
Don't do it.
Just run away, okay?
I'm sick of running away.
Don't worry.
I'll buy a well-renowned law firm and go on the trial...
to clear my name.
What? You'll buy a law firm?
- Where will you get the money from?
- What?
I'm the only son of Sunwoo Group's chairman. I have inheritance.
- Oh, what?
- Sun Jae has grown the company.
I'm sure it won't be a big deal.
You'll bring food for me if I get locked up, right?
What? Of course. Eat up.
Oh, is someone calling me?
I had a call. I'll be right back.
(MY SON)
You're here early.
You'll need to get rid of Cha Ji Won before the shareholders' meeting.
If he causes trouble again,
- I won't stop him this time.
- No.
You'll need to work harder to stop him.
Did you already forget the Chairman Cha incident?
And one more thing.
Make sure that the casino complex resort business is trouble-free.
Do not disgrace Sunwoo Group which I've worked so hard to protect.
It looks like I was worried for nothing.
I'm glad to know that these things don't scare you any more.
Is there anything else you want to say?
Your father wants to speak to you urgently about your friend.
Answer the call. Your father is waiting.
- Hello?
- Sun Jae. Don't hang up.
Ji Won is back.
He wants to turn himself in to find Ji Soo.
Pardon?
The bigger problem is...
he wants his money back.
He said that he'll claim his inheritance.
You have to take up the chairman position soon.
What should we do?
Where are you now?
- I'm asking you now!
- Oh, yes. Sorry.
Well... We are...
You know that main road, right?
You seem to be very busy.
I got the bill. I'll see you again.
Hey, Ji Won. Ji Won!
Hello?
He will turn himself in?
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Me, too.
Gosh, spending money is tiring.
Oh, have you heard?
Everyone is saying that Ms Yoon is seeing someone else.
Aren't you the one who spread the rumour?
What good would spreading that kind of rumour do for us?
It's better for us that Ms Yoon doesn't get divorced.
Sunwoo Construction will be split in half if she demands the partition.
Why do people want that happy couple to get divorced?
People are so mean.
Don't try to protect her just because you're close to her.
Even five years ago, she was going to marry Chairman Cha's son...
and sent out wedding invitations but ended up marrying her friend.
She's something else.
Yes, I'm here. I'll go out.
Hello. I'm really sorry about yesterday.
I'll visit you soon.
- She must've heard us.
- Gosh, what should we do?
Your husbands could lose their jobs because of your chatters.
Goodness, you should really watch what you say.
He is really picky,
so I'd love some help with styling.
This is my first time in Korea, so I don't know my way around.
It's your first time in Korea?
Your Korean is so good!
I live with a Korean man.
So you're married?
I don't have to be married to live with someone, right?
- What's the matter?
- I felt like someone was following.
Oh, right. Have a meal with the president of MRB Funds.
The strength of the distribution channel won him over,
but he initially wanted to work with Sunwoo Construction.
The president of MRB Funds is in Seoul now.
It looks like the two live together.
- Shall I arrange a dinner?
- You're better than Mr Choi.
Don't work too hard. I'll see you at home.
Okay.
Call me right away if he gets in touch.
Yes, of course.
I'm your dad, so I'll look out for you.
No matter how close I am with Ji Won, I'll always be on your side.
You should go now.
Yes, okay.
But Sun Jae.
Five years ago,
you didn't actually do anything to Ji Won...
- and Chairman Cha, did you?
- Get off.
Yes, okay. I'll go now.
Don't skip meals, okay?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
May I try it on...
if you're not going to buy it?
Gosh, no. I don't like plaid.
I only wear solid colours.
You can't go for a movie wearing that!
Goodness. It's dark, so no one will even see me.
What about me? You don't think I have eyes?
You wear the same thing every day.
It embarrasses me!
Ma Ri. Do I really embarrass you?
I'm going to embarrass you more.
Wear this.
- Hey, how could you...
- All right.
Let's go. Let's go to the room and get changed.
Hang on.
We're... We're going to the room?
Shall we shoot a movie instead of watching one? An erotic film?
Goodness! Stop it!
Listen to me, okay?
From now on and forever,
- only wear things I approve, okay?
- For the rest of my life?
Do you like me that much, Ma Ri?
- Goodness. Hey!
- Ouch!
- Ouch! My arm!
- Gosh.
I can't?
I want to wear what you picked out.
Ms Yoon?
What do you think of this one?
Let's browse more.
It's me.
Come to my place if you have something to say.
Pretend that you don't know me here.
I told you to wait for me.
Don't do this.
- I'm with an important guest.
- I told you to wait.
You promised me.
It's all in the past.
Did you not read...
the card I sent you?
What card?
Don't show up before me like this ever again.
Ma Ri, Merry Christmas.
It's still summer here.
I miss you even in my dreams.
Christmas in the middle of summer.
I feel like I'm still in my dream.
Don't forget that I'll come back for you no matter what it takes.
Father.
Why did you do that?
Why?
I'm going to die in front of them...
to go back to you.
Don't be too shocked even if you hear that I'm dead.
You look good in that jacket.
I do?
Yes, it's cut out for you.
Remember our promise...
that we'll get married barefoot on the beach.
I won't ever die and leave you behind.
I love you. From Ji Won.
That's all.
Let's go with this schedule.
Once Sunwoo Distribution buys the land for the resort,
we'll sign the contract.
There won't be much difference from signing right now.
If it gets behind the schedule and the construction takes longer,
we'd have to wait longer to get our investment back.
We'll deal with it by this month.
If you feel uncomfortable,
you can add articles regarding the land and construction period.
In that case,
I want a higher compensation in case you breach the contract.
Of course.
In return, I'd like the deposit of 20 million dollars...
by this week.
- This week?
- If you're going to work with us,
you should speed things up.
MRB Funds isn't the only investment company we can work with.
He is going firm.
We'll need the money as soon as possible.
Don't grudge.
You'll get way more in return soon enough.
President Kim.
Hey, Black.
Were you at the party?
That's why you weren't surprised.
Are you sure you'll be okay fighting against them?
You could report to the police if I seem to be in trouble.
Everyone is ignoring me.
They're hiding a criminal, aren't they?
It would be interesting to go to prison with Sun Jae.
I shouldn't go to prison without my friend.
- Then should I...
- I won't tell anyone I met you.
Hey, Ji Ryoon!
Woo Jin.
I'm sorry, I didn't know he had a visitor.
We need to talk.
Where is Swan?
I don't know.
What were you thinking when you introduced her to me?
I don't have time. Give me the money.
I don't owe you any money.
Where is it? I'll go.
I have to be the one going.
I have to be the one to find Swan.
I don't care if it's cash or a credit card. I need something.
- Call me if anything happens.
- Okay, thanks.
I'll take care of some errands and contact you again.
I'm sorry. That was a friend of mine.
He's the editor-in-chief of news company Swan works for.
Aren't you curious how Swan is doing?
- I'm sure she's doing fine.
- She's still searching for Ji Soo.
Why? I'll find Ji Soo.
Please tell her to stop.
She won't listen to me.
You know how headstrong she is.
Everyone thought Black was dead, but Swan was the only one...
who believed you were alive.
If you aren't going to go see her, make sure she doesn't find you.
- Wow!
- Yes, I won!
How long is he going to stay here?
Leech won't be happy about this if he finds out.
What?
I won't be here for long, so exchange these into big chips.
Where did you get that money?
Stay out of this. I'll get Park Ho Sik.
What?
This is your pay check. You're fired.
Says who?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Can I have a glass of water?
What should I do?
Got it.
We're to get Park Ho Sik's signature and get rid of him today.
Yes, sir.
We have to leave.
What do you think you're doing?
They're going to get rid of you like they did with Kim Jung Ho.
You know him, don't you?
Didn't I see you at the funeral?
- Be quiet.
- The reporter?
Hey!
- Who in the world are you?
- I told her to stay out of this.
This is all a scam!
You're all in this, aren't you?
How dare you!
Why you...
Mr Seo!
Why that little...
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
- Let's get out of here.
- It's the police!
Get them all!
Come this way!
- Mr Seo! Find Park Ho Sik.
- Are you all right?
I'll find him. You get out of here.
That way!
Come this way!
Get Park Ho Sik!
- We need to get his signature!
- Yes, sir.
- Close the door.
- What's this?
- Who called the police?
- Who was it?
- Goodness!
Move it!
Mr Park Ho Sik!
Wait in the car.
Get her!
Get Park Ho Sik!
Mr Park!
Catch her!
Stop right there!
- Hey!
- You!
Where's Park Ho Sik?
Stay still if you don't want to get hurt.
Stop right there.
Wait.
I told you to stop!
Stop!
It's me, Swan.
You're alive.
I knew you were alive.
Want a ride?
What are you doing?
It's Black.
I heard his voice. It's Black.
Are you out of your mind? Cha Ji Won is dead.
Hi, I'm Kim Swan.
I hope we can get along.
Take good care of her.
Good luck!
Ji Ryoon!
Come this way. I'll show you your desk.
Who is this? Your boyfriend?
No, he's my husband.
- It's going to be tough on you...
- Husband?
if you're married.
We work 24 hours.
I'll do my best.
Let me.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Cha Ji Won?
How long did you think you could fool me?
How can a dead person run away?
You're not even married.
I'm not lying.
He ran away and hasn't come back yet.
It was a fake marriage,
but we were able to hide behind it.
That's how we survived.
He made scrambled eggs for me...
and drew pictures when I told him I couldn't read.
What about Swan?
Swan.
He even named me. How could I forget his voice?
I know it's him.
Does he know...
that you're waiting for him?
I guess that isn't important.
In order to survive,
we need food more than anything.
I'm starving.
Let's go, I'll make you eggs.
We found nothing.
Don't worry. They won't find anything.
Make the delivery as soon as the sweep is done.
And find Park Ho Sik.
Make it quick and clean.
Okay.
He caught the bait. We just have to reel him in.
Why are you holding me here?
Are you kidnappers or what?
I'm going to sue you for kidnapping and locking me up.
We're having eggs for late night snacks from now on.
- What?
Don't you hear me?
I'm going to sue you.
Are you serious?
Those are all complaints.
Stand in line.
The door is open.
You can leave if you'd like.
Miss, you said the gang was going to get rid of me.
How am I supposed to feel safe out there?
How are you related to Kim Jung Ho, who died on Mount Cheonggye?
Do you have any hunches to why he died?
I couldn't say even if I knew.
How am I supposed to trust a tiny news company like this?
Good boy.
I'll buy you a soccer ball when you're back on your feet.
Ms Yoon?
What do you think?
I wore the clothes you picked out for me.
Am I good enough for you now?
The weather is too good to watch a movie today.
Let's go out.
I will follow you. Be careful with your driving.
Okay, Sir.
Where are we going?
We have to keep our promise.
We're going to the beach.
Ji Won.
Goodness! Is he crazy?
What is it?
What is he doing? Is he drunk?
Hey! what on earth...
He's caught. I knew it. He deserves it.
What is going on?
Hey! You should drive better!
Let go! Let go of me!
What's this now?
(BOSS)
Yes, Boss. I'm waiting.
The policemen are here.
You see the road sign, right? Turn right,
and make a turn towards the road on my side. That's it.
Okay!
- The number is currently busy...
- Gosh, he's talking on the phone.
Yes.
- Move the car.
- Okay.
Let's go!
Gosh.
Knife.
What's this?
What's this? Where did it go?
Smell it. Smell it.
When it comes to smell,
money smells the best.
(20 MILLION DOLLARS DEPOSITED)
MRB Funds deposited the balance.
I checked it.
Now, we just need to sign the contract.
The money disappeared.
What?
Stay still if you don't want to get hurt.
Is there no surveillance camera?
It feels nice.
You should try to walk barefoot.
I've missed you a lot.
Talk to me.
Let me hear your voice.
Five years have passed,
and you haven't changed a bit.
Is it bad that I haven't changed?
You wanted to hear my voice?
Then just listen.
Why didn't you die?
You should've just died.
- Ma Ri.
- I...
got married in less than a year after I heard your news.
I gave up looking for Ji Soo, too.
Sun Jae treats me so well...
that I managed to forget about you and Ji soo.
- Stop it.
- I've been living like that,
and I am happy now.
You shouldn't have come back.
I would've missed you every once in a while then.
I don't care if you forget me.
But it can't be Sun Jae. I can't let you be with Sun Jae.
He's the one I chose.
Do you want to hear more? Please forget me.
Like you said,
it's too late now.
Even if you will leave, listen to what I have to tell you.
Right before the explosion,
the last person I saw...
Madam.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(COPYING)
Thank you.
- I hope you catch the pickpocket.
- Thank you.
A guy named Black sent it. Check it.
Oh, and this...
This is the interest.
I sent President Kim 20 million dollars...
to pay the balance today.
It was unbelievable.
The money we managed to steal today...
turned out to be exactly 20 million dollars!
Good job. You can take the rest.
The rest? There's nothing left.
Look. There's nothing left.
So I thought about it.
I think we should make it 7 to 3 this time.
I rented a car and hired 30 men. On top of that...
Keep your words. You get exactly half.
See you, Black.
Sun Jae.
Ji Won.
You should've come to me.
What is this mess?
You know, right?
You know who was trying to kill you.
Mr Min Sun Jae!
President Min!
It's okay.
He's my friend.
You don't have to go to a hospital?
This won't kill me.
But you were too harsh on a friend you haven't seen in five years.
How can you hit me with your car?
I warned you with the light.
I did it so that you don't get attacked from behind.
I thought you were trying to kill me again.
Have you forgotten?
You tried to kill me at every simulation training.
Be careful.
Why did you show up out of the blue?
What did you do for the last five years?
I thought you would've found who tried to kill me by now.
Don't blame me.
I told you to come to me when we last spoke on the phone.
I couldn't go to you.
That jerk killed me.
That jerk who smelled gunpowder.
Is he really the last one you saw?
If he isn't?
(GOODBYE MR BLACK)
I should've looked for you more like you said. I made a mistake.
Dig up all you want. There is no evidence left.
I told you not to get caught.
You know Swan will get in danger if she is with me.
Is he sick? Why isn't he smiling at all?
Be quiet, and go.
I'm Black.