What are all these?
- Is this a bribe?
- Don't feel pressured.
I'm simply expressing my gratitude for supporting our foundation.
Then it's not a bribe. Thank you.
You should give it to your daughter.
She asked me for an interview, but I couldn't make time for it.
I don't know if Swan will wear it. It's too delicate for her.
By the way,
what happened? You didn't have a daughter until recently.
Actually, she's a girl...
Ji Ryoon brought from Thailand.
Thailand?
I guess it was five years ago.
It was around the time when Ji Won died.
Oh, I'm sorry. I shouldn't have brought it up.
- I am sorry.
- It's all right.
Black!
I told you this is precious. Why would you lose it?
I knew you'd be alive.
You haven't changed. You still fear nothing.
- Wait in the car.
- No, don't go.
Wait. I'll be back.
How did it go?
I'm going after her.
Got it.
Long time no see.
He said he'll be back.
I know he'll keep his word.
Tell me. Who hired you?
Your friend, Min Sun Jae.
Is it you, Sun Jae?
I don't care who you are.
You'll have to hide well to get away from me.
Do you know him?
No.
Remember his face.
He's the guy that smelled of gun powder.
He's the minion of the guy...
who killed my father and framed me as a murderer.
He must have been looking for me...
if he showed up here.
I asked him who hired him,
and he told me it was you.
What should I do with him?
Let him go so that he can go back to whomever is behind this.
I'll have someone follow him.
I knew I could count on you. We'll find the bad guy soon.
I'm glad I took your advice and didn't turn myself in.
How have you been?
Not very good.
I thought you forgot about me.
How could I?
You said we were so close.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Get rid of him since Ji Won knows who he is.
Take care.
When I called...
Why did you pretend not to know it was me?
You were asking for someone else. My name is Black.
Wow, you even drive.
It's nice to get away without having to run.
I miss running away with you hand in hand.
I barely survived. Be careful when you drive.
Look straight ahead.
Where are we going?
I don't know. I'm going to keep going forward.
- I'll look and push forward.
- Stop the car. I'll drive.
Swan!
I told you to stop the car.
Come on.
She's a girl Ji Ryoon brought from Thailand.
I guess it was five years ago.
It was around the time when Ji Won died.
I'm here to meet a reporter named, Kim Swan.
How do you know her?
I know her personally.
This is her seat. She'll be back soon.
Have a seat over there, and make yourself comfortable.
Hey, she must not be a human.
She's gorgeous.
Even I would look that good in heels and designer clothes.
Here. Why don't you go and get us some coffee?
Wake up.
That's her wedding photo. Haven't you seen it before?
Excuse me?
This place is packed. What if people notice you?
Everyone knows I'm back because of you.
What do you want?
I'll have the mango juice.
- Two of those, please.
- Okay.
(LEECH)
Why now?
I had some urgent matters to take care of.
Hey, Swan.
- It's a life or death matter.
- Where are you now?
I'll be there by 9pm.
Hello?
He hung up while I'm talking. He has no manners.
You seem busy.
- Shall we drink this on the way?
- I don't need to go anywhere.
I'm not busy at all. I'm totally not busy.
These lights here look like...
the sky lanterns we flew in Thailand, don't they?
Do you know what I wished upon the lanterns back then?
- I wished that we...
- Swan.
I have a favour to ask you.
You know everything, right?
You know what Baek Eun Do and Min Sun Jae did to me.
I will catch them.
I don't want you to get involved in this war.
You got it wrong. I'm doing it for myself, not you.
I saw them killing someone.
I obviously know who did it.
I can't pretend that I know nothing.
If you hadn't met me...
I would've been living off of garbage dumps...
while selling fake mango juice.
I would've lived just because I was alive and would've not cared to die.
Now, I know what I should do.
You've done so much for me.
I gained the desire to live after meeting you, Black.
It's just that what I want to do and what you have to do are the same.
- Swan.
- I have to be there until 9pm.
Let's go.
(PANDA MAGAZINE)
Go in. Be careful, okay?
You, too.
Thanks for being alive.
That's more than enough for me. Bye.
- Where is Ma Ri?
- She's not home yet.
- I'll give her a call.
- It's okay.
What if she rushes back and gets into an accident?
(CHA JI WON)
- It's nice to hear from you.
- Hello, this is Min Sun Jae.
Whenever I hear your voice, my heart flutters...
because it sounds so sweet.
Ms Yoon stopped by briefly in the afternoon.
Yes, I'm aware. I'm just calling to say hello.
I will visit you soon.
Please take care.
Focus. You better not make spelling mistakes.
I'll focus.
She smiled after being hit.
Something happened to you, right? Why are you humming?
You said you were busy earlier. What did you do?
- I just met with someone.
- Who is that someone?
- Just someone.
- What are you up to these days?
Yoon Ma Ri was here because of you.
Did you say Yoon Ma Ri?
Did she see this photo? She can't see this.
- Did she see this?
- I'm not telling you.
Mr Seo!
Why are you home so late?
You startled me.
I was worried about you.
Were you at Ms Jung's place until now?
Yes.
She wanted me to stay for dinner.
I was waiting for you to have dinner together.
- Did you take care of him?
- It's me.
- Ma Ri?
- I want to ask you something.
Could we meet up tomorrow?
Why do you sound so down?
Did something happen?
- Ma Ri.
- Let's talk in person.
- Meet me at 2pm.
- Okay. I'll see you there.
(RECENT CALLS)
(CHA JI WON)
(IS SUNWOO DISTRIBUTION A BROKER FOR ILLEGAL GAMBLING?)
The content is good.
- The spelling must be...
- I double-checked.
- Jae Woo.
- Yes.
Post it at 9am sharp on our website, and distribute it on the internet.
We'll meet again at 12pm. Sunwoo Distribution might counter attack.
Where are you?
- You told me to come.
- When did I say that?
Ji Ryoon, I'm going to break the news about Baek Eun Do today,
and I'm feeling nervous.
Do you happen to have any other information?
I do. Listen to me carefully.
At 2pm of this coming Wednesday at Red Moon Hotel.
A ceremony is held to celebrate MOA between Sunwoo Distribution and MRB.
They're making it a media day, okay?
- Okay. Then Ji Ryoon...
- Yes, Woo Jin.
I'll call you back later.
I'm sorry for making you come all the way here.
Not a problem at all. I'm happy to be here.
You'd like an extension on repayment of the debenture?
I'm preparing for a new business, so I need a capital fund.
Please kindly allow an extension.
May I ask you what kind of business it is?
It's still in the preparation stage.
I'll tell you when it becomes more concrete.
Sure. I trust you, Mr Min.
Take Sun Jae's side in whatever circumstances...
so that he doesn't give up the casino complex resort project.
Oh, no. I have to leave for my next meeting.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
If you want to look, be a man, and look at her properly.
Why are you hiding and peeking at her? You idiot.
When did I peek at her?
- Are you not leaving?
- You said we're meeting at 12pm.
You, silly. He's asking you out for a date.
Gosh, what are you talking about now?
Oh, right! I almost forgot.
Wear this.
Ms Yoon brought it for you.
- Why did she give this to me?
- Because you're my daughter!
You know how much influence we have on Sunwoo Group.
Do you control them?
- Did you receive a bribe from them?
- Shut it! Stop talking nonsense.
Okay. I'll get ready.
- Where are you going?
- Where do you think she's going?
- She has to get changed.
- Ouch.
Don't walk. You have to run to lose that big belly.
I might die of heart attack before I lose the belly.
I can't go any further.
Your daddy's going to die!
You go first!
My heart...
How evil she is!
She only got the bad things from me. I can't do it any more!
I will take some rest first. Gosh!
No way. It's not him, is it?
Hey.
Oh, dear.
Hey!
Gosh! Hey, you surprised me!
Meutong?
You got the wrong person.
The fat back and the big head! You are Meutong!
I am not!
Who is he?
He's a swindler. Catch him.
Whatever!
You swindler! I'm glad I caught you!
Hey! How dare you speak so rudely to an adult?
Khaya, you are just the same...
as when you lived off of garbage dumps.
Garbage dumps?
You call yourself an adult? You're a swindler who fabricate ID cards.
Who got me those ID cards?
You picked people's pockets and sold them to me!
Who picked people's pockets?
And I don't steal!
You are the one who sold me for a reward.
How could you do that to me? How could you?
Hey, I didn't get paid at all because you ran away!
Anyway, digging the past...
is dirty for both of us,
so let's not get involved with each other again. Okay?
Meutong!
- Who's here?
- Khaya!
That unbelievable girl appeared in front of my place...
with Seo Woo Jin!
What will you do now? Because you were driven by...
tiny bit of compassion for Khaya and saved her,
this tragic thing happened!
You see. If she continues to go around like that,
it will be a matter of time before people find out about you and us!
She might ruin everything before we even start our plan.
You take care of it.
Why are we going this way? We were walking that way.
By the way, how did you know I was here?
Did you follow me?
I wouldn't put it that way.
No.
Honestly, I was curious.
I was curious about who you were seeing.
I am a reporter after all.
A news reporter is supposed to dig whatever that intrigues...
I was just taking a walk. I wanted to be alone.
So you should go first.
- Hey, Swan.
- Or I will go first.
Never mind. I will go.
I am sorry for disturbing you.
I'll use my authority as an editor and give you an extra hour.
Just be back before 1pm.
Don't be late.
Is there no post-box here?
What are you doing here?
Black!
What are you doing?
Well, I came because I have something to give you,
but someone followed me.
And I saw Meutong. You know Meutong, right?
The fake doctor who's mad about money.
He might report you if he sees you. Be careful.
I think I made a mistake.
I shouldn't have appeared in front of you.
- What?
- I do my job.
And you do your job. Remember?
- You should go now.
- Wait.
Take this.
It's nothing, but I hope it will be helpful.
I was going to go after I give you this.
I didn't get to find Ji Soo,
but I am sure you can find her.
Don't worry. I will never come here again.
Still, watch out for Meutong. Okay?
I will go now.
(THE ARTICLE HAS BEEN POSTED.)
(SUNWOO DISTRIBUTION)
There you go.
(RECENT ARTICLES ABOUT SUNWOO DISTRIBUTION)
I wanted to look at it with him.
(THE PAGE IS NOT FOUND.)
(IS SUNWOO DISTRIBUTION A BROKER FOR ILLEGAL GAMBLING?)
I blocked it from going out and made sure they won't spread further.
What's going on?
Our website is down.
I think our server has been attacked.
What's wrong with this?
The article also went down.
Sunwoo Distribution must've done it.
They are so fast, aren't they?
They must be guilty since they acted so fast.
Be on stand-by for now. I will be right back.
Take the laptops and the important things! Hurry up!
Who are you?
- Mr Seo!
- Go!
Destroy everything.
So why would you write the article in the first place?
Leave the place!
Let's go! Hurry up!
(EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTRE)
I registered. How is Mr Seo?
Gosh, you are a troublemaker.
Why didn't you just die?
Isn't he Seo Jin Tak from Sunwoo Construction?
I didn't know, but he's Mr Seo's father.
It's better not to have a son like you anyway!
Why would you try to hurt your own father...
and get yourself in trouble?
Calm down, Sir.
Seriously!
- Sir.
- Move!
President Baek.
What brings you here?
It was you. Stop playing innocent.
How dare you touch my son?
Look what you've done to my son!
Do you think I will just watch this?
If I did it, it wouldn't have stopped there.
I would've killed him.
Then who was it?
It must be someone trying to ruin my business.
Why are you here?
Gosh, I am not sure...
if I should say this. Well...
Ma Ri is...
She said something absurd.
She said this company and the house belong to Ji Won.
She said we should return everything to him.
You are her husband, and yet she sided with Ji Won.
By the way,
is there a chance Ma Ri still has feelings for...
She didn't say anything wrong.
If Ji Won wants it back, I should give it back to him.
If there is something still left to give.
Madam. I thought you were a different person.
I thought it was a little hot today.
- Do I look strange?
- You look like a single woman.
Men will drool all over you.
Madam.
What brings you here?
I got an order from the president.
She is supposed to get a blood test today,
but he doesn't have time for it, so he sent me here.
He hates the thought of...
your lying on a bed all alone in a hospital.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Am I late?
You are supposed to meet my wife, aren't you?
She forgot she had an important check-up today.
So I came instead.
Why did you two plan to meet up?
What did you two have to talk about?
Is it something I shouldn't know about?
I guess.
We were going to share some secrets,
but you caught us.
We should get a drink.
Hello, it's me.
Did you get your blood test done?
I'll bring Ji Won home.
Did you meet him?
Why don't you show off your cooking for him?
The least we can do is invite our long-lost friend over for a meal.
I think he misses you very much.
All right. Come with him.
- A media day?
- It's at 2pm on Wednesday.
There will be the Memorandum of Association between the two.
- Let's aim for that day.
- Do you think we'll be okay?
Sunwoo Distribution seems like a bunch of bullies.
Don't let them intimidate you.
War correspondents even go to war.
We don't have to worry about bullets at least.
Can I ask what a media day is?
It's doing public relations with reporters from the major press.
There will be a lot of reporters that will blow the horn for us.
Just give them the bait.
They'll help us spread it.
They probably bribed all the reporters that are coming.
Don't worry beforehand.
- At least one will have conscience.
- I'll do it.
- Let's go and do this.
- Do you think it's that easy?
Not anyone can get in. We aren't allowed inside.
Don't you know ignorance is the route to courage?
Swan, make sure you get inside.
- Can I count on you?
- Of course.
I'll show you how ignorant and brave I am.
Hello?
Is it Kim Swan?
- Who is this?
- It's Yoon Ma Ri.
Make yourself at home. I'll go get changed.
Honey, Ji Won is here.
You're here.
Why did I bring up that interview?
Ma Ri, have a seat.
It's because you're here.
She never does any work around the house.
Oh, right. Ji Won changed his name.
It's Black. What do you think? Doesn't it suit him?
You have a guest.
You're here.
Hello.
Is she here to see you?
Have a seat.
Didn't you meet her at the party?
This is Kim Swan, President Kim Ji Ryoon's younger sister.
She's a reporter and wants to interview me.
I don't believe we were formally introduced.
Hi, I'm Min Sun Jae.
I can wait outside since you're having dinner.
It's okay.
Join us.
I guess we'll need more wine.
Honey, would you help me choose a bottle?
I didn't know you were here.
- I'll leave.
- It's fine.
Have a seat.
You seem weird today. Why would you invite her?
What if she recognises Ji Won?
You said he's Black.
What are you worried about when he even changed his name?
Even if she recognises him, she's President Kim's sister.
She won't report to the police.
- Ma Ri.
- This one looks good.
Should I get you something else?
No, this tastes good.
Here. I know you like this.
Thank you.
Oh, right. I stopped by your office yesterday, Swan.
Your colleagues are humorous.
Yes, I heard.
They told me you are married.
Is that true?
You got married at a young age.
No, it was just a joke.
- It was really a joke.
- Good.
I'd like to introduce you to someone.
What kind of men are you into?
Well, I...
like my men honest.
You must be in a good mood tonight.
Why wouldn't I be?
You said your name is Black, right? Why aren't you saying anything?
I seem to be doing all the talking.
Am I boring?
I had the guest room ready, so you can drink all you want.
Am I a guest here?
Ma Ri.
I missed your food.
Why don't we just enjoy it?
Swan, would you like another glass of wine?
No, I should get going.
You can call me later about the interview.
Ma Ri.
Ms Kim Swan!
I'll have our driver take you home. It's late.
- I'll be okay.
- My wife is sensitive these days...
because she's trying to get pregnant.
I'd like to ask you to write an article about Sunwoo Group later.
Could I ask you for that favour?
Didn't you read my article on Sunwoo Group today?
I should get going.
Why are you back?
What's the real reason?
Are you really here for me?
If I choose to go back to you,
will you accept me?
- Yoon Ma Ri.
- Answer the question.
Will you accept me if I choose to be with you?
This was unnecessary.
You lied to me first.
When you said that,
I was shaken.
- But you...
- You don't love me any more.
Cha Ji Won.
Why would you be confused if you still love me?
You would just choose me.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Do you think I'd let you go back to him?
Do you know what I did to win you?
Swan!
You're making me look back.
It's late. I'll take you home.
Go back. Why are you here?
You wanted to go back home.
That's your home. Where are you going?
Why are you acting like a fool?
Are you a just guest?
You said you miss Yoon Ma Ri.
Then go and make her yours again. You can't do that?
Shall I go and tell her?
You kept calling her name even when you were dying from getting shot.
You called out her name even in your dreams.
- Swan.
- If it's because of me,
I'll tell her that I'm fake.
It was a sham marriage.
I'll tell her that you had to lie in order to return to her alive.
I know how you're feeling. I know everything.
Don't look at me like that, Black.
(JI SOO IS ALIVE. I FAILED, BUT I'M SURE YOU'LL FIND HER.)
Ji Soo is alive.
Spero spera.
I failed,
but I'm sure you'll find her.
Black.
You need to take your medicine.
I told you not to forget. Don't act like a kid.
How much longer will I be able to live?
I don't know.
Don't forget to take your medicine before you go to bed.
Spero...
spera.
(JOINT VENTURE OF CASINO COMPLEX RESORT PROJECT, MEDIA DAY)
(LIST OF ATTENDEES)
- Sir!
- Please say a few words!
(CEREMONY OF MOA BETWEEN SUNWOO DISTRIBUTION AND MRB FUNDS)
We just arrived at Red Moon Hotel.
You ask the question to Baek Eun Do.
- You want me to do it?
- Be a fearless fool.
If you don't do a good job, you'll really be fired.
Don't worry. I'll make sure to do it.
I told you no other companies would want me except for Panda.
Swan, let's go.
I'll talk to you later.
Good luck, Swan.
Did it already start? Why is it so quiet?
Are we at the right place?
Oh, it's over there! Phantom Hall.
I have a weird feeling about this.
What's going on? Where are we going now?
I thought we were going to Red Moon Hotel.
This isn't the right way.
It's taking place at the head quarter due to urgent circumstances.
I see.
The venue has changed. It'll take place at the head quarter.
What's going on? No one is here.
Ji Ryoon.
Swan, there has been a venue change for the press conference.
It'll be at Sunwoo Group's head quarter.
How long will it take to get to Sunwoo Group from here?
It'll be 30 minutes without traffic. With traffic, I have no clue!
He is entering now.
(CEREMONY OF THE MOA BETWEEN SUNWOO DISTRIBUTION AND MRB FUNDS)
Now, we will begin the ceremony of the MOA between...
Sunwoo Distribution and MRB Funds.
(CEREMONY OF THE MOA BETWEEN SUNWOO DISTRIBUTION AND MRB FUNDS)
Now, a question and answer session will follow.
If you have any questions, please raise your hand...
and say your name as well as which media company you represent.
Is there any alternate route we can take?
The street is completely blocked up, so we can't move at all.
Gosh, Baek Eun Do!
I can't believe they went to this extent to leave us out.
Exactly.
They must be really scared of Panda.
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
You have a list of other reporters' phone numbers and user names, right?
Send it to me.
- Why do you need it?
- I'll upload the video of...
the interview with Park Ho Sik and text our article to reporters there.
Hey, Baek Eun Do invited all those reporters there.
It'll be a different story if we get there and break the news,
but they will just ignore the text message.
That's right.
There must be at least one person with conscience.
- Let's believe in justice.
- Gosh.
Hey, give her the phone numbers.
Let's believe.
President Baek, what is the final goal of this project?
Well, I'd like it to invigorate the tourism industry...
and contribute to the country's financial growth.
I'd like to create career opportunities for the young as well.
What a liar!
I got a text message.
What's going on?
(IS SUNWOO DISTRIBUTION A BROKER FOR ILLEGAL GAMBLING?)
- Illegal gambling? Check this out.
- Really?
Seriously?
It looks like we'll be here all night.
- Is it up yet?
- We sent out the text a while ago.
I don't see our article. I only see positive articles about them.
We did all the work and gave it away.
Hey! What did I say?
I'm Lee Joon Yeol from Namjang News.
I have a question for the president of MRB Funds.
President Baek is a wine lover. Have you had drinks with him yet?
I'm Koo Jae Chul from Joseok News.
We heard that your company might be affiliated with illegal gambling.
Is it true?
- What?
- Seriously?
Questions unrelated to the project won't be accepted.
Yes, I already told you.
Mr Kim Jung Ho of Sunwoo Distribution...
is a broker for illegal gambling.
- What is going on?
- Is that true?
What is this about?
That jerk lured all of the business owners who worked with...
Sunwoo Distribution into illegal gambling.
Are you saying that Sunwoo Distribution got them...
hooked on illegal gambling on purpose?
They targeted all vendor owners in Incheon.
They paid off their gambling debt with their real estate properties,
all of which ended up becoming Sunwoo Distribution's.
President Baek is trying to build the casino resort on that land.
Yes! Do you really think it's a coincidence?
Of course I know that I shouldn't have done gambling.
I admit that I made a mistake.
But if Sunwoo Distribution planned all of this,
it's just not fair at all. Don't you think so?
President Baek Eun Do, please answer my question.
Is it true that you purchased the site for the casino illegally?
Is it related to illegal gambling?
- Stop it.
- What are you doing now?
What are you doing to him now?
We will end the press conference here.
Is it true the real estate contract with Park Ho Sik was forged?
The contract was forged?
We exclusively obtained this conversation between
the informant and Sunwoo Distribution's employee.
The agreement is dated as March 27.
Isn't today the 31st?
It's one of the conditions we want.
- Is there a problem?
- Gosh, no.
It's not a problem at all.
If a problem arises later,
Sunwoo Distribution should take the responsibility.
Panda has found the situation of Sunwoo Distribution...
buying the site of the casino complex resort in Incheon...
even by forging contracts.
The majority of the land owners...
was people involved in the illegal gambling.
Is this really a coincidence?
You can find more details at Panda's official website.
This was Reporter Kim Swan of Panda.
President, we should leave.
Gosh.
(CEREMONY OF MOA BETWEEN SUNWOO DISTRIBUTION AND MRB FUNDS)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Congratulations.
Now, you get to work with Sunwoo Construction as you wished.
Is it true that your company was involved in the illegal gambling?
Is it true that you forged the land sale contract?
- Please say something.
- Are you really involved in it?
- What is the truth?
Please say something about forging the contract!
- Please say something!
- What's the truth about...
(CEREMONY OF MOA BETWEEN SUNWOO DISTRIBUTION AND MRB FUNDS)
We appreciate your work today.
You'll soon be the team leader at the city desk of Joseok News.
Thank you.
You will be receiving the deposit...
and penalty.
The deposit of 20 million dollars is not the problem.
I am so humiliated!
Gosh.
Mr Min. You should take responsibility not just...
for Sunwoo Distribution but for the entire Sunwoo Group.
But you won't be able to get away from the responsibility of...
choosing the wrong business partner.
You see.
What should we say to our investors?
Okay.
Let's think of a way that we all can win.
(MEMORANDUM OF AGREEMENT, INCHEON COMPLEX CASINO PROJECT)
Due to this event, the head quarter of MRB Funds in the States...
will ask Sunwoo Group for inspection.
Are you confident?
Of course. It is always welcomed.
Here.
- Let's toast to our partnership.
- Great.
- Here.
- Cheers!
No way.
Sunwoo Distribution's involvement in the illegal gambling...
is still the most popular search keyword on the internet!
The following is broker,
Panda and Kim Swan!
Please say something, Ms Celebrity.
Yes, it's me.
I am Reporter Kim Swan.
This is a beautiful night.
Is this an award ceremony?
Reporter Kim Swan, may I pour you a drink?
Sure. Go ahead.
As of today, I am no longer on probation.
Return the salary.
Cancel the dismissal.
Why would you remember that?
Of course I remembered it.
I was saving it for a day like this.
I'm tipsy.
- I will go get some air.
- I will go with you!
I will go.
Okay.
Did you see the article, Black?
I told you. I told you I was going to kill them all.
It's just the start now.
Start what?
Are you sick again?
Do you want to call your fake husband up there?
He must've seen it all.
Swan.
You did really well today.
You're going to write the follow-up article, right?
There must be something else when you dig into Sunwoo Group, right?
No. I already chose another subject to write.
What is that?
You.
- What?
- I'm so curious about you.
So I am going to start covering you.
What's that?
You're crazy! Seo Woo Jin!
- It hurts!
- You are definitely crazy!
I hate you!
Hey... Are you crying?
Due to the gambling scandal,
the stock price of the entire Sunwoo Group,
including that of Sunwoo Distribution, fell drastically,
and it caused a severe damage to the company.
As the election for the new chairman of the group is upcoming,
people are interested in the development of the situation.
The inspection team from the MRB Funds has arrived.
I am the executive manager of Asia Pacific Sector, MRB Funds.
I'm Black.
Should I begin...
the inspection now?
(GOODBYE MR BLACK)
I am the executive manager of Asia Pacific Sector, MRB Funds.
I'm Black.
Should I begin...
the inspection now?
You made a frequent business trip to Thailand.
- What's the reason for that?
- What happened?
What are you doing with Black?
I heard the suspect who tried to kill Cha Ji Won has...
a bullet wound on his shoulder.
Since there is evidence, we just need to catch him.