(Episode 10)
It was hard today, right?
It was hard because of the article, because of me.
No...
Yes.
A little.
You didn't look like it was a little hard when you got out.
It was a little hard.
Your look said, "It was very hard."
Do you know how relieved I was when I saw that?
Thank you for coming to me.
I didn't know I'd come here twice today.
The first time, you came to return the dress and get mad at me,
and the second time, you came because you wanted to see me, right?
No?
Mr Lee brought me.
You didn't want to come at all,
but you were forced to come because of Hwa Shin?
I wouldn't have had the courage to come if it weren't for him.
That's what I thought.
We should be good to Hwa Shin.
Yes.
But...
where is he?
He must be in his car.
What time is it?
Where did he go instead of going to the hospital?
He could go with me now.
I didn't get to give this to you at the funeral.
- I got this for you from Paris. - What is it?
For guys. You know.
It's good for the bedroom at night.
Paris has a lot of impotent men like you, apparently.
- Tae Ra. - Put it away.
How could you be impotent at your age?
It's so embarrassing.
Aren't you going to get married? Aren't you going to have kids?
My goal this year...
is to make you have kids before marrying Jung Won off.
I'm busy. If you're not helping me with the dishes, just leave.
Hey.
With our family background, your looks and education,
what do you lack that you need to rot...
in this shabby town, making stupid noodles?
You were doing all the kitchen work during the funeral.
It's because you live like family in this villa,
that you don't want to sleep with women.
Tae Ra!
You yell only at me.
You're so nice to everyone else.
Darn it.
The doctor said...
I'm being punished for dating women too readily,
sleeping with them too readily...
and breaking up with them too readily.
Leave me alone.
I have no desire to even touch women...
or kiss them. How could I make it to the bed?
Don't come back to the villa again.
- Hey. - Also,
don't look down on the people here.
You said they can't even pay rent on time.
I said to leave!
Hey.
The medicine your doctor gives you don't work anyway.
I know my own illness.
They said it's psychological, not physical.
Hey.
I was sitting on the steps of some street in Paris,
and Madam De Pont was selling this.
See? It says right here.
It means...
she awaits for her husband's return.
It's supposed to be more effective than ton dieu, pelle la magique...
or haute porte ennuience.
Haute porte... Nonsense.
It has a side effect of making you wink a lot,
but who cares?
If you see that happen, it means it's working.
It's the latest.
Even if a woman is naked, I'm just not interested.
- Do you want some water? - Get out.
Do you remember the shocking story...
of a five-year-old girl escaping barefoot from her step-mum?
When you hear the term "family", you think of blood relations,
- but in reality, - Just this year alone,
- people you have breakfast with... - there have been 15,000 cases...
- of child abuse this year. - and greet you at home...
- We need a solution. - may be the true family.
Dad.
Oh my gosh.
Do you want to date me?
What's his problem?
He's wasted. What's his problem?
Oh my gosh.
Date me.
What is he saying? He must have lost his mind.
Mr Lee, what's wrong?
- Please move out of the way. - Excuse me.
I like you.
Do you want to date me?
I'm charming.
It's hard to refuse, right?
Sure, let's date.
I'm your sister-in-law.
There has been a recent riot of people nervous about...
Do you want to date me?
In exchange for the coffee.
Do you have time for this with the anchor audition coming up?
Date me.
Don't you want the nine o'clock news? Did you give up?
Prepare for the audition with me.
You know it hurts if the team chemistry score is low,
even if the individual score is high.
You don't want to date me?
Do you even know who I am?
No, I don't.
You stupid moron.
Snap out of it, punk.
If you're drunk, go home and sleep, you idiot.
How dare you...
come to the sacred newsroom and yap about dating?
You're going to blame it on the alcohol in the morning...
and pretend you don't remember, right?
And this is the newsroom, where you conceited reporters...
claim only the truth may be spoken, you scum bucket!
You're good.
You curse really well.
It was crazy today because of the article, wasn't it?
I'm sorry.
I can't marry you.
Let us each marry someone that we like.
Do you like someone?
Don't you like anyone?
No.
Do you like someone?
I like Pyo Na Ri.
The weather forecaster? That Pyo Na Ri?
Since when?
Did you go on the blind date with me although you liked someone?
I first met Na Ri...
after our blind date.
I'll talk to both of our parents...
and take the blame.
Okay.
The parents did rush it when we never even went on a date,
but I didn't mind.
Don't worry.
I'll tell my parents.
- I'm glad you get me. - Exactly.
We get each other well.
- Thank you. - Sure.
(Applicant)
I'm an employee here, but my number...
is 234.
Where should I shoot my introduction video?
Did he go to the hospital or not?
Whatever.
Mr Lee...
Thank you for taking me earlier.
It's okay.
I'm going to lose my mind.
Are you insane?
I told you it's dangerous, even if it's stage one.
What's wrong with you?
Are you determined to get sick?
Did you decide not to listen?
You don't go to the hospital, but you drink instead?
Why are you upsetting me so much?
She says I'm upsetting her.
Gosh.
Are you upset because of me?
Do you know how long Jung Won and I looked for you earlier?
You only look for me when I upset you.
What?
You drank a lot.
You're insane.
Just how much did you drink?
Do you want to date me?
Aren't we dating already?
That's what people are saying anyway.
This is incredible.
How do you enunciate so well even when you're drunk?
It's amazing. Is that why your pronunciation is so good?
Do you want to date me?
I'm dating Jung Won.
I'm going to make it work with him.
I know you're drunk, but how could you say that?
There are things you shouldn't say. Don't you agree?
I'll do whatever you want. Date me.
Goodness.
You used to hate it when I even looked at you.
Really? Anything?
Yes.
Anything you want.
Sing for me. "Wrongful Meeting".
No.
I didn't hear you sing it last time because I went to throw up.
I want to hear it.
Not that.
Forget it. Forget it.
Anything, my foot.
When will I understand love
When will I understand life
Excuse me. Not that. "Wrongful Meeting".
How long must I live to understand
Will that day ever come
You said you'd do anything.
I cried, saying it couldn't be
Because I had to give up both my love and my friendship
Dance!
My other friend patted me on the shoulder
- And told me to forget - Oh my gosh.
- But I can't - Sing me a ballad! Ballad.
Things that passed are passed
That in itself is meaningful
You can't rap, can you?
My name is Lee Hwa Shin
- Your name is Pyo Na Ri - Pyo Na Ri
My heart is bleeding
Can you see how I feel
I don't know what I feel, do you?
No, you cannot
You don't need to
You call me, "Mr Lee"
I respond
"Let's date"
Make me laugh.
Look at me.
I can do just one.
I can do just one eye.
Dance!
Get up. Get up.
Get up.
Your favourite song. Your favourite song.
- Now, the end is near - No.
No. No. Dance. Dance.
Get up! Get up!
Sing. Sing.
If, just if
We were too young
How would we be now
Fart.
It's your speciality.
Fart, just like you did when we were in the hospital.
Fart. Come on.
I can't do that.
Fart. Fart for me.
Fart. Fart.
Do it, just once.
Fart.
I think of the sound of your fart at times.
Hey.
Isn't it a waste to end your crush on me...
after three years?
Don't you think about your investment?
No.
Did you love me?
How can a crush change?
I want cup-noodles.
I don't have any.
I want cup-noodles. Make me some.
I don't think I have any left.
How can a crush change?
Uncle's not in. Let's make some noodles.
Okay.
What's this?
You should give healthy stuff to students.
How could he take vitamins by himself?
Here they are.
The morning air has become chilly.
Autumn has really come now.
Sadly, it will be difficult to see a clear sky today.
There is a thick cloud pattern...
and rain clouds are approaching as well.
We expect rainfall in Seoul this night of up to 20mm.
Except for the East Sea and Jeju...
(Granny's Market)
Who is that? Is that Na Ri?
Yes.
The current temperature in Seoul is 17 degrees.
It is expected to reach a high of 23 degrees.
Take an umbrella. They say it may rain.
Other mums come to the school with umbrellas when it rains.
Okay. You'll be late. If it rains, I'll come pick you up.
Ppal Gang, I saw your report card yesterday.
You are 200th in your school.
How can you go to college with grades like that?
You're a senior, but you play with those guys upstairs all the time.
Don't hang out with them.
Hang out with them. Stick to them like glue.
- Ja Young. - They're 1st and 2nd...
in their school. She's 200th because of them.
Without them, she probably won't even be 300th.
You must be embarrassed that I'm 200th in my school.
There isn't 300th. We have only 200 students in my school.
She's last?
Are you saying you're last in your school?
How could someone I gave birth to be last in her school?
I've only been top of my school.
Even if you put one answer for every question, you wouldn't be last.
Are you a bird brain? Do you even have a brain?
How could you say that to your daughter?
Yes, I have rocks in my head,
but how dare you nag about my grades when you never once cooked for me?
- Nag? - You never once came to my school.
How dare you act like my mum?
Act... Act like your mum?
Ppal Gang, don't talk to your mums that way.
You stay out of it.
Why do you talk like that?
Is that what your dad taught you? Is that how your dad raised you?
Your dad may have left you to do anything as you pleased,
but I won't. Look at your nails.
Those aren't the nails of a high school senior.
Why are they so long? And they're painted, too.
You brat. Clip them right now.
How dare you women tell me what to do about my nails?
Why are you acting like my mums when you're not?
What? Say that again.
I'm not your mum...
but I'm acting like a mum?
Hey. How dare you slap my daughter?
She's my precious daughter.
She won't learn any manners otherwise.
Saying "yes" to everything doesn't make you a mum.
Do you know how Dad treated me even though he had no money?
I never once watched Na Ri do the weather.
If it rained, Dad waited for me at the school with an umbrella.
If it was cold, he waited there with a jacket.
If it snowed, he waited there with roasted sweet potatoes.
And I never once clipped my own nails.
Dad always clipped them for me before they got long.
I haven't been able to clip my nails once since Dad passed away,
because I feel like Dad will clip them for me again. But...
But...
who are you to tell me to clip my nails?
When he apologised that those things were...
all he could do for me because we had no money, where were you?
You never once made me lunch. Why should I call you my mum?
She'll be late for school.
Ppal Gang, let's go. Let's go.
Guys, get in.
Get in.
Good morning, Mr Lee.
You wanted cup-noodles. This is in its place.
When did I do that?
"When did I do that?"
See? Look at that.
Don't follow me.
I'm not following you. I'm just going my way.
Hello.
Get in.
Mr Lee, are you going to date me or Ms Park?
What? I wasn't the only one you asked to date?
You girls back off. He's going to date me.
Not you.
After telling the entire studio that you're dating Na Ri...
What is wrong with you?
You asked every woman at the studio last night to date you, didn't you?
What will you do?
Whom will you date?
You shouldn't drink any more.
I'm going to date Hye Won.
(Truth, Perhaps Lies, How Can a Crush Change?)
Hye Won, you've been selected.
Have a nice day.
Mum slaps hard.
- Hello? - This is the real estate agent.
I found a place.
Is it close to Ppal Gang's place? That is all I care about.
Of course. Would you like to sign the lease?
Yes. I'll send you the deposit.
Hey.
Are you dating Na Ri? For real?
Are you dating Na Ri?
I'm not dating anyone.
If you're not dating anyone, are you...
Why are you so angry?
Wait! Wait. Wait.
- Are you crazy? - I need to tell you something.
I have to get somewhere.
It's very important.
What is it?
Do you want to date me?
I'll do whatever you want. Date me.
Did you love me?
How can a crush change?
Don't tell Jung Won I had a crush on you for three years, okay?
You can't, okay?
Please promise me.
Was that so urgent and important?
Yes.
Okay.
Make sure to go to the hospital with me.
- Okay? - Please move.
Okay?
I said to move.
Mr Lee.
Of course, crushes change. It isn't preserved.
- Did he think it would last? - Freak.
I'm not a statue in a museum. Did he think I'd stand in place,
staring at him forever or something?
It's not like he likes me.
You've lost your mind.
He always looks down on me.
Now? Now?
I have a meeting.
Your girlfriend says it's going to rain today.
She says it'll rain tonight.
Does it look like it'll rain?
She's a good liar, isn't she?
She lies to the nation every day on TV.
I'm sure she lies to you, too.
You know not to believe what girls like that say, right?
Why is being wrong about the weather the forecaster's fault?
Then whose fault is it?
It's the cloud's fault, right?
It's up to the clouds, right?
Your father called me.
- He did? - He called for the first time...
after three years, and said if I marry you to Geum Soo Jung,
he won't divorce me.
He said if I can't get the marriage through,
he doesn't need me any more.
Jung Won.
Don't say my name...
so sweetly.
Save me.
You'll make me sway.
Don't make me a divorcee.
Even if it's not real, let me live this way. Please?
I want you to be happy.
Of course.
You want me to be happy too, right?
That's good, then.
Don't trust her.
All of the women near you are only after your money.
Soo Jung's family is wealthier than we are.
They have more than enough money.
She's obviously not after your money.
She just likes you for you.
She's sincere and innocent.
Did Soo Jung say she likes me?
I just had brunch with her.
She says she likes you.
She says she wants to have you meet her parents.
I'll drive myself.
Do you want...
to make your mum a divorcee and date a girl who lies every day?
No, right?
Soo Jung is the one who's lying.
What?
That jerk!
How could you take that wench's side even if I become a divorcee?
Don't worry.
I'll tell my parents.
She says she likes you.
She says she wants to have you meet her parents.
She quietly stabbed me in the back.
I hate people who stab me in the back.
Do you want to fight me?
- What? - There is no fund in that account.
I sent 10,000 dollars to that account.
I think you were the victim of voice phishing.
No. No.
Darn it.
How long will it take to sell Chinese stock?
What?
Overdrawn...
Sell them as soon as possible.
It can't exceed one minute.
Slowly.
Hello.
I am announcer applicant number 78539, Pyo Na Ri.
This...
This is my last chance.
I am Pyo...
I am Pyo Na Ri...
Hello, Ms Bang.
What were you doing there?
Do you need something? I can do it.
I wasn't doing anything much.
You look like you were caught stealing.
The broadcast ended a while ago. What were you doing?
I don't steal, no matter how little I have.
Take Ms Hong to the conference room.
- Yes. - Yes, Ma'am.
Look.
You know...
that red puppy key chain in your locker?
I have it.
Let me keep it. I'll buy you a new one.
Okay. Thank you.
Ms Bang.
You are fair and impartial, right?
I'll do my best.
I want to gain your approval,
at least once.
Sharpen your knives.
Sharpen them all.
I need to use them, so sharpen them well.
Yes, Ma'am.
(Chumsungdae Sauna)
I have this.
(Show this text at the front desk for special services.)
Where are you going?
Go back.
Once you pass through strict security,
there is a sea of illegal gambling machines.
He risked his life for this.
Come on. Come on.
These gambling establishments have spread to the farmlands now.
They have soundproofed the room...
and have black-out curtains to ensure 24-hour gambling.
On the outside, it looks like a regular spa.
It filters the clients using invitations by text,
thus evading the police.
Did you put something on that?
Yes, it's fine.
It's fine.
The owner is Moon, in his 50s.
Hey, you. Let's talk.
You don't have the game I like.
- What? - What is that in your hand?
You rat.
He even hired men who used to be...
in organised crime.
Who are you? Who are you?
Who are you?
What is that? Give it to me!
Give it to me.
(Illegal Gambling Establishment)
(SBC News Live)
Great work, Mr Lee Hwa Shin.
The illegal gambling rings, which we thought quieted down,
had actually been very active.
Yes, that's right.
The industry people and employees use burner phones.
Their methods had become more discreet and complicated.
It was shocking that it had spread to a remote farming town.
How will the investigation proceed?
The police arrested the owner and the employees.
They stated that they plan to search the vicinity as well.
Illegal gambling rings pop up whenever you're about to forget.
His eyes are bugged out. Great.
Okay, VCR stand by.
Cue!
From the second half of next year, starting with the capital...
That was great.
Take it easy.
Don't work so hard to win points because of the anchor auditions.
You stand out more than the story, punk.
I know they hate me.
I'll make sure they have to give me high scores.
Just wait.
Focus.
- Hi. - Let's go.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
You didn't get hit here too, did you?
Why are you here instead of out on a date?
I came to have dinner with you.
I have plans.
With whom?
Eat with us. Who is it?
It's a secret.
Whatever.
You're making that up so that we can eat alone.
Don't do that.
The three of us can go on dates every day.
What?
Why not?
What should we get?
I like being with the two of you.
I really have dinner plans.
- You do? - Why did you come? Just go.
Why don't we all go together?
You have no plans. I can see it in your eyes.
I want to eat with you.
Please leave me alone, will you?
Go eat by yourselves. Please.
I'm being sincere. That is my wish, my hope and dream. Okay?
You are so dense.
Go!
Please, get out of my sight! Now!
Do you think that'll make me give up?
The more you do this, I...
No, we have to eat with you.
Right, Miss Poop?
You feel the same way, right?
Well, why don't...
the two of you...
Why are you dragging me into your relationship?
When you're happy, the more the merrier.
We haven't had a decent meal together since you came back.
No, no. The two of you can eat.
I can just have cup-noodles...
Cup-noodles...
Cup-noodles. Why?
You said you don't have any cup-noodles.
I thought we were going to have dinner.
What?
Yes.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Did he really have plans?
He says they're dating.
Who did? Hwa Shin said that?
Yes.
She really isn't his type.
What's his type?
Similar to mine.
I doubt that.
He doesn't like women like me.
That's because you don't know.
Hwa Shin likes you.
That's why he set us up.
He wouldn't have done that if he didn't like you.
We're really good friends.
You and Soo Jung were made a fool of.
You look so cute like this.
Let go.
Sweetie.
What should we eat? Why do you eat noodles?
You don't eat well or sleep well.
And you just got out of the hospital.
We'll have to eat something tastier than Hwa Shin is.
We should, Mr Ko.
Mr Ko?
"Mr Ko" sounds weird.
I wonder what they're eating.
This is too heavy.
I'll take that.
What did you get?
Thank you.
I wanted to cook for Ppal Gang.
- Thank you, Chef. - Not at all.
I'm sorry.
How did he hold it back all this time?
That means...
nothing happened with Ja Young, right?
Oh my gosh.
That scared me.
Seriously.
What is this?
My goodness.
(Dear Daughters-in-law)
This tastes good.
Dear Daughters-in-law, I made 1,000 octopus dumplings,
which Ppal Gang likes.
So yummy.
If any go into your mouths, I'll cut you with a knife.
I listen to your show all the time.
- Thank you. - You're so pretty.
- Look who it is. - Hello.
I guess the announcer lady came because it's supposed to storm.
I know. What time is it already?
Oh my.
- Where's Ppal Gang? - She's coming.
Look at your uniform.
I...
I just wished you were my mum.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
You don't have a mum?
How could you ask that?
I'm sorry.
I'll be your mum too,
if you don't expect a great mum.
What? I thought you were going to be Ppal Gang's mum.
Being a mum isn't a big deal.
I can be one if I want.
Right?
Get in.
Ppal Gang's coming. Ppal Gang!
It has a side effect of making you wink a lot,
but who cares?
If you see that happen, it means it's working.
When was the last time a woman got you excited?
Is it a sin if you get excited and wink at a woman,
want to touch them, kiss them...
and sleep with them?
It will make your heart, the man's heart, pound.
Isn't it cool?
(Rak Pasta)
Where does your niece live?
On the third floor of this building.
It really is nice and close.
It's too close. Much closer than I expected.
You lost to Ms Gye and Ms Bang, right?
Yes.
You can see everything that happens in that other rooftop place.
You can even jump across.
Thank you for the ride, Sir.
Sleep at home tonight.
- I will. - Why do you call me...
"Mr Ko" and "Sir"?
Do you work for me?
I'll go now.
What?
Get home safely.
You don't have the basics of someone dating.
Both at the restaurant and in the car.
Ever since I asked you to date me,
you act like my personal assistant.
But you are a boss.
Stop that.
"Mr Ko" is more comfortable.
What about me?
Am I supposed to date, treating you like my assistant?
Must I date as if I'm with Mr Cha?
I... I haven't dated much.
And you've been an assistant?
No. I don't know much about that, either.
I'm just trying to look good.
Look at this girl.
Look favourably on me.
Goodness.
I'm the one that needs to look good.
Why would you need to look good? What's looking good?
Do you think I'd like it if you call me "Mr Ko"?
I don't know, to be honest.
I don't know anything.
Then...
just do as I say. Exactly as I say.
- What? - Everything. Whatever. Anything.
What? Are you scared? Tough.
I won't ask what you want to do or eat or where you want to go.
What did you say all night long?
"Anything is good. I like everything. That's fine."
"Yes. Of course."
"Thank you. Thank you for dinner." Right?
I didn't take you to be so clueless. What's wrong with you?
I was nervous.
I'm the man who wants to love you.
Don't turn me into a man who makes women uncomfortable.
I don't know when I last received love.
Maybe it's because I'm not used to being loved.
You don't seem to be used to giving love, either, Ms Pyo.
You're right.
Is it frustrating, Sir?
Sir? What? Sir?
Stop being so formal.
- Is it frustrating, Sir? - Again?
Stop it.
Is it, Sir?
Goodness, you are so frustrating.
Okay.
Am I... Am I being dumped already?
This girl...
Bye.
You're bold.
Good night.
That's Hwa Shin's car.
Why did you bring me here?
Lend me money.
How much?
10,000 dollars.
Did you ask me to date you to borrow money?
You're becoming too pathetic.
Forget it, if you don't want to.
Will you date me even if I don't lend you the money?
I won't date you even if you lend me the money.
Don't be stupid and tell Na Ri...
that you like her.
Never.
Why not?
You saw. She's dating my friend.
- Take her away. - I can't. I introduced them.
- Take her away anyway. - How?
She had a crush on you for three years.
She'll come to you if you ask.
- Really? - She'll come right over,
from what I see.
Do you think so?
Of course. Na Ri may be waiting for it.
Really?
Forget about stupid friendships.
Others don't even worry about things like this.
I guess that's possible.
Love. Love is the most important.
Naturally.
You'll just be a scumbag, that's all.
A scumbag?
Yes.
You don't want to be a scumbag?
Are you teasing me?
Obviously.
So, Hwa Shin,
don't become a scumbag,
and do the nine o'clock news with me and date me...
- and... - You don't think I can do it?
I can be a scumbag.
Did something happen between you two?
Don't talk to or even look at Na Ri.
What are you doing?
Please, get lost!
You get lost.
I'm going out of town tomorrow with Ms Gye for a story.
Don't you want to see the ocean?
Let's go.
Is dating what changed you?
Get your act together.
You'll lose both your friend and your love.
Don't let Na Ri find out how you feel.
- Are you scared? - Are you challenging me?
Are you scared?