Don't be stupid and
tell Pyo Na Ri that you like her.
Just shred your friendship to pieces.
Yeah, I suppose so.
Love comes first.
Of course, you'll just
become a son of a bitch.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
Of course I am.
So, Senior... don't be a son of a bitch.
Do the 9 p.m. news with me,
date me, and...
You think I can't do it?
I'll become a son of a bitch.
Reporter Lee.
What are you doing there?
What are you two doing there?
I moved here to take care of Red.
The two of you, together?
Don't worry.
I can't live in a place like this.
It's not that I'm worried.
I'll get going now, Senior.
I'll do that favor you asked of me.
Then, are you going to live there now?
Do you not like that?
Do you?
I don't need an answer.
I have to see you every day.
It's a bit strange.
A bit strange? It's very strange.
Oh my god.
This is unexpected.
You heard everything so shouldn't you
ask your friend directly?
Why are you asking me about it?
Because I don't think Hwa Shin will
even try to make excuses to me about it.
Your friendship brings tears to my eyes.
Are you sure it's not
because you're afraid?
Did I hear the whole story?
Reporter Lee Hwa Shin
can't become a son of a bitch.
If he knew how...
he wouldn't have been chased to Thailand
after all those exclusive stories he did.
He would have joined hands
with me by now too.
He wouldn't be pining for Pyo Na Ri
who was in love with him for three years.
Pyo Na Ri doesn't like
Reporter Lee anymore.
She likes you now.
[HWA SHIN]
He's doing his best to forget his
feelings because you're his friend.
How about you ignore this
and go about your business?
Are you home, Sis?
Yes.
I'm glad you're home.
- Why did you get thinner?
- Did I?
Chi Yeol.
Did the person who lived on
the rooftop before move away?
That man who always walked around
in his underwear moved.
It worked out well, right?
Should we move too?
No, I don't want to.
That place is so close.
You can see and hear everything.
It's kind of annoying and uncomfortable.
Doesn't it interrupt your studies?
I don't want to move.
Why not?
You're here.
Did your date go well?
Yes.
I'm sorry, friend. I like Pyo Na Ri.
So what?
- I'm going to tell Pyo Na Ri I like her.
- You can't.
I don't need your permission.
I'm going to tell her.
- You can't.
- Jung Won, let's stop being friends.
I feel so sorry to you and can't even
look at you, so I can't be your friend.
That can't happen either.
So, what can I do?
Leave things the way they are now.
The way things are now?
Watching your backs like I am now?
I think I'm going to go crazy with the
way things are now, so how can I?
I'm going to take
Pyo Na Ri away from you.
Pyo Na Ri will come to me
if I tell her how I feel.
I want to hold her hand, hold her,
kiss her, and sleep with her.
Say that again.
I want to hold her hand, hold her,
kiss her, and sleep with her.
You son of a bitch!
Is this you being a son of a bitch?
How can you say we should
stop being friends over a girl?
Yeah, I'm a son of a bitch!
At the very least, I wanted to
tell you that I like Pyo Na Ri.
Because even if I die,
I can't say these words to Pyo Na Ri.
Because of you...
I can't say them.
Pyo Na Ri won't know, even when she dies.
She will never know.
So, don't worry.
What happened today...
I'm going to pretend that it didn't.
I'll pretend I didn't hear it.
I'll let it go this once.
Chef, is there a problem with your eyes?
I'm worried I'll do
something by accident.
Come on in.
Oh! You look cool, Uncle.
Why are you being creepy
and wearing sunglasses indoors?
Can you even see?
I can do this with my eyes shut.
Can you even tell
which one is salt or sugar?
Since you brought the kids,
I'll treat them to something good.
Tell me whatever you want to eat.
Really? Kids, what do you want to eat?
Red, what should we ask Chef to make?
Chi Yeol has agreed to be
my son starting today, Chef.
Let's ask him to make something
that's not on the menu.
I'm okay with just anything.
What do you mean, just anything?
What are you doing, punk?
Uncle, the school needs you to come in
to consult with the teachers.
Red, I'll need to go for you too, right?
Mom will go for you.
They want me to bring my mom.
Why would I bring you?
They're all in the same class.
Why don't we go together?
Should we do that?
Yes.
Thank you, Chef.
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm sorry.
That man is cute.
Beom, look at the time.
Why are you here and not sleeping?
Go to sleep. Go on.
Come on.
Eat up, go home, and sleep.
Oh, Reporter. Reporter Lee.
- Wait.
- Gosh.
Why? Reporter.
What?
Do you want some ice cream?
[I LOVE YOU, PYO NA RI.]
Gosh, can you just get lost?
Hey! Who are you to tell me to get lost?
You moved in right in front of my house
so why should I get lost?
You should be the one
to get lost, Reporter!
- Can you get lost, Reporter Lee?
- What?
If you haven't moved in yet,
can't you find another place near Red?
It doesn't have to be that place.
It's very uncomfortable.
I can see and hear
everything you are doing.
I only used ice cream to bring that up.
Is that anything to get upset about?
- What right do you have?
- What?
What right do you have to tell me
where I should or shouldn't live?
Am I looking for a place for
us to live in together?
I'm living there alone,
so who are you to say anything?
Unless you're going to live with me
don't say anything
about liking it or not.
Move.
Also, stop hanging around in front of me.
Don't show your face
in front of me again!
Just disappear from my sight.
Go emigrate to the moon or the stars.
Go up to the clouds.
Just vanish, please!
Are you finished?
Don't even speak to me.
Hey!
Oh my gosh! What did I do?
I'm so sorry, Reporter. I didn't know.
What should I do? What do I do?
I didn't think it would actually hit you.
Oh no! I'm so sorry.
It's chocolate flavored too.
Your clothes are all ruined too.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'll wash it for you.
Take it off. Take it off.
Reporter, you've been going
to the hospital, right?
Is my chest yours?
Do you have a lease on it?
You think you own it?
This won't do. Go home and take it off.
Throw it to me from your roof.
I'll catch it from my roof, wash it,
iron it, and return it to you.
I always told you not to eat dairy.
I'll buy you really good ice cream.
Please, forgive me.
I won't eat it.
You can't eat it often,
but once in a while is okay.
Strawberry? Vanilla?
Do you not like vanilla?
Should I buy you chocolate too?
I'm so sorry, Reporter Lee.
I'm sorry, Reporter.
This isn't right.
What should I do?
How could she be so cute?
I'm crazy.
[THREE YEARS AGO]
What would you like?
I'll have the chicken.
It's best to eat it warm.
Thank you.
Reporter, do you mind if I sit here?
Which one are you eating?
Mine is chicken.
Steak sandwich.
I want to try the steak too.
Should we eat half of each other's?
We can try both kinds.
You can eat it all.
They're both delicious.
He should eat with me.
Not coffee. I'll take a mango smoothie.
Okay.
- Oh, you startled me.
- Reporter Lee.
I wasn't following you, Reporter.
Assistant Director Choi asked me to
buy some drinks before coming back in.
Oh, I see.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Yum, so good. Is yours good too?
Did you know many people
come here for blind dates?
Don't you ever have them?
No, I don't. How about you?
I have one in five minutes.
Didn't you say you had to
buy drinks for people?
Yes.
She's so bothersome, so bothersome.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
Here you go.
[HAN JI MIN]
- Ji Min.
- Yes.
You're an Eastern medicine doctor.
Ah, yes.
I had appointments until the evening.
I'm sorry I could only make time now.
Oh, it's no problem.
What is it?
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
A weird girl wanted to share
her sandwich with me earlier.
I think I was just taken aback
and now I have indigestion.
I'll take a look for you
if you take off your jacket.
Oh, okay.
One moment.
Your pulse seems normal.
Please turn around this way.
Okay.
Right here.
Do you know that person?
I don't know her.
Does that feel better?
Yes.
How is that? Does that feel better?
I'm sorry.
You must feel much better now.
I'll do that for you
whenever you get indigestion.
Really?
I guess I won't need any
digestive medication.
I'm free next Friday or Saturday.
How about both Friday and Saturday?
Truthfully, I'm free on Sunday too.
That's good.
Should we order?
Don't pay any attention to her.
Look at me.
What would you like to have?
I'll have...
chocolate tea.
Hey, I heard that Pyo Na Ri
has a crush on you.
The entire news department
is talking about it.
Why don't you just accept her feelings?
I feel sorry for her.
Do you get into a relationship
out of pity?
Pyo Na Ri must have issues.
Why would she like a guy like him?
I'm so annoyed by it too.
Hey, just go on a few dates with her
when you're really bored
with nothing to do.
You know, if you get sick of pretty
girls or girls from good households.
Dong Gi.
Hello, Director.
You have issues.
Reporter Lee,
you looked good on screen today.
Your shirt looked good too.
Have you eaten yet?
We had octopus.
Do you like me?
What?
Do you like me, Pyo Na Ri?
- Well, that's...
- You don't, right?
If you don't have a boyfriend,
pick one from here.
What the heck?
Why would you tell her
to pick from one of us?
Choose one.
Pick anyone except me.
Who is that? What was that?
Aren't you going home?
Your mother asked me for
Pyo Na Ri's number.
What do you think that means?
"I don't think you need
to know her number."
"When a young man
and woman are in love"
"the love grows more passionate
the more people try to pull them apart."
"It seems they already
have issues anyway."
"It is best to take a
few steps back and observe."
"There is high chance that they will
break up on their own, ma'am."
Are you okay, President?
Drive Pyo Na Ri to the station
tomorrow morning.
Me?
Sis, are you busy tomorrow morning?
I have to go to the beach
and report live.
I can't come home. Why?
- It's nothing.
- What is it?
Nothing. You'll be late. Go.
Go back in and get some more sleep.
Sleep!
I wonder why he didn't come today.
Are you already assuming that
he has to come early every morning?
He's much busier than I am.
I should be telling him not to come
even when he insists on coming.
If you really are
his girlfriend, that is.
I should buy a car
even if I have to take out a loan.
Who is it at this hour? Who is it?
- Oh my!
- Red!
Where do you think you're going?
Get out, get out!
Red! What are you doing?
Who is it?
I'll take you to school starting today.
I'm not going to school.
- That girl.
- Get out!
Get out here now!
People let you get away with everything.
What do you mean you're not going?
- Come on.
- Hey, we have to feed her first.
Let's eat.
Here you go.
Red, I'll make sure you go to college.
She's last place in her school.
I'll help you get married too.
You don't need to get married.
Who needs to get married
in this day and age?
So, don't worry about a thing.
Think of me as a dad
and tell me if you need anything.
You can lean on me if things are hard.
I can give you an
allowance if you need it.
How much do you need?
Okay. Give me 10 million won.
10 million won?
What do you need that for?
I'll hear you out and
give it to you if you need it.
You really don't know?
Dad had a debt of one billion won
after he was ruined, thanks to you.
You don't know what he went through
trying to pay that off.
Pay me 10 million won per month for
a year and that will be one billion won.
You really must be last place in school.
You should calculate properly.
If you get 10 million won a month,
that's 120 million won in a year.
So it would take eight years and four
months to get to 10 billion won.
You're so annoying.
I hear that multiple times a day.
That's mine.
This is my mom's cooking.
Did she come by?
Mom.
Just as I thought,
Mom's dumplings are the best.
Are you not wearing a bra these days?
I told you that I'd be wielding my knife
if anyone besides Red ate the dumplings.
Reporter Kye started
eating them yesterday.
Reporter Lee ate them too.
How can the two of you
live in the same house?
I just can't understand it.
- Me neither.
- What are you doing here at this hour?
- I moved.
- What?
The executives are all here.
As for the expected changes in sales
for the first half of next year
as you can see, the operation profit
will be used for the property taxes.
We should not feel safe though.
We should increase our efforts
in the Indian market.
What's wrong with him, Secretary Cha?
Hey, I told you not to
hit me in the back.
You shouldn't look away.
Are you going to keep
hitting me in the back?
Sorry, I can't control myself.
Stop glaring at me and look at that.
It'll put you in a good mood.
The Yellow Sea beach has been designated
a UNESCO World Heritage site.
Go down and get a good story.
What's up with you?
Why would you give me a good story?
Because you're just my favorite, okay?
I want you to go there and suffer.
The Morning News team is there and
they're doing the weather there tomorrow.
You can meet them there.
- I'll go alone.
- Why?
They'll get in my way.
Why would you send a reporter?
I had already contacted the mayor
for an interview.
- Reporter Kye!
- Really?
You're an anchor though.
You should be at your desk.
How long could it take?
It's just a short distance away.
I already know what the interview will be
so it'll be quick like bam, bam, bam.
I'll get a wide shot of the beach
from the helicopter.
- It won't even take half the day.
- Really?
If an anchor went out
herself for an interview
it would feel more realistic.
Since it's an event to celebrate,
it means more for the anchor to go.
It makes it special.
Director, it'll look good to the bosses.
I think it sounds good.
Hey, is this cutting in line,
hitting, or outright thievery?
I'm standing right here with my eyes open
so how can you steal my item?
What law says I can't?
Is there a rule that says an anchor
must have her butt glued to the chair?
Do you think doing this means you'll
get the 9 p.m. main anchor job?
Don't come after me like this.
Let's be fair about
our competition, okay?
Oh, I'm so scared.
I'm okay with it.
Reporter Lee.
Reporter.
Do you like live squid?
I'm going to the beach.
Should I go get some live squid
and make some squid stew?
I'm really good at making it.
Just forgive me for yesterday.
You live across the street and it's
so awkward to leave things like this.
If you don't like squid stew,
we could just eat seasoned squid.
But you have to cut the thing
on the cutting board so cruelly.
Can you help me with that?
Then let's have fresh squid and soju
on the rooftop once I come back.
Let's do that with Go Jung Won.
Do you want to call Jung Won?
Answer me.
I'm sorry. Sorry, sorry!
Gosh, Lee Hwa Shin gets angry so easily.
The more I think about it,
I can't hold it in because I get angrier.
Yesterday, I wasn't able to say anything
because you took me by surprise.
I'm not going to let you take
Pyo Na Ri away from me.
Don't even look Pyo Na Ri
in the eye or talk to her.
Okay.
You're a lowlife who set me up with her
because you didn't
even know you liked her.
You're a crazy idiot who used Red as an
excuse to move in next to Pyo Na Ri.
You're a pervert who looks
at his friend's girl
and gets excited and turned on.
You're a total jerk who even hit me
in the back when we were boxing.
- Okay.
- You...
You shut your mouth.
Just shut your mouth.
With the upcoming departure,
there were expectations and excitement.
The families were waiting to meet...
Pull yourself together, Senior.
You'll lose your friend
and your love at this rate.
Jung Won and I wouldn't waver
so easily over a girl.
We wouldn't waver so easily.
You think so?
Why did you let Pyo Na Ri stay in a
one-sided love with you for three years?
- Leave.
- Why?
I've never seen President Go like this.
Let me see something fun, Senior.
You should've made it
so she got over you quickly.
How hard do you think it was for her?
You called yourself a man and
let her do that for three years?
Even if it was a one-sided love,
you received it for free for three years!
You arrogant piece of crap.
- Stop it.
- Stop what?
I haven't even gone three minutes.
Think about the girl
who suffered for three years.
You can't handle three minutes!
I know I caused my own problems,
so stop it already!
If I had accepted Pyo Na Ri's feelings,
this wouldn't be happening today.
You wouldn't be in the middle of this
and we wouldn't be fighting.
Is that what you want?
Are you getting mad at me
because that's not what I did?
So, should I go change
Pyo Na Ri's mind now?
You crazy punk.
You'd better not let Pyo Na Ri
find out about your feelings.
Don't ever let her find out.
You're too late.
You couldn't do it three years ago.
You don't have a chance anymore.
The moment you set her up with me...
- Are you not confident?
- You really...
- Are you not...
- want to give this a go?
Pyo Na Ri is coming.
Why are you here, President?
Don't ever get caught.
You're dead if you get caught.
I'm trusting you.
Don't trust me.
Hey.
Let's go.
What is it?
Hey!
Don't trust me!
Don't trust me! Don't trust me!
Don't trust me! Why are you trusting me?
Why are you trusting me? Just don't.
Don't trust me so I can do what I want.
What a waste to see this by myself.
I can't do anything
because you keep trusting me.
Please don't trust me.
Reporter Lee.
You can do it!
Did something happen between you two?
Did you fight?
Do you guys fight too?
We don't fight.
We've never fought before.
You should've called before coming.
Didn't you come to see me?
I'm leaving the city with
Reporter Kye tomorrow morning.
I'm staying over one night.
Don't you feel like seeing the sea?
It would be nicer to see it together.
Pyo Na Ri was in a one-sided love
with you for three years.
You can win her over
if you just tell her.
Do you like me or Hwa Shin more?
What?
- That's...
- Don't answer that.
My question is childish.
Why is it funny? Who do you like more?
- That's...
- No, don't answer that.
My question is so immature.
He's not being won over even
when I seduce him with the beach.
I told you to find out that weather
forecaster's number, so why no news?
I don't think you need to
know her number.
What?
When it comes to love
between a man and a woman
you know it becomes more passionate
when you try to pull them apart.
It seems they already have issues anyway.
You saw that he was acting strange
during the meeting earlier.
He even sent me here to Pyo Na Ri's home
by myself this morning.
- Really?
- Yes.
If you take a few steps back and observe
there is a good chance
they will break up.
All right, you can go.
I did what you asked
regarding your mother.
- Did you take the medicine?
- I'm glad you're here.
Do the dishes, okay?
Oh my, oh my!
You... you...
You took them, right? You did.
- Are you experiencing side effects?
- The things I do because of you.
Do the dishes, okay?
You have to do these things.
It's the only way to have kids.
It's the only way to get married.
Yeah, have fun with Reporter Kye.
Have some good sashimi with Reporter Kye.
Na Ri, have some soju too.
Yes, I'm going to.
Yes, Doctor.
Let's go to the hospital. Okay, let's go.
Reporter Lee, look at me.
How could you not even
look at me all day?
Was it so wrong to throw the ice cream?
What are you doing?
I don't want to see you.
Do you not want to see me that much?
I'll get in trouble if I'm with you.
- With whom?
- My mom.
Since when have you listened to your mom?
Since when have you listened to anyone?
Get out.
They want you to come now.
The doctor called me.
They said you haven't been in for
radiation since you went with me.
Are you really trying to die?
Okay, I'll give you one of these.
Eat this and let's go, okay?
I'll open this for you.
Let's eat and get going.
Let's go. We have to go.
Wow! This is so good.
Am I a child? A child?
Of course, you are.
A child who's afraid of the hospital.
A child who hates the hospital
more than anything.
Let's go.
Should I open you a new one?
When you start dating a guy...
do you always change like this?
Do you melt like ice cream
to the men you're dating too?
I don't know.
I've only ever been
looked down on by you.
How dirty. Get out.
I said get out.
Which one of your moms is coming?
I don't have a mom.
Are they both going to come?
If they both show up,
I'll die of embarrassment.
Hey, you have to be back here by 10:00!
Na Ri will be here, right?
She's not coming?
How could she not on a day like today?
She should come even if she's busy.
Did you not tell her about it?
I'll take care of it.
Hey, even so...
She won't care about saving money and
she'll try to send me to medical school.
I want to stop making her suffer
once I get to college.
If Na Ri finds out that you chose a major
without letting her know about it
you will be buried alive at Rak Villa.
She will get a shovel and come at you.
Call her now.
Don't get buried by her.
Why do you think she goes around
early in the morning doing the weather?
You said she's doing the announcer
exam again to help you study.
Are you crazy?
Gosh, you punk. You're too much.
[CHEF KIM RAK]
- Yes?
- I was wondering if Red told you.
Did she tell you about the meeting
with her teacher today at 10:00?
I'm not saying you have to come.
Announcer Bang is going,
so you should sacrifice this time.
What time is it now?
Hey, stop the car.
Stop the car now.
Okay? Stop the car.
Hey, go buy some rice crackers there.
- What?
- Go.
Okay.
Go, go. Hurry.
Go to Gureum High School, okay?
Oh my! Hey, Reporter!
What am I supposed to do?
[PYO NA RI]
Is this yours?
Do you want to sell this to me?
Sell it to me for 1,000 won.
I'll give you 2,000 won.
3,000 won.
You'll stand out among the mothers.
It's my first time going
as a student's mom.
Don't be nervous.
I hope Red is happy to see me.
Gosh, this is a school zone.
- Are you okay?
- Oh gosh.
It must be a woman.
Reporter Kye?
Oh my goodness!
She's going to get there before me.
I told her not to do this.
Reporter Kye, stop right there. Stop!
Where is Red? Both moms are here.
Did your mom say she'd come?
Teacher, hello.
- Teacher, hello.
- Hello.
You must all be busy.
Thank you for coming.
- Please sit down.
- Thank you.
- Dae Gu?
- That's me.
Yes.
And Red?
Red's mom?
That's me. I am her mom, Teacher.
I am Red's mom.
Ah, I see.
Red's mom, you must have
worried about being late.
You must have run here.
Please, use this.
Thank you.
You look very familiar.
I'm so sorry, Teacher.
I know I must look terrible.
I've left my daughter in your care and
I'm a sinner for only showing up now.
No need to say such a thing.
Teacher.
If you can send Red to college,
I am willing to do anything.
I know she's not good at studying,
but studying is not everything, right?
Let's find something that's not studying,
but something she's talented at.
We can still send her to
a good college, right?
It's a problem that there can
only be one number one.
We should look at other criteria,
not just studies.
Wouldn't society be happier
if everyone could be number one?
Don't you think there is something
my Red is very good at?
All children have at least one thing...
No, they most definitely have one thing
they love and are passionate about.
I believe that every child has something
they can be first place in.
I will do anything you need.
I just want my daughter to find
something that excites her
so she can be first place.
Please help her find a college
that suits her.
If you inform and teach me,
I will do anything to help her.
- Okay, Teacher?
- Yes!
Then...
Me, Teacher?
I... am Chi Yeol's stepmom.
Chi Yeol's mom.
You should've come earlier.
Chi Yeol is so talented.
No, he'll be the top student.
But that kid says it's too expensive and
he doesn't want to trouble his sister.
He refuses to go to medical school,
no matter what.
I'm going insane.
- Teacher, I'll choose my major...
- Medical school?
Medical school? Of course I'll send him.
- He has the grades for it.
- Ma'am...
Don't worry.
He will become a dependable doctor
because Chi Yeol is so mature.
Leave it to me.
Then should we get started on
each person, one by one?
I'm sorry, Red.
You're embarrassed because
I showed up looking this way, right?
Wow, it's the beach!
You guys!
- Finished, right?
- Yes.
This caller is unavailable
to take your call.
Didn't you come to see me?
I'm leaving the city with
Reporter Kye tomorrow morning.
I'm staying over one night.
Don't you feel like seeing the sea?
It would be nicer to see it together.
She said she was going with Reporter Kye.
Call the weathercasters' office
and find out where Pyo Na Ri is.
- Hello?
- Hey!
Kye Sung Sook can't make it to
that story she stole from you.
What do you want to do?
Chi Yeol is a senior.
I can't even feed him good food.
I'm going catch this live squid
and feed it to him.
Oh, here it is.
It's here.
Hey, squid!
I'll go borrow some clothes for you.
It's okay. I want to see her now.
There's one here.
Gosh, she went to catch live squid for
her little brother and she's still at it.
Is that Pyo Na Ri?
Isn't the tide coming in at 10:30?
Is she planning to die
just to catch a squid?
Tell her to come back in.
Pyo Na Ri, hurry back in!
My throat hurts.
I don't think she can hear.
Take this and go to the car.
Pyo Na Ri!
Get over here.
What brings you here?
I'm not in a place I can't be in.
You came here on purpose.
You can't give up on her?
Were you going to try something
when I wasn't around?
Gosh, seriously?
Don't you work, by the way?
Do you have nothing better to do
than follow a girl around?
Or did you go on about trusting me,
when you actually don't?
Did you come here to watch over us?
You only started liking her
because I liked her, right?
You want to take her from me
because she's my girl.
I ought to just...
You've always wanted everything
that was mine.
You've always been jealous of me,
haven't you?
Get over here, you.
Live your entire life
being jealous of me.
If you do 10 things for her,
I'll do 100 things for her.
I'm going to do things for her that you
can't do even if you try all your life.
This one is nice and big!
I've never known jealousy.
You can spend your life being jealous.
That's the best you can do.
What, you punk!
Are you a billionaire or a gangster?
Why are you so good at fighting?
Do you think it's easy
for me to hate you?
Are we still friends?
We are, you punk.
Of course we are, you punk!
You're worried because of me, aren't you?
It's because you're jealous!
Yeah.
I am jealous of you.
And you're worried and anxious
because of me.
This is all because of that one girl.
This is so embarrassing.
Don't be jealous.
You shouldn't get caught being
worried about me. You're a man.
What kind of a man
sits around being jealous?
Hey!
She's mine.
I know.
No, I don't think you know.
I'll confirm it for you.
Let go.
Let me go!
Let go of me! I don't need to see.
Just let go of me.
Pyo Na Ri likes me.
Let go. I don't want to see.
You don't need to show me!
Let me go!
Let go...
You don't need to show me.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Why are you good to me?
You're sick.
You're so young and you're a man.
I feel sorry for you. I do.
I wish they were both my wives.
He likes me.
He actually likes me.
Are you dating Hong Hye Won?
I am dating her.
- You're dating her?
- Get out!
Why is he being like that to me?
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
I was worried.
I'm going to end it with her.
I'm going to forget her.