Okay, let's eat everyone. Let's eat.
It's hot. Be careful.
Thank you for the food.
Let's eat.
Your uncle must be back.
Red, you look very young today.
What did you do different?
You look like a teenager.
We are all teenagers.
Right? What's wrong with me?
I thought you were all in your twenties.
I must be crazy.
It's nonsense.
Why is he staring?
Eat up. Eat, eat.
It's getting cold.
Pyo Na Ri!
Just date us both.
She can date us both and then
choose which one of us she prefers.
- Reporter Lee...
- Date both of us.
Come out.
I want to sleep.
I'm going to jump over to your roof then.
Do you want to break your leg?
Make me ramen too.
You want me to date both of you
and make you ramen.
Why do you want so much?
You're going to do it though.
- Who is?
- You are.
Look here.
You'll end up doing
what I'm asking you to do.
- Buy me an ice cream.
- I'm going to sleep.
Now.
What are you going to do now?
You've been caught by
Announcer Geum's parents and your father.
What are you going to do now,
you bastard?
Let go. Let me go!
You poured in too much water.
It's not salty enough.
You said you didn't like salty food.
Still, the seasoning
should be just right.
This one or this one?
Neither.
Open it for me.
Don't you have your own hands?
I want to be loved.
If you open it for me,
I feel like I'm being loved.
It'll be like we're dating and
you like me more than I like you.
Don't eat it if you don't want to.
You would've opened it for me
if I hadn't said anything, right?
What did you do for a month?
You went on like a dozen
arranged dates during the month.
I went 10 times, not a dozen times.
You have two more this week.
What? Are you a police detective?
That's mine.
What are you two doing here?
I'm going to date another man.
You...
shut your mouth.
I'm going to date a man
who has no friends.
Be quiet.
Not a man with lots of money.
Shut your mouth.
Not one who's so great
that he makes me anxious.
I said shut your mouth.
I'm lonely.
You have two guys
so why would you be lonely?
What guys? I don't have any right now.
This girl is getting
funnier by the minute.
Sit down.
Sit down, would you?
Sit.
Hey!
How come you don't listen
when I tell you to sit
but you listen to Go Jung Won?
You had those dates at my hotel,
so you weren't really trying to move on.
You did it to show me and
pretend that you were doing well now.
- Stop pretending.
- Let's all do it.
Are you serious about that?
You don't want to?
Why would I do such a thing?
Yes, I said I had two hearts and
did a crazy thing with two men.
Are you saying this is how
I have to take responsibility for it?
Yes.
I am sorry for that.
I admit I was wrong.
So, let's be clean of this and move on.
I'm saying let's not be together
in this awkward way ever again.
Why are you doing this to me,
Reporter Lee?
I'm not going to see you two again.
Don't come here again.
Just... date both of us.
You can date Hwa Shin too.
President Go!
What is it?
Eat it. It's good for us at our age.
We should prepare. It will come soon.
I don't need it. I'm still strong.
What? Who are you kidding?
You have the fan on every night
saying it's hot, even in this weather.
I'm only eating it
because you gave it to me.
Eat lots beforehand
or we'll end up that way too.
Change the light bulb.
You do it.
How can I do it?
I can't even reach it.
We don't even have a man to change it.
What have we been doing with our lives?
Why are you acting
like this too, President?
Even if you refuse to do it,
Hwa Shin will not stop.
If I can be in your heart
for a little longer...
I can do it.
I want you all for myself.
But those are just my feelings.
You like us both and it confuses you
enough that you broke up with us.
So this is your chance.
You can get to know me better
and date me.
Get to know my feelings better.
- Let's do it.
- Good, then.
We'll start tomorrow.
It's not like you're doing this
behind our backs.
We are asking you to do it.
You don't need to be sorry.
Pyo Na Ri doesn't need
to give her permission.
It would be strange for her to okay this.
Right? I am not okay with it.
Why would you do
something like this, President?
Reporter Lee,
do you really want to do this?
A weird relationship like this? Really?
We didn't even get to start at all.
I feel very wronged.
I feel more wronged.
My friend betrayed me.
Forget about common sense or
whether this is ridiculous or not.
Is anyone going to give you
an award for ending it like this?
Are you going to hang
that award up somewhere?
I guess you'll receive
the "Regret" award.
You'll get the "Regret" trophy.
All three of us will know
that I'm dating the both of you.
What am I supposed to do in the middle?
Sure, I can forget about my pride.
I can restart that difficult
one-sided love I was in for three years.
But, date two guys?
I can't date two guys.
It doesn't suit me at all.
I'm about to get angry.
What do you people take me for?
You come here so blatantly
like you're giving me a present.
You're telling me to date two men
as if you're proposing to me.
I will never do it.
Who am I to do that? I can't do it.
I'm busy enough making a living.
You want me to... what?
Date two men at the same time?
Don't come back here again.
I'm very serious.
Why are you becoming crazy like me?
You're making me crazy.
Sorry about today, but...
Hey, you went too far.
How will I look to the parents?
You're just like the rumors say.
I thought you might be nice.
You must not know because
you've fallen so hard for Pyo Na Ri.
Pyo Na Ri liked Reporter Lee
a lot for three years.
It was surprising that
Reporter Lee wasn't swayed
by that kind of devoted love.
I'll come here every night.
I'll tell you one thing Pyo Na Ri did
for Reporter Lee every time I come.
I'll tell you just how much
she loved Reporter Lee in detail.
You can go to bed every night
thinking about that.
You're curious, right?
Don't you have anything better to do?
No, thanks to you.
I won't let you love so easily.
Your true nature is very sexy.
Go play somewhere else.
Marry for love? How tacky of you.
I'm rooting for Reporter Lee Hwa Shin.
I told you not to drink, didn't I?
I bought you cup ramen and ice cream.
I even came out while I was sleeping.
Shouldn't you listen to me now? Huh?
Huh?
Stop drinking right now!
Are you trying to upset me on purpose
drinking right in front me?
Are you trying to die or something?
You're so annoying!
Please stop drinking in front of me!
Are you worried about me?
You can come here next to me if you are.
You need to do something about
that mouth of yours, Reporter Lee.
Just don't open your mouth at all.
You shouldn't talk or drink.
Just shut it.
Go back to your mom's house
and live there, please.
Am I a child?
Why would I live with my mom?
I could live with you.
You can come over here if you're worried.
I don't want to sleep alone.
What?
Sleep with me.
Goodnight.
Mommy!
Why are you here making me feel bad?
Is that why you came out
an hour early? To run away?
What is it? Are you looking for Hwa Shin?
No. No, I'm not.
Don't think about Hwa Shin
when you're with me.
When I'm with you, I think about him.
When I'm with him, I think about you.
Why? Can't I do that?
When you're with me,
think of only me, okay?
I can't control that and what can
I do when the opposite happens?
That's why I said I didn't
want to date both of you.
I really can't do that.
Why are you here early in the morning
making me feel sorry to you?
I can't control my feelings.
I'm not very smart,
so I can't control my thoughts either.
I just feel guilty and I feel ashamed.
I keep doing the
opposite of what I want to.
Okay.
Then think about Hwa Shin
when you're with me.
Make sure to think about me
when you're with Hwa Shin, okay?
Is this guy crazy too?
What?
You just thought "Is this guy crazy?"
Don't call me President from now on.
Don't use titles.
Say "Hey, you" or "That guy."
If you call me "Go Jung Won" or
"Jung Won" 100 times, we can break up.
Really?
- Try it.
- Really?
Hey, you.
Hey, Jung Won.
What? That was twice.
Jung Won.
Three times.
Is this guy crazy?
Good, good. Give that to me.
Give it to me. Let go of it.
Come on, get in. Get in the car.
Hey!
She's good at it.
Help me. I like her... more...
She must have gotten
a ride from Jung Won.
Do well today. Go on in.
Say thank you. I did something good.
Don't you have any manners?
Gosh, seriously?
Yesterday, this girl came by.
She said she'd come every night
and tell me the things you did
when you liked Hwa Shin.
I have to dream of those things
every night, so what do I do?
You should be held responsible.
Who is it?
Who has nothing better to do?
I'll tell you over dinner.
Come if you're curious.
Wait.
Hey... hey!
Home sharing is a new way of living
where strangers of different genders
come to live in a home together.
It first started in Barcelona.
It then spread to Paris and all over
Europe before entering our country.
It is a way to live with
low rent and have company.
Therefore, it is very popular with
college students and single people.
It is said that many
people end up meeting
and marrying in these homes, as well.
Reporter Lee Young Seok has the story.
This is a shared house in Seoul.
According to recent surveys
6 out of 10 people
in their twenties and thirties
said they wanted
to live in a shared house.
They also said
they intended on living in one.
Those who lived alone were a large factor
in the rise in popularity
of shared houses.
The biggest concern about a shared house
is getting along with housemates.
It's been a month since you've come in.
Yes. Hello, Director.
Still no manners.
I came back from England.
It's been three years, Hwa Shin.
Hello, Senior.
There's a flickering bulb in our house.
Can you come change it?
It's not out yet if it's flickering.
It's still on, so I'll change it
when it's completely out.
It's causing such a headache
that we can't go into the room.
Then you two can leave the house.
- You have nice houses.
- I'll change it for you.
Why would you?
Director, why don't you come do it?
Why would I?
Put some nails in the wall for us, too.
Why would I go to your house to
change light bulbs and hammer in nails?
Why can't you do it?
Sung Sook, I'll do it
after we finish the news.
Where do you live?
We shouldn't let just any man
into the house.
Why am I just "any man"?
Wait. If he's just "any man,"
then what am I?
What am I that I would go to your house
to change light bulbs and put in nails?
- What am I?
- Oh...
- You are...
- Yes?
Just a... comfortable man?
Your servant? Okay.
Ah, so when you call me "any man,"
it's because I make you nervous.
A man should make a woman nervous,
isn't that right Hwa Shin?
What a joke.
Hwa Shin, you got
your notification, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Do a good job with Hong Hye Won.
Okay. There are lots of men
to change the light bulbs.
That guy needs a beating
to pull himself together.
Sleep with me, sleep with me,
sleep with me, sleep with me.
Did you sleep well?
You were good today.
You looked good on screen too.
Have you been going to
the hospital in the past month?
Hey, is that the only thing
you're curious about?
I'm not a patient. I'm a man... a man.
Not a patient. A man... a guy.
- I'll get going.
- Need any light bulbs changed at home?
No.
- Nails that need hammering?
- I have Chi Yeol.
Let's have dinner later.
I have an arranged blind date later.
Well, then...
Hey, eat more.
- Eat with me.
- Take your time eating.
Did you get a ride from
Jung Won this morning?
No.
You haven't forgotten about going
on that date in my place, right?
No. Don't worry.
Did you know Go Jung Won tried
to help you on the day of your test?
It seemed like you didn't know.
What are you talking about?
Due to the sharp rise in
the price of cigarettes last year
the decreasing sales in volume of
cigarettes had an increase in...
Wow, Hwa Shin sure is lucky.
Reporter Woo, who got the 7 p.m. spot,
ended up being a foreign correspondent.
Now he gets to take his empty spot
even though he was disciplined.
You're the lucky one.
If Hwa Shin hadn't been disciplined,
you wouldn't be in the 9 p.m. slot.
Pyo Na Ri's going on that date for you?
Aren't you and Pyo Na Ri over?
Is he a decent guy?
Are you holding on to her?
- Are you being messy about it?
- Forget it.
You wouldn't send her
if it were a decent guy.
I did ask her to go because
he didn't seem so great.
I don't know what happened,
but he's sending a replacement.
- Who is he sending?
- Someone good.
Must be someone very aggressive.
Who is it?
If you're so curious,
forget the live news and go.
What?
If your love is that great,
I will acknowledge it.
I will acknowledge that your love is
unlike any love in this century.
What is he doing? Hey.
Sit down now.
You won't be able to go.
You want to keep pushing me?
You said you'd be a son a bitch.
You were like a little puppy.
You're a coward.
It's at W Hotel in Cheongdam-dong
at seven o'clock.
- Hwa Shin!
- They must be meeting now.
Sit down now.
- Hey! Where are you going?
- What is it? What?
- Hey!
- Hwa Shin!
- Where are you going?
Three seconds... anchor, stand by!
Jo Deuk Hwan, a close associate
of fraud Jo Sang Chil
was arrested in China
after four years on the run.
You are Announcer Pyo Na Ri, right?
I am Go Jung Won. Nice to meet you.
What are you doing?
Go and catch Hwa Shin now.
I went to use the restroom. Sorry.
- Are you in your right mind?
- Yes.
What are you doing?
You pulled that stunt
with the helicopter
and you go to the restroom
when we're live?
Are you crazy?
I'm getting 10,000 new white hairs
a day because of you.
Hey! You shouldn't have had any water.
Even if you have to pee,
you should stay in your seat.
Even if there is a bomb dropping,
an anchor must stay in his seat.
It was a Hong Hye Won solo shot
for the next line.
I knew I could go for a bit because
I wasn't going to be on screen.
Hey, do you have some sort of issue?
What's wrong with you?
The light is coming on.
With the excess supply of crude oil
continuing to be an issue
international oil prices
have fallen below 40 dollars.
Reporter Kwon Joon Hyuk has the story.
Let's pretend this is the first time we
met and that Hwa Shin didn't set us up.
What do you think?
Sorry, but someone will be
coming to sit there soon.
Stop doing these dates.
Just date me and Hwa Shin.
It would be even better
if you didn't meet Hwa Shin.
You're already dating two men.
To go on blind dates on top of that...
Isn't that being too cruel to us?
Who said I was going to date you two?
Someone is coming soon.
He isn't going to come.
- Why?
- Well...
I told him my girlfriend was only doing
this because she was mad at me.
That she's someone
I'm considering marrying.
Why would you lie?
Lie? What lie?
I never lied.
What?
What is it? Are you not feeling well?
No, no.
I'll drive you.
That she's someone
I'm considering marrying.
I've never been told that before.
That she's someone
I'm considering marrying.
No, no, no, no.
Get it together. Get it together.
Scary, scary.
Hey... he didn't ask to
see you again, did he?
Reporter Lee, I haven't ever
really thought about marriage before.
Did that guy ask you to marry him?
What kind of a guy brings up marriage
after meeting you just once?
How would he know if he wants
to marry you or not? Is he crazy?
Is he any crazier than a guy who
tells me to date two men at once?
- Let's watch a movie tomorrow.
- Are you busy?
- Reporter Lee.
- Is your finger broken?
- You should call.
- Why don't you respond to my texts?
Are you still wearing
the clothes Jung Won gives you?
You're not doing broadcasts
with Hwa Shin, are you?
Don't wear them.
Take that off. Wear my clothes.
- Reporter Lee.
- What should we do this weekend?
What should we do this weekend?
Don't think about Jung Won
when you're with me.
Don't think about Hwa Shin
- Gosh, Reporter Lee.
- What?
I'm so confused and dizzy.
This is so difficult.
I feel like I'm about to wither
and die because this is so hard.
If you insist on me dating both of you
how about I date Jung Won this month
and then date you next month?
How about taking turns like that?
- No.
- Why not?
You'll fall for him in one month and
you won't date me when my turn comes.
We could change the order,
but then Jung Won will say no.
I won't fall for him and I promise
I will date you next month.
- No.
- Then...
How about mornings with you
and nights with Jung Won?
How about we divide up the time?
No, nights...
I like nights. I want nights.
What do you want to do at night?
I'm not going to do any of
the things you are thinking about.
I want to hold your hand, hold you,
kiss you, and sleep with you at night.
That's what I thought.
If you can do it in the morning,
I can do mornings.
I won't do it at night and
there's no chance in the morning.
- Then, when?
- Reporter Lee.
I should have a conscience
and manners if I date two men.
How can I do all that with two men?
Are you insane?
That's why I'm saying I can't do it.
Do you really like both of us
the same amount?
When I liked you four years ago
how nice would it have been
if you had looked my way too?
I liked you so much for three years.
Back then... you wouldn't even
shoot me one kind glance.
It's not like it costs you money.
You couldn't even say one kind word.
Why are you showing up now
and giving me such a headache?
It is much nicer to receive love
than it is to give love.
Receiving love makes life easier.
Things were so good with Go Jung Won,
so why come now and ruin things?
Do you like Jung Won more?
I don't know! I don't know, I don't know.
You like me more, don't you?
My feelings for you are
hidden deep inside my heart.
So how am I even supposed to know?
I thought I had no feelings left at all,
but they keep popping up.
They're so deeply hidden that
even I don't know they're there.
So how can I know who I like more?
Do a good job.
Can you hold me tightly?
- Tighter.
- Are you almost done?
It's done.
Bang Ja Young, turn on the lights.
That's strange.
Should we try once more?
You said you knew what you were doing
and that you weren't a man
if you couldn't do it.
- Get off.
- Hey!
It is scary.
What should we do? Call Chef?
What else can we do? Call Chef.
Thank you, Chef.
I changed the electrical conductor.
You shouldn't have trouble anymore.
If I knew that was the problem,
I could have done it easily.
What? Are you feeling jealous because
Chef could do something you couldn't?
Ah, my stomach hurts.
The bathroom is outside, right?
I'll be back.
Since only women live here,
it's a bit of a problem.
We're sorry we had to ask you.
Call me whenever you need.
I'm your neighbor.
How did it go?
How did it go in there?
It looks like you really plugged it up.
You'll need to call a plumber tomorrow.
The toilets in England aren't like this.
The toilets here are very sensitive.
I brought you here to fix the light.
Why would you break the toilet?
It's not like you even
bought us toilet paper.
Are you marking your territory or what?
Why would you do that?
What are you going to do? What?
Don't you worry. I'll take care of it.
What are you doing?
Don't call me President from now on.
Don't use titles.
Say "Hey, you" or "That guy."
Call me "Go Jung Won" or "Jung Won."
[JUNG WON]
[REPORTER LEE]
[PYO NA RI]
This world is full of breasts.
Why must it be my son's breast?
How could a young man have breast cancer?
He has to get married
and hold his wife to his chest.
How can you put a
woman's bra on that chest?
Since things have turned out this way...
please do not let the cancer relapse.
Please take care of my son
Hwa Shin's chest and protect it.
If there is a nice girl with large
breasts who will hold him in her arms
please bring them together.
I pray to you. I pray to you.
There is a lot of fluid in there.
You must have been in pain.
Men almost never get it.
This is very strange.
What?
Is there a problem?
By any chance... have you been drinking?
I told you not to exercise,
but it looks like you have.
Your surgery wound
opened up quite a lot.
Or did you get into a fight?
Seeing the state you are in,
you probably ate food like pork belly.
You had dairy, too.
You decided to ignore your doctor
to see if I would win or you would win.
- Is a room open?
- Yes, Doctor.
- What?
- It's a seroma.
You said it wasn't last time.
How much did you drink, exactly?
Also, why are you here alone today?
Why aren't you here with Pyo Na Ri?
Did you two really break up?
How can I be admitted again, Doctor?
- There is a two person room.
- Wait a minute.
You know I can't share a room
with another female patient.
Who told you not to listen to
any of my warnings?
You drank, fought, and didn't
come in for radiation treatment.
You need to be admitted.
If you haven't broken up,
tell Pyo Na Ri to come right now.
I don't like it because
she treats me like a patient.
I'm going to be treated
like a man by her from now on.
Look at you.
What is wrong with Reporter Um?
Na Ri?
Chief and Reporter Kye,
what brings you by?
Can we use your bathroom?
Ours is broken and the one
on the second floor is just guys.
It seems weird to use the restaurant's.
Yes, of course. It's over here.
- You're making kimchi pancakes.
- Yes.
The kids are studying on the second floor
so I thought I would feed them some.
Looks good.
- Do you want some?
- Do you have soju?
It's good.
Reporter Kye, I'm enjoying you
on the 9 p.m. news.
I'd like to learn how to be
charismatic like you.
Suck up to me at work only, not here.
- It's uncomfortable.
- Gosh, do it to me.
Chief, you're getting
more and more beautiful.
- How do you do it?
- What good is it?
I'm not on video, only audio.
Plus, I just got canceled.
- You did?
- Yes.
- Here we go.
- Cheers.
What about you?
Who is it? Who do you like more?
- Excuse me?
- Do you think we're stupid?
They're friends, at that.
Yesterday, Lee Hwa Shin said
"Sleep with me" to you.
You knew... how did you?
You knew about it?
How long has it been with President Go?
He comes to drive you to
the station every morning.
Decide quickly and
don't make them suffer so long.
I just hate girls like that.
You should clink glasses.
They want me to date them both.
- They said that?
- Really?
So I said I would
break up with both of them.
Don't worry. I can't date them both.
I can't do it.
I'm breaking up with them.
I'm in the process of ending it.
Wow...
You should do it, Pyo Na Ri.
- Are you crazy?
- When else will she get the chance?
She will need to try going back
and forth in order to figure it out.
Once she figures out who she likes more
she won't want to
go back and forth at all.
Yes, but I have a little brother
who is a senior right now.
You won't be able to
get married and grow old.
I'm getting a bad feeling that you'll
grow old while taking care of Chi Yeol.
Chi Yeol wouldn't like that either.
Don't run away or avoid it
and just do it, Pyo Na Ri.
That's not right.
Don't you think I've had two men
follow me around saying they liked me?
Reporter Um and Lee Joong Shin?
Yes.
I only went after one.
I ruined my own life,
but I have no regrets.
If I had dated both men at that time,
my life would be even more twisted.
Just choose one man.
You are only supposed to love one man.
Date them both, Pyo Na Ri.
Those guys really like you.
It's like they're on their knees begging.
The men were the ones
who asked you to date them both.
Date them both, love them,
and then make the decision.
It's the best you can do for them.
- No, no. I can't do it.
- You can do it.
Just pick one.
So, who is that one man?
It has to be President Go.
You need to dump Lee Hwa Shin.
Yes. We think alike on that one.
You will realize that once you
start dating our brother-in-law.
You don't know the truth about men
until you live with them.
What is Reporter Lee like?
Oh no. It's okay.
Are you going on a business trip?
- What?
- Are you going on a business trip?
- No.
- Then where are you going?
On a vacation.
Right. It is the weekend.
Why? Do you want to go too?
Should I?
Really?
Why not live my life recklessly?
It's all over if you go on
an overnight vacation with me.
It's over with Jung Won
and you have to date me.
- I know.
- Do you?
Yes.
Gosh, you...
Next time.
Let's go on an overnight trip.
Let's go spend a night somewhere.
Has she lost her mind?
Okay?
No.
I'm going alone.
What is this?
Are you going with another woman?
Hey, what other woman do I have?
How would I know?
No, next time.
What's a guy going on
vacation by himself for?
It's very suspicious.
I think you're even more suspicious.
Why are you suddenly like this?
Suddenly? This isn't sudden.
You have always been sexy, Reporter Lee.
Since the moment I met you until now,
you've always been so manly to me.
To me, you are still
the manliest of all men.
All right.
Still, next time.
Bye.
Pft.
He's an anchor.
You are receiving that love.
You were born to be loved.
You have been receiving
that love in your life.
The love of God began with creation.
It has connected us
through our fellowship.
Because of your existence in the world
it brings us all so much joy.
Are you mad because I'm here?
Why are you here?
- Let's go.
- Leave.
- Then, I'll leave.
- Where are you going?
Let go of me!
Give that to me.
Just let it go for one day.
They don't recognize you.
Close the curtain.
Just for one day, Reporter Lee.
Who are all those people?
Oh, what are you doing here, Jung Won?
- Have you been doing well, Uncle?
- Yes.
Have you guys been okay?
What brings you here?
Do you have an extra room in your house?
Can I stay there?
Why?
I like Pyo Na Ri. I want to be near her.
How does my sister feel?
I don't know.
I must not be good enough yet.
I don't think I've
won her heart over yet.
I want to impress her.
Your sister keeps pushing me away.
I need to impress you, too.
I don't know.
Yes, a little brother
should be hard on me.
Sorry, but why don't
you guys go eat outside?
Why?
Doctor Geum called me
yesterday and told me.
Are you hiding it from me too now?
What were you going to do on your own?
I guess you can go to
women's public baths too.
So, Grandma. Should I scrub
and wash your back for you?
Should I wash your back for you?
Let me see.
- Does that feel good? Is it here?
- Hey, stop that.
- I'll clean your back for you.
- Stop that!
Here? Here?
It tickles.
Gosh! I knew this would happen
when I saw you drinking.
I don't want to be treated like
a patient by you anymore, so go.
So you still have your pride.
You're still a man, huh?
I'm coming in now.
Go inside and get changed
in the dressing room.
You have the post-op bra, right?
I have to use it again?
- I don't want to use it.
- Did you bring it?
Just go!
He has to use it, right?
Once we use the needle to
take out the fluid in his chest
he needs the post-op bra
to put pressure on the chest.
- Go on in.
- I won't do it.
You have to do it this time.
I will not do it.
Right now, please.
I'll go downstairs and
buy it myself, so just leave.
I won't go in until you leave.
Why would you buy it
when you have two already?
I'll go to your place and bring them.
I'll get them
while you're getting treated.
Give me your keys.
Are you going to keep acting
like my guardian? Just go.
I heard Pyo Na Ri was in a one-sided
love with Reporter Lee for a long time.
It seems like everyone knows
about that darn one-sided love.
Honestly, I feel hurt.
I'm also anxious because I feel like
she might like Hwa Shin more.
I would lose to Hwa Shin
if he knew I felt like this, right?
Yes.
Don't get caught.
Just show her who you really are.
Not the image of you that your family
taught you to show to others.
You caused lots of trouble in
junior high and high school in the US.
You had lots of girlfriends too.
You're much more charming up close,
rather than from afar.
Though, everyone only sees you from afar.
Come. I'll give you a room.
- Okay.
- You can do it, nephew.
I can do it.
Hey, you, Jung Won... which one?
Oh... Jung Won.
Are you home?
Oh, no.
Where are you then?
I'm out right now.
See me for a bit. Right now, I'm...
Sorry, but today I'm a bit...
Today, you're what?
I think I'll be busy.
I might be up all night at the station.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Okay, then.
In the name of Jesus Christ
we pray, Amen.
How many times do I have to tell you?
The surgery went well
and his prognosis looks good.
If you have time to worry like this,
make sure your friend doesn't drink.
Please make sure he
doesn't get into fights, either.
Go now.
I said go.
What are you looking at?
Don't look at me like that.
Lee Hwa Shin, I'm here to
give you a shot of painkillers.
- Can your friend pull your pants down?
- What?
I'll do it myself.
I told you that you
cannot use your arms today.
Can your friend please help out?
But still...
Hurry, please.
More.
It will sting.
If you move your arms today,
the fluid will build up again.
You could get an infection.
You could lift your arms in your sleep
so it might be better
to stay up all night.
Hold on.
We can also tie your arms up.
What did you say? What?
It was a shot into the muscle so
you have to massage it for a long time.
Like this.
I'll be back to take your blood pressure.
You know how the test started
20 minutes late that day?
He was worried you
wouldn't be able to make it.
President Go created a traffic jam using
multiple cars to make his mother late.
You know what kind of person he is,
and he did something like that for you.
Shouldn't you thank him?
He didn't even tell me.
- That's enough.
- She said massage it for a long time.
It would've been nice to do this earlier.
I would have been cold about it
even if you had breast cancer.
I wouldn't have given up Pyo Na Ri
over something like that.
You shouldn't.
I'm not going to either.
Stop now!
You don't listen...
You two must have made up.
No.
I'll be heading home now.
- Where are you going?
- Your friend is here now.
I don't need to be here.
He's is more considerate and
better at taking care of you.
Don't go.
- You told me to go.
- Don't go.
Let's all stay here.
You go.
I said I would sleep there.
You're too tall, Jung Won. This is short.
- I can't sleep.
- Me neither.
- Reporter Lee.
- Call me Hwa Shin.
Jung Won.
What?
I like it that the three of us
are here together.
Do you two not like it?
It's not so great.
- What about you?
- I don't like it.
You just want to be with me?
- Yes.
Then should I be honest right now
about how I really feel?
Can I say it?
- Talk.
- Say it quickly.
Should the three of us
just live together like this?
Let's not bother with me
dating both of you.
Let's just all live together instead.
We don't need to
date separately and have meals.
We can all watch TV, eat fruit,
and drink coffee together.
Then we can all go to
work together in the morning.
I can't live together if it's just two,
but I could do it if it's three of us.
We need to live together
to really get to know one another.
Dating is really only
getting to know half the person.
We can poo and smell each other's poo.
You have to live together
and bother each other a bit.
That way, you really know one another.
Then I can really figure out
which person is the answer.
If we really live together,
you two may end up not liking me.
You may end up losing feelings for me
after living together for a month.
You have to live together
in order to really fight too.
You don't get into proper fights
when you're dating.
If one month isn't enough,
then we could do two months.
Well, one person could end up
disliking me and pack up to leave.
Or I could end up leaving.
I might end up being
disappointed in both of you.
What do you think?
You don't have to if you don't want to.
I just thought it might be better
if we were all together.
Gosh, forget it.
Goodnight.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Sleep with me.
That she's someone
I'm considering marrying.
Hello to all our viewers.
It is too late, but I apologize.
I apologize for calling
Anchor Pyo an easy woman.
I don't like easy girls like you.
[APOLOGIZING TOO LATE]
I will repay her by being an easy man.
When Anchor Pyo touched my chest in
Thailand, my heart was already yours.
Truthfully, I was very nervous then.
I pretended not to know that she was in
love with me before I left for Thailand.
I was wrong.
I knew how Anchor Pyo felt
and played with her heart.
I am reflecting on what I have done.
Let's look at the video.
I can't do it. Kiss another guy.
Honestly, I really wanted to kiss her.
No one knows how much my heart
was racing when I looked at her lips.
From now on...
Hurry up.
I hope I get many more opportunities.
That will be all for today.
We hope you have a nice day.
You were so good.
Good job.