Should the three of us
just live together like this?
You don't have to if you don't want to.
I just thought it might be better
if we were all together.
No, no. Gosh, forget it.
Only I can initiate any touching. Okay?
Hey.
This is all for now and only I can do it.
That will be the only
rule of living together.
Are we pieces of wood or something?
You're the only one who can do it?
If you break the rule,
you have to leave.
That person has to leave the house.
We can live at my place.
- You think you can do it?
- I'll have to.
What about you, Reporter Lee?
If I say no to this...
you're not going to
live with him, are you?
There was lightning and
a torrential rainfall in Seoul...
Nurse Oh, do you have any painkillers?
Where are you hurting?
If we really live together,
you two may end up not liking me.
You may end up losing feelings for me
after living together for a month.
Is she doing this to try and break up?
Well, one person could end up
disliking me and pack up to leave.
Or I could end up leaving.
I think she is doing it to break up.
How could Pyo Na Ri say
something like that? Is she crazy?
To break up without regrets.
She wants to be
done with us and break up?
It's going to bother her
forever that we are friends.
No matter who she chooses,
our friendship will be ruined.
Who asks to live with someone
in order to break up? Such nonsense.
It makes no sense for the three of us
to live together to begin with.
What makes sense
in this situation at all?
- Let's not do it.
- Let's do it.
I can't go along with someone trying
to break up with me, and I won't.
She won't choose either of us.
She'll live with us and say
she doesn't want either of us.
The decision is already made.
Still, let's do it.
Let's do whatever Pyo Na Ri asks of us.
Let's do everything she wants.
Pyo Na Ri started it the way she wanted,
but we can end it differently.
Thank you.
Do you have indigestion?
Yes, I think so.
I suppose I ate something
I shouldn't have.
Was it something good?
This is the only way
to end things quickly.
This way we can decide quickly.
I'm going to make this work.
Stop.
Didn't you hear her say
no touching is allowed?
I'm going to marry her within one month.
I'll end it within 10 days.
Grandma, I'm coming in.
Grandma, how are you feeling?
What about this arm of mine?
How long do I have to keep my arm still
and keep it right by my body?
Grandma, you can be discharged now.
Don't move your arm for today.
Starting tomorrow, you can move it a bit.
Today...
Today, as well?
Ask Pyo Na Ri to
help you out just for today.
Do you want to watch a movie with me?
Me?
Why would we watch with you?
You only have two tickets.
Either one of you will do.
Either one of us?
That is the worst thing you could say.
Don't bother if you don't want to.
- Are you feeling lonely?
- Be quiet.
You're lonely?
With your wife and kids in
another country, you must be lonely.
Get off quickly.
You scared me.
Hey, do you want to
watch a movie with me?
- What?
- It's just...
I have tickets.
"Darling, Will You Stay?"
The title is a bit much.
Why would I watch a
romance film with you?
Reporter Lee? Sorry.
I got you discharged. We can go.
Are you dressed?
Isn't it hard with just one arm?
I don't know. Don't talk to me.
Should I help you get dressed?
I'm putting my underwear on.
Reporter Lee, you can't use
your arm out of frustration.
You'll have to be admitted again.
Just take it slowly. Slowly, okay?
- Did Jung Won leave?
- Yes.
I really don't want the
three of us to live together.
Is one month going to be long enough?
Yes.
I'll end it for you within 10 days.
Here we go.
One for women and two for men.
A 30 pack is enough for a month, right?
Let's buy more.
One is more than enough.
Don't buy just a month's supply.
You could end up staying
more than a month.
Come in and stay for coffee.
Sit down.
Sit down. I came knowing
you'd be here, Mom.
Hello.
I'm going to marry Pyo Na Ri.
When it comes to marriage,
I won't make any sacrifices for anyone.
Not for you, friends, or anyone.
Will you marry me?
I told you I would decide
after living with you.
It isn't right of you
to push me like this.
Are you overconfident about
everything like this
because you have money, or what?
That is why I asked you
if you would marry me.
If I were your mother,
I would be very upset too.
And how do I come off looking?
Were you always this way?
You don't think about the consequences?
You're scary when you're angry.
Move.
You've brought out the competitive
rebel in me that had disappeared.
That's why I like you.
You can yell, curse, and
treat me however you want.
Just be comfortable around me.
Hey, move! You'll fall.
There you go. Good job.
This is my card. There's no limit on it.
I want my woman to spend
the money that I've earned.
I wanted to give it to you,
but I couldn't.
I want to show off my money to you.
I want to ask you why you bought a bag
at another store instead of mine.
I want to argue with you and
tell you to stop buying new shoes.
There's so much good food besides
black bean noodles I want you to eat.
There is nothing better in the world
than black bean noodles.
I have the right to know what the
woman I'm marrying spends money on.
You can accept this card.
I don't understand why you
never let me spend any money.
But you like me anyway.
Here.
Hello, there.
Sook.
Go see a movie with me.
Why is everyone dying to see this movie?
"Darling, Will You Stay?"
Sorry, Chi Yeol. I'll be staying
at the station for a while.
Don't do the laundry.
Leave it in the laundry basket.
I'll come on the weekends to
make food and side dishes for you.
Make sure to eat properly, okay?
Your sister.
Have you all eaten?
Hello.
Where is he?
It just kills me to come out
early every morning.
Hello, Director and Senior Um.
- Good morning.
- Yeah, get ready.
Yes, sir!
- Hello.
- Look at his clothes.
I've seen that somewhere before.
Gosh, kids these days.
His clothes are really something.
Senior, even if they're not on camera,
aren't sweatpants kind of too much?
Who do you think you are?
Pardon me?
You're just a contract employee.
Who are you to say anything to the
main anchor about what I wear?
I apologize.
Why am I partnered with you?
Gosh, I have the worst luck.
I'm sorry.
[I'M GETTING MARRIED.]
[HONG SOO YOUNG]
Soo Young? Hong Soo Young?
Why would she send a wedding
invitation to an ex-boyfriend?
"I'm getting married.
Annoyed, aren't you?"
Should I be annoyed?
Who is Soo Young?
What is she thinking sending
a wedding invitation
to a boyfriend from 15 years ago?
"I'm getting married, you jerk."
"Annoyed, aren’t you?"
"You jerk"?
Get in.
Is Reporter Park bothering you?
Oh, no.
Really?
He is good to me.
Tell me if he is looking down
on you or bothering you.
Should we go?
Reporter Lee.
Let's get going... to hell.
What should we do if rumors start?
Rumors about what?
One woman living with two men.
It won't be worse than a
male anchor who had breast cancer.
Three of us for a month.
It will be like hell.
I can't do it and I won't.
Let's end it quickly.
All right.
Okay.
Welcome.
Here is my rent.
It's for one month.
There are three rooms, right?
Since you keep insisting on it,
okay, I accept your rent.
- What about you?
- I'll send it to your account.
Okay.
There are two rooms on the second floor
and one on the first floor,
but it's an open space.
Pyo Na Ri can use a room on the second
floor and I will use the other room.
You can have the first floor.
You're going to be on
the second floor together?
While I'm alone on the open first floor?
I won't have any privacy at all and have
to eat and sleep in the common area.
That won't do.
You like the first floor bed
whenever you come over.
I always sleep on the second floor.
- It will do.
- It won't.
- It's my house.
- Jung Won.
This isn't a house to me,
or a even a friend's house.
This is a war zone.
The person who decides
who sleeps on the second floor...
should be Pyo Na Ri.
You're fighting even before
we have entered the house?
How much more will you
fight once we go inside?
So, what do you want to do?
You should decide.
You feeling confident?
Of course, I am.
My name is Soo Young.
Soo Young?
I'm Hye Kyo.
Soo Young.
Is your last name Song?
Song Hye Kyo?
Let's all split up and head out.
Okay.
- Bye.
- Let's hang out together.
You can eat this.
Okay, but I don't really like sweets.
Thank you to all of you for coming to
Heart Thumping Disco.
My name is DJ Biscuit.
- Don't let me go.
- Trust me.
All you couples better watch out today.
Let's get started!
You with the glasses,
hold on to your girlfriend tight.
What are you doing?
You with the hat,
are you already out?
You should just wipe the floor
while you're there.
You two high school kids there.
You with the glasses.
What kind of relationship are you in?
It's just a ride that uses
centrifugal force and gravity.
You won't be thrown out, so don't worry.
Okay.
You're smiling? I guess you still would.
I will wipe that smile off your faces.
I will get you two today.
We will get started for real now.
Put all your weight
on your back and hold on.
All right.
Hey, what is that position there?
Aren't you two minors?
These high school kids.
What are we to do with them?
All right, then...
You need centripetal force
to go in a circular motion.
Think of me as the pivot.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Oh my! What a frenzy!
"Please don't let me go!"
He's still holding on. It's all good.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Wow, no need for that here.
It's getting hard to watch all of this.
Jung Won doesn't live around here.
Did you do well on your test?
I only got three wrong
on the practice exam.
I got 393.
- You got 393?
- Yeah.
That's really great.
I'm going to Seoul University.
It's been a dream of mine to
kiss a Seoul University student.
I thought that baseball hat
was yours that day.
That's why I chose it.
But it wasn't yours.
I like you better.
They say that your
first love will work out
if you kiss during the first snowfall.
That's why I'm here today.
It snowed yesterday, too.
Should I leave?
No.
Choose one.
I told you I would use the second
floor room from the beginning.
Reporter Lee, you wear glasses?
Put them on. Go on.
You said you were in
a one-sided love with me.
You said you were in love with me
but you never saw me wearing glasses?
When I pull an all-nighter in
the editing room, I wear glasses.
I've worn them many times.
What kind of one-sided love is this?
I really didn't know you wore glasses.
Let's go to the second floor.
What is this?
There are no doors on the first floor
or any privacy here.
I'm like a fish displayed in a market.
This is heavy.
Gosh!
Yes.
- Can I come in?
- Yes.
It feels strange because it's
your first night, right?
By the way, can you really marry me?
You must think I won't be able to.
It seems like you fear your mother.
Are you teasing me?
You look like you'd
listen well to your mom
Hey.
If we were ever to get married,
I'd only want you, Jung Won.
Not your family, money, or anything.
Just... you.
Then would I better than Hwa Shin?
Did you get that wedding invitation too?
- Are you going?
- Why would I?
You really did date Soo Young, right?
I'm telling you that I did.
So, she really did date us both.
I wonder who she's marrying.
I'm going to go.
You still have feelings for her?
I'm going to take Pyo Na Ri.
She was sneaky and dated
both of us for over a year.
So I'm going to ask her
who she liked more.
I'll ask so Pyo Na Ri can hear.
What is that?
I'm confident. Soo Young will say me.
She's a pro in dating two men,
and if she chooses me after 20 years
wouldn't that mean a lot to Pyo Na Ri?
We should help her not waste her time.
What if she chooses me?
I said I'm confident.
Don't do anything stupid and sleep.
The three of us are already
doing something stupid.
What Soo Young says
and what Pyo Na Ri says...
I'll let you know when I get back.
Oh, Red.
Why did you ask me for, Uncle?
I thought I should give this to you.
Here.
Your dad gave this to me
right before he passed away.
At first, I kept it to myself because
I was worried about this and that.
I think it's best that I give it to you.
Neither of your moms know about it.
I want you to read it and decide.
From what I can tell,
they both seem like good moms.
Bang Ja Young will raise Red.
What is it?
Nothing.
I have movie tickets.
Do you want to go with me?
[BEFORE I MET YOU]
Okay, sure.
I'll see you at the theater.
Really?
Gosh, you scared me.
Hey... go get me a coffee.
- We'll be starting soon, Senior.
- Yeah, so hurry up and get it.
Yes, all right.
Oh, we're starting soon.
What is with the young kids these days?
Where are you going at this hour?
Aren't you on air soon?
Senior.
Coffee makes your mouth dry and
makes it difficult to pronounce words.
I mixed cold and hot water.
It's lukewarm water.
You should drink this.
Your tongue will feel better.
If I told you to bring me coffee,
you should bring coffee.
Who told you to bring me lukewarm water
then give me a lecture about my
pronunciation being good or bad?
There goes Reporter Park trying
to discipline his partner again.
- Hwa Shin, Hwa Shin...
- Get what I asked for!
Why is he going up there?
I'm sorry.
Reporter Park.
Yeah, Reporter Lee.
- Drink this.
- Huh?
Okay. Thank you.
Oh, that's nice.
Senior, should we go over
our opening for today?
There were many stories
that developed overnight.
News Morning is starting now.
Do I have to go over this with you?
You're the only one who
needs to work on getting it right.
What kind of girl keeps stepping up
where she shouldn't be?
I'm sorry.
Also, I'll be doing the
third and fourth items here.
You won't be able to do it.
Then can I do the first and second?
No, those are mine too, of course.
Yes, I understand.
That punk hasn't changed at all.
He treats his partners however he wants,
even when they go out to drink.
All right, I got it.
Let's talk about it after, okay?
How many more minutes are there?
Get ready to go.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
That will be all for SBC News Prime.
Thank you to all our viewers.
How is your rooftop apartment?
Fine.
It's not uncomfortable?
It's a good place to live.
Was Reporter Park a bastard
when he worked with you, too?
Never mind.
You know that girl who you
just did the news with?
She gets prettier every time I see her.
Does she have a boyfriend?
She likes me.
Don't joke around. I'm serious.
Try to make it work with her.
Mom, just wait 10 days.
I'll bring my girl to you.
What's with that facial expression?
I haven't given up on you yet.
See you tomorrow.
She really is quite something.
I wonder if Red is here.
Reporter Kye?
You can hug people?
Why are you in here instead of sleeping?
You haven't even changed yet.
Do you have something to say?
Yes.
- I'll come out. Let's talk outside.
- No.
What, what? What is it?
Is Reporter Park bothering you?
- No.
- He is.
- No, he's not.
- He doesn't look down on you?
He's good to me.
What are you doing sitting here
instead of going to sleep?
I'm feeling anxious, okay? I'm nervous.
- Are you crazy?
- That little punk.
If Reporter Park wants to drink
with you, don't ever go with him.
Don't go out to eat with him either.
Don't even look him in the eye
when you're doing the news.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
I want to be with you.
So?
Sleep with me tonight.
Let's pack up and
get out of this hellish place.
Yes.
- Reporter Lee?
- Yes?
Stop bothering me and leave.
It's not Reporter Park
who's bothering me, but you.
- Yeah.
- Yes, you.
All right, then.
I'll just sleep. Just sleep.
The first floor is so wide and open
that I can't sleep.
It doesn't feel right.
- Be careful.
- I feel restless there.
Just let me...
You are too harsh.
Don't break the rules.
Please, let's go home.
Just this once, okay?
Aren't you curious?
No, I'm not curious.
If you're feeling a bit strange here...
we could go to the first floor.
Okay, let's do that. That'd be better.
Okay.
Hey!
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your food.
What was Red thinking setting us up
to watch a movie together?
It was a romance movie, so I think
she wanted me to watch with you, Chef.
She chose me to watch with you
and not Chief Bang.
I think that means she is
thinking of me as her mother.
I know Red will ask me to live with her.
Hey.
So, I'm going to tell you just how much
Pyo Na Ri liked Reporter Lee.
Do you know what time it is?
Shut your mouth.
Stop telling me about Pyo Na Ri
liking Lee Hwa Shin. Stop it!
I don't want to hear it, so just stop it!
I said I'd come every day.
I'd come tell you about Pyo Na Ri and
Lee Hwa Shin like writing in a journal.
You're supposed to write
in a journal every day.
I know all about how you played around
when you were studying abroad in the US.
Have you had lunch?
No.
Let's go eat.
Okay.
We're going to eat here?
Hi.
My girlfriend.
Congratulations on your wedding.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
You didn't think I'd know about you
dating both me and Jung Won, right?
I was going to hold on to it
and not forgive you.
If you do one thing for me
I'll remember you as
my beautiful first love forever.
What is it?
Did you like me more or Jung Won?
Reporter Lee.
- Will you give lots of gift money?
- Yes, I will.
You liked me more, right?
You liked me more than Jung Won, right?
I'm the one you still thought about
even after breaking up, right?
Am I wrong?
Of course I liked Jung Won more.
I'm very materialistic.
I'm materialistic.
Materialistic girls like me too.
Then why did you
break up with Go Jung Won?
Yes, that's right.
He's a filial son.
He is now and probably always will be.
Between us girls,
filial sons aren't so great.
I am not filial.
Then why did you break up with him?
He is selfish.
Hey.
He doesn't know how to give love.
He is only used to receiving.
He gets more jealous than
any girl and gets angry easily.
He's only a man in title.
Just because you're getting married...
What's with you?
All he knew how to do was study,
yet he wanted so much recognition.
You wouldn't know this
if you haven't dated him long.
He is neat freak to the point that it's
like an illness and he's picky with food.
It made me anxious just to
go to a restaurant with him.
I was worried that there
would be a hair in the food.
Then that day's date would be ruined.
Thinking about cooking and living
with a man like that seemed impossible.
He would complain about my food saying
it's too spicy, salty, bland, or sweet.
He would always be complaining.
He would probably say annoying things
while I was doing laundry or cleaning.
They say life is most comfortable
when a woman has control over her man.
He is not a man who would
ever be controlled by a woman.
When he was leaving for the army,
he was telling me not to wait for him.
He told me to move on from him
and acted like he was so cool.
I went out to say goodbye to him
and even shed fake tears for him.
Then I went to a night club
and had a ton of fun.
He never even let me go to a club.
He'd throw a fit if I went to a club
and a man's shirt even
touched me in passing.
He'd get angry at amusement parks
saying I was looking at men.
This country is half men and half women.
How can I only be looking at him?
He isn't even considerate.
He can't even do any housework.
He can't even lift a finger
and tries to get out of it.
Gosh...
That's why I broke up with him.
Should I go on?
There's more?
There can't possibly be more.
Hey! Why did you invite me then?
I told you before.
I want lots of money for my wedding gift.
I wanted to show off
my husband too, you jerk.
You're annoyed, aren't you?
Should I take a picture
of you two? Sit down.
Yeah right.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
You made all of this on your own?
You'll wake Hwa Shin.
Oh yeah.
I lived alone in the US for four years.
If I cook such good food
for you like this
you won't want to cook for me later.
Isn't that right?
I'm a good cook.
Let's sit.
What did Soo Young say to you
at the wedding yesterday?
Was it you?
She said it was me, right?
You're probably the only person
who would go to the
wedding of an ex-girlfriend.
You'll be getting another
wedding invitation soon.
I'll send you one that says
"Go Jung Won and Pyo Na Ri" on it.
You have to come then, too.
You went to Soo Young's wedding.
So I'm sure you will come to ours.
Do you want some stew?
Here you go.
Red, why did you do that yesterday?
Uncle.
Have you made your decision about
which mom you want to live with?
Yes.
I've always been obedient of my dad.
So you were worried your
other mom would be lonely?
That's why you got her
to watch a movie with me?
Yes.
[FIRST PRESENT FROM DAUGHTER.]
Where are you?
Our morning news team is
going for drinks. I'm almost there.
- Go home without me.
- Where is it?
Hwa Shin! What are you doing tonight?
Let's go have dinner.
I thought the morning news team
went for drinks, so why are you here?
Morning team drinks?
They left me out?
- Where are you?
- Hey, where are you?
Oh, me?
The morning news team is having drinks.
Hey, I'm busy now, so bye.
Are you guys going for drinks?
I heard all about it
so what do you mean you're not?
Everyone else must be late.
Hey, pour me a drink.
Isn't anyone else coming, Senior?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
My arm is going to fall off.
Pour me a drink.
Yes.
Here. You should have a drink too.
It's okay. I'm not going to attack you.
Drink.
Okay.
The two of us...
have never done anything
to help with team-building.
You agree that we need
to do something, right?
Yes.
Then I will let it all out to you
tonight so that we can resolve things.
Senior, I will work very hard.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Yes, work hard. Sing a song, okay?
- Okay.
About Assistant Director Choi Dong Gi...
Hey, don't bring that guy up.
I won't feel like drinking anymore.
Here, let's drink.
Let's drink everyone.
Okay! "Wrongful Encounter"!
Pyo Na Ri, Pyo Na Ri!
Pyo Na Ri! Sing it!
I trusted you as much
as I trusted my friend...
What is it?
You dirty bastard.
Where did you pick up these nasty habits?
You go around shaming all reporters.
She's your partner, not just some woman.
Pyo Na Ri is not a woman to you?
You pathetic man.
You're treating her however you want
because she's a contract employee.
- Follow me.
- What are you doing?
You use force on the weak and
act weak to those stronger than you?
A reporter should go easy on the weak
and use force on the strong.
That's a true reporter.
You dare to send her on coffee errands.
You do the news in sweatpants and jeans.
You steal lines from the female anchors.
You ought to be ashamed of yourself.
Why would you come 10 minutes early
to practice the opening
if you're just going to yawn through it?
If you call in your partner
to drink or eat one more time...
I'm going to kill you.
And this?
It's to repay you for that cigarette
I got from you before.
Reflect on your actions
while you smoke this.
Go home to your wife and be loyal.
Why are you doing this?
Reporter Lee!
Hey, hey. Not over there.
Reporter Lee.
Why are you bringing your shoes?
You're confused because
it's not your home.
It's weird, right?
I'm not drunk.
This is the bench at my place.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Go upstairs and sleep. Get up.
Go up to your room.
I knew exactly what
Reporter Park was up to earlier.
Do you think I was
insane enough to go alone?
I told all our staff and crew
to come beforehand.
I bet the bill came out
to a lot for Reporter Park.
Don't ever meet him alone.
He's a dangerous guy.
Come on. Go up and sleep comfortably.
I was even prepared to
record it all, just in case.
Your job isn't an easy one.
You need to stay on your toes.
It's over here.
- Sleep.
- Okay.
- Reporter Lee.
- What?
You look very handsome today.
It's because you're drunk.
But you know all those things
Soo Young was saying?
Strangely, I keep thinking
that Soo Young liked you more.
She said she liked Jung Won more.
- No, no.
- Don't be ridiculous and just sleep.
No, it's not true.
Soo Young liked you a lot more.
Should I take your socks off?
Okay.
Soo Young knows too much about you.
She still remembers it
and is still hurt by it.
It's like she still has feelings left.
Soo Young even thought to herself
how awful it would be to marry you.
She even imagined those things.
Yeah.
Girls don't imagine such things
unless they really like a guy.
- You have pretty feet.
- She lied.
She's still angry at the guy who
dumped her before going to the army.
This is my gut feeling as a woman.
I'm right. She liked you a lot more.
Sleep. You have to get up early tomorrow.
- Reporter Lee.
- What?
Don't go.
You're very drunk.
Just stay next to me.
Don't seduce me.
Do you not want to?
You'll think I'm an animal
tomorrow morning.
Oh my. Did I say
I wanted to sleep with you?
You are cruel. You really are.
Reporter, Reporter, Reporter.
I have a favor to ask,
so can you please do it for me?
Please?
What is it?
Put on your glasses.
Forget it.
Go to sleep.
They're just glasses.
What is it? Why are you back?
Why are you sitting here? Get out.
I don't touch drunk women.
No, just go.
You asked me to stay.
Hey.
I don't touch drunk girls.
I have my pride.
Yes. I am drunk, so don't touch me.
I know.
It is nice though.
I am dizzy from being drunk
and you're nice and warm.
It was like hell before,
but now it seems like a long time ago.
Did you hit Reporter Park a lot?
I wanted to kill him, but I didn't.
Reporter Lee.
I'm right here so stop calling my name.
- Reporter Lee.
- What?
Why did you like Soo Young?
I don't know.
Did you sleep with her?
What is there that you don't know?
You know everything.
I don't know what I don't know.
Is that so?
I think I'm tired now.
You should go to sleep.
I'll just watch you fall asleep.
Oh, what happened to your seroma?
Is your chest okay?
Can I see it?
Have you ever asked my
permission before looking?
That's true.
- Still...
- But you can't today.
Why can't I?
You just can't.
I want to see if it's okay.
I've been getting treatment
and it's fine. Don't worry.
Don't drink.
Okay.
Don't smoke either.
- Don't eat lots of dairy either.
- Okay.
I'll just die if
something happens to you.
I doubt that.
I really will.
- You will?
- Yes.
You must be trying to kill me.
Sleep with me.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Hey! You can't go in there!
You were here too, Reporter Lee?
Sorry, you can get mad at me if you want.
How come you can't do it to Jung Won,
but you feel okay doing it to me?
Why take your anger out on me?
Things were going all right with
you two, so what's the problem?
I, Kye Sung Sook,
am Red's biological mother.
I have never thought of her
as the daughter you gave birth to.
Red is my daughter.
Don't touch me.
Don't put a hand on my body. Get lost.
Don't kiss any other women.
Are you jealous?
You like me more, don't you?