(EPISODE 2)
Uncle seems happy.
Is that Lee Hwa Shin?
Why is he the first one?
Are you happy?
Mum, is it fun?
Dad might die.
- 2016 SBC Open Casting.
Bring Dad back!
Who did this to Dad?
Why did he become like this?
Why did he drink every day?
You can't let him go like this, Uncle.
Bring Dad back!
Tell your uncle to come here.
Where is he?
Your chest feels like my mum's.
- You might have breast cancer.
- What?
- My mum had breast cancer.
- So?
So did my grandma.
It runs in the family. I get a check-up every six months.
I'm a man.
I'm sorry for laughing, but I'm a man.
I'm a guy.
A man.
Your grandma is a woman, your mum is a woman,
and you're a woman, too.
Aren't men human?
Don't men have a chest?
Men and women are the same.
Mum said it can happen to everyone.
I mean...
Wait.
What...
It's nice.
- Turn it off.
- Yes, Sir.
I'll turn it off.
- Have a good time.
- Edit it again.
Director approved it.
Hey.
It was President's order.
Don't use him as an excuse.
Because the first teaser was too boring,
President ordered the second one to be funny.
So I even danced for the sake of the station.
Lee Hwa Shin is young,
- incompetent and immature.
- All right.
Why does he appear first?
He lacks humanity.
I'm scared there will be another reporter like him.
Do you favour him because you're from the same university?
Is he treating you to golf rounds and girls in Bangkok,
providing you with flight tickets and hotel rooms?
You used to be married to his brother.
You know that.
Is that why you put us together...
at the end of that video?
Do you really want to start and end the video with him?
Cut him out.
Let me appear first.
- Also, - It has already been aired.
the flower of the station is reporters.
Especially, pretty female reporters.
They're the flower.
You don't even have to recruit announcers.
If you recruit pretty and smart female reporters,
they can read the news themselves.
We don't need any announcers.
The news will sound more trustworthy.
You'll be killing two birds with one stone.
Make the most of them.
The example is...
standing right here.
I'm...
not just a parrot that reads off the prompter.
I convey the liveliness, tension, conflicts and details...
of the scene through news.
And...
Hwa Shin must have gotten so much massage in Bangkok.
His face is getting greasier and greasier.
Does he really deserve to appear first in the video?
Cut him out.
Cut her out, too.
Show me, the producer, the cameraman and...
There's one missing.
Find the best-looking male reporter.
Make a new video.
Mr Choi, book the editing room.
- Are you done?
- I'm not done yet.
Did you forget to suggest that we shouldn't recruit announcers?
You gave me the thumbs up.
- When?
- At our team dinner.
You said it'd be economical and reasonable.
You even gave me a high five.
Hey.
Do you know what people say about your midnight news?
They're afraid you'll burst through the TV.
Haven't you read any comments about your arrogant attitude?
They need to go to bed after watching the midnight news.
They change the channel because you look so scary.
You keep track of the viewer rating all the time.
Why don't you take a look at your own face?
Stop glaring at the camera.
Let's face it.
After the recruitment advert last year,
do you know how many applied for the announcer position?
3,000 applied. There will be more this year.
Announcers are the flower of the station.
Reading news is not their only job.
You don't understand how broad the scope of the announcer is.
- Should they be temporary?
- What?
Their contract should be temporary like weather forecasters'.
Existing announcers can't wait to be freelancers.
We could hire freelancers instead of educating new ones.
How much do we pay 100 announcers every month?
How are we going to afford that?
Hey.
It's not your money.
Director.
We're not recruiting any announcer this year.
I'll be at the final interview.
I'll be at the final interview for reporters, too.
I'm going to recruit tons of female reporters.
Only ugly ones. Be prepared.
- Hello.
Hi, Mr Choi.
Why are you here so early?
I was done with everything.
I couldn't wait to work.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Don't go in there now. The atmosphere is terrible.
Why?
It's because of you.
Hey.
You shouldn't be around here for the time being. Leave.
Why didn't you listen to me?
- Leave.
- Let me just say hi.
Just go.
- I just want to say hi.
- Just go.
They should know I'm back. Let go of me.
- Don't go there. They'll slap you.
- Let go of me.
Can they make us temporary employees?
Does Ms Gye have something against announcers?
I'll tell my father...
to send Ms Gye to another station or something.
He should focus on the government affairs.
I can ask my grandfather to stop sponsoring...
Ms Gye's news.
Stop sponsoring?
That's not right.
We need sponsors no matter what.
Then what should we do?
We should fight on our own.
We should prove that the station needs announcers.
Go!
Announcers!
I'm...
Oh, my.
I'm not done yet.
Why did you run away when I wasn't done?
What is it now?
I'm no doctor.
I'm not saying that you have breast cancer.
I just want you to see a doctor once.
It might not be tumour.
It could be just muscles.
Please.
Find a gynaecologist and book a check-up.
A gynaecologist?
Is it embarrassing for you?
Is it too embarrassing?
Should I...
come with you?
Come here for a moment.
Hey.
Do you still like me?
I don't like...
girls like you.
I hate girls like you.
What do you mean, "girls like me"?
I mean, easy girls.
- All right.
- Okay.
Easy?
There will be a board meeting this afternoon.
Don't disappear like last time.
Hwa Shin could wear this on the news when he's back.
It makes you look confident and trustworthy. It'd suit a reporter.
Hwa Shin should wear it.
We imported only one piece from Paris.
It'd be better to give it to a popular actor.
Actors don't like wearing clothes someone else wore before.
Hwa Shin has priority when it comes to shirts.
If popular actors are number 1, Hwa Shin is number 0.
Give it to someone else when Hwa Shin says no.
People don't care about what reporters wear.
That's not what I want.
I just...
want Hwa Shin to look...
honest and trustworthy...
when he delivers news.
Also, Hwa Shin said,
when he's wearing something I gave him,
he pays more attention to if he's saying...
only the impartial truth.
Okay.
Imagine a man making such a promise to himself...
while buttoning up his shirt in front of a mirror.
Isn't it so cool?
Do you believe his lies?
He just wants his friend...
to keep giving him...
expensive shirts...
that even actors...
don't get to wear.
- I know that.
- Then why?
What are friends for?
Who is it?
(LEE HWA SHIN)
Gosh.
- Hello.
- I'm his friend.
He's not available right now. I'll tell him to call back.
I just wanted to have some coffee with him.
Again?
He's in Italy again.
He is? When will he be back?
Soon. I'll tell him you called.
Does he think Thailand is so close?
(DELETE)
He's busy.
Let's go.
Don't hang that shirt at the store.
Let's give it to Hwa Shin when he comes back.
You're here.
Doctor. How did it go?
The bleeding stopped,
but there's a risk of cerebral infarction.
We should keep him in the intensive care unit for now.
When will he wake up?
We don't know yet.
He might wake up for a while,
or not wake up at all.
Thank you.
Hello. This is Hwa Shin.
I can't seem to reach my mother.
For 10 days?
Okay. Bye.
Why can't I reach her?
What happened to her phone?
No one welcomes me back.
Pyo Na Ri is...
the only one who welcomes me.
Gosh. What's up with the weather?
What a depressing weather.
It's not very nice, is it?
It isn't.
Go and get some coffee.
We're seven.
- Get a stamp on the coupon.
- Okay.
Here.
(2016 OPEN RECRUITMENT)
Gosh.
Who applies offline these days?
- Hello.
- What are you applying for?
The announcer position.
Aren't you the weather forecaster Pyo Na Ri?
Well...
My friend wants an application form.
Thank you. It's for my friend.
(SBC OPEN RECRUITMENT APPLICATION)
It's raining.
Let me get the umbrella.
Good job, Mr Lee.
- Whatever.
- It was nice.
- Aren't you hungry?
- I am.
There's a nice tom yum goong place near here.
Eat with us.
I should eat with the crew.
Mr Lee, thank you for today.
- No problem.
- Okay, then.
Didn't you miss anything?
He was more cooperative than I expected.
- It's raining.
- Oh, no.
I don't have an umbrella. You're so thoughtful.
I'm starting to like you.
Wait!
You have an umbrella.
I'm a weather forecaster.
Let's share it. I'll walk you there.
Forget it. We're okay.
I'd feel bad.
Share it with my friend.
Your friend is nice.
Share it with your boss.
My friend...
is not used to getting wet. He's too well-off.
He hates getting wet.
Fine. No one should use it.
Why would you waste the umbrella?
The owner should use it.
I hate seeing people getting wet in the rain.
I feel like I did something wrong.
I blame myself.
Why do you care about the weather in Thailand?
Let's just share the umbrella.
Come on.
Squeeze up. You'll get wet.
Gosh.
Are you happy now?
How nice is it?
Let's go.
Is the restaurant far?
We're almost there.
- Do they have good food?
- No, they don't.
Oh my gosh.
Darn it, Na Ri.
You're a fake.
Oh no.
This is crazy.
There wasn't a single cloud in the sky.
Oh no.
I said it wouldn't rain.
What is this?
I should stop being a weather forecaster and just starve.
I feel so bad whenever this happens.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
- Hello?
- You said it wouldn't rain.
You said it wouldn't rain, so we didn't bring an umbrella.
We came out on a picnic, but what is this?
Do you know how busy we are?
Who is this?
We trusted you and didn't bring an umbrella, and now look at us.
What will you do about this?
Did you watch my weather forecast?
Are you walking in the rain because of my forecast?
Are you soaked because of me?
Oh no.
- What is it? Is that a complaint?
- Wait.
Yes. He's so angry.
- But...
- That's right.
Yesterday,
you said it would be a beautiful day in your pink dress...
that was super tacky.
I'm terribly sorry.
- I'll be more careful...
- Give me that.
- Hello?
- What?
The rain is up to the clouds.
It can rain and it can be clear.
Don't you know the weather...
is fickle in the summer and difficult to predict?
How can you look up her personal number...
and call to complain? How rude is that?
We know the viewers are king,
but you should have some manners too.
Don't ever call this number again.
Hello...
"Eat air and poop cloud"?
Is this weather forecaster's name "Eat air and poop cloud"?
Who was that rude employee?
Here.
Don't mind him.
These are people with nothing better to do with their lives...
than complain that society is unjust.
I will mind it.
- I want to mind it.
- What?
Why are you hanging up on a call that came to me?
This is my precious fan.
He called to complain. He's no fan.
He called to complain to me because he saw my forecast.
Even the reporters that I see every day...
working at the same station...
turn off the news before my forecast comes on.
They don't consider it news.
You too. You're one of the stars too.
I got a complaint from someone who considers my forecast news.
Can't a nobody like me get a complaint?
I've been too easy on you.
Stop glaring at me.
Attention.
Don't be mistaken.
I don't like you any more.
That crush ended three years ago.
Why would I continue with it?
And I'm not interested in your chest any more, either.
Attention? Give me a break. I was already at attention.
Why did you have me do that?
Just.
Don't get drunk and leave your phone at bars.
You had to use my phone.
I'm glad you're here.
Bring this to Ms Geum. You're headed there, right?
No, I'm not headed there.
Bring it to her anyway.
Okay.
Put this on Mr Oh's desk and also,
tell him I'm leaving straight from the editing room.
Okay.
This is weird.
I'll take care of it.
Isn't that Hwa Shin?
Where does my brother live?
Why must I know where my ex-husband from 10 years ago lives?
Where does Ppal Gang live?
Forget it.
Hwa Shin.
Don't you see me?
Why are you ignoring me? You should come and report to me.
I'll report when I come in officially for work.
I came to see my sister-in-law.
I'm not your sister-in-law any more.
You've called the correspondents in Washington, L.A.,
England, New York, Japan, Paris, Australia, Russia and everyone,
but you never called me once during my three years.
Bangkok will report once I come in officially for work.
That moron. He's a moron.
Hey.
Get lost.
Where does my niece live?
Your mother wouldn't tell you, either?
She's incredible.
- She's away.
- You'll find out when she's back.
Oh. You want to pretend to be a good uncle? Now?
- After what you did?
- I guess you don't know.
They seem to move around often because of you!
Gosh.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry!
(A MAN WHO COOKS, KITCHEN STARGRAM)
Is it ready?
(HANDSOME CHEF, RAKRAKRAK PASTA)
- Shrimp.
- Yes, Chef.
(THIS IS WHY I EAT)
Hey!
Punk.
Hurry it up.
Chef. Why don't you give the women a smile?
You know how I am.
Get back to work.
You have a call.
Hello?
She packed her things and left?
She said she's going home?
That punk never listens.
Okay, bye.
Ppal Gang!
Which one is her mum?
Is it her?
Wait.
If you find out where Ppal Gang is, let me know too.
I have a right to know.
- Why?
- I'm her mum.
- Do I need a reason?
- Why haven't you used...
your great investigative skills to locate her yet?
Darn it.
Do you know how old I am?
Letting the Lee family...
dictate what Ppal Gang does...
and letting her live with them...
ends once she graduates high school.
I'm being patient until she goes to college.
Nothing will change just because she goes to college.
That's what you think.
Don't be greedy and live as you have been.
Continue to live purely for...
the advancement in your career.
She can't hate me as much as she hates you.
She probably wants to kill you.
Isn't that why you ran away to Bangkok?
If you find Ppal Gang, don't tell just Sung Sook. Tell me, too.
I won't tell Sung Sook and I won't tell you,
so please get out.
Get out.
Not six months after living with a man...
who lived with Sung Sook... I was crazy.
I know.
I had no idea you were superficial. I was crazy.
What?
How could you say that?
You made your brother go bankrupt and ran away to Bangkok...
and ignored both your brother and Ppal Gang for three years.
Did you forget everything?
Whose fault is it that Ppal Gang keeps moving...
and doesn't call me, whom she called "Mum" and adored?
Whose fault is it that I got a divorce?
Jerk.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Your dad won't die.
You can't even see him because it isn't visiting hours.
Would he want to see you crying here instead of going to school?
Go to school. I'll talk to your teacher...
so you can come during visiting hours. Let's come back.
If Dad dies, so will I.
You should be careful when you eat beef brisket.
A famous beef brisket franchise headquarters...
was caught selling fake beef briskets.
We have the exclusive.
- Lee Hwa Shin.
- Yes.
The franchise at which Lee is the CEO started in Seoul...
and grew to be a large franchise with more than 500 stores.
If they weren't selling beef briskets, what were they selling?
They weren't selling beef briskets but actually beef loin.
Beef brisket is precious. A cow that weighs 365kg...
produces only 6kg of beef brisket.
Therefore, there is a difference in price.
They sold beef loin, which is about four dollars per kilogram cheaper...
as beef brisket and deceived the customers.
Let's take a look.
We are at the office of...
- a franchise with more than 500...
- You're impressive.
I heard that franchise headquarters is your brother's company.
Isn't he Ms Bang's husband?
Yes.
If I didn't do it, somebody else would've anyway.
That's better for you and your family.
I thought it would be better for me to honestly expose their fault,
rather than let it blow up and have his company destroyed.
Your brother will be cast from society,
and you'll be shunned by your family.
That means restaurants...
are selling fake beef briskets.
Hey.
You really did it?
Are reporters not human?
Ja Young! Get down!
Can't you see we're live?
You're hiding behind the fact that you're reporter...
and murdering your brother!
Ms Bang. The clip is almost over.
You can kill him after the live broadcast.
Look. It's not like people die from eating beef loin.
How could you kill your brother so cruelly?
- In 10 seconds we're back!
- You jerk. You rat.
Let go of me.
In order to prove...
the illegal acts of the suppliers...
Gosh.
(ANNOUNCER APPLICATION)
How many announcers are they hiring this time around?
One man. Either one or two women.
They may not hire any if the selection isn't good.
- What?
- Really?
That's crazy!
Over 3,000 people applied. They should keep their word.
How could they not hire anyone?
How could there be nobody decent among 3,000 applicants?
I agree. That's a bit...
Hey.
Did you apply?
Why you little brat.
Did you resign yet?
You didn't even resign?
You see...
You were Miss Korea, so you deserve to be an announcer?
Did you do weather for six months to see how you look on camera?
Is that why you backed out...
when we asked for a raise from 70 dollars a show to 100?
No. That's not it.
You've been kissing up, haven't you?
I go on at noon, so even my friends don't watch.
No one recognises me.
I don't expect the 9 o'clock slot.
It's not like I'll get 7 o'clock, either.
They think I'm unemployed.
I was second runner up in Miss Korea but they think I'm jobless.
Na Ri.
Did you hear her?
She says she wants your 7 o'clock slot.
Will you give it to her?
I'm speechless.
Really?
Is that true?
No wonder a newbie kept kissing up to Ms Bang.
Hey. Does Mr Oh know...
you're kissing up to the director of another department?
Enjoy.
Get up.
Ppal Gang.
Eat.
You can't pass this up, too.
You love this.
No?
That's more like it.
You've never refused their chicken.
Do you have a smoke?
We were being nice because your dad was sick.
Don't abuse it.
Don't think you can do anything you feel like.
Do you smoke?
Since when?
Who taught you how to smoke?
If you're going to smoke,
drink this...
- instead.
- Drink beer?
She won't even drink water. She needs to drink something.
You've never had this before, have you?
Give it back.
Hey. Stop. What are you doing?
This isn't yours.
Finish it and get it away from her.
- Give it.
- Wait.
That's mine!
Who do you think you are? Hey.
Who do you think you are?
- Let go of me!
- Hey.
Give me some!
How dare you?
This isn't right.
Get up, Chi Yul.
Let the girl win.
Why do you want to win against a girl?
You punks.
You brats.
Why aren't you at gym class...
and having your own gym class here?
That hurts!
Are you really drinking in front of the station?
Why are you drinking alone?
Whom would I drink with?
You're on soon.
I won't drink. I'll eat and go in 30 minutes.
Did you finish writing your report?
Tomorrow's weather is the same as today.
Let's have a drink.
I can't drink. Especially soju.
It's with meat.
About today...
Sorry about earlier.
Good luck.
Na Ri.
You're younger and prettier than I am,
and you have more potential.
Look. You're super hot, too.
I could never pull that off.
I'm not as bold as you.
I'd reapply too, if I were you.
Come on.
Are you...
ashamed of us?
You are, aren't you?
I'm ashamed of myself.
I felt humiliated all day long.
Gosh.
What's wrong with me? I must have lost my mind.
To be honest, I don't know what I'm doing.
Didn't you come to comfort me?
Here.
Let's have some soju and brush it off.
I can't.
Take it. You need to drink at a time like this.
Okay, let's drink this one shot...
and forget what happened today.
Okay, let's forget it.
- Cheers.
- Press your chest into it.
- Okay.
Your ribcage is fine according to the x-ray.
I see. I hit my chest against the steering wheel in the accident.
There is no fracture.
The bone is fine.
That's a relief.
Are you sure...
you don't have a bruise or a burst blood vessel...
on your chest?
I don't know. Do I?
- Shall I take a look?
- Excuse me?
Yes, sure.
- Relax.
- Okay.
Let's see.
Hold on.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Just in case, why don't you get a breast examination?
I'll get going.
- Mr Lee?
- What?
I recommend a breast examination.
I'll refer you to a specialist.
Are you saying you suspect breast cancer?
Why would I get a breast examination?
Doesn't that mean I should get tested for breast cancer?
Aren't you an orthopaedist? A specialist in bones?
How could a man have breast cancer? Are you a quack?
You grope...
a man's chest and that's what you say?
A man with breast cancer?
It's so absurd, I don't know what to say.
I've never heard of a man having breast cancer.
- Goodness.
- So,
why don't you pretend to believe...
an orthopaedist quack and get it checked out?
I'm sure it isn't, as you say.
I'm sure it isn't.
I hope it isn't, either.
Aren't men human?
Don't men have a chest?
Men and women are the same.
Mum said it can happen to everyone.
(COMPLAINER)
Okay. Stand by! Five minutes!
Na Ri, why won't you answer the phone?
Pick up.
Where's Na Ri?
She must be in the restroom.
It's almost time.
Get ready.
You answered.
It's me, Mr...
Mr Viewer.
(EAT AIR AND POOP CLOUD)
Earlier this afternoon,
you called to complain about the weather.
I felt so bad that I hung up on you like that.
It was nagging at me.
It's fine.
Are you still angry?
Your picnic must have been ruined because of me.
Were you drinking?
Yes.
It was the first call I got since I started doing the weather,
so I was happy.
I know you suffered because of me.
I'm sorry.
In exchange, I was thinking I could give you...
the weather forecast for a week...
over the phone, just for you and only you.
A special gift.
A special live weather forecast...
for one special person. What do you think?
I think you should stop drinking.
Okay?
You'll regret it tomorrow.
Okay.
Looking forward to it.
Who made you smile so much?
Oh no. I have to go on air.
Let's go. I have to go on air.
You finish this.
Let's go.
Then you finish the meat.
No thanks. I'm full. Let's go.
- Two?
- It isn't too much.
It's too big.
It's to commemorate our drinking together and becoming friends.
Open up.
Oh no.
I'm so sorry.
Is that a company suit?
Yes.
They're going to have a fit.
- Oh no.
- It's okay.
We have some spares in our office, right?
Excuse me! Bring us some wet towels!
Wet towels!
What do I do?
(SBC 7 NEWS PRIME)
Oh no.
Here you go.
What do I do now?
(SBC 7 NEWS PRIME)
I'll bring Ms Geum of the 9 o'clock news her outfit.
- Okay.
- I'll bring that.
That way.
I'm almost there. I'm almost there.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry.
What if you don't make it?
Go to our office. I'm going to return this outfit...
and touch up my face. Meet me at the studio.
Okay!
Oh no.
(LEE HWA SHIN)
Hello? What?
Just.
I have to go on air. Goodness.
I just thought of you.
I'm so hot.
Our CEO...
brought it himself.
The CEO?
Yes.
Mr Ko?
Mr Ko? He was just here.
Where did he go?
Na Ri! Na Ri!
Where's the outfit?
There aren't any.
- What?
- Oh no.
What do I do?
Excuse me.
Please help me.
Am I supposed to go on naked?
You have an hour.
You reek of alcohol.
Na Ri! Na Ri! This way!
Here. Hurry. Be careful.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Why you...
- I'm sorry I'm late.
- I'm sorry.
- I smell alcohol.
- Were you drinking?
- I was not.
- Get in position.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm late.
We'll switch over to weather.
She's here. Let's go.
- Mr Oh.
- What?
Let's take out the weather.
- What do you mean?
- We should take it out.
We can't air like this.
What are they doing?
- Are you drunk?
- Excuse me? Me?
What do you mean? I didn't drink.
I can do it.
I never missed a day other than weekends...
for 4 years. This is my 1,029th broadcast.
I can do it with my eyes closed.
I can do it. I can.
- No.
- We're starting weather now.
Get out. You're fired.
- Mr Oh!
- Get out.
- What do you mean, fired?
- Stand by.
Stand by!
Five, four, three, two, one.
Cue!
What's this? Hurry.
- Mr Oh.
- You'd better not mess up.
- Darn it.
- I can do it!
Cue!
The heat finally broke just before the weekend.
Some parts of the south were in the 30s, so it was hot,
but the temperature will come down over the weekend and we expect...
sunny skies. Perfect for outings.
However, the central region is expecting showers like today,
so don't forget your umbrellas.
I got cursed out today because of the sudden shower.
The hot temperature seems to remain, but the heat wave has passed us.
Autumn is approaching.
We expect clear skies and the air dust level is down,
so it should be clearer than usual.
We expect a nice, cool breeze as well.
The capital and Chungcheong region will get cloudy...
and expects to get light drizzles in the evening.
The expected low high in Seoul is 27 degrees.
The same is expected for Gangneung.
Gwangju will be hotter, reaching 30 degrees.
The south region is expecting blue skies.
You should be able to see the stars at night.
You should be careful not to catch cold at a weather like this.
We expect autumn rain starting next week.
That was the weather.
Cut.
This will conclude the SBC 7 o'clock news.
Thank you for tuning in.
Have a good night.
Get out. You're fired.
Thank you!
- Thank you.
- Good job.
Good work.
Na Ri!
Good! That was great.
Perfect. Perfect.
Applause, everyone.
Good job.
Did I do well?
It was the best. As long as you got the weather right.
Why do I feel like I didn't do a good job?
Mr Oh.
You're fired. Get out.
I didn't miss the broadcast.
Fine. Let's say you worked every day for the past four years.
Does that mean you can do...
the 1,029th broadcast like that,
reeking of barbeque,
and drunk? Is that okay?
Look.
I gave you a chance...
because you said you could do it with your eyes closed.
I was being considerate,
so that your career won't be ruined for missing a broadcast.
Na Ri.
Get out. You're fired.
I'm sorry.
Is firing her enough?
She disgraced SBC News.
How could you talk about your personal experience?
Why should the nation hear about you being cursed out...
because of the rain today?
That was a huge blunder!
Are you seducing someone...
through the news?
Look at her outfit. A belly-tee and shorts.
This is SBC.
It's a national broadcast. During the evening news, too.
With your legs wide open. You've lost your mind.
You're insane.
I'm sorry.
Please leave.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Where did he go?
Why did you come here? You didn't even deliver it yourself.
- I know.
- Are we leaving?
Yes.
Mr Ko...
(WEATHER FORECASTERS OFFICE)
(SBC OPEN RECRUITMENT APPLICATION)
What a sight.
What did Mr Oh say?
I'm leaving.
Do better tomorrow.
Do you realise how much you made my heart...
My heart was racing...
while you were doing the weather because I feared you'd mess up.
I was so scared that you'd make a mistake.
What's wrong with you?
Who said you could drink before going on air?
Why do you make my heart race?
Why do you make...
my heart flutter?
I'm really not interested in your chest any more.
Don't worry.
That was my final broadcast.
I'm really not interested in your chest any more.
How many weather forecasters are you a fan of?
My fan? Whatever.
I'll audition for the anchor position.
- What's that?
- Taxi. Taxi.
You knew it wasn't a taxi.
Why is my life so pathetic?
What are you wearing?
It's going to get even smaller.
Make it pretty, like it originally was.
You did well today.
It's okay if I get dumped. I want to date.
I guess this is the last time.