Subtitles by DramaFever
Let's get married.
And bring me that kimchi if you have it.
You can take two ramens
out of the thousand.
I will cook you ramen a thousand times.
This is a proposal.
It is a proposal.
Marry me.
You asked me to marry you and
asked for kimchi at the same time?
Can I just do one of the two?
Yes.
I'll bring you the kimchi.
Here. Eat lots.
That's kimchi.
[Episode 21]
Was that a rejection?
Did Reporter Lee just say it because
he felt bad when I got angry at him?
He's acting weird.
Is she saying no or what?
I just don't know.
Now, let's move on to today's weather.
With the late fall,
the morning temperature has dropped.
The density of the fine
dust particles is at a good level
just as it was yesterday.
It will continue to be at a good level
through the weekend.
You asked me to marry you and
asked for kimchi at the same time?
Can I just do one of the two?
That's kimchi.
I'm doing an announcers
photo shoot up on the roof.
Did I say anything?
Oh no.
Reporter Lee, can you fix this for me?
No.
- My glove is caught in this.
- No.
Should I be like this in the photo?
What happened?
Are you busy later?
No.
Then, I made some new kimchi,
so come by later to pick it up.
All right.
You could have done a better job.
That wasn't your first time
with Hong Hye Won, right?
- Gosh, really!
- The director's office wasn't the first.
- Nothing happened.
- Then what was it?
I don't know.
You always say you don't know
when you're put on the spot.
- It was nothing.
- Why was it nothing?
Hey.
You're trying to talk your way out of it
because it was something.
- Stop arguing.
- You're making me argue.
I'm saying that you don't need to worry.
I told you that you're an expert
and genius at making a girl worry.
What?
If you're going to argue,
let's just shut our mouths and go.
You don't date the same woman
for more than three months.
Get off.
That's a very short expiry date.
Three months.
Let's just stop.
It's not true, right?
Just stop! Stop!
You'll date me for more
than three months, won't you?
Hey!
- Did you press the roof?
- Yes, Chief.
Hey! Didn't the magazine
ask for announcers only?
Are only announcers brides?
They actually called me first.
What are you saying?
Get on the next one.
No.
Can't you see this one is full?
- Hey.
- How many brides is this?
Five brides?
Do I have to get married five times?
Crazy punk.
Who would marry you?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
I'll go with this one.
How about dinner after the meeting?
Let's not do that.
I don't want to appear like we're trying
to use money to win them over.
Okay. Also, these are dresses that
were sponsored for the photo shoot.
These are the stills.
You must not want to take it off.
You should do the 9 p.m. news in it
and go home in it, too.
They want us to do a group shot,
so I'm just waiting down here.
I don't know why they didn't
do a group shot to begin with.
I was looking everywhere for this.
It is pretty.
Pyo Na Ri?
No, I'm talking about you.
You fired her yourself
after part one of a live program.
Who would date you, Brother-in-law?
You said you liked her,
but then fired her yourself.
How would she trust you and date you?
You got dumped, right?
I asked her to marry me.
Maybe that's the reason why,
but she hasn't answered me yet.
I haven't brought it up again because
I'm scared she'll completely reject me.
She hasn't answered you?
Should I ask again?
- You want to get married?
- Yes.
That's something new.
I don't want to lose her
like I lost my brother.
Though I know I'm a cold person
when it comes to work.
Let's go together.
- Pyo Na Ri!
- Yes.
- Come in.
- Okay.
Get up.
What?
Excuse me?
You're on the news, right?
Did you two fight?
- Yes.
- No.
Today is your last day of radiation.
So, how do you feel?
Good.
If you had come regularly,
you would've been done ages ago.
- However...
- That's what I'm saying.
At first, you didn't listen to me at all
and upset me all the time.
Still, you did everything I told you.
So, you're a good patient.
You did well, Grandma.
Then, am I done now?
We will need to check on
your leukocyte count.
You just need to do some blood work
to check platelet levels and for anemia.
Since it's your last time,
you should get an overall physical.
I'll add some extra tests.
- Okay.
- This and this.
- Please make sure to check all of these.
- Yes.
Good job getting through
the radiation, Grandma.
No, Reporter Lee.
I'm finally done with this awful thing.
Are you happy?
I'm excited.
Yes, I'm excited.
In a few months, I can take baths
and scrub my body all I want.
I can drink, too.
It's not like you weren't.
I can exercise, swim, and dance.
You suffered a lot, Reporter Lee.
Are you crying?
Why are you crying?
You won't ever relapse and
you'll live a long, long time, right?
Why are you crying?
I don't know. I just have tears.
Gosh, why would you cry?
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
The tears just keep coming.
You cried when you first heard
I needed surgery for breast cancer too.
Stop crying.
Goodnight.
I'll have a good night too.
Look at me, Na Ri.
What is that?
Stop frowning.
One, two, three, and four.
- Good, good.
- Oh yeah! That's great.
Yes, that's it! One, two, three, four!
Voice phishing?
You? That was you?
I just hated you all so much back then.
I called both of you and Uncle,
but only Uncle got fooled.
This is the 10 million won
that he sent.
Who did you do it with?
I... I did it by myself.
Seriously, you!
It was a male voice,
so how could you have done it alone?
Stop lying! Stop lying and tell us now.
Tell us! Where did you
learn such bad things?
Do it properly!
Let Red go, Chef.
It was us who did it.
You say you care about Red!
You don't try to stop her.
Instead, you help her out?
Don't go easy on them, Chef.
Is there a stick?
You little punks.
I'll beat your behinds with it.
You guys aren't students.
You're criminals.
If we report you, you'll become convicts.
Voice phishing, Criminal Law Act 347.
In the occurrence of fraud
where there is monetary gain
there is a maximum of 10 years in prison
and a maximum fine of 20 million won.
Even if you are first time offender,
you get a minimum of one year in prison.
You foolish high school kids.
Are you crazy?
It's all my fault. It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
Yes, Detective Park.
How many recent voice phishing
cases do you have?
What are the jobs of the victims?
None of them are reporters, right?
Yes, of course there aren't.
I was asking because I know one
who was a victim in college.
Thank you.
Goodness...
So? Did he report it?
No. Thank goodness.
It would be a bigger issue if he had.
What a relief.
Lee Hwa Shin was probably
too embarrassed to even report it.
How could a reporter go to the police
about being a victim of voice phishing?
Especially a current news reporter.
He could change his mind
and report it even tomorrow.
Jung Won.
I'll go to your place.
See me for a moment.
I need to talk to you, so okay.
Are you okay?
Thank you for that day.
I only ended up suffering
by walking home by myself.
You can lean on me
if you're having a hard time.
Reporter Lee proposed to me.
He wants to marry me.
So, what happened?
If Reporter Lee asks me
properly once more
I will say yes to him.
So, it really is over now.
President. Date other women, okay?
That can't be.
Hwa Shin is someone who insisted
that he never had thoughts of marriage.
Even when we were in college,
he spent the money he earned on himself.
He has never dated a girl
for more than three months.
He said he found the responsibilities of
having his own family burdensome.
He didn't want to get married.
That isn't Lee Hwa Shin.
You punk...
Did you ask Pyo Na Ri to marry you?
I did. Why?
Do you mean it?
Of course I mean it.
Be honest. You never wanted marriage.
With all your heart and mind,
you've been against marriage.
You hated it.
You should go in without me.
Are you two going to fight again?
- No.
You'd better not fight, okay?
You'd better not fight again!
You know what? Just fight.
You two just go on and fight.
I'll just be that girl who broke up
two longtime friends forever.
I was being greedy and hoped that
you two were getting along better.
I barely managed to try
and have some peace.
Don't marry Hwa Shin.
What? Who are you to say that?
He doesn't mean what he's saying.
That's a great friendship you have there.
Stay out of it.
Okay, you two should fight, then.
Go on and fight.
Marry me.
Why would she marry you?
You'll suffer all your life
if you marry him.
- Hey.
- He's the type to even cheat on you.
- Hey!
- He won't do any housework.
I can help out too when I want.
He's so crazy about his work.
His love will grow cold so fast.
Men are all the same.
You're not much different.
You say you're going to love her
passionately forever? You?
You're away on business trips
for over half the year.
I'm sure I told you that I wanted to
take her around with me on the plane.
Don't you think Pyo Na Ri
has work she wants to do?
You want her to ride around next to you
and give up all her work?
You want her to be like your secretary
and take care of you?
Then get a secretary!
Don't pretend it's about marriage.
I know you're not
the type to get married.
I was going to wait a little longer
and stand on the
sidelines a little longer.
But you go around playing
with her heart in this way.
Then you won't take responsibility
for it until the end.
Please! Stop fighting, would you?
All right, I admit it.
Up to now, I never met anyone
who made me want to get married.
No one made me fear getting
broken up with, and that's why.
Can't a person change his mind?
Can't my heart change?
You're doing this because
I'm still here, not giving up.
Didn't you spit out the proposal
because I made you anxious?
From what I know about you,
you're more than capable of that.
You're more understanding, Jung Won.
Please stop, okay?
Or you can hold it in,
even if you're petty, Reporter Lee.
Hey... hey.
I want kids, too.
I want a wife, too.
I must have learned it from you.
Every time you, my friend, dated a girl
you used to seriously consider marriage
and I found that frustrating,
but now I'm like that, too.
I used to think that peeing in Han River
wouldn't change it from being Han River.
But I must have learned from you.
I must have changed, too.
I don't know what marriage
or burdens are yet.
I don't quite know what
responsibilities are yet.
I really do not want to be
apart from this woman.
With that in mind,
I asked her to marry me.
Can't I do that?
Is that something I'm
never allowed to say? Huh?
Am I more petty than Jung Won?
Tell me.
Sis, I'm sorry. I know I was wrong.
What did you do?
- You don't know?
- What?
I'm just sorry for everything I've done.
My kind little brother.
No, Chi Yeol.
Out of all the men I know in this world,
you're the one without any flaws.
You are the only without any negatives
or anything wrong with you.
If only I had met you as a man,
I could love you, my Chi Yeol.
Then I wouldn't have to date two guys
or any of this nonsense.
Chi Yeol, aren't there any guys like you?
No, it's because you don't know me.
What is it?
Were you second place this time?
- Gosh.
- What?
Hey! How long are you going to
keep meeting Jung Won?
Are you going to see him
every time he asks you to meet?
Don't pick up even if he calls.
Just delete his number from your phone.
- Let's go inside.
- Who are you to say that?
What's it to you who my sister meets
or whose calls she picks up?
Why would you yell at her
in the middle of the night?
- Let's go.
- Hold on, okay?
Are you looking down on my sister?
I pretended not to know
and didn't say anything.
You're that reporter my sister liked
for over three years, aren't you?
I wanted to go beat up the guy
who didn't like my sister back.
Do you know how much I held myself back?
Keep going. Keep going.
How could you not like my sister?
Keep going. Go on.
Are you blind?
Yes, okay.
I must've been blind back then.
I admit it.
I'm normal now.
I like your sister.
I can't like her, right?
Without my permission...
you cannot date, marry,
or do anything with my sister.
From what I heard from Chef,
Go Jung Won sounds like a better guy.
You should date him.
Good job.
My number one ranked brother.
Let's go.
I'm... a good person too.
Have you had breakfast?
- Yes, I have.
- Not you.
- No.
- Should I buy you some?
Do you need money?
I can lend you some if you need.
- How much?
- About 10 million won.
Oh, sorry.
I was held up by the president again.
He's making me crazy.
Why didn't you start it?
I'm not the director so that
I can avoid running meetings.
You sure are a petty man.
Before we start,
I saw on the morning news
that the fine dust
particle level was good.
That's completely wrong.
Take a look outside. It's hazy out there.
Since we're on the topic,
I think we should do a story on it.
Me. I'll do it, Director.
We've done so many stories on it,
so reporters don't want to do it.
That's why I'm saying I'll do it.
I'll go out to film on scene.
I'm the expert on weather.
I've done fine dust particles
so many times
and I know about the
dangers of it very well.
Anyone else want to do it?
No, there isn't.
Make sure you have all of the equipment.
So, do you have a good story?
The location will give us one.
Okay. Let's go.
We are in the city streets of Seoul where
many citizens and children enjoy the sun.
The level of fine dust particles
announced today was 30 micrograms.
This is a good level.
However, the true level of
fine dust particles is...
85 micrograms.
That is a bad level.
60 percent of monitoring stations
for fine dust particles are on rooftops.
Also, they are inside parks.
Why don't we see what the level
would be at the height of a child?
My face is approximately at
the height of a five-year-old child.
At this height, the level is...
120 micrograms.
It has gone up 35 from before.
Now, I am at the height
of a three or four year old.
At this height, the level of
fine dust particles is...
150 micrograms.
That would be considered very bad.
It is because dust built up on
a surface does not move very well.
High levels of fine dust particles
at 150 micrograms
are flying around and entering the
bodies of children ages three or four.
You're done, right?
Should we do a closing
No, wait! Hold on, Director.
- I'll keep going like this.
- What?
In the case that a three year old
takes in fine dust particles for an hour
I will see what can occur by putting
myself through the same levels.
Director, put on a mask.
Hey! Bring me a mask!
- You sure you don't want one?
- No, I'm fine.
It's been 40 minutes.
Are you really going to go an hour?
Kids usually walk for an hour
when they go outside.
Kids are breathing in the air.
We should know for sure.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Yes. What is it?
The results for Lee Hwa Shin came out.
Is there a problem?
You should open it up.
Peek-a-boo.
Peek-a-boo. Peek...
Beom is far too old for peek-a-boo.
He graduated from that ages ago.
Is that so?
I guess you ought to get married soon.
Beom, do you want something to eat?
Ma'am.
- Me?
- Yes, you there.
Buy us two red bean breads
if you have time.
Why would I do that?
Why is he eating ice cream in this cold?
Hey! He'll catch a cold.
I'm sorry. Oh no.
Beom. Oh dear.
- Gosh.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay. I'm sorry. It's okay.
- Get up now.
- Stop eating this cold thing.
Don't eat this. You stop
eating it too, Reporter Lee.
You must be full from eating
all those fine dust particles.
Are you sick?
Oh, I feel like I'm going to die.
You're just overreacting.
Seriously, my whole body
doesn't even feel like it's mine.
What are you doing?
You said your body isn't like your own.
Let me try holding another woman.
We're in our neighborhood, Reporter Lee.
Are you cold, Beom? Beom is cold.
That's because you had
ice cream so late at night.
I'm cold, too.
You, too?
Why do you only adore Beom?
There is no living being
prettier than you.
Weren't you someone
who only states facts?
It is a fact.
You can believe me or not.
Let me try hugging another girl.
Don't get jealous.
- Na Ri.
- What?
It's nothing.
Reporter Lee.
Don't you have something
you want to say to me?
What?
Something you should say properly.
- Say properly?
- Yes.
- No.
- Oh, there isn't?
Okay, never mind.
Wow!
It's snowing.
Oh my.
It's really snowing?
- Wow!
- Wow, really?
- Beom, what is this?
- Snow.
It's the first snow. First snow.
We should definitely return
the money and apologize to him.
No, you can't!
Why not?
Chef, you don't know his personality.
He could put his own niece in prison.
Then what do you suggest?
We should put it back secretly.
Are you crazy?
We should hold on to it for now.
We need to put it back so that we have
something to say if we get caught later.
Our daughter did voice phishing
and the moms held on to the money?
Did I say we should keep it forever?
It's just obvious we'll get caught
if we return it.
He'll start digging into who did it.
Let the kids take the
college entrance exam first.
You are both abnormal.
You have to tell him the truth
and return it to him directly.
- You can't do that!
When Lee Hwa Shin isn't around,
let's go put it there secretly.
We should return it later.
He'll be too embarrassed
to report it, anyway.
I'm telling you we should
go to him directly.
Then... let's do this.
Hey! You have to be held
responsible if you get caught!
Chef, go stop her. What are you doing?
It's snowing.
Wow. It's the first snow already.
Reporter Lee proposed to me.
He wants to marry me.
So, it really is over now.
I want kids.
I want a wife, too.
It's the first snow. Why are you alone?
Come here.
Here, it's cold.
The first snow came early this year.
Did it?
Yes.
It wasn't in the forecast, but it came.
- What a waste.
- What is?
The most exciting weather forecast
to do was the first snow.
If it snowed before a weather forecaster
could even give the forecast
I would feel strangely upset,
like it was such a waste.
It's like you lost your chance
to give some exciting news.
It's the first snow.
- Reporter Lee.
- Huh?
The first snow is falling.
Yes.
It's the first snow and we're together.
Yes...
It's my first time being with
my boyfriend during a first snow.
- For real.
- So?
Is there something you want to say?
It's the perfect time now.
This is the perfect time.
Here, take this.
- What is it?
- Pork belly.
You took in a lot of fine dust particles.
You should go home and eat this.
All right, I'll grill it for you.
- Pork belly...
- We can have it with that kimchi.
Should I make you a snowman?
Have you seen enough snow from
a first snow to make a snowman?
I can make a small one, then. Hold on.
Here you go.
Live with me like these two here.
What is that? Don't they have
eyes, noses, or mouths?
Live with me.
Are you finished making it or
are you in the middle of making it?
Do you not want to?
We can make it together.
Eyes, nose, mouth... all of it.
Everything, together.
We can have two kids, too.
Hey.
Hey...
Sit down here. Okay?
Like this?
Like this.
You really live in this house, right?
Oh, yes.
I'm trusting you, Chef.
Thank you.
- Get going.
- Bye.
I really don't know if
this is the right thing to do.
I told Chef to stop her.
Why is he doing that with her? Why?
Oh, the snow is so pretty.
This is too small.
Pick up. Pick up, Bang Ja Young.
- What is it?
- Hwa Shin is here.
Get out now. Get out.
Hwa Shin, Hwa Shin!
Our shoes!
Hurry, hurry.
It can't be...
It's morning. Wake up!
Chief Bang.
Yes, Chef.
Here.
Put them on.
Thank you.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
What was that?
What else? Let's date.
After I breathed in what a
three-year-old child would for one hour
I realized the air above
and below is very different.
Even once I stood up,
I felt a foreign substance in my throat.
I had a prolonged dry cough.
Not bad.
If these fine particles get
into their respiratory organs
it is terrifying to even think about
what could happen to our children.
This SBC's Pyo Na Ri reporting.
WHO has listed fine dust particles as
one of the top carcinogenic substances.
She worked hard on it.
She sacrificed herself
to make it provocative.
By 2060, Korea is expected to be
ranked first among the OECD countries
for the number of people
who will die from air pollution.
The day we die from merely breathing
does not seem too far off.
What was that?
That wasn't the line.
Why did she close in such a scary way?
She went out herself and suffered.
I guess she felt the line was boring.
Seeing her do a news story,
I remember when she was a forecaster.
Don't you want to see Pyo Na Ri
do the weather again?
Yes, Doctor.
You're coming today
for the test results, right?
Yes.
Well...
I think you should come alone today.
Why?
Just... because.
Don't come with Pyo Na Ri today.
Come alone today, Reporter Lee.
I don't want to, Doctor.
You always told me to come with her.
Why are you telling me to come alone?
Do you have a bad result for me?
Is there a problem?
Why aren't you answering me?
I'll be there with Pyo Na Ri.
I don't want to go alone.
I'll be going with her today.
Yes, Hwa Shin.
- Mom.
- Yes, what?
Why is my heart racing so fast?
Did you drink too much coffee?
No.
Why did you call?
- What are you doing later?
- Later?
I'm going to be home.
Hey, when are you bringing
your girlfriend around?
Get married and give me some grandkids.
Okay. Let's have dinner later.
I'll pick you up later.
Really?
Wait. I have to go then.
I need to get ready.
I have to go to the hair salon. I'm busy.
Bye, now.
I don't have time to be doing this.
What did I do wrong?
What?
You did this before.
It was too amateurish, careless,
and seemed like a beginner did it.
It lacked logic and reasoning.
It also lacked the details used
to appeal to people's emotions.
Also, your emotional closing
in the studio....
It was obvious you were
trying to scare the viewers.
According to your conclusion,
people shouldn't even breathe.
Okay.
I understand.
I knew it would be harder
to get recognition from you
than to get a full-time position.
- Okay.
- Na Ri.
Later, in the evening...
- After the hospital?
- Yes.
Let's have dinner with my mom.
Already?
Are you scared?
Yes.
I'm even more scared right now.
Can't I meet her a little later?
She thinks I'm Jung Won's
girlfriend, doesn't she?
I'm worried you might change your mind.
All right. I'll meet her.
It's not like she'll kill me.
I suppose I'll just die if she does.
I'll say I love you even if she kills me.
Okay?
Okay.
[Fortune teller]
[Lee Hwa Shin, Pyo Na Ri]
Show me your bride.
You need to see her physiognomy, as well?
Of course.
Oh, really?
- Her?
- Oh, that scared me.
No, no.
She... she drinks well.
Are you his black rose?
- You're lucky.
- She cries a lot, too.
I haven't taught her
everything I know yet.
She's not that good at
taking care of herself.
If something happened to me...
If something happens to you,
I'll just die.
she would just die.
There are no girls like that these days.
There are.
Could a guy like me...
make one woman happy?
I've become curious about my life
because of the woman I love.
By any chance...
am I going to die early?
Grandma.
I want to live a long,
long time with this woman.
It's me.
Doctor Geum says she suddenly had to
go into surgery so I shouldn't come.
She told me not to worry
about the test results.
Go wait at the restaurant.
Okay.
Reporter Lee.
Yes.
Has the cancer relapsed?
Don't be nervous.
Is it a relapse?
No.
Then why did you tell me to come alone?
You're not alone.
Because you might want to
keep it a secret from Pyo Na Ri.
I don't want any secrets from Pyo Na Ri.
Please tell me now.
You have me.
We will have to run
some more tests, but...
it looks highly probable
that you are sterile.
I love you.
Your male hormone levels have
dropped a lot lower than normal levels.
It would be difficult.
Sterile, Doctor?
You're saying... I can't have children?
That's why you told me
to come without Pyo Na Ri.
But why...
Why? Why is it me?
It wasn't enough
that I got breast cancer.
Now I can't have kids.
Am I finished as a man?
Come on. Who said that?
That makes me finished. Does it not?
That's why you told me
not to bring Pyo Na Ri.
Are you finished just because
you can't have a child?
There are many couples who live
without children and love each other.
Live just loving each other?
I don't want to.
I don't want to!
I don't want that for myself!
Other people can live like that.
Why me? Why is this happening?
Was breast cancer not enough?
Breast cancer...
Why are the gods doing this to me
and not letting me have children?
How could this happen?
Why does this happen to me?
I was born a man
and I want to die a man.
So, why, why?
What did I do so wrong?
I want to get married.
I want to be normal with two kids.
That's all I want in my life, so why?
Doctor, I'd rather jump into
Han River and die right now.
That's how I feel right now.
Come on, now.
I had breast cancer and now I'm sterile.
Do you want to marry me, Doctor?
Nurse Oh, do you want to marry me?
You're telling me to live alone forever
and never get married.
That's what you're telling me.
That's what this is, Doctor.
Fix this somehow, would you?
Do something and fix it.
Please, fix it.
I'll live my life being careful not to
relapse and get breast cancer again.
Just let me live like other men.
Doctor.
Please save me, okay?
Subtitles by DramaFever
This is nice.
Even if we do this,
don't you think no one will know?
Mom, should I just live alone?
My wife says she saw you
getting radiation treatment.
Are you okay? Dong Gi, she's not okay.
Is the breast cancer okay?
Did you know Pyo Na Ri had breast cancer?
Are you okay?
I don't think it will easy for Pyo Na Ri
to become a full-time employee.
You might never get to sit here.
Don't be sorry, Reporter Lee. I'm fine.