[Episode 22]
Mr Lee.
You left your phone.
You're here already?
Yes, Mum.
Is your girlfriend here?
Look.
What?
I didn't tell her to come.
I wanted to play hard-to-get.
I mean,
she won't introduce me to her family.
If I introduce her to you,
she'll think I like her more.
What's wrong with that? Why
didn't you tell her to come?
The guy is supposed to like the girl more.
That creates a happy marriage.
You should like her more.
You should keep liking her more.
It's okay if she finds out.
I'll wait inside, so call her now to come.
I'm fine.
I don't want to.
Let me weigh my options and see if
there's a better girl out there.
Let me do the maths.
Don't you think I'm losing out?
Aren't you sad about letting
some other girl have me?
I'll think hard about whether or
not I should marry this girl.
You freak.
Why are you wasting my time?
You brat.
I spent the whole day getting my hair done.
Hey. What?
You'll think about it?
- Think about what?
- Come on.
- I...
- Hey.
Why would I be sad to lose you?
I'm not sad at all.
Please get married.
My blood pressure won't
go down because of you.
Whoever it is, I'm about to
bow down to the woman...
who is willing to marry you to
please take you off my hands.
- Sad? Whatever.
- Mum.
Should I just live alone?
Shut it!
You punk.
Look.
If you ever say you'll live
alone in front of me again,
I'll pull out every
single hair on your head.
If you did something wrong,
go beg for forgiveness.
If you're not good enough, go
kiss up and say you'll do better.
Don't try to kill me by saying
you'll live alone. Got it?
Answer me.
Kiss up?
No.
You little...
- Hey.
- Are you on your way?
I forgot I had a radio show tonight.
I can't make it.
Did you call your mother?
Yes.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Don't be sorry.
Yes.
- Okay.
You need a pretty heart to be a woman.
A pretty face doesn't make you a woman.
A woman whose heart doesn't change
once she gives it to a man.
Is a true woman.
When I knew love.
Hey.
Even if she were to go blind.
Did something happen?
Her eyes sparkle like the stars.
You need a pretty heart to be a woman.
A pretty face doesn't make you a woman.
Were you dumped?
Shut your trap.
- That is a true woman - Hey, hey.
Are you trying to see if
you can beat alcohol?
Historically, alcohol is bound to win.
- It wins all the time.
- What?
- How did you know?
- Hey.
Are you really dating Na
Ri, as the rumours say?
Where the flowers.
Bloom and wilt.
On the fields.
Yes?
Who is it?
What is it?
You reek of alcohol.
Where do you think you're going?
With whom did you drink?
You said you had a radio show.
Where are you sitting?
Did you just sit? Get up. Now.
Chi Yul is studying downstairs.
Get up. Hurry. Get up.
Goodness.
Chi Yul will be here soon.
What do you plan to do?
What's wrong with you?
With whom did you drink?
How much did you drink?
Do you want some coffee?
Water?
You're so frustrating.
Why aren't you talking at all?
My gosh. Why are you taking that off?
You need to go.
Go home and sleep. Go.
I'm going to sleep. I'm sleepy.
What are you doing?
You're fine. Don't act drunk.
Don't act confused. Get up.
You know this is my bed and my home.
Get up.
Come on.
Fine.
Go. It's late.
I can't believe you drank as soon as
you finished radiation treatment.
Hey.
I checked our compatibility.
You don't like things like that.
I don't like it. I hate it.
I'm not interested at all.
But I wanted to check
because it's with you.
I was curious if I'd be
able to make you happy.
And?
What did they say?
- It's a secret.
- Come on. Don't be like that.
Then don't bring it up.
Tell me. Is it good or bad?
Go on. Tell me.
Seriously.
Tell me. You brought it up.
The curiosity is killing me.
We have no kids.
Who said that? The fortune teller?
- Yes.
- Who was it?
Why?
I'll go and ask myself.
I don't know.
Did you go to a famous fortune teller?
Is that person supposed to be good?
I think so.
Really? Then we'll ask someone else.
Are you not okay about having no kids?
Of course I'm not okay. I
want to be a good mum.
Is that okay with you?
See? You like kids too, right?
Did you get plastered because of what...
one fortune teller told you?
My goodness. Are you that upset...
because that one fortune teller
told you we can't have kids?
Are you upset?
What time did you say I was born?
8am.
I was born at 8pm.
You got that wrong already.
Look. Let's go together next
time to check our compatibility.
Don't give them wrong information...
and get some ridiculous predictions, okay?
Why do you like me?
Because you're manly.
- Not that.
- Not that?
There's nothing else.
Don't tease me.
Is it...
okay that I have breast cancer?
Even if it's just one fortune teller,
she said we can't have kids. Is that okay?
Are you okay with a man...
who has breast cancer and can't have kids?
What's gotten into you today?
I am a man, right?
Don't laugh.
You got surgery, so the
breast cancer is fine.
I'll go to 100 fortune tellers...
and find a bunch that say...
we'll have lots of kids, okay?
What's the problem? What's wrong?
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh.
You're acting suspicious. Why did you hide?
I wasn't hiding.
I dropped my pen, so I was picking it up.
I don't want it.
It's good for you.
Did you put the money back
without Hwa Shin catching you?
Yes.
Did you get stuck there...
until morning because Hwa Shin came home?
Yes.
My goodness.
Where did you hide in his tiny apartment?
In his closet?
- What?
- That's the only place to hide.
Together?
Yes.
Until morning?
Nothing happened, right?
- Like what?
- I'm sure.
You can spend 100 nights
with an asexual man,
and nothing will happen.
After counting all the festivals
that were held nationwide,
we found out that there were 46 every day.
829 million dollars were
spent for the budget.
Was it really a waste? Was
it held just for themselves?
Lee Hyun Jong reports.
- Yesterday afternoon...
- Finally, the weather.
You know there were breaking
news earlier, right?
The weather completely changed from before.
Are you ready?
- Okay, stand by.
- Okay.
What's wrong with her? What's wrong?
Joo Hee, are you okay?
- What's wrong with her?
- Why are you sweating so much?
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Can you do it?
Are you okay?
Hey, are you okay?
She doesn't look well.
Hey.
Dong Gi, I think Joo Hee is sick.
She doesn't look well.
Get her out of there.
Hey. Can you do it?
I can do it.
Are you very sick? Where does it hurt?
I need to do the weather.
It's going to get very cold.
Her appendix. Her appendix burst.
- What are you doing? Call 911.
- Appendix?
The weather. Do the weather first.
- Hurry. Hurry.
- Dong Gi, she can't do it.
What's the special weather report?
There was a warning of strong
winds since 15 minutes ago.
It's not a hurricane. Let's
just skip the weather.
Really?
Should we take it out? Can we take it out?
It was a warning.
The weather is news, too.
We can't take it out.
Do we have a replacement if we take it out?
You can't take the weather out.
Hey. Do you have a one-minute news clip?
Hey. Look for something
that we can throw in.
- Find something!
- The wind advisory was just issued.
If people walk around in this
cold without an umbrella,
they'll catch a cold.
Today's weather is as
important as the flu shot.
Stay quiet. We don't have a weather
forecaster. What can we do?
Dong Gi, did you find something?
I'll just drag out the closing.
The weather and closing is the same thing.
I'll do the weather.
- You?
We found something.
We'll play something we
were going to use at noon.
Hold on.
You have to do the closing...
right after the weather. Can
you make it back in time?
You may never be able to sit here again.
I can make it back in time.
The advisory was issued 10 minutes
ago, so people are unprepared.
They may look like they aren't watching,
but they listen to the weather
to decide what to wear...
and whether or not to bring
an umbrella with them.
I'll do the weather.
What should we do? What should we do?
Hurry. Decide.
- How many seconds do we have left?
- Is Na Ri doing the weather?
I'll do the weather.
This morning,
a weather advisory was issued
for strong winds and rain...
- Is Na Ri doing the weather again?
- During your morning commute.
This is a sudden rain forecast
after the sudden first snowfall.
Seoul's temperature will
drop to five degrees,
and with winds of up to 4.8m per hour,
it'll feel even colder.
In Gyeonggi, Chungnam,
Honam and Jeju Island,
there is a strong wind warning.
In Seoul and other regions such
as Yeongdong and Yeongnam,
a strong wind advisory was issued.
The expected rainfall is...
20mm to 60mm in Jeju Island.
In the southern region,
10mm to 30mm is expected.
The other regions are also expecting...
up to 20mm of rain today.
Try to avoid glass and
windows during your commute.
The strong winds may result
in signs and billboards...
falling onto the streets or onto cars,
so please be careful.
If you need to go outside,
don't forget your umbrella...
and bundle up in winter clothes.
That was the weather.
Hurry. Hurry. Run. Run. Run.
That concludes today's...
SBC News Morning.
Do the closing statement.
Thank you for tuning in.
What happened? Was the vacant
female anchor seat on TV?
You zoomed in on him, right?
Why did you do it? We told you not to.
Darn it. Are you a weather
forecaster or what?
Whatever.
What happened? What? What?
I don't know. Let me know
later what happened.
Hey.
Are you an anchor or a weather forecaster?
Are you a weather forecaster
or an anchor? What?
Choose one. Get your act together.
Darn it.
What's going on?
(Weather)
Where do you think you're sitting?
An anchor with breast cancer who
may quit because she's sick.
Will you actually get hired full-time?
Hey, my wife said she saw you...
getting radiation treatment.
That's...
Tell Hwa Shin...
to come to me and beg on
his knees for forgiveness.
Then I won't tell anyone.
That will not happen.
Hey.
Just do your own job.
Your eyes are sleepy. Are
they rotten fish eyes?
People will fall asleep
while watching the news.
Don't only work on picking
on junior reporters.
Really?
Fine.
That jerk.
Why that...
He needs another beating.
What did he say to you?
Nothing much.
That jerk.
There's never a quiet day.
It's so annoying. I'm so sick of it.
Darn it.
- Hey.
- What? What?
- About Na Ri...
- What now?
Did you know she has breast cancer?
What?
I feel so bad for her.
- Mr Oh.
- Knock first.
Sorry.
Did you know Na Ri has breast cancer?
- Breast cancer?
- What?
I feel bad for her.
- Sung Sook.
- Ja Young.
Did you know Na Ri has breast cancer?
- What?
Poor thing.
Seriously.
Did you or did you not watch
the weather I just did,
which I risked my anchor position for?
Did I or did I not say that there
will be strong winds and rain?
My gosh. It's pouring hard.
- Mr Lee.
- Where were you going?
I came after you to bring you the umbrella.
You stormed out of the studio,
so I knew you were going
out without an umbrella.
That's why I ran after you with
one, so you wouldn't get wet.
You know these things after
having a crush for three years.
For three years, I couldn't give
you an umbrella even if I had one.
Now, I can run after you and
hold it over your head.
I'm so happy.
Mr Lee.
Look outside.
It's morning,
but because of the rain,
it's dark and feels like night, doesn't it?
It does.
With the rain and wind,
doesn't it seem like people
can't see inside the car?
Yes.
This is nice.
What is?
They can't see us.
You said the sun will be
out in the afternoon.
No one can see what we do.
So?
I'm just saying.
- My gosh.
- Right?
Mr Lee.
They wouldn't know even
if we kissed, right?
It's thrilling at a parking lot.
Right?
Yes.
Get out.
- Are you busy?
- Yes, I'm busy.
You're getting a car wash.
Why are you so busy?
I don't need a car wash any more,
so I'm going out for a story.
- Mr Lee.
- What?
You were going to get a car
wash, so you have time to kill.
Let's go to that fortune teller
you went to yesterday...
and get another reading together.
You see, 8am and 8pm are
completely different.
I'm sure there will be
kids in our next reading.
Okay? Let's go. Let's go.
Don't be so upset.
And don't drink.
Get out.
Let's go.
I said get out.
Give me the umbrella.
His mum's over at his place.
Why isn't he picking up?
You have no other problems.
But you can't have kids
in your current state.
Is it because of the breast cancer?
The radiation treatments increase
the amount of exposed blood,
so you can't completely ignore it.
But since it was breast cancer,
it was only in the torso,
so it's very rare. We'll
have to keep monitoring.
Smoking and drinking may
affect it, as well.
People usually suddenly find
out that they're impotent.
No one suspects that they
are impotent beforehand.
I thought a thorough test would
say something different.
Don't tell Na Ri.
I won't.
Do you plan to marry her
without telling her?
Then why are you telling
me not to tell her?
Are you going to break up?
No.
Are you going to marry her?
Are you going to date her?
No.
Then you won't do anything?
- No.
- Then what will you do?
I'll do everything.
You're out of your mind.
How could I not be?
You should get psychiatric help.
I'm too nervous. You'll
end up doing something.
Don't be afraid of psychiatrists.
It's nothing to be afraid of.
You just talk to them and consult them.
Your mind need to be at peace
so that your body can heal.
I'll go to a breast cancer
clinic, a urologist...
and a psychiatrist. You also
said my liver is unhealthy.
Whom do I go to for that?
Every time I come to this
hospital, I can just...
go from department to department...
and get diagnosed, treated,
diagnosed and then treated.
I'll keep getting psychiatric
help throughout.
Here's your prescription.
Don't forget to take your
medicine every day without fail.
What do I say if she calls?
You're good at lying.
It's my first time meeting a man
with breast cancer who is impotent.
I know.
Why me?
You are...
the manliest man I've ever met.
Is that supposed to console me?
Don't be alone.
Don't do anything rash.
I want to be alone, and I
want to do something rash.
I want to die. I'm afraid to see women.
Na Ri scares me the most,
and I'm embarrassed.
I'm confused of whether
I'm a man or a woman.
I don't know if the light is green or red.
Everything looks like it's stuck
in the middle. I'm going crazy.
I'm afraid of the camera
when I'm on air, too.
I've never once feared the camera,
but now, I feel like...
the camera is mocking me
and looking down on me.
I feel like it's jeering at
me and looking right into me.
Oh, no.
Anyway,
don't tell Na Ri.
If you do, I'll jump into the Han River.
Don't worry. I'll make sure to...
It cleared up so quickly.
It was raining so hard.
Hello.
Hi.
You're all bundled up.
You said to bundle up this morning.
Did you watch?
Of course.
Thanks to you, I wore a jacket this
morning and brought an umbrella.
But it cleared up quickly.
It did.
You should come when he's home.
I only came to fill up his refrigerator.
I see.
Have you had lunch?
What?
The seasoning is slightly salty.
It's perfect for my tastebuds.
Really?
Hwa Shin likes his food too bland.
I have to eat such bland
foods because of him.
Even still, you need a little flavour.
Don't you agree?
Of course.
What kind of a daughter-in-law do you want?
What kind of a daughter-in-law?
What do you mean?
Nothing matters as long
as Hwa Shin likes her.
- Really?
- Of course.
He seems to have someone.
He was supposed to introduce her
to me, but he changed his mind.
What about you?
Are things going well with Jung Won?
No.
Let's see.
Is it cooked?
It's good.
- Do you like it?
- I do. Here.
Try one.
From here...
to here. Give me everything.
That too.
I'll take it all.
That's 998.
Give me everything from here to there.
I'll take these, too.
Hey.
Why?
You don't think I can afford it?
Have you lost your mind?
I make good money.
I want it all.
I have money. Do you
think I can't afford it?
Do you think I took clothes from
you because I didn't have money?
I'll change into a new one every hour.
This.
Bring out anything else you have!
They're all mine. Na Ri is mine, too.
I'm the only man for Na Ri.
I'm the only man.
How have you been?
- Hi.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Hey.
You looked so excited doing the weather.
I liked it, too.
But seriously,
I heard Mr Park is going around
saying you have breast cancer.
It isn't true, is it?
He picks on you, and now, he
spreads a ridiculous rumour.
What's his problem?
It's true.
What?
I had surgery.
And it's stage one.
I finished radiation treatment, too.
I'm fine now.
But you're so young.
You should be careful.
You're employed under contract.
The company wouldn't like that.
I'm all better now.
It's okay. Just make sure to pass gas.
It won't come out.
But I smelled it.
What are you saying?
Are you not okay about having no kids?
Of course I'm not okay. I
want to be a good mum.
Is that okay with you?
See? You like kids too, right?
Are you looking for something?
This.
I'll take everything here!
Everything.
Are you moving in?
Take them all. They're all yours.
I bought them all for you.
What...
Are you insane? Why did you buy so much?
What is this? Baby clothes?
Aren't they cute?
How many kids do you want to have?
Why did you buy these already?
We'd better start now.
Right.
Is something wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
- Yes, there is.
- No, there isn't.
Hey.
Sorry.
- For what?
- That I can't be like others guys.
That's not true.
- No. I'm not qualified.
- To do what?
To receive your love.
Why do you like me?
You're sexy. You're super hot.
You look so good when you do the
news that I want to watch it alone.
Can you live without me?
Answer me.
Why are you asking that? You're scaring me.
I can't live without you.
Where are you going?
Nowhere. Sleep.
Sleep.
Hi. You're home.
Where are you tiptoeing off to
in the middle of the night?
Just study.
No. No!
Stop it!
Where did she go now?
Where did she go in the
middle of the night?
Did he cure his asexuality?
Really?
I should've been the one
to put the money back.
I should've been the one to
get trapped in the closet.
What a waste.
I'm so lonely.
I'm so cold.
The National Statistical
Office's investigation showed...
that the price index for the consumer...
rose 1.3 percent compared to last year.
I hear it's breast cancer.
It's the biggest increase
since last February.
When did you find out?
The price has risen...
- Be good to her.
- And has brought up the cost...
especially for certain items...
like vegetables.
I heard you went to the hospital with her.
That is all for today.
Yes.
Good job, Na Ri.
Good job everyone.
- Thank you.
Yes, it's true.
I got surgery and finished
getting radiation treatment,
so I'll make sure there's no problem
being here to do the news every day.
Having breast cancer isn't a sin.
Wow. I didn't know Hwa Shin...
would go somewhere like that for a woman.
I misjudged him.
My gosh.
I think HR found out that
she has breast cancer.
Na Ri won't be able to get
a full-time position.
My goodness. Darn it.
Hey, Hwa Shin.
My goodness.
- What?
- Did rumour spread that it's you?
Did you know about the rumour?
Then why didn't you tell me?
Was I the last to find out?
Just stay quiet.
You may not get the full-time position.
I don't think they'd decide
based on something like that.
If I don't get it, it won't be
because I have breast cancer,
but because I'm not good enough.
So please just stay quiet.
Okay?
What am I doing to you?
I want to keep watching you do the news.
And it's not a big deal for a
woman to have breast cancer.
It's the same thing. How
is it not a big deal?
Did you know? Did you
date her when you knew?
Na Ri isn't sick. She
isn't the one who's sick.
I'll handle it.
What will you handle?
Is this how you handle things?
Mr Lee.
Hi. Have you had dinner?
I have.
It's time to stop...
pretending to be the patient for me.
I'm going to tell the company that
I'm the one with breast cancer.
I'll tell them the fact that
you pretended to be sick...
so that people wouldn't know.
So keep that in mind.
Don't you dare.
I'll take a short break.
You do, and I'll kill you.
I'll let you kill me then.
I won't see you.
Don't see me.
Let's break up.
Yes. Let's break up.
- It's really over.
- Yes. End it.
It's for the better.
Are you insane? Have you lost your mind?
The rumour's out already. Just let it be.
If people find out...
that a man has breast cancer,
imagine how differently they'd look at you.
I'll do anything else you ask.
Okay? Come on, Mr Lee.
Do as I say, okay?
I like acting like the
patient in your place.
I was happy because it gave
me a reason to be with you.
- Even now?
- Yes, even now.
Even now, when people talk
about you, stare at you...
and treat you uncomfortably,
mixed with pity and sympathy?
Yes, even now.
The lie that it's me is 100 times better...
than the fact that it's you.
Don't you dare.
I'll go back to Jung Won.
Are you afraid I won't make
full-time because I'm sick?
I'll do better.
I need to watch you anchor the news
every night to digest my food.
I need to watch that every night.
Don't you dare.
I told you not to do it, okay?
I want to stop feeling
apologetic towards you.
Stand clear of the closing doors.
I hear it's breast cancer.
Na Ri won't be able to get
a full-time position.
Just stay quiet.
I want to keep watching you do the news.
I like acting like the
patient in your place.
I was happy because it gave
me a reason to be with you.
(Breast cancer treatment room)
Please help me.
Come in.
Hey. Listen. Why won't they go to Kenya?
Personally, I'd love to go
to Kenya to drink coffee...
and play with giraffes
and lions for a year.
They're so lazy. They won't
go for just one year.
- Mr Oh.
- What?
Let me do an investigative report.
It's been a while.
I'm itching from sitting
at the desk all the time.
Sure. That's good for me.
What's the story?
- Leave it to me.
- Okay.
- Mr Oh.
- Yes?
People will forget in a year, right?
- About what?
- Anything.
- Like what?
I'm going.
Is that why they won't
go to Kenya for a year?
How are you feeling?
I'm well.
I finished getting treatment. I'm fine now.
It doesn't hinder my
work performance at all.
I heard Hwa Shin took you to the hospital.
I didn't take her. I'm the one with...
He was very good to me
because I had breast cancer.
It wasn't Na Ri. It was...
You got something on you.
How embarrassing.
Mr Lee.
Didn't you say you were late?
You should go.
You should get to work. It's okay.
You went into that place
swarming with women?
I'm impressed.
I really am.
Right? He held my hand real hard, too.
Watch what you eat, okay?
- I will.
- Eat up.
What are you doing, Mum?
I'm waiting to watch your news.
Why? You watch it all the time.
Still.
I didn't have dinner yet.
I want fish stew for
dinner, so make it for me.
What?
There's no fish at home.
Why are you suddenly craving fish stew?
Go out and buy some fish, then.
I'm really craving it.
Fine.
Bye.
Gosh.
Is he pregnant or what?
Why is he suddenly craving fish stew?
(SBC 7 News Prime)
The planned revisions of the
medical law which will toughen...
penalties for abortions
is provoking controversy.
Korea is the second worried
country among the OECD members,
following Mexico.
According to the National Cancer Centre,
there were 61 male breast cancer
patients in Korea in 2013.
Let's find out the causes, symptoms...
and treatment for male breast cancer.
- Stay tuned for SBC 7 News Prime.
- No, Mr Lee.
Regardless of how tall they are...
or how handsome they are,
all men do their best to
grow their chest muscles.
That's because a broad chest...
is a symbol of masculinity for men.
However, among 25 million Korean men,
around 500 to 1,000 men end up having to...
get their chest cut out through surgery.
I'm talking about male
breast cancer patients.
The first male breast cancer patient
in Korea was found in 1923.
Since then, the number of patients
has been constantly growing.
Currently in 2016, there are
500 to 1,000 male patients,
and they account for 0.5 to 1 percent...
of the total number of
breast cancer patients.
Some male breast cancer patients
are luckier than others.
Some find out about it at an early stage.
Lee, a man in his 30s, had never
imagined he'd have breast cancer.
It was a miracle that his cancer
was detected at an early stage.
One day, someone pointed out
that he had a lump in his chest.
It was stage-one breast cancer.
If he had been unlucky,
he would have found his
cancer at a later stage...
as most other patients do, and
would have died helplessly.
Shouldn't you apply some ointment?
It won't stop bleeding. My goodness.
Your chest...
feels like my mum's.
You might have breast cancer.
If someone detected your
cancer before you did,
you should be grateful to
that person all your life.
If that person is your loved one,
you must be a match made in heaven.
You're also lucky...
if your spouse or girlfriend
is aware of your illness.
Many male breast cancer patients...
fear visiting hospitals.
To visit a breast clinic...
that's always full of women...
is something men dread of doing.
Many male patients hesitate
before seeing a doctor...
in fear of what other people
would think about them.
This is how the examination works.
The examination is even
more painful for men...
because their chest mostly
consists of muscles.
If your partner is not
aware of your cancer,
you'll have to go through
the pain all alone.
After the surgery,
you need to wear a special
bra to stop the bleeding.
However, can you imagine a
man buying this bra himself?
Male breast cancer patients stand
out more than any other patients.
Everyone gossips about them.
Everyone stares at them.
It is a battle that is too
difficult to fight alone.
Sometimes, the patient's
spouse books an appointment...
under her own name...
to pretend as if she's the patient.
She's taking the risk of being
gossiped about herself.
That approach isn't always necessary,
but if the male patient
feels too humiliated,
it could be a way to help.
If you detect your cancer
at an early stage,
and if your partner
supports you, you're lucky.
However, this miracle does not happen...
to every male breast cancer patient.
The most difficult part is that...
you can never talk about
your illness to anyone.
You have to continue working,
pretending to be healthy.
You also keep it a secret if you're
afraid of losing your partner.
That's because what they
fear the most is...
not the pain, but the prejudice...
that they're not manly.
You might not believe this.
I'm also a breast cancer patient.
What...
I found out at an early stage,
and my partner supported me.
But I had to fight against
deep-rooted prejudice.
I was in despair.
I could not tell anyone
at work about my illness.
I was afraid that...
I might lose my position at work.
But there was something more
important than my position.
I lost a part of my chest,
but in order to protect the person I love,
I'm making this confession.
I have no regrets.
I'm just sorry I couldn't do this earlier.
Male breast cancer patients are no
different to other cancer patients.
Fighting against cancer
is difficult enough.
They shouldn't suffer more
from other people's prejudice.
I hope realistic measures will be taken...
for male breast cancer patients.
I dream of a country where
minorities can be happy.
This will conclude...
the SBC seven o'clock news.
Thank you for watching.