Episode 23
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Gosh...
Are you crazy?
Why didn't you listen to me?
What are you going to do now?
I know what you're going to say.
Don't worry.
These are all facts.
There's nothing inaccurate
about what I said.
This is how it should be.
This is how news scripts
should be written.
Go home.
Man, that was embarrassing.
So embarrassing.
Geez.
I must be crazy.
Where is he going
instead of heading home?
Oh, Mom, it's me. I don't think
I'll be able to come home for dinner.
Make me dinner next time.
Hey, you crazy bastard!
You'll never get married now!
Make sure you hold on tight to the
woman you're dating now, okay?
Hold on tight to that girl who first
told you that you may have cancer
and went to the hospital with you.
If you lose her now,
you'll never be able to get married
and you'll have to live
as a bachelor forever!
Don't cry, Mom. Stop crying.
Who else would agree to go on a
date with you if you break up with her
especially after you had to undergo
surgery for breast cancer?
No woman would ever
entertain the idea of dating you!
No woman would ever take
you seriously as a man!
The entire country
knows about this now.
Oh my... my poor Hwa Shin!
Come on, Mom. Don't cry.
My poor son!
What am I going to do if
my son can't get married?
Who cares if I won't be
able to get married?
I just won't get married, then.
So... stop crying already, Mom.
The person you are trying to
reach has shut off their phone.
[DO NOT FLEE FROM DATING]
Watch where you're going.
Lee Hwa Shin still isn't at work yet?
Gosh, really...
Wow, what a mess.
Man, that punk.
Wait, what's this?
[LEAVE OF ABSENCE REQUEST]
When did he leave this here?
- Hello, sir.
- Yes.
Have you contacted Hwa Shin?
You can't reach him?
Geez.
So he disappeared without
saying anything, even to you?
Yes, Director.
All right.
You can go now.
Oh man...
[REPORTER LEE HWA SHIN]
He told me to go home, and yet...
With the last mock exam before
the National College Exam over
it has been revealed that a question from
the language section has been leaked.
This is shocking news for students with
the National College Exam coming up soon.
Reporter Kim Sung Bae has the story.
The person you are trying to
reach has shut off their phone.
You will be forwarded
to their voicemail.
I'm sorry, but you're his friend, so...
is there any place you think he may be?
I'm looking for him, too.
I'll make sure he comes back safely.
Don't you worry.
Looks like I've lost to Hwa Shin.
Reporter Lee.
How could you help Reporter Lee get
interviews just because he asked you to?
He disappeared after
doing the news on that night.
He won't pick up any calls
and nobody knows where
he is or if he's even alive.
Really?
I think he was too embarrassed
to continue his job as an anchor
and ran away to a place
where I couldn't find him.
About his test results that day...
they were all okay, right?
Oh, of course!
So did he come here alone to
see his test results that day?
Yeah. Yep, yep.
I told you, he's totally fine.
[EVEN THE MINORITY SHOULD
BE HAPPY IN OUR NATION.]
Let's... break up.
The Chinese government has
decided to give North Korea
which has recently suffered
from a huge flood
20 million won in aid as well
as 3.4 billion won in cash.
Due to the flood that was caused
by the Lionrock typhoon
in North Hamgyeong Province
there were more than 100 casualties,
and about 400 people have gone missing.
Reporter Kim Sun Young has the story.
That crazy bastard...
You look like you've been waiting for me.
Yeah, I was.
I was totally waiting for you.
I was dying inside and missed you
so much! Come with me, now.
Hey, grab him! Grab him!
You make me flip-flop between loving you
and hating you every 10 minutes!
Out! Get out!
Get out of here, punk!
Hey, hurry up and get ready!
Get over here.
Oh! You're here, Reporter Lee?
Where have you been,
and what have you been doing?
Are you feeling okay?
I'll get to the point.
If you're here, hurry up and get on air.
- What?
- What!
- I don't want to!
- Why did you come here, then?
Don't I get a warning?
I didn't come to work for a week.
So please, give me a warning!
I only came to work today for that.
And... I don't want to be in front of
the camera for the time being, either.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
It's been a week since I last saw you.
Let's break up.
Let's not break up.
Sure.
Yeah, so, have you been doing well?
Obviously not.
Where did you go,
and what were you up to?
Just... you know.
Yeah, I'm sure.
"Just... you know"?
Hey, why aren't you eating?
You eat, too.
Where did you go,
and what were you up to?
Huh?
What were you thinking,
disappearing like that?
I felt embarrassed.
Why did you come back, then?
You want me to leave again?
I liked that place.
You didn't consider how I'd feel?
- I did.
- And yet, you acted like that?
That's why I came back after a week.
If it weren't for you
I would've lost my mind thinking
that people were staring at my chest
and I would've ended up
going back to Thailand.
Why'd you shut your phone off?
Isn't that "Going AWOL 101?"
I guess you have a lot
of experience, then.
It's my first time.
So? What was the decision you
came to after coming out of hiding?
Let's break up. Let's break up.
Let's not break up.
Did you see my broadcasts?
No, I didn't. I didn't have a TV.
Where did you go that you had no TV?
Let's break up!
Let's not break up.
Well, duh.
What happened to your hand?
It's fine. It's not a huge injury.
Hey, let me see.
Give me your hand.
Let's stop seeing each other!
Let's break up!
Let's break up, please!
You selfish bastard.
You're so selfish.
Oh, fancy seeing you here!
I was just about to call
you into my office.
You're being sent to Kenya as
an overseas correspondent.
What? Director!
Stop complaining. You have
to go if your company tells you to.
Hey, you'll get to drink all the
Kenyan AA coffee you want.
- You'll be gone for two years.
- Director, please!
Oh, damn it!
There's plenty of good coffee
here in Korea, too!
Stop staring at my chest.
It's mine, not yours.
Really? Then... are you okay?
It's not on that side.
Oh, really?
Gosh.
You seem fine to me,
seeing as you're fighting back.
I heard you asked the director
to give you a warning.
You wanted a warning and
to step down from being an anchor.
Yes.
You don't know how many viewers posted
comments on the station's online forum
and called the station
asking about you, do you?
They weren't asking
about you out of curiosity
and they weren't waiting for your
comeback out of pity, either.
They just want to see you
on that time slot every day.
They asked where you went,
and whether or not you got fired.
And there are tons of
complaint calls coming in now, too.
On top of that, there's also your
unwavering love for Pyo Na Ri.
They want to see you sit there and
see that you're overcoming this well
and see that you're healthy
every single day.
So did you really have to run away,
like some kid going through puberty?
Yes, I know.
Everyone is talking about you two!
Didn't you see the banner that they
hung up, as per the president's orders?
He will milk you two for
all you have for the time being.
I'm going to give up on you now, Senior.
It's over.
I'm not going to like you anymore.
Did you find a better guy than me?
I still think your chest is sexy...
and I want to work with you
for a long time.
So, be healthy.
A health supplement made with
red ginseng and gastrodia elata
replaced the expensive lingzhi mushrooms
that were supposed to be in there
with sophora, which can cause clouded
consciousness and stomach problems.
Let's not break up.
Let's break up.
Where did you go for a week,
and what were you doing?
"Ah."
Mom.
What?
Let's stop seeing each other.
Why, you little! I ought to...
Hey. How could I ever
stop seeing you, huh?
I can't! I won't!
It's so easy to say it to you, so
why is it so hard when it comes to her?
Are you done working?
No.
Yeah.
Want to get dinner?
No.
Sure.
What should we eat?
Thank you.
I thought you wanted to eat rice.
Why did you pick udon?
Oh, that's good.
I find myself thinking
about udon sometimes.
Is it okay if I get some soju?
Since when have you ever asked me
before doing those things?
Excuse me, can we get a
bottle of soju here, please?
Right away!
Reporter Lee.
Let's get dinner together with Chi Yeol
after he's done with his college exam.
Chi Yeol hates me, though.
Yeah, he does hate you.
Well, he'd probably act like a
father-in-law... no, mother-in-law
no matter who I bring home, anyway.
He thinks his big sis is the greatest
in the whole world, after all.
- Next time.
- Next time?
What next time?
You live right next door, anyway!
You should properly say hello and treat
him as your younger brother-in-law.
Okay?
Should we just have dinner on
the day he finishes his exam?
What, are you scared of
Chi Yeol or something?
But you know, Beom is your
younger brother-in-law, too.
- Na Ri.
- Yeah?
Let's break up.
Is it because you're scared of your
younger brothers-in-law? Huh?
What? Is it because
you're infertile now?
Is that why?
You knew?
Since when have you known?
Did you play dumb and toy with me
in the palm of your hand?
You were just observing, is that it?
I found out a bit after you disappeared.
Slow down!
Leave me alone.
I bet you thought that I was so pathetic.
Good, then.
Let's break up.
I don't want to.
Let's end this.
I'm fine with us never
being able to have children.
It's really okay.
All I need is you.
I don't have any confidence that I'd be
good at raising a child anyway, and...
Wow, you sure are great at lying.
I'm not lying.
I'm really okay with it.
You sure know how to make someone seem
really pathetic in a matter of seconds.
Did you pity me?
- Don't be sorry.
- Did you pity me?
Is that why you just stood by and
watched without saying anything?
I wanted to give you time.
I thought that you'd tell me about it
when you were comfortable doing so.
So I just waited.
I'm fine with never having a child,
but I can't live without you.
I can't break up with you.
But I'm not okay with it!
This isn't an issue we can solve
just by having you be okay with it.
It doesn't automatically make me feel
better just because you're okay with it.
You know that?
I'm totally confident
that I'll love you forever.
But I've questioned myself
thousands of times...
about whether or not I can
make you happy forever.
So...
- I can't break up with you.
- Let's break up.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
He said that he was going to
come see the test results that day
but you had to do a seminar,
so he rescheduled.
Huh? Oh. Oh, yes.
That happened. Yes.
Yep, yep. That's right.
Why are you lying to me, Doctor?
Reporter Lee said you told him to come
later since you had to perform surgery.
Is... Reporter Lee not completely well?
Did he have a relapse?
Any man in this situation
would feel quite uneasy.
Watch over him, will you?
He'll be going crazy for quite a while.
Don't get caught up in it,
and leave him alone.
I'm sure that he'll be able to
overcome this internal struggle of his.
Oh, hey.
There's been a problem
with my family in England.
I have to go to England,
for just a week.
What about the 9 p.m. news, then?
Are you crazy?
Do I have to push through
and keep working
despite my mom
being in critical condition
just because of the nature of my job?
If I'm not with my mother
in her final moments
I don't think I'll ever
be able to eat again.
I mean, how could I eat if
I did such an inhumane thing?
Your mother is in critical condition?
Oh, man.
Hey, can't we just have Hwa Shin
fill in for me? Just for a week.
Hwa Shin?
Hey, you could end up
losing that spot to Hwa Shin.
Who knows what might happen?
Do you think that the president
will let you on that slot
if Hwa Shin gets popular?
Please, help me.
This is driving me insane...
Tell this to the president
yourself, then.
Yes, sir. What?
With Pyo Na Ri?
Um, sir. I...
Yes, yes.
Yes, I understand, but...
But this is too soon for her.
It'd be better for us to be cautious.
Anyway, I'm completely opposed to
having them do the 9 p.m. news together.
Think about this if it were
the other way around.
Would you want to break up with me
if I couldn't get pregnant?
- Would you?
- Go away.
To be honest, I can imagine what
it'd be like to be married with no kids.
I'm sure it'd get tedious after
a while if it were just the two of us.
It'd be nice if we could cheer up while
looking at our child, who looks like us.
We'd be able to resolve our arguments
right away for the sake of the child.
And the child would
probably make us happy.
And worried sometimes, too.
But we'd get through it together.
Good, then.
But I can't even imagine being
married to someone other than you.
After you disappeared,
I realized that
not being able to have kids
pales in comparison
to not having you around at all.
Because you weren't by my side,
I came to realize that
I won't wish for anything else,
as long as you're by my side.
So, please.
If you don't hate me and you
haven't gotten sick of me already
don't say things like
"Let's break up."
If you say that one more time, I...
Let's break up.
How can you be so cold?
- Shut your mouth, right now.
- Let's break up.
I'm going to stitch
your nasty mouth shut.
I said, let's break up.
How can it be that easy for you
to say something like that?
It's very easy for me to say
things like that. Let's break up.
You're such a terrible person.
Let's break up.
It's just infertility.
There isn't anything that's
100 percent impossible these days
due to all the medical breakthroughs.
We can just try every day.
Let's just have sex
every hour of every day.
And eat things that are good
for you before doing it.
Let's get you in shape,
and sleep together.
No pressure. Just think of it
as a super passionate nap.
Okay?
It's completely possible,
just as long as we don't give up.
Please?
You want to just have sex every day?
Let's do our best.
This is so pathetic.
- Hurry up and go home.
- I'll be good to you.
What if you still can't get
pregnant, despite all that?
Say that after you've slept
with me at least 100 times.
And after that?
Then... let's take a hot, passionate nap
every time you eat ramen at my house.
And what if you still don't
get pregnant after that?
We can just buy more ramen.
Don't look at me like that.
I won't marry you.
Do you even know how much
ramen is at your house?
It's less than a thousand.
I won't marry you.
Marry me.
Let's break up.
Let's break up!
Leave.
Did you just dump me?
Yeah.
Did I just get dumped?
You won't regret this, right?
Yeah.
All right. Let's end things, then.
Yeah. Let's just break up.
Let's break up.
Hurry up and go back home!
Oh, whatever.
Wow, you sure are great, huh?
Your pride is really amazing.
You really are more stubborn
than anyone I know.
Good for you.
I honestly did all that I could.
Don't be disappointed in me.
I tried as best as I could already.
Don't you dare say that you're
disappointed or whatever later.
And don't curse me, either!
Yeah, whatever.
Let's just give up.
- Go home.
- Let's just give up!
- You'll freeze to death.
- Forget about it all!
Damn it!
Reporter Lee, do you want
to have one last ramen?
- One last one?
- Yeah.
No.
No to what? It being the last time?
Ramen? "Napping"?
Yeah, whatever.
Let's just give up.
Let's just give up. Give up!
Just give up on all of it!
Hurry up and leave!
We broke up anyway,
so don't worry and just sleep.
Na Ri.
What are you doing over there?
You saw, right? Your sister got drunk
and is clinging to me, acting absurd.
Clean her off my property.
What did you say?
How dare you say that about a woman?
- Huh?
- Hey!
Hurry up and get over here!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Are you two heading to work?
Are you... going somewhere?
Yes. I have some business
to attend to, you see.
Oh, yes. See you
later tonight, at the hotel.
Oh... yes.
What are you doing at the hotel?
I'll have to head there to find out.
You two are going to
hotels together already?
Make sure you don't bring that up.
All you have to do is
keep your own mouth shut.
You'll have to eat dinner alone.
I figured as much and made the
cod stew you like. It's in the fridge.
Don't just eat whatever because
you're alone. Eat a proper meal.
Okay?
Heat it up before you eat it, okay?
You do know how to heat food up, right?
No!
I don't like the fact that you're dating.
I'm bored.
It feels like Chef is stealing you away!
Hey, are you being
serious right now?
I won't heat it up and eat it!
I don't know how to! I'm not eating it!
How could you change so much?
Hey, it's been like 500
years since I last dated.
Can't you help me out?
All right, Hwa Shin, Pyo Na Ri.
You two are doing the 9 p.m. news.
Why? I don't want to do it with her.
It's the president's orders.
Just try your best for just a week.
I'm sure Reporter Kye
won't stand for this.
The president said that we
should have both of you fill in
since you're filling in anyway.
You two are being talked about as of
late anyway, so it may boost our ratings.
- Happy now? Do I keep going?
- No.
This isn't a request.
It's an order, punk.
How are you so damn self-centered?
This is a great chance for Pyo Na Ri.
She'll be able to improve her image
after what happened with the election.
And Reporter Kye said that
she'd never work with you.
She said she's taking a week off.
I'll do my best, sir.
Thank you for this opportunity.
I told you I can't, Chief.
Get out.
You won't be able to
get married, at this rate.
Why not?
If you do the 9 p.m. news with me
people who were unaware of
our relationship will soon find out
and it won't benefit you in any way.
The broadcasting company
is just using us.
To get more views.
Are you sure it's not that
you're not confident that I can do it
even though it's only a week?
I'm going to adhere to my beliefs
and do well, even if it's only a week.
Sure you will.
You're not ready for this yet.
If you stand in the spotlight,
you'll be attacked more, too.
It could become dangerous for you.
I've never once worked
in a safe environment
so maybe that's why it doesn't
really scare me when you say that.
- I'm not kidding.
- Neither am I.
We broke up.
You said we shouldn't get married,
pretending it was for my own good
and now you're doing the same thing
with the new anchor position?
Why did you become such a scaredy-cat?
Why did you become so spineless?
Don't forget that I have breast cancer
and that I'm infertile.
Are you an idiot? Reconsider.
Why did you become such a scaredy-cat?
Why did you become so spineless?
I wouldn't ever be someone's replacement.
You know that I'm doing
the morning news, right?
You won't be able to get that slot back,
because I won't give it back.
Do your best.
Thanks, all of you.
Why are you acting so pitiful?
It's not like you.
Do you know why I said
I wouldn't do the 9 p.m. news?
You met me when I was in high school
so I'm forever a
high-schooler in your mind.
You're right.
How could I do the 9 p.m. news
with a high-schooler?
Straighten up.
Do you think that I'm not
aware of what you're thinking?
You're not planning to
fill in only for a week.
You want to keep this spot, don't you?
You think this may be an opportunity.
Isn't that obvious?
Stars are usually born
through chances like these.
Oh, don't worry.
My big sister can't win against me.
Um, I'm going to head
to the bathroom for a bit.
Oh, yes. Go ahead.
Okay.
This is your first time,
so be alert.
10 seconds!
Nine! Eight! Seven! Six...
All right, cue the catchphrase!
The world can't change the news,
but the news can change the world.
I'm Lee Hwa Shin
of SBC News Hot Nine.
I'm Pyo Na Ri.
- Wow, they're on fire.
- Yeah... okay.
What kind of woman is she that
she cured you of your asexuality?
I was so curious to know that I ran here!
And she's young too, I presume?
She is.
Younger than you, at least.
Oh.
Senior.
Hey, Bang Ja Young!
What brings you here?
Say hello, Big Sis.
This woman, to me, is the
sexiest woman in the whole world.
It has been decided that
ex-Chairman Kang Yong Jae of D Group
who evaded taxes and fines
and is being held at his workplace
will be paid four million won per day.
He will have four million won
taken off his 3.8 billion won fine
for every seven hour workday.
- It's quite...
- Could he be mining diamonds there?
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, Hwa Shin!
That punk! What else is
he adding on, now?
Hey, stop it!
And days such as weekends, days off,
and national holidays will all count.
One may think that the deal he
got may be too good to be true...
Hey, Pyo Na Ri!
Hurry and cut in!
The average rate one receives for working
off their fine is 100,000 won per day
so it'd take one over 100 years to
work off 3.8 billion won in fines.
He should be considerate of the
hardworking citizens of this country
- and ex-Chairman Kang should...
- Hey, don't do it!
Are you crazy?
Why are you doing this?
He should make an exception for his own
department store's shopping bags, right?
All right, that is all.
That's the end of SBC News Hot Nine.
Why do you have to do
this when I'm the PD?
Why did you have to insult someone
on live TV when I'm the PD, you bastard?
Please have a good night.
Good work.
You still think I'm a coward?
You think I'm just pretending?
Hey, it was nice,
but take it down a notch.
Acting like this can
end up backfiring on you.
Hey, what if D Group's department
store says they'll pull all their ads?
Why are you trying to get
yourself fired on the first day?
I'll just fold shopping bags like
that chairman if I get fired.
Oh, whatever.
Great freaking job!
This is a brand new blanket.
Yes, but you should wash a
blanket once before using it.
- Goodbye!
- Bye, now!
Why are you following me?
Oh, it's here.
What is all this?
This is the rice cooker that
we picked out together.
And this is an iron for me
to iron your shirts with.
And this is a blanket for us.
I just bought it, but had it washed
so we can use it right away.
Like, immediately.
I thought you said that you'd
give up on our relationship.
I'll be going now.
Wasn't that rice cooker for you to use?
No. The lid on the rice
cooker at my place is loose
but my mom used to use it,
so I can never throw it away.
I'll probably use it for about
10 more years or so.
Let's break up.
You don't have any of
these things, anyway.
You moved in here without
even bringing a winter blanket.
Let's use it together
while we live together.
These are the only furnishings
I'm bringing into our marriage
so don't ask for any
more stuff from me.
I'm not marrying you.
You won't?
All right, then.
Forget about it.
Bye, then.
What do you want me to do with all this?
I'm saying that I'll make you rice
with this, iron your shirt with this
and take nice, long "naps"
with you under this!
Why are you so clingy?
I had one-sided feelings
for you for three years.
Then we started liking each other,
and were even about to get married.
Then I just received word from
you that you want to break up.
So I think it'll take a good 30 years
before I can break up with you.
I'll break up with you
after 30 years. Okay?
Why are you acting so foolishly?
Booyoo Group's Chairman Choi Jang Go
has been fined 170 billion won
in accordance with the
special economic crime law
for embezzlement and tax evasion...
All right, finish it up!
Last year, Booyoo Group
cited financial losses
as a reason for firing full-time workers
and hiring only contracted workers.
- That is all...
- Booyoo Group's slogan is
"Booyoo Group will stand
alongside the nation"
"until the bodies and minds
of all the citizens are enriched."
Hey! Hey!
There he goes again.
Hey, stop! Stop!
But the truth is that Chairman Choi
was more interested in enriching himself.
That'll be all for the News Hot Nine.
Thank you to all of our viewers.
He has a talent for the news, but
Hwa Shin is getting into some hot water.
You still think that I'm a coward?
Why do you keep butting in
without letting me know?
Give me a signal or something. I'm going
to die of a heart attack because of you.
Hey, it's not out of the ordinary for
big companies to embezzle money.
I told you right before we
started the news, didn't I?
You were to speak of Chairman Choi as
drily as possible and state only facts!
Drily?
Do you think I'm a dryer, or something?
You don't think I have emotions?
You think I'm a robot?
Am I supposed to just read
off the prompter like a parrot?
You said that we could make the
concluding statements as we wished!
I can't just talk about
Chairman Choi like a dryer or a robot
so how can I only stick
to delivering the facts?
You didn't put me here to
do just that. Am I wrong?
But you're going way overboard!
I'm just saying,
don't make any snide remarks!
That tongue of yours
will be ripped out at this rate.
Are you trying to get
that to happen?
Does it make you feel
better to say those things?
You think that'll help us
raise our ratings?
Who cares about that if they threaten
to pull all their ads tomorrow?
Who the hell is going to
take responsibility, huh?
At this rate, you...
Hey, Hwa Shin.
You'll... get...
Ugh!
Hey, Beom.
Can I have just one bite of that?
Come on, just one bite.
Geez, you're so stingy.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Younger Brother-in-Law.
Younger Brother-in-Law,
give me just a bite of that.
Thanks.
You're not even saying hi?
Reporter Lee, I'm really curious.
Where did you go while you went missing?
I mean, what happened there that you're
just doing whatever you please now?
Huh?
[LEE JOONG SHIN]
How'd you know I'd be here?
I didn't know for sure.
I just searched everywhere...
and I just happened to get
lucky enough to find you here.
I think... I like you more
than I like Pyo Na Ri.
Are you confessing
your love to me, right now?
I...
thought that I was quite a lonely guy.
But seeing your back as you left
made me think that you
may be much lonelier than I am.
You're not the same
person I knew anymore.
I saw how great and true your love was.
You taught me what it means
to give up on something.
I'm going to treat you now
as if you're a new friend of mine.
I can do that, right?
I hung out with my older
brother and my friend.
Your friend? Who?
A new friend of mine.
Reporter Lee. We've never had a staff
dinner after doing the 9 p.m. news.
Let's go for a staff dinner.
Just the two of us.
I thought we'd broken up.
Yeah, so let's have dinner
as 9 p.m. news partners.
It's because we never had a staff
dinner that we're so out of sync!
- Who said that?
- Me!
I've got a bone to pick with you.
So let's go.
You didn't even have dinner yet.
So if you want stew,
let's head to my place.
No thanks.
Come on!
[NEWS DEPARTMENT DIRECTOR]
It's the president.
Yes, sir?
- What's he going on about now?
- Um, yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Just how many ads has
Reporter Lee Hwa Shin lost us so far?
Make sure that he can't
ever be a reporter again
and send him to work at the
company's kindergarten!
Let's eat, Reporter Lee.
It's good.
Wow, really? Let me see.
Oh, so it's perfect for you if
it's a bit bland for me, huh?
Okay. I'll make it like this
for you from now on.
But you know, Reporter Lee,
we don't need to have a kid.
We have one already.
Pyo Na Ri is raising Hwa Shin, after all.
Shut your mouth.
How am I supposed to
eat if I shut my mouth?
Only open your mouth to eat, then.
Are we really going to
break up over this?
Yeah.
So stubborn.
Also, mind your expression when doing
the news instead of worrying about me.
But you keep making me worried!
Speak more nicely!
Did you hear that we're not getting ads
from that department store anymore?
At this rate, they'll have your head.
All right, fine.
Here, here. Okay.
Just eat. I'll nag you
only a little bit after that.
Hey, listen up. Anchors are only to be
preoccupied with the viewers, all right?
If you worry about other things,
you'll lose confidence.
It'll be the end for you
if you lose confidence.
Ugh, you're so annoying.
Why do you have to be
like this when we're eating?
You used to say that I was cool
when I said things like this!
I did?
You not only said it, you had
"You're so cool!" written all over you.
But what did you say?
I'm annoying?
Really? Was I so
head-over-heels for you then?
Why, you little...
Looks like you don't want
to hear that from me
even though you wanted to break up.
Here, have a snack, too.
I hate anchovies more than
any other snack in the world.
Eat it anyway.
It's good for your chest.
No.
Wow, you really don't listen!
Why should I listen to you
when I don't even listen to my mom?
Listen to your mom, and listen
to me too from now on, then!
- What?
- And also, when we're doing the news!
Why do you keep interrupting me
whenever I say something off-script?
Do you know how much you
surprise me whenever you do that?
- That's...
- Are you a reckless driver?
Or are you a new driver?
You're obviously the new one,
so I'm the reckless one.
Either way, they're both dangerous!
Reckless drivers are overconfident
and get into huge accidents.
A new driver is better.
At least they're really careful, so they
don't get into any big accidents.
In this way, you're even
worse than Reporter Park!
What?
How could you possibly
compare me to that punk?
What? I'm worse than him?
How, exactly? Tell me.
Stop being ridiculous!
Reporter Park may ignore his partner
but he's never
interrupted me like you do.
Honestly, when I go on air with you,
I feel like my heart is going to drop
and I get so nervous that I feel like
I'm going to have a heart attack!
That's why I told you not
to do it from the start!
I thought you couldn't handle it,
which is why I told you not to do it!
Why should I?
You're the one who should think of
cooperating better with your partner!
- What?
- Are you a dictator?
- Shut your mouth.
- Are you a tyrant?
I told you to shut it!
You think it's cool to
be a reckless driver?
Na Ri!
Oh no! What do I do?
It's Chi Yeol!
You're scared of him, right?
Hurry and hide!
- Hurry! It's Chi Yeol!
- Why should I?
Aw, man.
Why isn't it opening?
I told her to fix it! Ugh!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
You're drinking alone?
Huh? Yeah...
Hey, I thought you were going to study
with Dae Gu. Why are you already home?
- I left my study room key here.
- Why did you leave that behind?
Get it together, okay?
Go to sleep, already!
Okay.
I really just want to be alone.
It's been hard for me lately.
Bye.
Good luck!
Reporter Lee!
I'm so sorry! Are you okay?
Sorry. Sorry.
Wait. Look at me.
Why did you kiss me before?
Because you were
driving me crazy, so...
I just wanted to shut you up.
I don't know.
Is it okay for us to kiss
when we broke up?
I don't know.
Do you want to sleep with me?
Sleep with me.
Are you really... okay with this?
How many times do I need to tell you?
Are you really okay with the fact
that we'll never have a kid?
I told you, it's fine!
No.
Just trust me.
No, no, no!
I'll take responsibility for you. Okay?
No, no.
Why do you keep saying no? Damn it!
Just a second.
Can you help me with this?
Why did you wear
something like this? Geez.
Why is it so tight?
No, no, no.
Gosh!
Are you going to keep saying no?
But... do you think I'll really
be able to make you happy?
Stop brushing me off, already.
I'm not marrying you.
Hey, put your hands up.
- What?
- Put your hands up!
I... I'm not marrying you.
- I won't.
- Shut up and take this off!
Help me out, here!
Here, move. I'll do it.
Oh my gosh, how embarrassing!
Don't wear any turtlenecks.
I won't wear them, either.
They're hard to take off.
Did you win, or did I lose?
It's a draw.
No going AWOL without telling me.
And you have to eat anchovies.
And we have to take
plenty of good "naps."
Subtitles by DramaFever
[I'D LIKE IT IF MY NA RI
WERE A HAPPY NA RI.]
You really want to get married?
I want to live with you
as soon as possible.
What's up, Brother-in-Law?
If you mess with
my sister, I'll kill you!
Do you have any money saved up?
You... saw it?
Did you hear that he's getting
assigned to the kindergarten?
Why won't you even let me quit?
Please make him happy.
You really can't do the
kindergarten thing?