Subtitles by VIU
(Final Episode)
Did you win or did I lose?
We tied.
You have to sleep well, too.
Hey.
My brother-in-law. You're home.
(Rak Pasta)
What time is it?
Why are you coming out now? What were you doing?
Why were you hiding?
What did you do that you had to hide?
Hey, let go. Let go.
Calm down.
Hey. This is no way to treat an adult.
Ever since my sister had a crush on you...
while receiving no love for over three years,
I hated you.
You thought you were so great that you refused to accept her...
and made her lonely and suffer.
I was already angry with you.
But if you're toying with my naive sister's feelings,
I won't forgive you.
If you hurt my sister, I'll kill you.
If you think easy of her,
I'll shut your mouth forever so you can never talk again.
Hey!
- What? - How old are you?
I'm 19. So what?
If you're 19,
that means you're under age.
My goodness, you're just a kid.
How dare you talk like that to a 36-year-old adult...
and grab me by the collar.
You're only half my age, you punk. How dare you.
Is that how your sister raised you?
My sister cares for and likes me more than anyone in the world.
- Not any more. - You're mistaken.
I am not.
Your sister cares for and likes me more than anyone in the world.
And I...
will be the man who will never forget that, even for a moment.
I don't like you.
I don't like you, either.
Gosh, that hurts.
Darn it.
(Rak Pasta)
Is he following me?
Why are you following me?
Go inside!
So I'm saying I'll cook for you with this, iron your shirts,
and nap with you under this blanket.
Use it while living with me.
These are all the gifts I can offer you.
(Banquet Hall)
Approximately what date are you thinking of?
I'd like to set a date as soon as possible.
We don't have any availability for the rest of the year.
There's one on Christmas Eve because of a cancellation.
- I'll take that. - Yes, Sir.
Hey.
This is the president's orders, so just listen.
You don't need to report to the newsroom any more.
You know the kindergarten for the employees?
Report to the kindergarten management team.
- What? - Just go.
What... That's absurd.
- Why? Why? - Do you think...
we don't say anything because we don't know...
how to say those things?
If you acted brave alone, you should pay for it, as well.
You deserve to suffer at the kindergarten.
Did I say something wrong? Did I?
It's not like I made anything up.
How could they kick out a reporter for uncovering something...
they want to hide?
Didn't you expect this much?
You punk. Go.
- What are you doing? - My goodness.
I quit.
Quit what? Quit what? Quit what?
You can't quit. I won't let you.
My gosh, seriously.
How could none of you be on my side?
And you'll go around claiming to be reporters with a conscience.
- Why that... - My goodness.
The nine o'clock news...
will revert back to how it was,
and Ms Uhm will do the morning news that you used to do.
The company says we'll only be hiring part-time announcers now.
Hang in there.
Wait on stand-by until you get assigned to another program.
Think about what kind of a program...
you'll enjoy doing, too.
Okay.
By the way,
did you hear that Hwa Shin has been transferred...
to the company kindergarten management team?
I guess he can't return to the newsroom.
The company kindergarten?
He won't be an anchor then?
He can't even be a reporter, let alone an anchor.
I guess he can't return to the newsroom.
Oh, no.
Hey.
You cry so much.
Is it about me?
No.
It obviously is.
What will you do at the kindergarten?
And how could they...
have a reporter watch kids?
Let's get lunch.
Why aren't you angry?
You're angry and crying on behalf of me.
Let's go.
You really want to get married here?
Do you prefer soup or a buffet? They asked us to taste it first.
This is no time to plan a wedding.
Forget it. Postpone it. Cancel it.
Hey. Do you know how hard it is to get a reception hall?
You must feel terrible right now.
Why are you rushing?
Why do you want to make me into an insensitive bride?
My heart is breaking because you can't be an anchor.
I'm afraid you won't marry me if I'm unemployed.
Is someone chasing us?
It's also rude to ask guests to come here on Christmas Eve.
It's too soon.
And you're in no state of mind...
to get married. Let's cancel. Let's postpone. Let's go.
No. We're not cancelling. Do you know how much that'll cost?
How could you even set a date without asking your mother?
This is insane.
It's because it's my first time getting married.
It's my first time too, but I at least know the proper order.
Soup or buffet?
- Let's go. - Sit down!
I said sit!
Who should officiate the wedding?
Who should it be?
- Mr Oh? - Mr Oh?
Yes.
Hwa Shin used to be a reporter.
But from now on, he can't be a reporter any more.
He'll have to watch kids for the rest of his life at a kindergarten.
But at times like these, the two of you should cherish each other more,
love each other and live well together. That is my hope.
Maybe not.
They were destined for each other.
They let out gas in front of each other long ago.
They helped each other change their underwear.
And she consoled him when he had breast cancer.
She even embraced his impotence. They are a beautiful couple.
Was...
all of this a secret, by any chance?
Never mind.
I don't know why...
you asked a divorcee like myself to officiate the wedding.
There is only one thing I can say to the bride and groom.
If you realise later on that this isn't it, just break up.
Divorce?
It's being true to your feelings.
- Maybe not, right? - You only live once.
Why must we try our best to stay married?
If you get a divorce and decide to marry someone else,
please ask me to officiate...
your second wedding, too.
Okay?
Gosh.
Who should host our wedding?
- Dong Gi? - The groom, Hwa Shin, is crazy.
He's grumpy and arrogant.
He thinks he's better than anyone else in this world.
Even a jerk like this can get married, but why...
Hey! How much are you going to pay me for this?
To host a wedding like this, I'll have to buy a new suit...
and new shoes. Give me the money!
Why don't we ask my new friend?
Isn't this too much?
How can you ask me to host your wedding?
Hey! Hwa Shin!
I'm your only friend, aren't I?
Are you crazy?
He won't agree to do it anyway.
It'd be weird even if he says he will.
Hey. I thought you said Jung Won is generous and has a big heart.
That's still true.
Still, we can't ask him to host our wedding.
When you stand next to me
I fall in love with your eyes
I cried yesterday
But I have you today
So tomorrow, I'll be happy
It's not your looks
- Maybe not. - Hey!
- It's not anything superficial - My goodness.
All I needed was your gentle love
This won't work.
Gosh, getting married isn't easy.
You didn't quit your job, did you?
Did you?
What did you do?
(Resignation Letter)
Why won't you even let me quit? Why won't you?
Of all places, why does it have to be a kindergarten?
Mr Oh, that place will be pure torture for me.
Tell me to clean the office every day instead.
There are other ways to punish me.
Just don't make me change a baby's diaper.
I can't do it. I refuse to do it.
Just accept my letter of resignation.
Get out.
My gosh, seriously.
My goodness.
(From Groom Lee Hwa Shin and Bride Pyo Na Ri)
What is this?
Have you ever officiated a wedding?
Mum.
I need to borrow some money.
For what?
For my wedding.
Let me have a wedding.
Who are you getting married to?
I'll pay you back after I sell my stocks in China.
You haven't even introduced a girl to me.
Who are you getting married to?
Just attend my wedding.
Am I just another guest?
It's yours, isn't it?
No. It belongs to Ja Young.
She wears it often.
Really?
Hey. I can't reach. Can you put this up there?
- This... - Put it up on the left side.
What's this?
What's that?
What is this?
Why do you keep so much money here?
Use this money for your wedding.
How much is this?
It's not your fault that you fell for voice phishing.
I'm sorry.
Get up.
Uncle Hwa Shin.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who should say...
sorry.
I'm sorry.
Is your chest all right?
Yes.
Ppal Gang, you can go in now.
She called all three of us. You're the only one who fell for it.
- Are you stupid? - You're so stupid.
Have you ever officiated a wedding?
What did you say?
The company says we'll only be hiring part-time announcers now.
Hang in there.
Wait on stand-by until you get assigned to another program.
Think about what kind of a program you'll enjoy doing, too.
Yes?
Where's Chi Yul?
He's not here.
Are you scared of him?
Use this for our wedding.
What is it?
Are we really getting married?
What's all the rush about?
I want to move in with you as soon as possible.
Did you quit?
Don't quit.
Is it because you don't want to marry an unemployed man?
Your love overcame my breast cancer and infertility.
You even refused Jung Won's love.
But I guess it can't overcome my unemployment.
If you quit, how will we support ourselves?
Do you think I won't be able to support you?
This is no time to get married. Did you receive any job offers?
No.
You really don't want to work at the kindergarten?
(Resignation Letter)
You want to quit when you're getting married?
Do you think everything will work out once you're married?
Fine.
Then take a look at this, at least.
(News Programme Proposal)
What is this?
We'll only air my voice.
Only your voice?
We'll collect anonymous information.
The programme title will be "Whistle-blowers".
From unfair layouts to corruptions in industries,
we'll take the problems in this society,
and blow it out in the open.
What do you think?
Three senior colleagues of yours,
who you thought weren't worthy to be called reporters...
and look down on so much,
visited the president...
and begged him constantly...
to give their beloved colleague...
a job.
Why don't you try that instead?
- I don't want to. - Just go there...
and blow the whistle or whatever.
What job are you talking about?
This is so embarrassing. Why did they put my name on it?
Hey.
Here, you can say whatever you want to say.
No one will ever say anything to you.
The advertisement is over.
In 3, 2, 1. Cue.
Hello, everyone.
I am Lee Hwa Shin,
and I will be hosting the new health show,
"Lee Hwa Shin's Health Journal, A Conversation About Your Body".
This is health news that resolves women's concerns.
Today,
we will discuss the symptoms of uterine myoma and its cures.
Uterine myoma is common in women past the age of 30.
The symptoms include...
not being able to menstruate,
strong menstrual cramps and increased blood.
Please post your questions and stories about uterine myoma.
Let's take a break for a song.
This is Kim Sung Hwan's "Don't Ask".
Music, cue.
Hey. The social media page is going crazy.
There are a lot of listeners.
Get me some water.
Water?
There's no one to get it for you. Get it yourself.
Mr Lee.
What would I be good at?
- You? - Yes.
I don't know.
Wouldn't you be best at what you want to do?
What I want to do?
I don't know if it's only me,
but your weather...
always stood out and was the most enjoyable.
That's very subjective.
That's what I think.
You're a good DJ, too.
- Did you listen? - Yes.
Don't listen. I'm going to quit soon.
You're good at everything.
- Everything? - Yes.
Everything.
Everything like what?
Everything. Just everything.
So tell me more specifically.
Just everything.
Whatever.
You're good at kissing, too.
My brother-in-law is too clueless. You third wheel.
Why... Why you freak.
What are you doing to Jung Won's girlfriend?
Are you insane?
- Are you high? - It's not what you think.
Are you a dog? Are you?
Why are you acting like one?
Jung Won is a great friend.
Do you need to suffer in torment...
after stealing his girlfriend in order to learn your lesson?
How dare you steal your friend's girlfriend.
Just live alone, you rat.
It's better to live alone.
How dare you go after your friend's girl.
How am I supposed to face his mum? You punk.
- You little... - Calm down.
You too.
You're tough, and you cook well.
I liked you,
but you play with 2 guys and tear apart 2 best friends?
What's wrong with you?
Even if he hit on you, you should've remained with your boyfriend.
How humiliating is this?
I'm going to marry her.
Shut it.
Never!
She broke up with Jung Won!
I saw her eat with Jung Won and his mum not long ago.
I saw it myself!
She was seeing both of us!
Hold on.
She likes me more. I won!
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
I'm sorry.
Why wouldn't you let me explain?
Goodness.
You thoughtless kid.
What was so great about this girl that two guys would fight over her?
What?
What? Gosh.
Then don't come.
Don't come to the wedding.
Don't be like that.
She's too good for me.
You have no idea.
Do you know how unappealing your son is?
I'm someone who tries to quit my job every day.
I might get unemployed. I also have breast cancer and...
Ma'am, I'm really sorry.
I'll think about marriage a little more.
I'm not good enough to make her happy.
Don't you like soup?
If you don't, don't come to the wedding.
What?
I don't. I don't like it, you punk. I don't like it.
Why you...
- Good job, everyone. - Good job.
- Good job. - Do you want to get dinner?
Forget dinner. Let's grab a drink.
Okay. I'll be right back.
Do you have money saved up?
Why?
I want to try to be this much interested in you.
I have a car, a house and some land.
I thought you were broke after your divorce.
Fine. I live on rent, I'm still paying off my car,
and the land isn't something I can sell,
but I have a high salary.
Your salary is the same as mine.
You're not sick, right?
Why? Do you want to live with me?
I have high blood pressure, but I'm taking my medicine.
I have reflux esophagitis,
hepatocirrhosis,
and there's a slight symptom of irritable bowel syndrome.
You have nothing. Why do you have so many illnesses?
Do you have any good traits?
I'm honest, and I'll never cheat.
That's true.
It's not that you won't cheat. You just can't.
Anything else you want to ask?
Will you consider changing how you part your hair?
There. Do you like that?
The usual style is better.
Okay.
- Lose some weight. - Hey...
- The wrinkles on your neck... - Hey...
- Go see a dermatologist, too. - Hey...
I like men with soft hands, but your hands are so rough.
I won't say anything about the parts I can't see.
Can you at least do something about the parts I can see?
Do something about your clothes.
Just say you don't like me.
I thought after living in England for three years,
you'd end up becoming a British gentleman.
How did you get worse?
How did you get so old?
Hey.
It's a good thing when someone is curious about another person.
I find hope...
in your complaints.
Let's drink.
If you try...
to date my brother, I'll kill you.
Tae Ra.
What's wrong with me?
This is too little.
Ja Young.
How much do you want?
I can't believe I'm getting paid off at this age.
It doesn't feel so bad.
You have a weakness for money.
You like money.
I'll think about it.
Are there women who take money and break up these days?
Ms Uhm will do the morning news that you used to do.
Think about what kind of a program you'd enjoy doing, too.
What would I be good at?
Wouldn't you be best at what you want to do?
I can do it, Mr Oh.
I never missed a day other than weekends for four years.
This is my 1,029th broadcast.
I can do it in my sleep. I can do it even with my eyes closed.
I can do it, Mr Oh. I can do it.
Of all the things I've done in my life,
weather forecasting was the most rewarding job for me.
Your weather forecast always stood out and was the most enjoyable.
That was all for the weather.
Hi, have a seat.
My goodness.
As you might have guessed,
it's about renewing your contract.
Your salary will be adjusted according to your work experience.
So...
I'd like that.
- But... - But?
I'd like you to treat me...
as a weather expert.
I'll be a weather expert...
who can produce unique weather reports.
We'd love that.
I like it. Many viewers look forward to your weather forecasts. Okay.
I'll stay as a weather forecaster all my life.
Today, we'll talk about weather breast-feeding is...
really necessary or not.
Professor Geum Suk Ho, who is a breast specialist,
and Ms Oh Jin Joo, who is a nurse, are here with us.
- Hello. - Hello.
Many women have trouble deciding if they should breastfeed.
What are your thoughts on this matter as an expert?
When you breastfeed, the level of prolactin goes up.
Prolactin helps prevent...
breast cancer.
It's one of the strongest anticancer elements.
- It is? - Are you saying that...
childbirth is related to breast cancer?
Yes. Giving birth can help women prevent breast cancer.
By giving birth,
you shorten the time you're exposed to female hormones.
Therefore, it lowers the risk of breast cancer.
I see.
However, just because you didn't give birth or didn't breastfeed,
it doesn't necessarily mean you'll get breast cancer.
While breastfeeding is recommended,
it's totally up to the mother to decide if she wants to do it or not.
That's right.
Also, choosing not to breastfeed...
does not mean that the mother lacks love for her children.
I see.
Let's listen to some music.
Music, start.
Will you be busy on Christmas Eve?
No.
What about you, Ms Oh?
- No. - Don't you guys have a date?
Both of you should relax.
Well,
have you ever officiated a wedding before?
Me?
No, I haven't.
You've been waiting for me, right?
- Are you coming straight from work? - Of course.
I'm starving. Make me some food with the rice cooker you brought.
Here.
I didn't know you could do something like this.
By the way, Mr Lee,
I'm a bit worried...
because your mother doesn't like me.
Don't care about her. She's always like that.
She even disapproved of both my sisters-in-law at first.
- Really? - Yes.
Still, why don't we get married when she starts to like me?
I think she'll get hurt if we push ahead like this.
- I don't want to wait. - Let's do it next year.
- What's wrong? - Don't you want to marry me?
- Mr Lee. - Yes?
Quit your job if you want.
I don't want you to put up with a job you don't like just for me.
I don't want you to stay quiet just for the monthly salary.
I decided to start working as a weather reporter again.
Don't worry about money. Quit your job if you want to.
Work where you can say whatever you want to say, okay?
- Can I really do that? - Yes.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Then I'm quitting tomorrow.
Do it.
Okay.
- Are you hungry? - Yes.
I'll make you some food.
Let's just eat at my place.
- Is Chi Yul there? - Yes.
I don't want to go, then.
Let's just go.
- Let's go. - No.
Fine, stay here, then.
What?
What are you doing?
Wait.
It's from your sister.
What is it?
It's quite a lot.
Should we use this money...
on our dates?
How much is it?
Is it 100,000 dollars, or is it 10,000 dollars?
I'm guessing it's 10,000 dollars.
If I was 5 years younger, it would have been 100,000 dollars.
Didn't you check how much it was?
Why don't we...
just date, without getting married?
I don't...
want to get married without your family's support.
Let's...
Let's live all together, the three of us.
Who's not with me?
I'm up for it.
Let me think about it.
She smiled, didn't she?
(It's not your fault that you fell for voice phishing. I'm sorry.)
Do you admit that what you did was wrong?
Yes.
Is that all?
Please don't tell my sister.
I'm sorry.
We have a secret now.
Be nice to me.
Only if you're nice to my sister.
- Have you been well? - More or less.
(From Groom Lee Hwa Shin and Bride Pyo Na Ri)
You don't have to come.
Please...
make Hwa Shin happy.
Don't make him lonely.
Okay.
(From CBS weather forecasters)
(Groom: Lee Hwa Shin, Bride: Pyo Na Ri)
Befitting of Christmas Eve, the forecast calls...
for snow tonight through early morning.
Santa Claus will have to deliver gifts...
through the front door rather than the chimney.
It's because the chimney is very different from...
1700 years ago when Santa Claus first started.
The air is very polluted,
so if he goes into the chimney,
he can get quite sick.
Rudolf will also have to be careful of the snow filled with pollutants.
Santa Claus,
can you give us the gift of good, clean air next year?
I miss the days when we used to eat the snow falling on our lips.
I am Pyo Na Ri.
I thought Mr Lee would come.
You must be cold. Get in.
There's a lot of traffic since it's Christmas Eve.
(Think about it one last time. You can run off with Jung Won.)
Whatever.
The dress looks good on you.
You look pretty.
Thank you.
We will now begin the wedding...
of Lee Hwa Shin and Pyo Na Ri.
I don't see Na Ri's father.
He couldn't make it because there was a construction delay.
Oh, no.
Groom, please enter.
Here comes the most beautiful bride in the world,
who will love the groom...
through rain, snow or hurricane.
Here comes the bride.
Congratulations!
I love you!
The bride and groom will now bow to each other.
Hey.
Do you think they'll actually live happily together?
Gosh, stop jinxing them.
It depends on Mother.
What are you talking about?
You're the ones who got divorced. Why are you blaming his mother?
I'm saying it's a happy day.
Bride and groom, please bow to each other.
You look great today.
That's a given.
Why don't you say I look pretty?
It's a given.
Next, the officiant will give her message.
The officiant is Taeyang Hospital's surgeon...
specialising in breast cancer, Geum Suk Ho.
I'm more nervous than I am before a surgery.
I didn't even get married yet,
so I'm not sure why they asked me to officiate today,
but I think...
it may be because I witnessed this couple's first kiss.
For the groom, Lee Hwa Shin,
his first name was "Granny".
His next name was "Ms Pyo Na Ri".
And now,
he voluntarily chose...
to be called the male breast cancer patient, Lee Hwa Shin.
How a person overcomes a dangerous situation...
shows what kind of a person he is.
Breast cancer...
proved just how great of a man...
the groom Lee Hwa Shin is.
You once asked me if I would marry a man like you.
My answer is...
a total "yes".
If circumstances provide, please propose to me next time.
You may laugh.
Bride, Pyo Na Ri...
is more than qualified to embrace...
a man such as him.
Everyone loves,
but not everyone can protect that love.
Your hearts brought you together.
I hope you will protect your relationship with your hearts.
Thank you.
Aren't I better looking than the groom?
And you're dating Ja Young with that face?
Next, is a special song for the bride and groom.
Come on.
If you want, I will perform anywhere
Funny guys are in trend
A real man must know how to make a woman happy
He must play together
And know how to have fun
This is my debut performance to become a celebrity for you
Comedy, action, melodrama
Choose what you like
The shoot begins now
Let's film a movie
It ends with a kiss, just so you know
I'll become a celebrity for you
I will entertain you
I will act and sing
I will make you laugh
I'll become a celebrity for you
I will make you laugh for the rest of your life
My heart
Will never change
Who's making you sad?
You look pretty even when you cry
She starts laughing
With my talent
I'll put together a fun show, show, show
When you're down, just let me know, know, know
When you want to have fun, put on some dance music
When you want to get in the mood, belt out a ballad
When you want a beat, throw down some hip-hop
When you want to soar high, rock and roll
I'll become a celebrity for you
I will entertain you
I will act and sing
I will make you laugh
- Everyone, sing along! - I'll become a celebrity for you
I will make you laugh for the rest of your life
My heart
Will never change
Are you ready?
I'll become a celebrity for you
I am
A dance singer
Bride and groom. Exit.
Uncle Hwa Shin, you're so cool!
Go out with me.
Sure.
This is our day one.
Murder resulting from noise complaints.
It isn't new, but it is more sad...
because it was due to a misunderstanding.
One grade school had students write apologies to their neighbours.
The adults should learn from them.
- With that... - How nice would it be...
if the world was that beautiful?
However, the real-life pain that people suffer is much worse.
I've lived longer in this world,
and what changes the world is not a sledge hammer or a subwoofer.
It may be a single handwritten letter.
This concludes the news.
A handwritten letter is nice, but we should think of a real solution.
So what do you think...
- is the solution? - Those punks.
Na Ri, let's start the rehearsal.
(10 years later)
Na Ri, let's start. Cue.
Hold on. Wait.
Why are you sucking on that?
Did you give him his milk?
I told you to dress him warmly.
Do you only see the baby?
Are you jealous of the baby?
Finally, today, on Christmas Eve of year 2056,
we finally have the best weather in a month.
Everyone walks around with an oxygen tank,
but because I always did my exercise a hula hoop,
I was fine with just a mask.
Outings may become more difficult from now on,
so I think I should have some instant noodles...
by the Han River tonight with my husband.
You should all exercise regularly...
and be healthy.
This is Pyo Na Ri.
What's that?
Good job today.
Why did you want to come here?
We didn't do a wedding shoot. Let's use this instead.
I'm so tired.
I'll never get married again because it's too tiring.
Even if you're tired,
you can do it again.
Get married again if I die young.
My cancer may relapse within five years.
Then you can forget me and get married again to another guy...
even if it's tiring.
Sit down.
Did you bring me here to say that?
You never know with life.
What?
Death, too.
Whatever the case,
I will be stuck to you like an octopus until I die.
Even if I act like an annoying octopus,
don't use sesame oil to get me off of you...
or use salt to make me faint, okay?
I'll see about that.
I like that attitude.
May I ask you something?
What is it?
You grew to like me because you were jealous of Jung Won, right?
If he didn't like me,
you...
probably would've never noticed me, just like before.
- I don't know. - You don't know again?
Even when I was in the same hospital room as you,
I never even dreamed of marrying you.
- Me neither. - Am I crazy?
I wouldn't have set you up with Jung Won if I had.
- Right. - When I was in Thailand,
I did think of you at times.
Oh, my gosh.
Why are you so shocked?
Why?
You didn't think of anyone else, but you thought of me?
I don't know.
Were you lonely?
Did you wish I'd come to Thailand?
I don't know.
Why don't you know anything?
Let's just leave it at that.
You know everything. You're always showing off.
It's because there's so much I don't know, that I'm here.
There's so much that I don't know,
that I said I'll be an octopus by your side.
Is that how it works?
I...
may have been...
destined to go to the mud flat...
and act like a total fool for you.
The fortune teller said you will be the subject of my curiosity forever.
"The subject of my curiosity forever". I like that.
There isn't much to me.
That's what you think.
I will be curious about you...
- and love you forever. - Okay.
I will be curious about you and live with you forever.
- Okay. - But just don't drive me crazy.
(Being more jealous means you love the other person more.)
(One day in 2012...)
(4 years ago)
Mr Lee.
(Kong Hyo Jin)
(Cho Jung Seok)
That concludes Jealousy Incarnate.
- I am Pyo Na Ri. - And I am Lee Hwa Shin.
- Have a good night. - No, do not have a good night.
It's boring if it's always a good night.
Have a hot and passionate night tonight.
Thank you for watching.
I did not say goodbye.
Thank you.
We will be more cruel, cold and...
- Stop it. - And...
- I will stop. - Thank you.
I am truly sad.
I would like to sit here longer and keep talking.
How long will you go on?
How long...
may I...
(Thank you for watching Jealousy Incarnate.)