(EPISODE 3)
What a sight.
What did Mr Oh say?
(SBC OPEN RECRUITMENT APPLICATION)
I'm leaving. Do better tomorrow.
Do you realise...
how much you made my heart... My heart was racing...
while you were doing the weather because I feared you'd mess up.
I was so scared that you'd make a mistake.
What's wrong with you?
Who said you could drink before going on air?
Why do you make my heart race?
Why do you make my heart flutter?
I'm really not interested in your chest any more.
Don't worry.
That was my final broadcast.
Mr Ko!
Hello.
How do I look? Does it look good?
Thank you for bringing it yourself.
Do you like the outfit? Mr Ko is a fan of yours.
No matter how busy he is, he makes sure to watch your news.
Fan? Whatever.
You need to do the news,
so I'll let you go.
Why don't you watch me, since you're here anyway?
You've never seen the newsroom, have you?
No, I...
That's why he's here.
The outfit was an excuse.
This is the first time you saw each other since the blind date.
I wouldn't have been fired if I were only wearing that outfit.
(NEWSROOM DIRECTOR)
Did you fire Na Ri?
- Yes.
- Why?
- Yes. Why?
Hello.
- Two bottles of beer, please.
- Okay.
Have you changed in the three years that I was away?
You always loved the reporter...
responsible for the highest ratings...
among the 30 segments and carried them on your back,
showing unabashedly just how much you cared about ratings.
How could you fire her, rather than award her?
Should I carry you, too?
What are you talking about?
What is this?
(VIEWERSHIP BY MINUTE)
What?
Weather isn't the news.
Then why is it on during the news?
He only carries reporters, and she isn't one.
She doesn't read the news someone else writes, like a parrot.
She researches the weather herself, which changes daily...
and writes her own article...
and takes full responsibility for the weather.
If a weather forecaster isn't a weather specialist reporter,
what is she? An announcer? Then why is she a part of the newsroom?
(COMPLAINER)
I was fired anyway. Who cares about a fan?
May I join you?
Wait a second.
That seat isn't yours.
It's vacant anyway. Let me sit here.
There are plenty of vacant seats. Look, there's one there and there.
Look.
How many weather forecasters are you a fan of?
Which announcers are you a fan of?
Or are you a fan of every woman on TV?
- Is that wrong?
- Of course, it's wrong.
Isn't it wrong?
Is it okay?
I guess it's okay.
I don't think I did anything wrong to you today.
Why are you arguing with me whether or not it's wrong?
You're right.
Please...
sponsor me with your clothes.
Forget it, if you don't want to.
I'm a businessman,
so I don't take losses unless it's for a friend or girlfriend.
If I sponsor you, what will you do for me?
- Only a friend or girlfriend?
- Yes.
A friend or girlfriend.
Then I'll just become a friend or girlfriend.
I guess you don't need any more friends or girlfriends, right?
Right.
I'm sorry.
Because I...
always need friends and boyfriend.
You looked like you were passing by. You may go.
Will you be okay? You look like you drank a lot.
Yes.
You did well today.
There's no way.
(INTENSIVE CARE UNIT)
She hasn't eaten all day.
What if she faints?
She isn't sleeping either. Her light is on all night.
She stands by her window, looking out like a ghost.
She's asleep.
Kids!
Let's go!
Hello everyone.
We will now begin Newsleader...
for the last Friday of the month.
The first item.
You don't know where Ppal Gang lives, do you?
With 8th party congress soon to be held, it has been confirmed...
that North Korea launched another missile last night.
Do you know?
Are you meeting her alone or something?
They fired two, but both failed,
hurting their image.
Are you?
When you married my husband,
you handed me an invitation yourself. Do you remember?
But how could the ex-wife...
come to the wedding?
I gave a gift, too.
I gave 10,000 dollars. Don't say you don't remember.
How frightened do you think I was, as the bride,
when my husband's ex-wife...
gave 10,000 dollars as a wedding gift?
Do you think I gave 10,000 dollars...
because I liked you or Lee Joong Shin...
who was getting married in six months?
It was so that you wouldn't be cheap toward my daughter, Ppal Gang.
You used that to buy yourself a designer bag instead, didn't you?
Yes. How did you know?
I used the gift money from a snake...
to buy a bag made of an eel and I still carry it.
- Stop pretending to be a mum...
- Also,
I fed and clothed Ppal Gang...
worth much more than 10,000 dollars using my own money.
Who's the mum? The woman who gives money to the stepmum...
or me, who cooked her three meals a day plus dessert for years,
going grocery shopping and packing her lunch every day?
I can't wait any longer. I'm going to find her and raise her myself.
I even have a room for her at my place.
You've never cooked in your life.
Will you take in a high school senior and starve her to death?
- Get out.
- I'm leaving.
Relax your eyes.
Hey!
Taxi.
Come on.
Gosh.
Taxi!
Hi. Shinwol 2-dong, please.
Driver...
Please go to the intersection at the entrance to Shinwol 2-dong.
All right, to Shinwol-dong.
It was so hard to catch a taxi today.
Do you think it's because it's a Friday?
If it weren't for you,
I'd have stayed on the curb all night.
I was there for over 30 minutes.
Thank you so much.
I suddenly feel the alcohol hitting me. This is killing me.
Excuse me.
I feel nauseous. Could you please drive carefully?
I might throw up.
Excuse me.
You don't want to get in an accident.
You'll end up on the news.
Please.
I'm really going to throw up.
Look.
If you throw up here, you have to pay a penalty of 150 dollars.
I have to clean the dirty car,
and I won't be able to work for a day because of the smell.
Especially on a Friday like today,
150 dollars isn't enough.
Why are you trying to scare me?
This isn't a taxi.
Why you...
Are you sobering up from the walk?
Did you get in my car knowing it wasn't a taxi?
You wouldn't have given me a ride if I asked you to take me home.
Mr Lee.
Why do you think men never offer to take me home...
before I ask them to?
I always have to ask them to be my friend or boyfriend.
Why is my life so pathetic?
Where do you live?
It's over there. We're almost there.
I don't know how to thank you.
I've never had a taxi driver walk me home.
You're lucky a taxi driver is walking you home.
Mr Lee. Aren't you going to ask whom I drank with?
No, I'm not curious.
You're never curious about anything about me.
What are you even wearing?
Gosh. I don't believe this.
Here.
I'll carry her. She's heavy.
Make sure to move our car...
if the cars in front of the restaurant pull out.
Okay.
Na Ri?
I've never seen her with a man.
What's that? Is she drunk?
Na Ri looked totally sexy when she was doing the weather today.
Don't talk like that about Na Ri.
Stop talking about her and let's go.
Hey. Are you out of your mind? Where are you going?
Leave them alone and let's go.
You carry Ppal Gang.
I'd like to see the face of the guy...
that makes a girl drink when he's sober.
What's wrong with all of you?
Let Na Ri go on dates.
Here.
What am I supposed to do from tomorrow?
Go on blind dates.
Go on blind dates and get married.
What?
Do you think I'm being mean?
You should find someone better than me and rub it in.
Someone better than you?
Could that happen to someone who just got fired...
and lives on that rooftop?
Even you were out of my league.
Fine, I'd like to meet someone way better than you...
and love him with all my heart even if it doesn't work out.
You reveal your true self when you're drunk.
Is this it?
Yes.
Go in.
Okay.
Oh, right.
Why did you call me earlier?
I pressed the wrong button.
Why would I call you?
You wouldn't.
- Yes.
- Of course.
I guess this is it.
I guess so.
Bye.
(CORRECTION! MY DAD IS NOT A SWINDLER.)
Ppal Gang, stop this and let's leave.
Oh, no.
- Mother, Ppal Gang.
- Ppal Gang.
Do you think...
that low life would blink an eye if you stand here like this?
I don't think of him as my son any more.
He isn't your uncle. Or your brother-in-law.
Let's take Ppal Gang and leave. Come on, let's leave.
- Wait.
- What do you think you're doing?
Ppal Gang.
You're no better than a dog.
Come with Mum. Let's go.
Let's go.
- Come on, let's go.
- Ppal Gang.
(PYO NA RI)
Hi.
- What?
- Do you have anything to tell me?
Should I quit work and do something else?
Weren't you planning...
to prepare for the announcer test while being a weather forecaster?
Don't quit, since you never know.
I like that you're a weather forecaster.
I'm proud of you.
What are you proud of?
Do you really want to be an announcer?
Yes, I do.
Do you know why the strap...
of my name tag is red?
Announcers have blue straps.
What are you saying?
You never know when weather forecasters will get fired.
Announcers are always safe with the blue strap.
They're full-time employees.
Only the full-time employees have blue straps.
I don't know if it's because I have a red strap,
but I'm not curious about what kind of people...
those at the broadcasting station are.
I only see the colour of their straps.
Do you know how important it is to find the right line?
I studied at academies,
was trained at an announcer institution for two years,
failed the announcer test twice...
and barely became a weather forecaster.
It's been four years.
I don't know what I can do better than now...
or what I like.
My dream is to at least became an announcer...
and a full-time employee.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
I'll go home now. Finish up.
- Yes, Sir.
- See you.
Guys, take good care of Ppal Gang.
Here.
Aren't you going to eat anything?
Stop making a fuss about your dad being sick.
I can't stand it any longer.
Can you help me with something?
If you will, I'll eat.
Please sit down.
I was expecting a male doctor.
You've been transferred here by our orthopaedist.
Yes.
Your name is Geum Suk Ho. Obviously I was expecting a male doctor.
Do you know our orthopaedist?
- No.
- Because you're a male patient,
we decided to see you as soon as we could.
Isn't it too early to call me a patient?
We'll let you know the test result as soon as we can.
Well...
Would you prefer a male doctor?
Take a look.
Dr Choi is available in two months.
Would you like to come back then?
Fine.
Why are you...
Please keep it short.
Please change in the dressing room.
Show him the way.
Please come this way.
(DRESSING ROOM)
Is she in?
She forgot these.
A friend of mine was diagnosed with late-stage breast cancer.
It spreads so fast.
Gosh.
I see a nodule.
It's this white part.
We'll do a biopsy.
- Sorry?
- Please come this way.
Stand here.
Hold the machine.
Here, too.
Stand closer to it.
Stand closer.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
I'll do it.
Go ahead.
- Should I get closer?
- A bit closer.
It'll hurt a little.
The more it hurts, the firmer your chest is.
It means your body is young.
Hang in there.
It's for an accurate result.
Here we go.
A little bit more.
Hold on.
It's nothing compared to giving birth.
Keep breathing.
How could I breathe?
Hold your breath.
Did he get a check-up?
- I guess.
- Goodness.
Why is he here?
- He probably got a check-up.
- Probably.
Oh my.
What?
What is it?
Just.
I have to go on air.
My goodness.
I just thought of you.
I guess you don't need any more friends or girlfriends, right?
Right.
I'm sorry.
Because I always need friends and boyfriend.
It doesn't say it's an overseas call.
Are you in Korea?
I won't go easy on you.
Where are you?
There you are.
Okay.
Gosh.
- One more game?
- One more game.
I'll be more serious this time.
- I took out a new toothbrush.
- Okay.
The toner on the left side is better.
Do you want to sleep here?
I should go home.
You can sleep here.
It's been a long time. You haven't started working yet.
How did you know...
Stop playing hard to get.
Don't go anywhere from now on. I was bored to death.
Have you found any girl?
- Girl?
- Yes.
Do you remember Soo Young? She's getting married.
The girl who used to like me.
- Do you mean Oh Soo Young?
- Yes.
She didn't like you.
She followed me around everywhere.
You're kidding me.
My first kiss was with her.
What's that face?
What's up with her?
Was she seeing both of us?
What a brave girl!
She treated us...
like we were a half-and-half fried chicken set.
- Who would be the one with sauce?
- You, of course.
You're covered with money.
What would you be, then?
I'd be the plain fried chicken that's tasty as it is.
That's absurd.
Do you think she liked each of us as much as the other?
Should we ask her on her wedding day?
At her wedding?
"Did you like each of us as much as the other?"
"Was I the chicken with sauce?"
"I want to be the smoked chicken..."
"with no fat."
Do you really have to go home?
You're so stubborn.
Jung Won.
What?
My...
chest...
What about it?
Never mind.
- I'll get going.
- What is it?
Go in.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(YOU HAVE AN APPOINTMENT WITH DR GEUM SUK HO AT 11AM.)
Na Ri, you have a doctor's appointment today.
All right.
Hello.
You said you'd give me a personal weather forecast for a week.
Did you forget already?
- What?
- I'm not forcing you.
(COMPLAINER)
Oh, yes.
The thing is...
that I got fired and...
I look forward to it.
Wait a second. Let me wake up first.
Give me a minute.
Would it be okay if I washed my face first?
It's not like I can see your face.
Yes, of course. Okay, just give me a second.
You should shake off your hangover.
Thank you.
Okay.
Oh, yes.
Where do you live?
Cheongdam-dong, Seoul.
Okay, where are you going today?
That depends on what you say.
Oh, you must be planning to go on a date outside of Seoul.
Maybe.
All right, let's see.
It isn't raining, nor humid...
and the wind is breezy.
I think you could go anywhere in Korea today.
Anywhere.
Is that it?
There won't be any clouds in the sky tonight,
so you could go star gazing.
Is that it?
Yes, that's it.
- Then I'll have to go out at night.
- No, you don't.
You have to leave in the afternoon...
and go on a nice drive...
to find a nice place to see stars.
Okay, then let's meet at three.
All right.
What?
What are you doing?
Forget about the stars. Let's get coffee at three.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
I don't want to. My schedule is packed with things to do.
- You said you were lonely.
- What?
When did I say that? Are you trying to be funny?
What was that?
She said she always needs friends or boyfriend.
Who was that?
The guy from last night?
This is a voice I know from somewhere.
I asked you who it is!
I heard that there's a man who hits on announcers...
and weather forecasters pretending to be a viewer.
This is a weird guy. He asked if I'm lonely.
I thought he was a fan, but he's very weird.
Lonely? Isn't he a pervert?
- A pervert?
- I'm so upset.
- What's wrong with him?
- I don't know.
What's with him?
He's weird. He should be happy a guy is hitting on his sister.
We chose a few outfits you asked that are same as the announcers'.
Is five enough?
No, she's too busy to come.
(LUMPS IN YOUR CHEST)
Let's see.
This is Seoul District Court.
I'm Kim Min Chul, from the advanced investigation unit of the court.
You're working hard early in the morning.
So?
Do you know a Kim Jung Ho, who was arrested yesterday?
There are 200 people or so that had their names used illegally.
You're getting smart when voice phishing nowadays.
Your Korean is exceptional.
You sound like an announcer!
He worked at Gonghyup...
and two bank accounts under your name were found.
They were for two different banks.
They were used for fraud...
and the victims have sued you.
Really?
The account for Gonghyup...
I wasn't in Korea for three years and haven't used it for long.
What should I do?
Yes, what?
All right.
Yes, it works. I'm logged in.
What should I do now?
I already got a check up. It was nothing.
- Still...
- They never found anything.
Family members should go to the hospital together.
Bum, you have to get shots when you go to the hospital.
- It's this big.
- You're lying.
I'm not sick.
What are you talking about? You have constipation.
You need a huge shot to go to the bathroom.
- Mum...
- That isn't true.
You aren't going to go, are you? Let's go to the hospital.
You're going to get a shot on your behind.
- Mum...
- It's okay.
- See you later!
Na Ri!
You old lady.
I knew you'd use the same number.
Stand by and go.
Hello everyone.
- This is SBC news.
- All right, cut!
In the United States,
- people are making efforts to...
- I told her not to look so vague.
- Let's go for naengmyeon today.
- That sounds good.
Number one, stand by.
- And go. Wait.
- Are you kidding me?
- What do you think you're doing?
- Come on now.
Everyone is complaining.
VCR, start!
You always do that.
You tell the 1st camera to get ready and start the 2nd camera.
You tell the 2nd to get ready and start the 3rd camera.
Would you be happy if someone barged into your bathroom stall?
I'm just trying to make everyone...
stay awake when they're at work.
You ask for a beating.
Who nods off during a shoot except you?
- Director.
- Oh my.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to buy you naengmyeon.
Did he hear everything?
You always liked naengmyeon.
- I don't want you to buy lunch.
- But I do.
Stand by and cut!
Should I cut it for you?
Look.
Put the scissors down.
Say whatever is on your mind, pay and leave.
When I come back to work,
I'll audition for the anchor position.
For the main anchor of the nine o'clock news?
I heard we need a new anchor for the nine o'clock news.
You'll have to fight against your sister-in-law.
I know my sister-in-law...
I mean Reporter Gye...
I know she wants the job. Tell her to go for it.
I need competitors and people to make me look good.
The better my competitors are, the better I'll look.
How are you going to beat Reporter Gye?
She's better than most men.
Be quiet and eat your food.
Everything he said is right.
Is that all you have to say?
I won't ask for your help.
Just don't be a hindrance.
That's what I wanted to ask for.
Seriously?
I heard they have to hand in their medical reports now.
They should've done that earlier.
Anchors that sit in the same seat every day should be healthy.
- It's a promise with the viewers.
- You're right.
At the last newsroom athletic meet,
I was up against Gye Sung Sook.
And I lost.
I lost, too.
Do we have to submit our medical reports?
(TAEYANG HOSPITAL)
Hello.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
You need surgery.
Doctor.
Here.
The nodules and calcification...
haven't gotten worse.
We just need to keep an eye on them.
The problem is this.
There's a lump that seems new.
Do I have cancer?
It's...
not cancer.
Are you happy?
I'm so relieved it's not cancer.
Although the test came out positive,
it might develop into something serious.
We should get rid of it through surgery.
After the surgery, my breast will be even smaller, right?
Is it on the right side or the left side?
Will one breast be bigger than the other?
When others are putting things into their breasts,
I'm taking something out.
Every gram of my breast means so much.
I can't lose anything.
What are you talking about?
You were so happy a moment ago.
Do I need a general anaesthetic?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
It's big surgery, then.
(BALANCE INFORMATION)
Please take your card.
I hope it starts pouring.
Now that I lost my job, I need more and more money.
You have cancer.
It's breast cancer.
You're not the first one.
It has happened...
to about 100 men in Korea so far.
That definitely cheers me up.
Mr Lee.
Where are you going?
Do you expect me to believe that?
Do you? Seriously? I'm a man...
Why are you doing this to me?
It's better to have surgery as soon as you can.
You're young.
Sit down.
It's stage-one cancer.
We'll have to open it up to be sure,
but it doesn't seem so serious.
Because it's breast cancer?
Men can have breast cancer, too.
It doesn't mean that it's mutation...
or it's harder to cure.
You're just the same as female patients.
From the symptoms to the test, surgery and treatment,
you'll go through everything the female patients do.
It won't be any harder.
Please sit down.
You'll be fine after the surgery.
Look at this.
I can't have cancer now.
There's no right time for cancer.
I have an audition in a month.
An audition?
Please make me normal by then.
Sit down, then.
No one should know about it.
What do you mean, "no one"?
No one at all.
Medical staff are...
not supposed to reveal patients' secrets.
It'll be kept confidential.
You don't have to worry about that.
Make sure you get some additional check-ups...
before you leave.
Let's say this is...
your chest.
This is your areola,
which you know as your nipple.
Why do I have breast cancer, of all cancer?
Men can have breast cancer, too.
I see.
All right.
We don't know for sure now,
but you're at an early stage.
You can either get rid of just the cancer...
or cut off your whole chest.
You have to...
make a choice before the surgery.
Why would you cut off my whole chest?
How would I live without my chest?
How would I swim?
If half of my chest is gone when I wear a shirt,
how would it look?
Can I even get married?
Don't you care because I'm a man? Men's chest is important, too.
If you only get rid of the cancer,
the cancer might come back.
You'll have to receive radiation treatment...
for 10 minutes every day for 6 weeks.
How can I do that for six weeks?
Gosh.
What do you think?
What can I do?
I can't live with only half of my chest.
Please remove only the cancer.
- All right.
- Will there be any scars left?
It'll leave a bit of scars.
Please pay as much attention...
as you do to female patients.
Is there any way to leave no scars?
It'll look awful to have scars on your chest.
You can't help it.
They'll fade eventually.
Wait.
Look.
Since the areola is darker than the other part,
if you cut...
around the areola, the scars won't be as visible.
Wouldn't it be possible for women not to notice?
I see.
I'll do my best.
It shouldn't be visible.
Do you have anything else to say?
Please do a good job so that it looks normal.
You have cancer.
It's breast cancer.
Here's the surgery schedule.
(INTENSIVE CARE UNIT)
Pupillary reflex is observed, and he's breathing on his own.
His condition is a lot better now.
I'll play your favourite song.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
("PEOPLE ARE MORE BEAUTIFUL THAN FLOWERS")
Mum.
One, two, three.
Ppal Gang, did you see your dad?
Yes, I'll come back tomorrow.
- Please take good care of my dad.
- Sure.
(TAEYANG HOSPITAL)
Hello.
Is no one here?
Can I watch TV?
The two cholera patients in Korea...
are infected with the same kind of bacteria...
which is the El Tor type.
Can I raise the volume a little?
The symptoms of cholera by El Tor type...
Please let me know if it's too loud.
The classical type involves severe diarrhoea.
As the two patients were infected by different kinds of food,
it is not likely that it's a mass infection.
Water and food must be...
The station seems to be just fine without me.
I thought it'd shut down or something.
There were few more patients with same symptoms...
What should I watch?
Keep it there.
Mr Lee?
How can I share a ward with a man?
He's a man to me.
I'll leave. I'd just die in the worst case.
Do you have breast cancer of all cancer?
I want to see her in this to find out how I feel about her.
If you don't make it this time, there's no second chance.
Na Joo Hee can do this.
Go, Pyo Na Ri.
Can I kiss you?