[EPISODE 4]
Perfect.
You think I'll just do nothing
if you don't tell me?
Speed dial.
Her son or granddaughter should be one.
911?
That old lady.
I guess she wants to live.
[MY LIFELINE]
My lifeline?
It would be nice if it's Red.
Yes, we sell black bean noodles
tastier than any pasta.
We deliver 24 hours a day.
This is Jinjjaru.
Jinjjaru?
Yes, Jinjjaru.
Yes, what would you like to order?
She had the strength to
chase away two daughters-in-law.
She should be eating and living well!
She's living the typical life
of a single old lady.
What is number three, then?
[MONEY LENDERS]
Money lenders?
I had no idea this is how
Red has been living.
I should have looked for her earlier.
You call yourself a mother? Do you?
What's this?
Rak Pasta?
This is Rak Pasta.
Is... is there a student named Red there?
Who is this?
Do you know her?
I'm Red's mom.
Why am I acting like a burglar?
I'm only trying to find my own daughter!
You know Red, right?
My Red? You know Lee Red?
Don't move an inch and wait there.
I'll be right there.
Don't move, okay? Please.
Hey. Is Red upstairs?
The kids are at school.
Oh.
Excuse...
Did you just follow me?
What's wrong with following a person
who broke into a house?
Who is the person that called me?
Where is my Red?
Tell me where Red is. I'm her mom.
No! I'm Red's mom.
You can speak to me about it.
Who was the first?
I was first and she was second.
I wasn't second. He re-married.
So, you are Red's real mother?
Real? Are you saying that I'm a fake?
The only person Red calls "Mom" is me.
She calls that person "Ma'am"!
I didn't really know that.
So, you're her real mother?
What are you talking about!
I was the one in pain
and giving birth to her.
I was in labor for over 10 hours.
Then I had to get a
C-section to have her.
Should I show you my stomach?
Oh my!
Let go. What are you doing?
Have the two of you had breakfast?
- What are you doing?
- What is this?
Would you like to have brunch with me?
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
Let's all just hold one another.
Let's all just hold
one another with love.
Why don't we go somewhere and talk?
Chef was hugging those women?
[LEE HWA SHIN]
I told them not to do this.
Seriously, I told them
to take care of this.
Everyone will find out
about this at this rate!
Lee Hwa Shin.
When will a private room be available?
Also, I told you already.
I'm fine if you call me "Patient,"
"Hey, Patient," "Patient Punk," whatever.
Just don't call me by my name.
Why do you make me repeat myself?
Also, the other patients cannot find out
that I'm admitted for breast cancer.
It has to be a secret that a male has
been admitted into this department, okay?
Yes.
I'm going to take your blood pressure.
Take your jacket off.
We'll move you into a private room
once it becomes available.
When will a private room
become available?
I asked so many times.
Your blood pressure is
very high right now.
I'll come back later to do it again.
Who will be staying next to me?
A grandmother? An old lady?
- Please get changed.
- A young lady?
You need to take off your underwear too.
Is she pretty?
I mean...
Calm down and rest.
I'll come back to
take your blood pressure.
Please take care of my requests.
Those are Mom's clothes.
Yeah, do I look pretty?
Not as pretty as Mom.
Of course not.
Why are you suddenly
wearing Mom's clothes?
I feel like Mom is with me,
like I'm not alone.
I feel very strong and not scared.
Aren't you going on a business trip?
I'll call you.
Can you wear that during a broadcast?
He did that?
How expensive could pasta be
that he couldn't pay off that tab?
Yes, well...
He and Red were regular customers
and they built up quite the tab.
You said you were Red's mom.
I thought you were coming to pay it.
You said you'd come,
so I didn't say anything.
How much is it?
It really isn't much.
No, I don't need you to pay.
Even so, I'm sorry.
Do you happen to have their contact info?
They usually just drop by.
I don't know their contact info.
You should take it back.
They might come back though.
If they don't have money then,
you can use this to feed them lots.
No, I don't mind doing it for free.
Please take it back.
If they ever happen to contact you,
please call this number.
No... you can call here.
I have to run my restaurant now.
I should get going.
- Excuse me.
- Excuse me!
Please do this for me.
Please contact me... only me.
Call me, please.
I'll be waiting for your call.
Yes, okay...
Hello?
Do you mind if I watch some TV?
Can I turn the volume up?
Let me know if the volume is too loud.
This voice... Pyo Na Ri?
The station isn't in ruins
even though I'm gone.
Here I thought they'd
be ruined without me.
What should I watch?
Don't change the channel.
Reporter?
Let's watch what we were watching.
Eating snacks on
your rooftop is the best.
Yeah, I wish Na Ri would go on
business trips all the time.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
You're acting more like yourself, Red.
I feel much better to see that
you have your appetite back.
I think my dad is going
to get better soon.
His face looks so much more relaxed.
Yeah, we thought so too.
- Right, Chi Yeol?
- Yeah.
Chi Yeol, clean this up.
Nice rhymes.
I'm so full!
- Go home and sleep.
- No.
You think she'd want to go home
to a dark place alone?
You should lie down too.
- Where are you going?
- Pillow.
Huh?
It's not warm out anymore.
You'll catch a cold.
Doctor!
How can I share a room with a man?
I wouldn't do this if there were
empty beds in any other department.
He's just a patient, not a man.
What man? He's a patient.
How is he not a man?
Why are you doing this to me?
A male patient is man. A man is a man.
If a man is not a man,
then what is he?
What is this, anyway?
It's like a prison.
This is seriously like
a prison or something.
The nurse says there are no rooms,
so I want to be discharged.
I'm sorry.
But I heard you worked together,
so I thought you'd be okay with him.
You could tell me that all the men
in the world are just patients
but he will always be a man to me.
When I first started work, he was
the only one I thought of as a man.
I never thought of anyone else as a man.
- Is he your boyfriend?
- What?
We didn't know you liked him.
He's not my boyfriend!
I don't like him... anymore.
Doctor.
I will leave.
You can book me in for another time.
It won't be for a long time.
- At worst, I'll just die.
- What?
You've never even
dated a man, have you?
I'm the only person
you've thought of as a man?
I said so already earlier,
but I don't like you anymore.
I don't care if I get dumped.
I'm going to meet someone better than you
and have a passionate relationship.
I'm sure I told you that.
Why would you say you
don't care if you get dumped?
Why are you even here when you're a guy?
Isn't this what you wanted?
Do you have breast cancer too?
I have breast cancer.
I don't have it...
What?
You're a woman and you don't have it.
I'm a man and I have breast cancer?
Is that true? You have breast...
I only wanted you to get it checked out.
I didn't think it'd
actually be breast cancer.
Even if there's a lump there
it usually turns out to be
benign and not cancer.
I must be getting punished.
What?
How could this happen to you?
Do you have to get chemotherapy?
You're not in the late stages, right?
It's in the early stage?
It is, right?
Why are you alone?
Are you really here alone?
Are you crazy? It's cancer!
When is your guardian coming?
When is your family coming?
You don't have family, Reporter?
What are you going to do?
How could a macho guy like you get
breast cancer and not something else?
Be quiet.
Could it possibly be an error?
Do men really get breast cancer?
Can you please shut up?
You have no idea how I feel.
The day the station finds out
being an anchor and
auditioning are over for me.
My competitors will tear me apart as if
they were waiting for it to happen.
They will make me out to be
some strange reporter.
The 9:00 p.m. news anchor
with breast cancer.
I don't want to the main topic
of some gossip papers.
Once it becomes known,
my career as a reporter is over.
I can't tell my family.
You just need to
keep quiet about it, okay?
Reporter, aren't you scared?
You're dead meat if anyone finds out.
I won't ever tell a soul.
I won't tell even if I get paid
100 million won.
Reporter, be strong.
You should tell someone if they
offer you 100 million won.
When will you ever make 100 million won?
The surgery will go well.
Go to sleep.
Our doctor is the best
when it comes to breast cancer.
Let's just sleep.
Yeah, we need sleep
to do well in surgery.
Okay, sleep.
Let's go to sleep.
Your surgery will go well.
Goodnight.
I will have a good night too.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
He's a chef?
Chef, chef, chef, chef...
Yes, saffron.
They sprayed on too much perfume.
I'm sorry.
I feel like this happened
because of what I said.
I'm sorry.
Don't look at me like you're
looking at a cancer patient.
I thought you were asleep.
You... don't see me
as man anymore, do you?
No, don't worry.
I don't see you as a man.
You're just a patient.
Will I be able to wake up
from the anesthesia tomorrow?
Will I be able to get married?
What?
Women wouldn't see a man
with breast cancer as manly.
As long as I keep quiet about it,
no one will know.
You shouldn't tell the woman you marry,
even on your first night after together.
It's not sexy or anything just because
a man reveals all his secrets.
It's not helpful at all.
Can you lie about that?
I ought to tell the truth to the person
who is going to be my wife.
You think so?
You had a one-sided crush on me
for three years.
After finding out about this,
even you don't see me as a man.
So, what kind of woman would?
Stop thinking bad thoughts and go to bed.
Would you be able to sleep
if you were me?
They won't know for certain if it's
stage one or two until they cut me open.
Will I need chemotherapy or not?
Has the lymph node changed or not?
They won't know for sure.
If it has, then they have to
remove this entire breast.
You only have to
remove a little, is that it?
Your breast will get a little smaller.
That's it, right?
It's not cancer, right?
Can I kiss you?
See, it's not working.
You don't even see me as a man anymore.
I'm not sexy.
I'm just a pitiful patient
in the bed next to you.
Honestly, it's just a man
and woman in a room together.
There are beds in here and
you don't even want to kiss me?
Am I even a man?
Do it.
I want to.
Really?
Yes, really.
You really want to?
I can't do it.
I was just asking to see.
I only needed to hear your answer.
I feel like a woman now that
I'm a patient with breast cancer.
I wanted to confirm if I'm still
a man who is sexy and can kiss.
I just needed to hear
that answer so that...
But you did want to kiss me, right?
I'm still sexy. That's enough for me.
Kiss another guy, one who likes you.
But you did want to kiss me, right?
I'm still sexy. That's enough for me.
Kiss another guy, one who likes you.
You might regret it tomorrow.
Kiss a guy who's healthy
and actually likes you.
[THIS MESSAGE HAS BEEN SAVED.]
What if I don't have it?
Are you all right?
That must've hurt a lot.
- Are you okay?
- Oh no.
[LEE HWA SHIN]
No, cut that.
If you cut that out,
it doesn't show that it was self-defense!
What are you saying? Are you crazy?
They were fighting.
It wasn't self-defense.
- Just cut it if I tell you to.
- No, I can't!
Are you crazy?
Hey!
The outfit Geum Soo Jung was wearing
on the news was worth 10 million won.
So expensive.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Here you go.
Who are you?
Sorry about before... the nosebleed.
Someone bumped into you here earlier.
That was me.
It's okay.
Women are supposed to pretend that
it wasn't them, Pi Na Ri.
It's actually not Pi...
He says I should pretend it wasn't me.
Gosh, why is it suddenly raining?
Hello. I have an interview to go to.
Thanks, Hwa Shin.
Work hard.
The 9 p.m. news would be nothing
without Lee Hwa Shin.
- Let's have a drink to that.
- Cheers.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the restroom.
Have a drink before you go.
Okay, fine.
Cheers!
Reporter, do you want to
sing a duet with me?
No, I'm going to sing alone.
Okay.
That was great!
I heard you had an arranged date today.
Pi Na Ri, why are getting angry at me?
Just because, okay? Just because.
- Pi Na Ri.
- Yes?
Your lanyard broke.
- Thank you.
- Hold on.
You want to use this?
- No.
- Why not?
Just because.
Lee Hwa Shin's blood pressure
has gone down, right?
Yes, it's back to normal.
Where did you go?
Your first surgery is tomorrow.
Let's go in and sleep.
Come on.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Whether we kiss or not is up to me.
It's not up to you.
You may think that I'm crazy.
It may have been a one-sided love,
but it was for over three years.
I think it's crazy to end it
without even holding your hand.
I haven't been able to end it because
I haven't done anything with you.
That's why I've still had feelings left.
I don't have any regrets anymore.
Also, you shouldn't play around
with a woman's heart like that.
- Earlier, I was...
- Yes.
I lost all sense of affection
for you back there.
Hey.
Now that I've done it, it's no big deal.
Hey...
Hey!
I have no lingering feelings
for you at all now.
Hello to all our viewers.
Fall is coming upon us.
This is Kim Jong Tae for your
Monday morning news.
My name is Park Jin.
Hey, get me Pyo Na Ri's number.
- Why?
- What do you mean why?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
You acted like you knew everything.
You're scared too, right?
Don't be nervous.
It won't help with the anesthesia.
It will be over
once you sleep for a while.
You'll have lopsided breasts.
You'll have lopsided ones too, Reporter.
We'll head in now.
This customer cannot pick up...
Why isn't she picking up all day long?
Didn't you fire her, Director?
If a person says they're sorry,
you can forgive them once.
What's wrong with your personality?
Director, do you think another station
has scouted her already?
What are you saying? It's been two days.
All the other newsroom desks must have
seen the ratings for this day too.
What are you going to do about
Pyo Na Ri's time slot today?
What do you mean?
We have to get Pyo Na Ri in there.
Call her quickly.
Who would scout her anyway?
She's probably sleeping in or something.
Don't worry.
Oh, she's on the phone.
Wait, you were calling her.
Bovie.
- Hold tight.
- Yes, Doctor.
- Get this biopsied right away.
- Okay.
I'm going to close up. Irrigation.
- Get the new items in the display.
- Okay.
What about my mother?
She will be arriving tomorrow.
She would like you
to come to the airport.
It seems that she's been talking to
Announcer Geum Soo Jung.
She's in a good mood.
It's pretty, isn't it?
It will suit her well.
- Yes.
- I don't need to be there today, right?
No.
I'll get the car ready.
But, Secretary Cha...
I want to give this outfit
to someone else.
You'll tattle on me
to my mother, won't you?
What other person?
- The weather forecaster.
- Weather?
It's not... possibly...
Head in the Clouds?
Are you cheating already?
Your mother is planning to look into
a wedding venue once she arrives.
Suppose it is cheating.
Suppose I happen to marry a girl
that my mother chooses for me.
Why am I acting like this?
I just want to see
that girl in this one time.
Then I want to decide if it's cheating,
compassion, sympathy, or just nosiness.
Can't I just figure out
how I really feel?
I was just throwing out the question.
You don't need to answer.
When he's being this honest,
I can't go tattle on him.
Patient, please wake up.
Reporter. Reporter!
I've lost all attachment for you.
Patient, are you awake?
Yes.
Your surgery is over.
You've made it through the hard part.
We'll move you into your room.
How did it go? Did it spread?
Do I need chemotherapy?
The doctor will tell you the details
once we move you back to your room.
Oh, it's over.
The doctor will talk to me.
You can have water in four hours.
We're going to take your blood pressure.
We'll give you some painkillers,
so one moment.
You will be in pain today once your
anesthesia starts to wear off.
If you press on this when you're in pain,
you will get more painkillers.
Don't hold it in when it hurts.
Just press it.
One, two, three.
Gosh, this girl!
You'll have no one doing it at this rate.
Why are you being so stupid?
Thank you. You're really helpful.
So, who is doing tonight's
7 p.m. weather?
Are they going to tell me to do
the 7 p.m. weather live too?
You have the 9 p.m. golden time.
Your greed knows no end.
Do the viewers have to watch you
consecutively at 7 and 9 p.m.?
I'm only saying this because
there isn't much time left.
Pyo Na Ri is gone now, so how come
they aren't assigning anyone new?
They wouldn't be scouting
anyone new, would they?
In that time?
Maybe they're not doing weather.
Why wouldn't they do weather!
I'm just saying.
Sit.
Why don't one of you volunteer
before we have a broadcast mishap?
Is there a volunteer?
- Me!
- Me, me!
Just don't get caught by
Announcer Geum Soo Jung.
Is she my wife or something?
We went on one arranged date.
Yes, but your parents had
already talked before you two met.
It's not even cheating.
You're just feeling sorry for her and
you want to give her nice clothes.
That's probably all it is.
The phone...
Your phone is ringing.
I don't care.
Aren't you going to pick up?
I'm so thirsty.
What the...
What are you doing acting
so rude to your work boss?
Don't you know that you can't drink water
right after being under anesthesia?
You can drink after four hours.
Why didn't you come with a guardian?
You're being such a pain.
Seriously, I'm so sick.
You're one to talk.
Why isn't this working?
Hey, get your phone.
Turn it off if you're
not going to pick up!
Just suck on this as hard as you can.
They say it's not good to leave the
anesthetic gas in our lungs, so hurry.
I know, I know. I know that too.
I'm in so much pain and it's noisy.
Did your surgery go well?
You probably wish I died.
Listening to you talk,
I guess it went very well.
I told you to get your phone.
I'm not expecting a call from anyone.
If you're not expecting a call,
would you have a hundred...
What is this? It's the director's number.
Do you think the news is time for you
to show off your looks?
Is the news broadcast meant
to help you find men to date?
Is a weather forecaster a fake announcer?
Is the news a place for you
to make an appearance
so you can be like celebrities?
Is the news...
You can do it...
what Pyo Na Ri was doing.
- Take that off.
- Excuse me?
Wear something else. What is this?
Is this the army?
She is disciplining them well.
Kye Sung Sook should've been born a man.
Right, girls?
You're right.
Why didn't you pick up your phone!
You were sleeping all day, weren't you?
Did you have fun playing for two days?
Get here right now.
What? Then, am I working again?
Do you know how many times I called?
Okay, forget it.
You won't get another chance
if you don't show up. Hurry!
[WEATHER DEPARTMENT]
Yes, sir. This is Pyo Na Ri from SBC.
What is the forecast for tonight?
A localized torrential rain?
Oh, really?
SBC Station, please.
Okay.
Yes.
Will the wind be stronger, or the rain?
Which areas will be in danger?
And the maximum expected rain?
Yes. Yes, I understand.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Senior, I sent you a picture.
Please show localized torrential rain
in the midwest.
Please put a big graphic
of wind and lightning.
Yes, we'll use the arrows.
Yes, I'll let you know the status.
Yes, yes.
I'm sorry. I'm on my way now.
Yes.
So, you are the weather girl.
You must've been visiting
someone in the hospital.
Well, no. That wasn't really it.
Yes.
I almost didn't see you.
Ah, here you go.
- No.
- What?
This is for the 7 p.m.
weather forecaster.
Deliver it to her.
Yes.
Then, where is mine?
You should have stopped her.
What is this?
What is so important about a broadcast?
Why would she run out on the day
she got her surgery? Why?
What if it hasn't healed and
the wound ends up bleeding?
I wanted her to get married
and receive love.
I was so careful about it
being even over 0.1 gram.
I was so careful.
I focused so hard to do that surgery.
She just ran out of her room
like this, that patient!
You should clap for him.
She thinks a doctors word
is just a big joke.
My words are like dog crap.
What is this?
This is how people in broadcast are.
Are they just fearless or stupid?
Maybe they just have no manners.
Do they think they have many lives?
They don't know how precious
their lives are.
You're right.
There's a private room open.
You can move there.
Even if the patient comes back,
don't accept her.
Move him into the private room.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Pyo Na Ri is not here yet, Director.
Listen to me. Use Na Joo Hee.
Don't worry.
You'll get good ratings with Na Joo Hee.
She's prettier and younger.
She's not cheap-looking
and she fits our news image.
Pyo Na Ri couldn't even imitate her.
Then, should we do that?
So, who is it?
Who are you going to go with?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Hey, you...
You should've delivered it properly.
They said she's the 7 p.m. weather girl.
She's not "Head in the Clouds"?
They switched?
Yeah, I can hear you. I can.
Make your decision, Director.
Stop rushing me.
Stop looking for Pyo Na Ri,
who was fired, and just decide already.
Is this Pyo Na Ri, who was fired,
the one you were waiting for?
Seoul, Gyeonggi, and Chungcheong...
The expected precipitation...
Oh, I'm so dizzy.
I wonder if she's going to
wear Mom's clothes today.
Do your mom's clothes fit Na Ri?
My sister looks prettier than anyone
in the world in those clothes.
You'll see.
I'm sorry I'm late!
Sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry, Director. I'm sorry.
Is she here? Is she, Director?
Pyo Na Ri's here?
Yes, she is.
I'm sorry, Director. I'm sorry.
Is this why you gave me all that alcohol?
This... isn't your spot anymore.
Do you think you can even do it?
Yes, I can do it.
Where are those clothes from?
Let's just say it is cheating.
I think I am cheating.
Be strong, Pyo Na Ri.
I don't want to go to a private room.
Why are they both standing there?
We have to start soon.
Okay, standby. News title.
Three, two, one, and cue.
Can you really do it?
I can do it.
Even if I die,
I'm going to die in this spot.
Be strong, Pyo Na Ri.
I think I am cheating.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I don't think I'll die of breast cancer.
I'm going to die of frustration
because of you.
Gosh, I don't know!
You really don't listen, do you?
No! No, you can't! No, no!
Are you really going to cheat like this?
No! I really don't know anymore!
Are you going to broadcast that
I have breast cancer?
I should've died
but I've committed a grave crime.
Does Hwa Shin know that you're sick too?
We can have a secret, right?
You know your friend, Reporter?
Does he have a girlfriend?