Subtitles by DramaFever
Episode 5
Hey!
Are you okay?
You were fired. Why are you here?
Ah, you're here to get your stuff.
Yeah, I suppose you should take it
when they tell you to.
Take that important butt pad with you.
Is there anything else?
I'll help you.
- Give me that.
- Hey, what are you doing?
You're not going on air, are you?
You're going to wear this
tacky thing and go on air?
Yes, I look good.
I'm only giving you this opportunity
for one reason.
You were under general anesthesia.
So you can't eat
until you've passed gas.
Okay.
It's a sign that your intestines are
active and the anesthesia has worn off.
If you feel the need to pass gas,
don't hold back and let it out.
Oh yes, are you canceling
the request for a private room?
Yes.
Three minutes until the VCR is done.
Director, we have
three minutes until weather.
Make a choice about
who you're going to use.
Let's just not do the weather.
No, do the weather. Do it.
Should we not do the weather
and just do the closing, Director?
Is he crazy? How can we not do it?
There is a torrential downpour tonight.
We have to warn people
so they can avoid injury.
How can we not do the weather?
Why is he taking it out on me? Seriously.
He has to choose one of the two.
He must be insane.
Why can't you decide?
Pyo Na Ri was fired.
Director Oh told me to do it.
Pyo Na Ri, would you please get out?
Wait.
Leave already.
I'll be getting my cue soon.
Are you crazy?
Director!
I don't know. Anyone, just leave.
Everyone, get ready!
What are you doing?
Get ready now! Hurry.
You should leave.
This is my living.
So please get out of here.
Director said "anyone" should get out.
What is this? What are they doing?
I need to make a living.
Please, you leave.
Why are you doing this, Joo Hee?
He said "anyone" should get out.
Am I just anyone?
- Why are you being like this?
- You got fired.
- Seriously.
- Stop it.
Where did it go?
President...
What did you drop?
What did you lose? That remote control?
Isn't it that CG remote? That clicker?
You can't control the
CG graphics without it. Wait!
You two can do rock, paper, scissors.
Decide now!
Who does rock, paper, scissors
in the newsroom?
Don't we need that clicker to
change the CG graphics?
Can you control the CG without it or not?
Director, you can't do it.
What do we do?
You can't do it. You can't! Find it now!
- Gosh, seriously!
- We don't have time.
We have 10 seconds.
It's almost time.
We're going to start.
I really don't know anymore.
Weather title... go.
- Get off.
- What do we do?
This is a broadcast accident.
- Na Joo Hee, step off.
- No, I don't want to.
Pyo Na Ri, step off now!
We can't have a broadcasting accident.
We can't have two.
I will come off.
Hey! Get off!
Mom.
Mom, please help me.
I had been saving it,
and I finally wore your dress.
What if today is my last day?
What if today isn't the beginning of
being an announcer, but the end?
I will be so sorry to you, Mom.
Na Ri.
The accident happened.
We'd better write an apology.
It's been a hot and humid summer,
but it's becoming a cool fall.
You can feel the
changing season, can't you?
It's the 16th of the
24 seasonal divisions of a year.
During this time of the year
temperatures will fall
below the dew point.
What was that?
It's the time of year
you'll find dew on the grass.
They say that if it rains in this season,
you're bound to have a rich harvest.
Currently, we haven't had
as much rain as we had last year.
We'll take a look at the rain forecast.
Forecaster Na Joo Hee?
Yes.
We're looking at rain clouds
forming to our west.
I don't think I'll die of breast cancer.
I'm going to die of frustration
because of you.
This is the first time
I've seen this on the news.
Two of them.
Thus, rain, lightning, and thunder
are expected all night.
Seoul and the Gyeonggi area
are expected to get 150 millimeters.
The surrounding rural areas will get a
maximum of 70 millimeters of rain.
Please be careful during this
torrential rainstorm.
Tomorrow morn...
Tomorrow morning,
the rain will have stopped.
But the commute to work
will still be dangerous.
However, the temperature
will rise during the day.
Seoul and Daejeon, 29 degrees Celsius.
Daegu and Gwangju, 31 degrees Celsius.
Busan and Jeju will reach
28 degrees Celsius.
As the high atmospheric system of
the North Pacific passes
we can assume this will be the last
of the hot weather.
Once...
Once this...
Once this heat wave subsides,
we will have clear fall weather.
That was the weather.
What the...
What was that?
Have you passed gas yet?
I asked you if you passed gas.
That gas is not
what's important right now.
That gas is what's
important for you right now.
Senior, this was a
broadcast accident, right?
Reporter.
You have no discipline.
You should leave if I told you to!
You refuse to listen.
You insist on being stubborn
and ruining the broadcast?
Is the 60 seconds of weather yours?
You think it belongs to you personally?
Even if it belonged to you originally,
even if it were yours
what do you the two of you
plan to do in a spot for one?
The two of you caused this mess.
Do you think the viewers will even
remember if it will rain or snow?
They'll have to watch another channel
for the weather, you little wenches!
I'm so sorry.
Director, I'm sorry.
I didn't think we'd both
end up standing up here.
It was my fault.
I was crazy.
I must have lost my mind.
I was being greedy.
I seriously lost my mind just before.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Can you even dare to say that?
Can those words even leave your mouth?
You'd better sew up that mouth of yours.
Do you think I'm going to
let the two of you speak again?
Wow, seriously...
I've seen people with a lot of guts,
but this is really something.
I've lived a long time
and this is really something else.
Yes, President.
No, I wouldn't call it
a broadcast accident.
Yes, about that... no, I didn't do that.
No, I didn't.
Oh, that person?
It was Reporter Kye who put her there.
She is standing next to me.
I'll put her on.
Yes, this is Kye Sung Sook.
Yes, I told Na Joo Hee to go on.
Director.
President, thank you for this outfit.
You can leave now, Secretary Cha.
I think we should also... wait.
What is it? Why? Hold on... what?
If you keep doing this...
President! Wait!
Why would she hit the girls?
- Yes?
- What happened there?
The girls really tried their best.
It was the director and Reporter Kye
who went back and forth and caused this.
Turn the light off in the newsroom.
Let Reporter Kye reflect on what she did.
Just shine a spotlight on her.
What did the
weather forecaster girls do wrong?
Having no power is their only crime.
What are you doing?
I told you to turn on a spotlight!
President.
President!
President, what is the point
you're making?
You keep repeating yourself and saying
the same thing over and over again.
Are you going to do this all night?
Weathercasters are part of
the news department too.
Weather is the last part of the news.
We were only trying to deliver the
weather with dignity and integrity.
And there was a slight error.
Since when is it necessary
to wear butt and bra pads
and have them wear short skirts
while they stand sideways?
To have an S-line body,
Seoul, Daejeon, Daegu, Busan.
When did that become the norm?
Because most viewers
of the news are male?
Because you're a male?
Gosh, I'm not finished speaking yet.
Please don't interrupt or say anything.
Please just listen!
If you keep interrupting me,
I have to keep repeating myself too.
It's going to be torture for you.
My point is that the weather
can be done by men and women.
Looks are not the priority.
The dignified attitude in which you
deliver the news is what's important.
Understand? Are you okay?
Hel...
Ah, I want to drink.
Ah, I want a man.
Ah, I want someone on my side.
I'll take you home right now.
You sponsored clothes for Na Joo Hee too?
You shouldn't talk to the director
on a day like today.
He will only be angry at you if you do.
What's with your bosses here?
Are you a fan of Na Joo Hee?
Don't think about anything on
a day like today and just sleep.
Stop changing the subject.
Then, why did you kick that
remote control to me?
Of all the things
I wanted to give to you
that remote is the
only thing that got to you.
Do you still need friends and lovers?
Pyo Na Ri, are you okay?
What's wrong with "Head in the Clouds"?
Are you okay?
- Should I call an ambulance?
- Get the car.
President, isn't this the bracelet
they give to patients at the hospital?
- Then, let's go there.
- Okay.
I'll carry her.
I told you to go get the car!
Yes!
Gosh, that girl.
She needs to get here soon.
Is she getting in trouble?
This customer is unable
to come to the phone...
Is the phone turned off?
What kind of sister always
makes her little brother worry?
Something is off.
Of course it is.
How much work is required for 60 seconds
that two people would share?
Are they going to
split the pay in half too?
Na Ri never said anything to you?
Do you know where Taeyang Hospital is?
Yes, it's the most nearby hospital.
I think it's her phone.
Are you awake?
Don't get up.
You should stay like this.
The anesthesia must be wearing off.
It could be your family.
Shouldn't you pick up?
Maybe it's Chi Yeol.
Hello?
Where are you?
Are you on your way now?
None of your business.
I told you to go on a date
and just get married, didn't I?
You went under anesthesia, got your
chest opened up, and had surgery.
You really don't listen, do you?
You just pulled that IV out
and ran out of here like that.
Then you go through that nonsense.
Now look at you.
It serves you right. It really does.
Get back to the hospital now!
Forget it! You stay put right there.
I'm going to send the
hospital's ambulance.
Hello?
Where did she go?
Why does he keep telling me to
go on a date and get married?
You need a job to go on an arranged date.
Who would want to be set up with me
when I'm about to be fired?
By the way, where are we going now?
Where is this?
The day the station finds out
being an anchor and
auditioning are over for me.
Once it becomes known,
my career as a reporter is over.
You just need to
keep quiet about it, okay?
No, I can't be here. No!
No, no! Go to a different hospital. No.
Oh no! No, you can't.
No, no!
Please come out.
No, no. I'll go to a
different hospital, not this one.
Just not this one.
We saw the bracelet on your wrist
and that's why we're here.
- Don't worry. Take her, Secretary Cha.
- Yes.
No, no. Wait a minute!
There's a better hospital over there.
I'll just go to that one, not this one.
No, we should definitely go to this one.
- No, no! I can't!
- Just get out, please.
No, I can go to any hospital
except this one. Please!
Your hand...
Hurry up and get in.
Pyo Na Ri...
No, I'm not getting out. Just get in.
I just can't go to this hospital.
Please get back in.
- Just let go of his leg.
- Hurry!
I'll be fine on my own now.
You can go now, okay?
This is the hospital you were admitted.
What's the problem?
Are you taking her to her room?
- No, no, no!
- Yes.
Take me to the ER. I need to go there.
I need to be seen immediately.
Calm down, okay? Stay calm.
- No, you can't.
- Secretary Cha.
Go press the elevator button.
I'm in pain. It hurts! Go to the ER!
- Calm down.
- No! You can't.
You can't! You can't!
I don't know anymore!
Why isn't she coming?
Are you in a lot of pain?
[Pyo Na Ri]
The doctor will be here soon.
Are you her guardian?
- Yes.
Why would the two of you be my guardians?
She brought people
from the station with her?
Can you both wait outside?
I'm her guardian, so can't I stay?
That girl did this on purpose.
Then, do you want to
change her into this?
- What?
- What? No.
- Let's wait outside.
- Okay.
Yes.
Let's get you up.
Be careful.
- Hey, are you crazy?
- Patient, are you crazy?
I knew this would happen.
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
You made a mess at work so now
you're going to live recklessly?
You're going start a rumor about my
breast cancer and do what, exactly?
You're going to broadcast it?
Is that it?
Don't you care about my life at all,
you awful wench?
Wow, I was a stupid fool.
I was stupid for trusting a woman.
Living recklessly?
Patient, you shouldn't get angry.
Your surgery wound could tear.
On purpose?
Wow... yes, you are right.
That broadcast accident
didn't satisfy my anger.
So I planned it and brought him.
He's the biggest gossip
at the entire station.
He won't even
tell the truth of the facts.
He loves to elaborate and lie.
He posts things on the work intranet.
He's also someone who would
leak things to our competitors.
Yes, I brought someone who lies
every time he opens his mouth.
I really am sorry.
I should have just died.
Instead, I did something
I deserve to die for.
I had my surgery and everything,
but I guess I'll die by your hands.
Yes, that's how it is.
I can't even go on air anymore.
It won't be so bad to die by your hands.
I did barely manage
to get life insurance.
- Yes, I did.
- Hey.
That man outside is someone
who can give me 100 million won.
It's very hard for me to
keep this mouth of mine shut.
What should I do, Reporter?
100 million won?
Yes, 100 million won.
Putting people in new clothes
is actually our expertise.
I came up here in such a rush.
Which department is this?
Is she very sick?
Are you really going to cheat like this?
Go and buy something to drink.
Don't stay here.
It's her you're cheating with, right?
But it's just a passing breeze.
Someone might overhear
and think I'm a playboy.
That's what I'm saying.
You've always been lazy with dating
and only ever liked your friends.
Exactly, that's what I'm saying.
I can't date girls who act like girls,
like Announcer Geum Soo Jung.
I'm already lazy.
I need a girl who is like a friend.
Oh, so that "Head in the Clouds"
is a girl who is like a friend?
Well, she's not a girly girl.
- Are you busy?
- No.
Aren't you going to buy drinks?
I will... I will buy some.
Buy something healthy.
I just don't know anymore.
Once your mother comes back,
I'm going to tell her everything.
Here you go.
You must like saffron.
Oh, yes.
I'll have this.
That must be why Red knew to order this.
My Red ordered the saffron pasta?
Yes.
Please enjoy your food.
Yes, Chef.
I'm the only person Red calls "Mom."
Excuse me.
If you don't want to eat alone,
should I sit down with you?
Yes, I would be very thankful if you did.
I almost always eat alone.
Eating alone makes the food taste bad.
I feel the same way.
I grow very tired of it.
No matter how good the food is
there is nothing as bad as food
that you have to eat alone.
- Are you alone?
- Yes.
- Have you already done it once?
- What?
Ah!
No, I have never been married.
- Why is that?
- Well...
Here you go.
What are you talking about?
I was the one in pain
and giving birth to her.
Are you busy? Please sit.
- Do you have a girlfriend?
- No.
What about a wife?
The order of your questions
is quite interesting.
Reporters usually start out strong first.
I don't have a wife.
Any children?
Have you ever craved alcohol?
Have you ever craved a woman?
- No.
- Liar.
Uncle Rak.
Yes, Red.
How's your dad?
Are you hungry? What do you want?
Here. Eat up.
Thank you for the food.
- Red.
- Yes?
- You really don't miss your mom?
- I don't.
- You don't need your mom?
- No.
- Eat lots.
- Okay.
Hey... hold still.
You should do this for a woman.
Aren't you going to get married?
It's not that I'm not. It's that I can't.
Ah, excuse me...
Why did you bother coming back?
Who took this patient back?
I thought it was just this patient who
didn't listen, but you're all the same.
Are my words a joke to you?
I'm sorry, Doctor. I'm sorry.
Neither your grandmother nor mother
ever acted this way.
Where did the daughter
learn such bad manners?
I'm sorry. I won't ever do it again.
Her temperature and BP are a bit high.
Should I keep checking...
Of course.
- Are you the guardian?
- Yes.
Because she didn't have a guardian,
she didn't listen to me and ran away.
This is all your fault.
From now on,
watch over her for 24 hours a day.
Do not let this happen again.
- Understand? Do you understand!
- Yes.
I'm going to check the wound.
Does it hurt?
A little bit.
Don't hold back and tell me if it hurts.
I know you're good at
enduring pain, Pyo Na Ri.
At the hospital,
you're only fooling your doctor.
You're becoming a fraud. Understand?
Just in case, change the painkillers
if she complains tonight.
- Take new scans too.
- Okay.
Grandma.
Yes?
I'll be coming in now.
Grandma.
We have the pathology results
from the surgery.
Do you want to talk now or later?
Grandma, the heavens have helped you.
People often think that its
a knot in the muscle.
They don't find out
until it's stage three or four.
You suspected it was breast cancer
and came to the hospital early.
It is a huge relief.
You need to bow down in thanks
to the person who told you
to go to the hospital.
The lymph nodes have not changed.
You chose partial extraction,
so the mammary gland still remains.
You must come to the hospital daily for
six weeks to get radiation therapy.
You must receive that treatment.
You absolutely must.
Here at the breast cancer clinic,
every day.
Promise?
Come on, now.
You must.
Okay!
Ah, a private room?
Grandma, are you going to keep
changing your mind like this?
You said to earlier,
"I don't want a private room."
Don't you recall that?
Grandma, there are...
no private rooms.
Not anymore!
Aren't you going home?
She said I should watch over you
24 hours a day.
But... why are you suddenly
dropping honorifics?
Does Hwa Shin know too,
about you being sick?
No, of course not. He wouldn't know.
Reporter Lee doesn't even
have this much interest in me.
That's a relief.
Where are you going?
We're here to see Pyo Na Ri,
who just did the 7 p.m. weather.
Call her and tell her to come out.
- I can't reach her on the phone.
- You can't go in.
Hold on, Mister. Please, let us in.
My sister really is
a weather forecaster here.
Her name is Pyo Na Ri.
She's the best at weather.
Yes, I understand, but you have to go.
Wait, I'll just be a moment.
- You have to leave.
- I'll only be a second.
You have to go.
- I just need to see her face.
- Excuse me.
- Reporter Kye.
- You can let them in.
Pardon?
Ah, okay.
What are you doing?
- Thank you so much, Reporter.
- Thank you very much.
That door at the end is the office.
Thank you.
She must have left already.
She isn't here.
Hey!
Reporter! Reporter, wait!
You know my sister, don't you?
I do.
Is she going to get fired?
Is she someone who would
be fired so easily?
You ought to know.
You're her little brother.
I'll put these in here, so drink them.
I will. Thank you.
No need to thank me.
I wonder if that grandma is sleeping.
Yes, she must be.
I suppose grandmas sleep early.
It must get stuffy in there,
but she's keeping the curtains shut.
Goodness.
By the way, about that remote control
what gave you the idea to hide it
under your foot and kick it to me?
People would know
if I tossed it to you by hand.
Then they might take it away from you.
I wanted to make sure I got it to you.
Do you know how nervous I was?
If it weren't for that remote control
I don't think I would've been able
to handle it and would've run away.
You did a good thing
by standing your ground.
Do you really think so?
The station might give you a warning
because the two of you did it together.
You don't need to fear that.
That's how the weak have to survive.
If you ran away,
you wouldn't get another chance.
You'd be in the studio thinking,
"Two people can never stand there."
Suppose you let that spot go
for the sake of the station.
You wouldn't just get a warning.
You'd be branded as the one who lost.
A warning is better than
being the one who lost.
Maybe you're right.
You did well.
What a joke.
Oh my! Oh my...
Oh, wow.
Oh my gosh.
What kind of a woman farts like that?
That's not a woman, right? It's a man.
What? A man... the grandma?
I'm just kidding. It's a joke.
It smells like a man's.
She sure farts a lot in her sleep.
Should I open the window?
Window? It's on that side.
That grandma must have
had surgery today too.
Hey! Get rid of him now.
- Are you sleepy?
- Yes.
You can't sleep because of me.
Yes, I'll sleep once you leave.
I'll leave once you sleep.
No, I can only sleep if you leave.
I can only leave if I see you sleeping.
- Let's go, President.
- Yes.
You should go. Go, go.
Thank you for everything today.
Unexpectedly, I've become
very indebted to you.
We even smelled the fart of the
grandma in the bed next to you.
Why are you being so formal
now that I'm leaving?
You're being very stiff with me.
I've been very out of it today.
I thought we'd become closer.
We have become closer,
so I should say goodbye properly.
Ah... don't come back again.
I'm going to be discharged soon.
Also, I'll buy you a meal to repay you
for everything you did for me today.
I won't forget how you were
my guardian today.
Well, then...
Goodnight.
This is just patient care,
so don't feel too burdened.
Don't feel too much pain in your heart
since you had surgery.
I had Secretary Cha look into it.
Today's weather had double the ratings
with the two of you in it.
I think you'll get another chance.
Don't worry about getting fired.
Goodnight.
Wait...
Isn't this too fast?
It is fast.
But it's not a no, right?
So, then why...
Why did you try to
rush me off so quickly?
Are you scared?
Are you afraid?
Did you really think I was running
around all day just as your guardian?
Getting in trouble by the doctor
while sitting around by your side
sympathizing with you, who couldn't eat.
Gosh, you really don't know men.
Are you dense?
Or are you just bad at dating?
You're Reporter Lee's friend though.
You said Hwa Shin doesn't even
have this much interest in you.
So why does it matter?
True. That's true.
In Thailand, you know when
we all shared an umbrella?
There was thunder.
You didn't jump into my arms.
I... pulled you into my arms.
Did you have some tom yum?
- We're almost there.
- Is it good there?
It's not good.
You didn't know?
[Go Jung Won]
Hello?
Are you busy?
No, I'm going to go home.
Are you keeping any secrets from me?
Secrets?
No.
I can keep a secret from you, right?
Why bother having a
useless thing like that?
How can I only do useful things in life?
Let's do something useless.
- Are you okay?
- Of course I am.
I found out about a
great investment in Thailand.
I'm going to go in on it by myself.
You're already overflowing with money.
You don't need to know, right?
No, I don't.
You should go to the gym on your own
for a little while.
I'm going to take a break.
I'm a little busy preparing
for my audition.
Okay, when are you starting work?
I have a few days left.
Hwa Shin, you know that
weathercaster I met in Bangkok?
Pyo Na Ri.
Pyo Na Ri is sick.
I went to the station for my work
and I saw her passed out.
I took her to the hospital.
That's great.
Yeah.
You did a really good thing.
Yes.
Okay.
Okay, go on home. I'll call again.
That will be all for SBC News Reader.
Have a good night.
This was Bang Ja Young's Exciting Night.
That will be all for tonight.
I will meet you all again tomorrow.
Goodnight.
The doors are now closing.
Did you drink?
You drank alcohol and went on air?
You said something to Pyo Na Ri about it
and you did the news after drinking?
What's wrong with you, ma'am?
What's with all the perfume?
Who are you trying to seduce that
you're acting so pathetic, ma'am?
You're crazy. You're an anchor.
You're cut off from TV and doing
radio where no one sees you.
You sprayed on a bottle of perfume.
You're just acting atrociously.
What? Should I drag you to a police
station and throw you in jail?
Being drunk on air
is worse than drunk driving.
You're just telling the nation
drunken nonsense, not news.
- Why, you! I was upset so I had drink.
- What?
- Get off.
- Come on.
I'm so sick of the fact that we entered
this company in the same year.
It's a curse that we're retiring
at the same age too.
Can you please just leave first?
Do you know how much people
laugh behind our backs?
This is all your fault!
Why is it my fault?
Ever since I met you,
my entire life has become twisted.
You stole my daughter, Red.
- You stole my husband too!
- Hey!
You threw them away.
Who are you accusing of stealing them?
Who are you blaming for
your life being twisted around?
You awful woman.
You wench, you wench, you wench,
you wench, you wench!
It's all your fault!
Who do you think you are?
Let go! Let go of it.
You die too!
If you had been living happily,
I would never have met your husband.
If you had raised her well,
we wouldn't both be unable to see her.
We wouldn't be forgotten
and ignored by Red like this.
Even if it's my fault that
we're all living apart like this
why don't you know that you
have bigger faults than me?
Why don't you know?
Why are you the only one?
You'd better resign tomorrow.
I'm embarrassed to work
in the same place as you.
I feel dirty, like my body is inside out.
Hey, it's like I'm looking in the mirror.
I think of myself when I look at you
and I think of you when I look at myself.
The people at work talk behind our backs.
I'm the one who feels like
I'm going crazy.
Seriously, I'm so angry.
How can you fart in front of a man?
Is there a man here?
When did you two get so close?
He's your close friend.
Why can't you tell your friend?
I don't want to.
He doesn't seem like the type to
go around telling people about it.
He wouldn't.
I know him better than you.
I still don't want to.
Then, you must not be that close.
Even though he's my friend
I don't want to tell him
about my breast cancer.
He'll be worried.
He's already the kind of person
who gives too much of what's his.
He'll give even more
if he knows I'm sick.
Then our friendship will turn into pity.
Then I'll just become so pitiful.
I hate that.
On top of that, it's my chest.
A man's chest...
Gosh, not the man's chest again.
A woman's chest must mean nothing.
Why, you...
I can't control it. What can I do?
I'm sorry.
What do you mean you can't control it?
You'll be embarrassed if you
let it all out at once.
You're letting it out little by little
like a bag letting out air.
How dirty.
Is it because of me?
Do you still like me?
I'm still a man to you.
Well, you did kiss me first.
How can you say you don't
like me overnight, right?
You can think whatever you'd like.
But I really ended everything
with you yesterday, Reporter.
It's very tiring and difficult
because I got dumped.
Please stop bothering me.
Hey, let's be clear about this.
What do you mean you got dumped?
You're the one who liked me and disliked
me by yourself with all your emotions.
You liked and then stopped liking
all on your own.
I suppose you got dumped,
but it was your own doing.
You were in a one-sided love.
Dumped, yeah right.
Gosh! All right, you're right.
I got dumped and gave myself
a broken heart.
Don't turn your back on me.
You're planning on
farting in my direction.
How can two friends be so different,
even in the way they talk?
Does Hwa Shin know too,
about you being sick?
No, of course not.
Reporter Lee doesn't even have
this much interest in me.
That's a relief.
Goodnight.
Don't turn your back on me.
It's dangerous.
I'm hungry.
- I can't sleep because I'm hungry.
- Me too.
Are you sleeping?
- Are you sleeping, Pi Na Ri?
- I'm sleeping.
- I'm going to die of hunger.
- Me too.
- Do you want some?
- No, I don't.
Your best friend bought it.
He bought it for you, not for me.
- It's not mine.
- No need to nitpick.
I feel so much better now.
This day feels so long.
This is the longest night of my life too.
What's with that sucking sound?
That was good.
Don't turn your back on me.
Face me.
Then, face me and lie down too.
I don't need to.
I'm afraid you'll have
farts left over too.
- Reporter.
- What?
It's nothing.
Just say it. What is it?
About your friend...
Jung Won?
Is he a player?
Does he have a girlfriend?
Huh? Does he?
I don't really know.
Ask him yourself. Don't ask me.
I've become curious about him.
You still like me though.
Don't bother my friend.
You're pretending to be over me
by being curious about my friend.
I'm really not.
Sleep well.
Don't try so hard. Don't pretend.
Just forget me naturally.
You were in love with me for three years.
How could you... forget me so easily?
Subtitles by DramaFever
Do you know how sad, lonely,
and hurt my pride was?
You just have poor judgment of people.
If you had good taste in men,
you would never have liked me.
Don't come here.
I keep wanting to see you.
You no longer have feelings for me.
What's the problem?
No matter how one-sided it was,
there is an end to the relationship.
You've suffered a lot all this time.
I won't turn and look.
Let's just ignore each other.
Are you crazy?
I'll do anything you want.f
I want someone to be in a
one-sided love with me too.