Red should be raised by Bang Ja Young.
Not her biological mother?
- What are you doing?
- Good job, Bang Ja Young.
Red lives right upstairs
from your pasta restaurant.
But what? She's a customer?
You don't know her number?
She doesn't come by anymore?
Why did you lie to us?
How could you do such a thing?
You knew how desperate
we were to find her.
Are you even a human being?
Were you playing around with me,
feeding me your disgusting pasta?
Playing around?
- Keep going, Bang Ja Young.
- Do you think I'm crazy?
- Playing with a woman turning 60 soon?
- Hey!
I'm not interested in women.
I especially don't like
ones older than me.
Do I look like I'll be turning 60 soon?
I'm not even 50 yet.
Me neither.
What are you doing?
Why are you so quiet?
You usually talk way more than I do.
Anyway, it's true that you played us.
Women who say that my pasta is
disgusting give me nightmares.
If you're having nightmares,
then don't go to sleep.
Red should be raised by Bang Ja Young.
No, not my Red!
No!
You crazy punk!
- You're wearing a woman's bra.
- No, Mom...
Are you crazy, huh?
You pervert! It's not enough
to kill your brother.
Are you crazy?
What have you been doing?
That's not it!
Bring back your brother! Bring him back!
Stop it!
Just bite your tongue and die!
You bastard...
He just works with your sister.
Oh, that's a relief.
Stay strong, Reporter.
What are you looking at?
Do you want to see something?
It's Reporter Lee.
If anyone besides you sees that video...
it'll be the day of your funeral.
You and I will both die.
[Episode 7]
It's already 3 a.m. Chi Yeol!
Do a good job, Na Ri.
I think I should just sleep
in the work dorm room.
Then go on air.
I'm too anxious so I can't sleep
and I'm waking you up, too.
- I'm going now.
- Okay.
Don't bother coming out.
Go back to sleep.
Go to sleep.
Goodnight.
You've worked hard all this time.
What is it, Na Ri? Who is it?
Someone you know or not?
Is it a weirdo?
No, no! Go back to bed.
Okay.
Good morning.
Hi.
Did you wash your face?
So, this is how you usually
go around looking.
This is the style you like, huh?
That's not necessarily true.
I thought the way you looked at the
hospital was you at your least pretty.
I guess not.
Aren't you going to tell me to get in?
I was worried that you
might not get in, so thanks.
Get in.
You go on air at 6 a.m.
but you have to go this early?
I have to get the files from the
meteorologist, prepare, get the CG.
Then do makeup.
I have to go by 3:00.
How long had you been
waiting in front of my house?
Why ask something like that?
Did you come from work?
Aren't you busy?
I'm going to work after I drop you off.
This early?
I have to go to the airport early,
so I can go after I drop you off.
You don't even have a car.
How do you get to the station by 3:00?
Are you going to drive me every day?
Or will you just buy me a car instead?
- You like that kind of thing?
- Would you do it if I did?
I'll have to think twice
if that's what you want.
I totally want it.
How big of a car?
- A really big one.
- Ah, a big one?
Since we're at it, a super big one.
All right, that's enough.
Thinking about going
to work at this hour
and carrying all this stuff
is seriously...
it's so suffocating,
so I was just saying it.
I am very materialistic though
and I like free things.
You should think twice about it.
If I think twice,
I lose out on good clothes.
Women are the same.
Does Reporter Lee know
you're acting this way to me?
It hasn't been long since the funeral.
I'll talk to him later.
What will you say?
That I want to have a passionate
relationship with Pyo Na Ri.
Oh my god.
Even if I don't buy you a car
or drive you every day
will you still date me?
I wonder why there are no stars tonight.
It's very strange.
There should be some,
but there are none.
It's weird. There are no stars.
Hello, everyone.
Did you all have a good night?
This is the first "News Morning"
of the Thanksgiving holidays.
Oh! I think I'm going to fly away.
Who told you to cause all
that trouble and involve me?
Now we have shoot early in the morning.
What is this?
Pyo Na Ri, stand by!
Oh no! What do I do?
Hey, do something about that
crazy skirt thing flying around!
Okay, okay!
Pyo Na Ri, you look like
a mom at a wedding.
You could light the candles
for the wedding.
Seven seconds to lighting the candles.
Five, four...
- Hey!
- What's she doing?
Two, one. Cue!
Are you all enjoying your Thanksgiving
holiday with your families?
There is a typhoon in effect
over the entire Korean peninsula.
At the moment, strong winds
are blowing all over the country.
Did you see that?
That is how strong the winds are.
Oh! Good job, Pyo Na Ri.
The skirt is doing its job
of showing the weather.
The tail end of the typhoon will remain
with winds of up to 30 meters per second.
First, you will have to
prepare your signs
greenhouses, and other facilities.
It's a hit.
You will need to prepare.
Good! CG for the whole country!
In now!
- Here's your coffee.
- Thank you.
Reporter.
Let's go.
You probably shouldn't be drinking that.
- Are we going in one car?
- We got one more car.
Drink this one instead.
It has no milk or cream.
I'll go to the committee meeting
and bring the news source.
You guys start setting up
at the scene.
Okay.
Reporter?
Oh my. What was that?
Is going to pretend he
doesn't even know me now?
Red, it's Mom.
I know you're inside.
Open the door, Red.
Mom made you your favorite foods.
I'll leave them by the door,
so make sure to eat them.
Eat them with rice, Red.
Make sure to just study.
You're very pretty,
so be careful of boys.
Okay?
This lady has been coming every day.
Red, it's Mom.
I bought some clothes for you to wear.
Can you come out and try them on?
You need allowance money, right?
If you don't want to see me
leave your empty wallet
in the milk pouch.
I'll fill it up with money for you.
You can buy what you want to eat.
Buy whatever else you want.
Don't think bad thoughts
or do anything bad.
You don't have to open the door
if you don't want to see your mom.
I'm going to wait.
I can wait as long as you need.
I waited 10 years for you, Red.
I can wait much longer if you need.
Don't starve and make sure
to buy food to eat.
Open up the milk pouch.
Looks good.
Are they trying to buy their
daughter's love?
What are they trying to teach her?
It is the beautiful season of fall
where the skies become endless.
However, these endlessly high skies
can bring great danger to some.
This is an exclusive from
Reporter Lee Hwa Shin.
I always believed that high places were
beautiful, but that is not always true.
I am currently at
highrise building in Seoul.
I am outside of the 21st floor.
According to the industrial safety manual
when the wind velocity
exceeds 10 meters per second
no one must be outside cleaning windows.
In reality, the work is being done
even at winds of 18 meters per second.
Sir, how are the winds today?
This is considered to be a gentle breeze.
We have to work unless it's a typhoon.
Don't you have to stop when it's raining?
They say the dirt will come off better,
so we have to work when it rains.
Yes, I see.
This is the prime season in which
much of the window cleaning is done.
Unfortunately, the...
the accidents and deaths related to
window cleaning have been on the rise.
Today, I hid the fact
that I was a reporter
and called a window cleaning business.
Within five minutes, I received a call to
put me to work at highrise building.
They gave me a few things
before I started.
A safety instruction session
that lasted less than one hour.
This single rope that is deficient
according to the safety standards.
A shelf that I can
barely manage to sit on.
A few cleaning tools.
Also...
The weather is nice.
- Yes, it's fall now.
- Yes.
This coffee is nice.
There is a safety tool
for moments like this.
It is this plunger.
As you can see,
it is not particularly effective.
I apologize for alarming the viewers.
However, the shoe that fell
could have been me.
That goes to show that I have nothing
keeping me safe and no safety tools!
As for the industrial safety standards
manual for window cleaners
who exactly is making sure
these rules are followed?
Some see the sky from inside,
and some see the sky from out here.
It should be beautiful to us all.
This is Reporter Lee Hwa Shin from SBC.
Good work, everyone!
Gosh, that made me nervous.
What's with that guy?
Is he determined to die
just because his brother died?
He won't die.
When people are determined to die,
they usually don't end up dying.
You were reassigned to 6 a.m. weather.
What are you doing here?
Why are you hanging around here?
Go to the work dorm rooms and sleep.
It's only 8:00 p.m. How can I sleep?
Bye, now. Reporter Lee!
How was I today?
Not great.
Exactly what was not great and why?
Just everything.
Did you even hear me do my anchor part?
Your story was not so great either.
No, mine was perfect.
Look at that.
It's not just me he doesn't
want to talk to or even look at.
Don't even think of coming here again.
Mom.
Now that Joong Shin is gone,
these are all withering away too.
How dare she show up here?
I left you many messages
so I'm sure you got them.
I'm going to live with Red now.
If I take this court,
I will get parental and custody rights.
What do you think that means?
It means that the law
sides with the mother
who went through labor and gave birth.
How does the dirt taste?
Joong Shin is buried in the dirt.
You're alive and well,
eating with that mouth of yours
and spewing that terrible nonsense.
How did a wench like you
come into my house?
You only had the child and ran.
Is that a mother?
Even if you gave birth 1,000 times,
Red wouldn't go to you!
You should tell the truth.
I didn't throw Red away!
You took her from me.
You made Red hate me and you made
a mother and daughter grow apart.
This is all your fault!
Red is my daughter. She's mine!
Just a bit.
I want to respect your tastes.
So, pick out what you like first.
Are you really going to sponsor
my outfit every time I go on air?
The dressing room is over there.
How much is this?
There's no price tag.
Your mother is here.
Hello, President.
Oh, hello.
Mother, why didn't you call beforehand?
I wanted to pick some clothes out
for Announcer Geum.
Madam, Announcer Geum usually
wears the clothes on the first floor.
- Let's go to the first floor.
- First floor?
Why would I dress
my future daughter-in-law
in clothes on the first floor?
Is that what you've been doing?
Let's get your wedding dress
from here too, Announcer Geum.
If you choose it for me, Mother,
I would like that.
We don't sell wedding dresses.
You should look into
wedding dresses at a bigger place.
You can go to Italy yourself
and look into it.
You're always in Milan,
so it's no big deal for you.
Why would you get it elsewhere?
What kind of manner is this toward
the person you're going to marry?
What do you mean marry?
We haven't even gone on a date, right?
If you move too fast like this,
it's rude to Announcer Geum.
We can date after we marry.
My brother did that too.
He's very happy now.
She says all the right things,
doesn't she, Jung Won?
This is why I want an announcer
daughter-in-law like her.
Then, look around.
Come. Look around.
Well, we're not in a relationship
where we have to be concerned
about these things.
What is our relationship?
Just tasting.
Are you saying you're
getting a taste of me?
Can I get a taste of a rich man?
How is it now that you've had a taste?
Salty?
Spicy?
Sour?
Sweet.
It's incredibly scary.
Then, have a taste.
People have a taste
even when they eat stew.
You should have a taste of a man
you might have a relationship with.
Your surgery went well
and your scar is healing nicely.
I don't think you need to worry.
Thank you, Doctor.
Lee Hwa Shin hasn't come to his
appointments or for radiation at all.
Did something happen?
He hasn't come for
radiation therapy at all?
I told him it could come back
and he must get radiation therapy.
I told him more than 100 times.
He must think a
doctor's word is bullcrap.
Is he possessed by a ghost
who doesn't listen to people?
Does he hate me? Why isn't he coming?
The breast cancer clinic is full of women
like a women's bath locker room.
Is he scared of rumors?
Is he more scared of rumors
than the cancer coming back?
Even if it's stage one,
a recurring cancer can spread so fast.
Is he crazy or something?
I guess he must be determined
to die early or something.
What did I do so wrong
that he's so angry anyway?
He ignores me all the time,
so why should I?
Oh, Reporter Lee!
What is it? Did you get kicked out?
Huh? Did you get kicked out?
Reporter, Reporter...
Pyo Na Ri, bring him here.
What? Why should I?
Besides the doctors and you,
who else knows that he has breast cancer?
Aren't you two dating?
No, we are not.
Then, should we leave him to die?
Breast cancer patients have symptoms
similar to menopausal women post-surgery.
They're very sensitive and emotional.
Doctors consider them to be the
most difficult of the cancer patients.
Men with breast cancer could be the same.
There's a good chance
Reporter Lee Hwa Shin is in that state.
That must be why he's not coming.
Yeah, let's just let him die then.
Yes, that would be better.
Gosh, this is getting on my nerves.
What am I supposed to do?
He's acting like I don't exist.
Pyo Na Ri, bring him here.
Gosh, I don't know. He can die or not.
I don't know anymore.
Do you want me to go to
radiation therapy with you tomorrow?
I'll go with you.
Go to the bathroom and
just sleep. Sleep, okay?
How did you know that I'd be here?
It's obvious, man.
Were you busy until now?
Let's just go to sleep.
I was on a flight
so I couldn't sleep at all.
Then why did you come?
You should go home and sleep.
You got kicked out of your house.
I came here to get you.
Mom sure talks a lot.
It's obvious why your mom told my mom.
She's saying, "Stay at Jung Won's house."
I don't want to live according
to my mom's expectations.
- Let's sleep at my place.
- I'm comfortable here.
It's too narrow for me.
What are you doing? Stop being gross.
Since you've been kicked out,
come live with me.
I'll be the wife.
You know my entry code.
You could've gone even if I wasn't home.
Why are you suffering here?
Just go home.
Let's just go to my place.
I have to go film on scene
early tomorrow morning.
I'm coming every day until you come.
Stop with that and just go.
Ah, I guess you're telling me
to come back tomorrow.
No woman can hold you like this.
You crazy punk.
I... might not be as good as
your brother who passed away.
I'll be good to you like your brother.
Joong Shin was a good person,
so I'm sure he's in a good place.
He will be wanting the best for you,
more than anyone, from up in heaven.
Stop acting like a hedgehog
with its spines up.
Be good to Red and your mother.
As for you, I'll be good to you.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay.
You said okay.
Okay.
Okay, let's sleep.
Make sure to just study.
You're very pretty so be careful of boys.
Okay?
You like me, right?
Don't think bad thoughts
or do anything bad.
Hey! Let's go.
I should never have listened to you.
Don't you like me?
Oh!
Give it to me.
I thought you were a ghost!
- Where's your phone?
- What? Why?
Why? Why?
Wait, Reporter!
Why are you asking for my phone?
Why are you doing this?
- Do you really not know?
- What, what?
Is it that video from the hospital?
I saw you showing it to Jung Won.
Ah... that's why you've been ignoring me
and treating me like crap.
I told you, didn't I?
The moment anyone else sees that video,
both you and I will die.
Yes, you are right. You are.
You and I both are going to die.
I will die because I showed
the video to your friend.
You'll die because you're not
getting radiation therapy.
Don't change the topic and give it to me.
But how come you're not getting the
radiation therapy? Why?
Doctor Geum said that you could relapse
and it will spread quickly.
She's throwing a fit
saying you're in danger.
Do you think you have two or three lives?
You promised to go every day
and get the radiation for six weeks.
Isn't that why you got partial removal?
My brother is dead.
How can I try to live a long life
on my own like that?
Do I have to be diligent about
radiation therapy when he just died?
You think I'm that heartless?
I shouldn't care if
my brother died or not.
I got surgery to be
healthy and live long.
Now I have to get radiation therapy?
I'd rather just live like this.
No, I'm so apologetic to my brother that
I want to live a bit less than others.
I just want to go to my brother,
so don't concern yourself with it.
Just give me your phone now.
If you want to die so quickly,
why do you care about that darn video?
Gosh, seriously!
Even if I die,
I can't die so shamefully.
If you're going to die,
who cares about being embarrassed?
Is that so important?
You can die or not.
Really?
What if I'd been sleeping
in my underwear?
Yesterday I was sleeping in my underwear!
You're in sweatpants.
Oh my! Where are you groping?
Where is it?
Where are you touching me?
- This is sexual harassment!
- Sexual harassment? What a joke.
If you didn't like me searching like this
you would've stood up by now.
You still like me, don't you?
I told you I don't! Seriously!
I don't have the phone!
I looked everywhere and it's not here.
Do you sleep with the phone
hidden on your body?
What, what? What?
- You want me to undress?
- Why would you?
You getting undressed
is my worst fear in life.
Turn your pockets inside out.
Don't expect me to search you anymore.
Here, look.
It's not here, right?
Look.
It's empty, right? Empty, empty!
Gosh!
You sent me a text message earlier.
Where did you put your phone?
[Weathercaster Dressing Room]
Oh! What are you doing?
Then, go get radiation therapy
with me tomorrow.
I will delete it in front of you then.
Stop trying to make things happen.
You're trying to get involved with me
and try something again.
Wait!
All right, all right.
It's because you feel
like you're going to
a women's bath locker room, right?
I will pretend to be the patient and
you can pretend to be my guardian.
I have the breast cancer
and you're just the guardian.
I don't think anyone will think it's odd.
There won't be any rumors.
Really.
Have you ever seen the impossible happen?
I won't ever trust you again.
I can't trust you.
Why are you doing this?
Seriously! Gosh...
Should I buy you a phone?
Forget it.
Hey, hey!
Hey! Let's go buy
a phone tomorrow, okay?
Let's go buy a phone together.
Together?
There will never be anything
you and I do together, ever.
That's what I wanted.
Still, I'll buy you a phone.
Get out! Don't you know that
men aren't allowed in here?
What's going on with you two?
It's nothing. Let's go.
Why are you two fighting in here
when you were sleeping before?
We don't really get along.
- He's my enemy.
- Look who's talking.
Reporter Lee put my phone in the toilet.
Her phone? Why?
I said I'd buy you a new one.
Do you think this is about the phone?
I had important pictures and videos--
There were so many
important things on there!
There were pictures of my mom
things I can't forget,
and everything else.
What's with you?
Do you think it's because
of the video of you?
Shut your mouth!
What? That thing?
I have it here, too.
I thought it was fun and nice.
Did you throw her phone in the toilet
because she secretly filmed that?
Here. You can throw mine
in the toilet too.
This put me in a good mood
every time I watched it
so I even got her to send it to me.
You hated it that much?
Then go ahead and throw mine out too.
Hey, I know your brother's dead but...
you're being oversensitive like a girl.
Whose side are you on right now?
You're just the same.
The two of you watched that video
and laughed at me.
You saw it but didn't even tell me
and you alienated me.
It is worth laughing at a bit.
How can you not laugh at that?
You punk.
You're going to curse at me now?
- You wench and punk.
- Reporter!
I have the right to that video.
Aren't you going too far
with a sick person?
Are you sick?
You already know, so why are you asking?
If you were going to pretend not
to know then continue doing that.
What are you sick with?
You should know if you saw
the video of me in that br--
Let go!
- Are you crazy?
- His chest...
His chest hurts.
Because he lost his brother,
I think he's a bit traumatized.
Since that funeral,
how should I put it...
He says that he's in pain here and there.
He keeps whining
and it's driving me nuts.
If you're feeling sick,
why don't you take time off?
What do we do about Red?
Excuse me.
Hey!
Why, you little...
Where did you roll in from,
you rude thing?
Listen to you.
Are you a couple?
Who knew...
You laugh? Are you laughing? Apologize.
Let go and talk. Let go.
I knew she'd cause trouble.
She came here to cause trouble.
Where's Lee Hwa Shin?
Everything is all set up.
- Where is he?
- Hurry up and find him.
Hwa Shin! Hwa Shin!
Bastard Hwa Shin! You bastard!
This is what Pyo Na Ri showed you?
She thought it was great how hard you
practiced when you refused to do it.
So she secretly filmed it.
She says you do it better than anyone
when you set your mind to it.
She said it was cool and she envied you.
Well, who told her to film this?
I'm fine with it.
It was a bit harsh to curse at Pyo Na Ri.
You should apologize.
Why should I apologize?
Is he going through menopause
or something?
Why is he acting so out of character?
Hello? The police station?
You'd better apologize now.
Be quiet!
What's your name? Tell us now.
What's your name?
- It's Lee Red.
- Lee Red.
Resident ID number?
How old are you?
Hey! Red, you...
Are you going to keep taking my clothes
and going to clubs?
Hey, are you insinuating that
my Red is a thief?
Who called this lady anyway?
I called her.
We were the ones taking in money
during the funeral.
That announcer lady gave the most.
- How much did she give?
- Who called this lady?
That anchor lady said
that she was your mom
and told me to call if anything happened.
I'm her only real family.
These people are all strangers,
so call me if anything happens.
You say you're her real family yet
you didn't come see her for three years?
Why don't you just accept rent
if you're the landlord?
Her real uncle is here
so you can stop pretending.
Hey, Mister.
Don't talk to my uncle like that.
Red, I'm your uncle.
Yeah, don't talk to Hwa Shin like that,
Uncle and Red.
Aren't minors not allowed in that club?
Whose idea was it to go?
Dae Gu? Red, it was you right?
Hey! It wasn't Red!
Obviously these boys convinced her to go.
Dae Gu is not like that.
Just hang out with Dae Gu.
Don't hang out with Red anymore.
Why are you picking on Red?
Red, move out of that villa.
Come live with me.
If you leave that villa,
you won't have to be around those people.
Come with Mom. Let's go to my house.
Let go of her.
- Chi Yeol.
- Yeah?
- Dae Gu.
How did you guys feel having
your first kiss with me today?
- You...
- Let go.
It's not true, right?
It wasn't Red, right?
- You can do it at your age, but...
- Don't worry.
Is it true? Come with me.
They are so lame.
It's been a long time, Rich Bro.
You should call me Uncle.
I'm your uncle's friend.
I don't want to.
She's lying right now.
From what I know,
her first kiss was in junior high.
It's not a big deal, so don't worry.
Also, Red will be living
at her grandma's house.
You two should stay out of it.
Junior high?
Why does he get to decide?
How is it not a big deal?
She calls her uncle "Mister" and
calls her mom "some lady." What a mess.
That girl has a dirty temper
because she takes after me.
So, you do know.
You have full makeup on right now?
Red was at the police station!
That's why you're not a mom.
You had time to do makeup?
I did live radio and
was eating with my staff.
Who has time to remove makeup when
my daughter is at the police station?
Why is it that you put on makeup
every time you do radio?
- What?
- You're always ready to meet a man.
- I've never seen you with a man though.
- Really?
I had my first kiss in junior high.
I guess Red takes after me in that way.
I am so proud of her.
Go on in, Red.
Goodnight, Red.
- Bye, Red.
- Go inside now.
Thank you for the ride.
No need to thank me.
Hey, Hwa Shin.
Neither of you got any sleep
and you have to go to the station.
So let's go eat.
Come on.
Wait.
Me?
Both of you.
I have something to tell you.
Let's go inside.
You and Chi Yeol did it too?
Goodnight.
How did you guys feel having your
first kiss with me today?
What should we eat?
Get in.
Sorry, but can I go in this car?
You don't need to ask.
Of course you can go in this car.
Hey, I'm just going to go to the station.
How can you just go
after fighting like that?
What about Pyo Na Ri's phone?
You have to take responsibility for it.
Why should I take
responsibility? What for?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Let's go and resolve it.
There's nothing to resolve.
Then was it right for a guy
to throw a phone into a toilet?
Fine, I'll just set up a phone merchant
at the station, so get one there.
Gosh, you're making me out
to be a petty person.
Seriously, did I ever
ask you for a phone?
Yeah, an apology should come first.
Forget the phone.
I may have said that I liked
getting things for free.
But I'm someone who feels stifled
if I'm offered free gum.
But I do have to get what is mine
in order to feel better.
You owe me bra money
for what I bought you back then.
"Bra-mon" what?
Why are you trying to get it for free?
- I bought it for you.
- Let's go, okay? Come on.
You should've been
like this to begin with.
You're so stubborn.
Tell me where you're headed.
You're dead.
Which of your two moms
are you going to live with?
You didn't kiss me so why
did you tell the adults that you did?
Then, we can do it now.
What is it?
Are you going keep being confusing?
I've never been confused about anything.
I'm going to live with the mom
that is more jealous.
The more jealous a person is,
the more she loves me.
Goodnight.
How much?
45,000 won.
Here.
- This is 50,000 won.
- The 5,000 won is for buying it.
Reporter.
You told me to buy two
so that you could switch.
Two.
Here, here.
- I'll give you change.
- 10,000 won is for buying it.
I told you I don't like free things.
It's because I'm thankful for before.
What is this "bra-mon" thing anyway?
Hwa Shin, I will buy you lots later.
That sounds great, Reporter.
Are the calculations done now?
Done now?
- Done.
This is it. You and I are done.
Because you two said I played you both,
I was very hurt at the funeral.
To make it worse,
you said my pasta was disgusting.
I was extremely hurt.
So, I have prepared this. Please eat.
Taste it properly.
Determine if I played around with you
with disgusting pasta
or if I played around with you
with good pasta.
Also, I would like to apologize for
not telling you that I knew Red well.
As for hitting you...
I am sorry about that.
- Are you okay where you got hit?
- Yes.
Please.
Red is like my niece.
Red insisted that she no longer had
a mom and Joong Shin was very ill.
I had a lot to think about.
I had to do it without Red finding out,
so I ended up having to lie.
It is very important to me
what kind of a mom Red has, as well.
It is very good.
You're very good.
I mean... it's very good.
Thank you. Red grew up lonely.
She should be with a good mom now
and be happy.
That's what I wanted to discuss...
Is today's weather in studio or outside?
The first two are on the roof and
the second two are in the newsroom.
You do it four times?
The early morning news is like that.
Your stomach will pop out. Stop eating.
What stomach? Keep eating.
- Eat this.
- It's a problem when you're sideways.
When you eat before a broadcast,
it looks bad if your stomach sticks out.
You can eat after the news.
Who eats this much before?
We can't leave this food behind.
It's expensive.
You were trying to eat everything before.
Reporter Lee, have you even
bought me a bowl of ramen?
I paid for the tom yum in Thailand.
You did that for your friend, not me.
You don't let up even once
and argue back every time.
Red grew up lonely.
She should be with a good mom now
and be happy.
That's what I wanted to discuss...
I just want to hear Red
call me "Mom" just once.
She calls me Mom.
Isn't it your wish to become
the 9:00 p.m. anchor?
Why do you think I want to be
Though I gave birth to her,
Bang Ja Young raised her.
Now, her father is in heaven.
Now, we have a chance to determine
who the real mom is.
If I lose to Bang Ja Young,
I won't be able to breathe.
She can lose to me because
I'm her biological mother.
For me, it makes no sense.
I will be dying every second
and minute of jealousy.
Jealously will rip up my insides.
I will be engulfed and
wrapped up in jealousy.
I don't need anyone else.
I only want recognition from Red.
While others cooked for her
and did laundry
your mom clenched her jaw, fought
with men, and is sitting in the top seat.
I want to show her that.
Then she will call me Mom.
Isn't that the right thing?
I think it's too big.
About your friend...
Jung Won?
Is he a player?
Does he have a girlfriend?
I've become curious about him.
You two suit each other well.
You should date.
Can we?
Why are you asking me?
You and I have similar taste in girls.
Really?
I have better taste than you.
You have weird taste.
But wasn't there someone you liked?
Was there?
The stew is boiling.
How does it taste?
The taste isn't quite right yet.
Not right yet?
I think it'll be really good
if we cook it a little longer.
You should date him, Pyo Na Ri.
This guy is really great.
You said you don't mind being dumped.
You just want to meet a great guy and
have a passionate relationship.
- Are you saying I'll get dumped?
- Yeah.
- By a great guy?
He's too honest.
Am I the great guy?
Yes, you're the great guy
who would dump her.
What is this?
Are you telling us to date or not?
You should give it a try.
Don't get hurt this time.
Jung Won is a better guy than me.
Oh! Reporter Lee.
Reporter Park, funny seeing you here.
- Do you have a cigarette?
- Cigarette?
I thought you quit smoking.
- Did I?
- Gosh...
Return the favor.
Thanks.
Don't laugh.
I said don't laugh.
Receive lots of love this time.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Let's go eat.
I have plans.
You're staring at a man's face
too obviously.
You're no longer a size 55.
You're going to wear a Pyo Na Ri size,
the only one in the world.
Custom Pyo Na Ri size.
We're going to announce the anchors
at today's office dinner.
Announcer Kye will be
the 9 p.m. main anchor.
Do you like me?
Sit next to me. It won't be so bad.
Don't you have a date with Jung Won?
I'll figure that out.
You don't have Red's permission.
What are you doing?
This is illegal entry!
I'm moving in with Red.
Downstairs from Pyo Na Ri?
Do you have your bra on?
Can't you just leave
your chest in my care?