Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 8]
Hwa Shin just set us up, right?
He told us to give it a try.
He did set us up, right?
Yes, but it is kind of strange.
What is?
- Reporter Lee and you.
- Me?
Why would Reporter Lee tell me
to date his best friend?
Also, why do you like me?
I feel like I'm very lacking.
It's weird.
If it weren't for the morning news,
you would've had soju.
Yes, I would have.
Then, I'll have soju.
We've both had one shot of soju now.
Let's each say one thing
we feel we're lacking in
and do a plus-minus statement.
We won't know who's more lacking
until we do a proper calculation.
- I'll go first.
- What?
I have less time than Pyo Na Ri.
My company takes up too much of my time.
Why would I do something like this?
I'll feel worse the more we do.
I can't even wear what I want.
I have to wear my company's clothes.
I have so many other clothes
I want to wear.
You can buy many other brands
and wear whatever you want.
Stop it. I don't want to do it anymore.
You have a good boss like Hwa Shin.
I don't have anyone
I can depend on at all.
I have no one above me.
It's really not good at all.
I have to take all the responsibility.
I told you to stop now.
Do you really know me, Pyo Na Ri?
Is there any point to this?
See? I'm like a bum right now.
I'm begging for affection.
What is this, really?
You argued with Hwa Shin
over 10,000 or 20,000 won
like your life was on the line.
Why? You should be like that with me.
We should get going now.
So? The results?
Okay, I'll pay today, okay?
Happy now?
How much?
58,000 won.
Do you really know me, Pyo Na Ri?
I'm like a bum right now.
I'm begging for affection.
- Did you take Pyo Na Ri back?
- Yes.
- What did she say?
- About what?
She's playing hard to get.
I must not be attractive.
She keeps playing hard to get.
You even tried to set us up.
How long have you been
interested in Pyo Na Ri?
How long has it been?
Since the flight to Thailand?
You flew together?
It was by chance.
She was sitting in my seat
as if it were her seat.
It was very obvious that
it was her first time flying.
She said she felt like
her head was in the clouds.
Wow. I feel like my head is the clouds.
She was like a kid at a picnic.
I pretended to sleep with
a newspaper on my face.
She was just staring at me.
I was sitting alone in first class
on my flight back.
But then I thought of the girl
with her head in the clouds.
Please call the station
if I get the weather wrong.
You have to. You must.
You can complain, curse, and get angry.
It's been my dream
to get a call like that.
I thought it would be nice
if she were sitting next to me.
I just kept thinking that.
Be good to her.
I told you she's playing hard to get.
She won't be able to last long.
Pyo Na Ri's not very good at that.
- How do you know?
- I just know.
I wonder what she likes.
What kind of guy does she like?
Do you know when her
last relationship was?
Don't care about that stuff
and just be good to her.
Also, don't come here tomorrow.
I'm going to move into Red's house soon.
She's alone in my brother's place.
She'll get into trouble.
I might not be able to
replace my brother.
But I'll try to mimic being a dad,
at least until Red gets married.
That's downstairs from Pyo Na Ri's place.
[Lee Joong Shin]
Joong Shin.
I'll hold on to your will for now.
I'm still not sure who will
be a better mom to Red.
May I watch over them for a bit?
I can do that, right?
How can we have such similar tastes?
Whether it's food,
clothes, or even men...
You both even hate me too, right?
Keep talking. Go on.
How much condolence money
did you give at the funeral anyway?
I had money saved away for Red.
I gave that too.
I need to get those two
married off again.
Shouldn't they have let
some things go by that age?
Are you going to report on a story
looking like this?
I'm going to get an exclusive.
Have you ever seen someone tell
their competition where they're going?
You should give up
on the 9 p.m. anchor spot.
You'll just get hurt competing with me.
Also, no woman has ever done it.
You can follow me if you're curious.
I'll be in the mountains yelling "Yahoo!"
Mister, let's unload here.
Oh, what is that?
Mister, you can't park here.
Where are you moving to?
The third floor there.
Oh my! Here?
Unload mine first to the third floor,
I'll pay you three times the amount.
Okay, go!
- Hey!
- Everyone, move fast!
Get mine unloaded now!
- Stop it.
- Move out of the way!
You people are just too much!
This is breaking and entering!
It's my brother's house.
Mister, move the truck!
You don't have Red's permission.
What are you doing?
Even I'm waiting for Red to be ready
so I can move in.
Mister, move this out. Move it out!
Hey! Why would he?
Bring it up.
- Bring it down. Don't go up.
- Why bring it down?
Mister, no! Go up.
- Up, up, up!
- Bring it down.
Bring it down. Hey!
I told you to bring the thing down.
Hey, get off of my bed now!
Hey, Mister! There's a person on it.
Why are you moving it up?
It's dangerous. Get off.
- I'll pay you three times the amount.
- Gosh, seriously?
Go up. Keep going up!
Oh my goodness.
Why is this bed so big?
You're going to put this
in that tiny house?
- Get off. It's my bed!
- Seriously...
The mountain you spoke of
was on the third floor?
The third floor is a mountain to you?
You were going to shout "Yahoo"?
Okay, I won't ever let you
shout "Yahoo" from here.
I won't let any of you do it!
I'll shout "Yahoo." I'll shout it.
I'm going to sleep in this bed with Red.
I'll shout "Yahoo!"
If you got divorced,
sleep in this bed with another man!
Gosh, just get off the bed.
What a hit.
Ma'am, please take these utensils
and plates up first.
Please hurry up.
Mister, take this rice cooker
and those kinds of things up.
Can you take my makeup stand
up the stairs?
Please use the stairs.
I'll pay you three times the price,
even if it's harder.
Why are you so strong?
Get out of here.
Mister, no! That one is not mine.
That one is Kye Sung Sook's.
Why would you move that?
If you see anything of hers up there,
throw it out the window.
Just get out of here! No, you can't.
Get that bed down.
This lady is seriously...
Put me down!
Stay right here.
That... woman is Bang Ja Young, right?
Isn't that Kye Sung Sook? Hwa Shin?
Sis, just go home.
- What was that?
- Hey!
Now you're throwing things?
Really, what in the world?
Life would be over for any man
caught by those women.
They are really scary, right?
They're my juniors,
but I didn't know they were like that.
You'd better not ever
hang around those women.
Let go, let go.
Gosh, are you serious?
You can't go in.
This is the kimchi.
- Move.
- No, no.
Hey, move.
This is the kimchi that Red likes.
Let go! Where do you think you're going?
There's only one room.
Where do you think you're going?
- Where do you think you're going?
- Red likes this kimchi!
You people are crazy!
Oh no, my kimchi.
Kimchi...
It's all really fermented.
This is the real estate office, right?
Is there anything in that neighborhood
near Rak Pasta Villa?
I don't care what it is.
Please find anything quickly, right away.
Thank you very much.
Sis, you're going to die at this rate.
You kicked Hwa Shin out
and you're not eating anything.
Are you going to die here all alone?
Just go.
Didn't Hwa Shin say anything to you?
Your daughter-in-laws, Kye Sung Sook and
Bang Ja Young moved into Red's house.
What?
Those little...
I thought about it all night.
I'm going to make Red my girl.
Go ahead.
You're not even going to
think about it for one second?
What do you want me to do?
Shouldn't you worry and
think about it for a night too?
Red kissed you too.
Move.
Hey.
How does it feel living with two moms?
It feels similar to kissing two guys.
Aren't you guys even jealous?
Is that what you wanted?
Mostly from you.
Red, you are really a mean girl.
She doesn't like either of us.
No, Red likes both of us.
If a girl has someone she likes,
she won't kiss a guy she doesn't like.
I want to see you for a bit.
Dress code is tight short shorts
and a belly t-shirt.
You're not wearing a belly t-shirt.
I felt a little strange wearing one
at this hour on the bus.
Let's do this quickly and play.
What?
What are you doing right now?
The key point in a one piece
is the waist.
It has to be precise,
down to a tenth of an inch.
You don't have the hips of an ant.
What is it? What are you doing?
I'm sponsoring your clothes, remember?
Your arms are long like a monkey's.
I'm a size 55.
I fit into anything that's a 55.
You're no longer a size 55.
You're going to wear a Pyo Na Ri size.
Not sizes like 55 or 66
like other people.
It'll be the only one in the world.
Only one, Pyo Na Ri size.
Pyo Na Ri size?
When we do fitting measurements,
it's best to wear very little.
- Don't get the wrong idea.
- I'm not.
How long will this take?
I'll do the shoes. I'll do it.
Even if it's only 60 seconds,
you have to stand.
You have to wear better shoes
than the announcers who are sitting.
For bodies like yours that are skinny
with long arms like monkeys
you have to use clothes to create curves.
It creates more femininity.
It's pretty.
So, you like it?
I do like it.
Raise your arms.
Some more.
Sorry, sorry. Don't move.
There are pins everywhere. Sorry.
From now on, don't leave my sight.
Gosh, why isn't she coming home yet?
Look at the time.
Is she out doing something bad again?
This is why she needs to
live with her mom.
- This is why I--
- Shh.
Be quiet.
Goodness.
Dad.
This is the phone you left, right?
It seems just fine.
It shouldn't be.
Look.
Oh, it really is. Oh my.
Even the videos of Reporter Lee
are still okay.
- What are you doing?
- Let's go to the hospital.
- Come on.
- Let go.
- Let's just go.
Just go.
I'll take care of it myself so let go.
Seriously?
Your surgery wound is healed now.
You'll be in trouble if you
delay this any longer.
My mom delayed it because
she had a store.
She refused to close for even a day,
delayed it, and got worse.
Later on, she ended up passing away.
Don't you have a date with Jung Won?
I'll take care of that.
What about your post-op bra?
Oh my! What are they doing?
Do you have the bra on?
Hey, get over here.
I went to my appointments and
got my dressing changed all the time.
I don't need my post-op bra
anymore and I'm fine.
Let's go.
Don't touch my body.
It's my chest.
Don't worry about it like its yours,
and don't fondle it.
Please stop worrying it.
I can't stop so what can I do?
Do you think I want to be doing this?
I don't even want to
see you anymore either.
Then don't.
But you're ignoring your own chest.
It's your chest and
you're treating it so poorly.
When I think about your chest,
it reminds me of my mom.
Can't you just let me
take care of your chest?
Do I smell like kimchi, by any chance?
No, you don't.
Good.
Before the public recruitment
people are saying that all the
anchors may be shuffled around.
I've heard about that.
There will be an announcement
about the audition soon.
I think you should go for the 9 p.m.
that Announcer Geum is doing.
The moment that Kye Sung Sook
becomes the main anchor for 9 p.m.
will be the end of us announcers.
Why is that, Chief?
If the main anchor is a female reporter
then who would sit next to her in a seat
traditionally held by female announcers?
It wouldn't just be any male announcer.
It would be a good looking,
male reporter with a bright future.
The reporters will take all the
announcer seats and we'll all disappear.
That can never happen.
We can't let it happen.
Should I drive? I'll drive.
Just get in the car.
Why would you drive my car?
- Get in.
- I can open the door.
Thank you.
Hey, are they dating?
Pyo Na Ri was touching
Reporter Lee's chest before, right?
I mean it wasn't just anyone,
but Reporter Lee's chest?
I think it's obvious that Pyo Na Ri
is throwing herself at him again.
She is really persistent.
She had a one-sided crush on him
four years ago and it's still ongoing?
Still?
Reporter Lee Hwa Shin will be going
after the 9 p.m. anchor spot too.
He'll be butting heads
with Kye Sung Sook.
You need to use that to your advantage.
Don't laugh.
They say radiation takes
only 5 to 10 minutes.
Let's go eat. I'm hungry.
Why? We have to go to the hospital.
I'm hungry.
Are you serious?
I haven't eaten all day.
We can eat after we go to the hospital.
We can do that.
I'll buy you something good.
- Eat first.
- Hospital first.
Eat first!
Stop the car.
Hurry up and stop the car.
Hey.
I've been very mentally stressed out
since yesterday, okay?
Let's have beef rib stew.
Gosh, why aren't you listening to me?
Seriously!
Am I doing this for my sake?
Is this for my own chest?
Are you going through puberty,
menopause, or what?
Why are you acting like this?
Why won't you just listen to me?
If you keep acting this way,
I'm going to tell your best friend.
You're going to get dragged
to the hospital like this.
Why do I have to deal with this secret
all on my own and suffer?
Why should I?
I think I'm so frustrated by you that
I don't think I'll live out my full life.
You know what? Forget it. Just die.
Just die quickly. I don't know.
I have to audition
to be the 9 p.m. anchor.
- Let me go.
- If...
If people find out I have breast cancer,
it's game over for me.
That place is like a ladies locker room.
I have to go every day
for six to eight weeks
so how can we keep it quiet?
I know Reporter Kye and the other
competitors will come at me like hyenas.
They will tear into me like a
piece of meat and spread rumors.
Does it make sense to have a
male anchor who had breast cancer?
People will laugh behind my back.
I have to become the
9 p.m. anchor this time.
I'll make sure no rumors arise.
Then it's okay, right?
Forget it if you don't want to.
Pyo Na Ri?
Yes, I'm Pyo Na Ri!
- Come on in.
- Okay.
Here.
Your hair is... a little...
Hey, don't touch me.
You just heard, right?
They called in Pyo Na Ri.
You were so sensitive about rumors.
Pyo Na Ri and I discussed it and
came up with special measures.
Your name will be Pyo Na Ri from now on.
In the waiting area, radiation
treatment room, and dressing room.
Even in the imaging rooms,
your name will be Pyo Na Ri.
When they call in Pyo Na Ri,
you need to come in as her guardian.
You just pretend to be a guardian.
You're not going to have
issues with this, are you?
Then people will say that
Pyo Na Ri has breast cancer.
It's just stage one.
You're stage one so people will say
that I have stage one cancer.
Maybe it's not so great to say that
I'm getting radiation therapy, but...
You should bow down
in gratitude to Pyo Na Ri.
I don't like that either.
She is on the news too.
She says she's okay with it.
That's why I told you not to
do the partial removal
and do complete removal!
Reporter, it's stage one cancer
and even with partial removal
people make a complete recovery
with radiation therapy.
Most women know that.
Even if people mistakenly think
that I do have breast cancer
I don't mind that.
You just need to get better,
Reporter Lee.
All right? Okay?
You're the one getting the radiation.
You're the one going through a hard time.
It's not like we're
actually switching places.
I'm only pretending
to have breast cancer.
What's hard about that?
You have to pretend
to be my guardian too.
Also, they say your skin will get
damaged a bit when you get radiation.
Pretending is so easy. I'll be fine.
When I see this couple,
I think the woman loves the man more.
The man should be more like
the woman in a relationship.
We're really not a couple, Doctor.
What do you mean you're not?
I... saw you two kissing.
Oh my... oh.
Why aren't you telling them
it's not true?
You're a lucky guy, Reporter Lee.
Where will you find
another girl like this?
We really aren't together, Doctor.
Okay, why don't you get a CT
and start with the markings?
Pyo Na Ri?
Yes, that's me.
- Come in.
- Okay.
Please don't move.
You have to come in every day for six
to eight weeks for radiation treatment.
Just the area of skin
receiving radiation will burn.
So, you must stay away from anything
that irritates the skin, like saunas.
We will need to check your leukocyte
and blood platelet levels once a week.
Make sure to get blood work done.
Stay away from pork belly and dairy.
Of course, no alcohol or cigarettes.
Pyo Na Ri, you are young.
That means cancer can relapse and spread
very quickly, so don't ever forget that.
Please answer, Pyo Na Ri.
Pyo Na Ri?
- Pyo Na Ri?
- Yes.
Are you really okay with it?
Just do a good job
pretending to be my guardian.
- Aren't you hungry?
- Let's eat.
Do you want to eat something?
Let's go eat.
I have plans.
They're with Go Jung Won.
Do you want to go eat with us?
- Do you want to eat with us?
- No, you guys can go.
What are you eating...
what's on the menu?
Senior.
I wasn't able to make it to
your brother's funeral.
Here you go. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I heard that you are
best friends with Go Jung Won.
Once he and I get married,
we should see each other often. Bye.
[Go Jung Won]
- Where are you?
- With Pyo Na Ri.
It's Hwa Shin.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet?
Do you trust me?
I trust you.
I don't trust you.
Enjoy your food.
Okay.
What did he say?
He must trust me.
I know because he said
he doesn't trust me.
Have you two ever fought before?
Not yet.
I wonder who would win.
It depends on whose side you take.
We have no reason to fight.
By the way...
did you get your hair done?
Yes.
Bon appetit, Chief.
Yes, let's eat.
Reporter Lee Hwa Shin will be
going after the 9 p.m. anchor spot too.
He'll be butting heads
with Kye Sung Sook.
Good job, everyone.
Good work!
I thought I was going to throw up
because of his bad breath.
What the heck did he eat?
Anchor Nam was eating pork
and onions like crazy earlier.
Oh, pretty Hye Won. Good work.
Ouch, that hurt.
Everything that comes out of
your mouth is like art.
How could every word out of
your mouth be so pretty?
Some people are scary with
every single word they speak.
Good job.
Pretend you didn't hear that.
You insulted me behind my back, right?
I think I've done a lot
to warrant you insulting me.
Go for a drink with me.
Is that an order?
I'm not really liking your
tone of voice very much...
All the seniors and juniors
pander to you.
You think you're above everyone,
don't you?
Just go for the darn drink.
Tell me what, exactly, you said about me.
Go on.
I'm an announcer... an announcer.
I only say correct things
and good things.
Don't you have any political aspirations?
Not everyone can work in the
Blue House like your father.
I should be the 9 p.m. anchor first.
You're already a strong candidate.
Says who?
The person sitting across from you
is more certain.
Who? You?
Shouldn't you work a little harder
if you want to work with me?
Ma'am, one more bottle of soju.
Yes.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
How would we work at all?
When auditioning for anchor
both anchors should have
basic pronunciations down.
When they have us both in a two-shot,
do we give off a sense of security?
Do our physical forms seem unbalanced?
Our voices, tone, and even faces.
Don't you know that the pair itself
will be judged too?
Are you going to let Reporter Kye
become the main anchor?
I guess you could put in
some shoulder pads.
What?
I'd rather die than work with
a man with bad breath again.
Look at that.
You don't smell no matter what you eat.
You ate garlic, mussels, and snails.
Why don't you smell?
Do you have feelings for me?
Not yet.
Try sitting next to me.
It won't be too bad.
You're arrogant.
Who are you telling to sit next to you?
I know you want to.
Why don't you be a little honest?
Isn't it a win-win for both of us?
I have to win first place in the
audition to get the 9 p.m. slot.
But it would be a faster path
to get chosen by you?
I should do the news while
looking over my shoulder at you.
We could hold hands under the desk
while doing the news.
We could play footsie too.
We could date, love... even marry.
It doesn't matter to me
if you like someone.
Wouldn't it change right now?
Inside your heart?
A lot of women are interested
in my heart these days.
I've never met someone as bold as you.
How many men have you dated in this way?
About a hundred?
I'm dating someone right now.
I'll dump him if you agree
to sit next to me.
Hey...
Every man has left me
because he couldn't handle me.
I don't think you would, Senior.
What's your reason for doing this to me?
You're good at your job.
You treat me like I'm nothing.
Because of that... you're attractive.
Is this because I drank?
Are you sleeping?
I think it's because I drank alcohol.
My chest is itchy.
It's weird.
Do you have that ointment
that was prescribed before?
You always sleep facing the wall.
Where should we meet tomorrow?
There are people watching and all.
Let's meet two blocks away from
the station at the intersection, okay?
Are you sleeping? Look at me.
Oh, you're doing a face mask.
Are you sleeping with
your clothes off again?
Hey, it's fall already.
You'll catch a cold.
Yes, I got it from the meteorological
office, edited it, and sent it.
Yes, please check. Thank you.
Why is it so cold already?
Is it going to be winter soon?
Is he asleep?
He'd better not be drinking.
He can't drink.
I thought she'd throw a fit
if I told her I drank.
How odd...
Oh my goodness!
They're dating! Oh my gosh.
Pyo Na Ri, we're going to start.
Camera start.
Ready... cue!
On your way to work this morning
you will need to make sure
to carry an umbrella.
We have cold autumn rain falling today.
The rain...
Considering that it is fall,
a lot of rain is expected.
Everyone, please be careful
of catching a cold.
Attention.
Let's go out for a
company dinner tonight.
What? What's the matter?
I will be making some announcements
about the anchor auditions.
Now do you want to come? Huh?
Everyone has to come.
Announcers and weathercasters too.
Got it?
You're going to that pork belly place
we always go to, right?
- Go to a different place.
- You want Thai food?
Then, you pay.
Gosh, he can't eat pork belly.
You asked to meet here last night?
Gosh...
You must have forgotten in your sleep.
Doctor Geum said you must never drink.
What are you going to do tonight?
You can't eat pork belly either,
but it's always that pork belly place.
You shouldn't have slept undressed.
Here you go.
What?
- Undressed?
- It's not like you're at home.
I told you.
Hey, hey, hey!
Stop just eating the meat.
Let's have a drink too!
Cheers, everyone.
Cheers!
Open your mouth wide.
Say "Ah."
He's not supposed to eat pork belly,
drink, smoke, or anything.
Ma'am, can you get me an order of
beef that's very lean with no fat.
Just one order, please.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Cheers! Drink up, okay?
Stop eating the
pork belly meat, would you?
Eat this beef, okay?
I'm fine. Go sit down.
- What are you going to do?
- This is how these things are.
All right, everyone's settled in?
I want to say this one more time
before we get going.
This time around, the audition will be
aired live on an internal SBC network.
So, I will take into account
what all of you think.
You have to do well.
One more thing.
The president was going to use
a ranking-based system.
He was going to give
Lee Hwa Shin the top
with Reporter Kye on the bottom.
I fought him on that.
We put everyone on the same level.
Wow!
I'm not saying this to show off.
I'm just willing to do what it takes
for our news department.
Okay? All right? Do a good job.
Let's drink! Yeah!
All right, next, Assistant Director Choi.
Okay! Salute!
I am in line with the news department!
Salute, Director.
- Drink, drink.
- Salute!
Director, salute!
You're good at it.
Next, my lovable brother-in-law.
Yes, okay. I'll do it.
Cheers. Thank you.
Reporter Kye, I'll accept that love.
Please give it to me.
Why do you love me?
- I don't want your love.
- No.
I have to accept your love
no matter what. I will drink this.
Hey, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Director, Reporter Kye, and Chief Bang.
Salute to all of you!
Oh, okay.
Wow, what's with you?
Why would you steal his drink though?
- Here. Have another one.
- Yes, Director.
Let's just finish having drinks.
Thank you for the drink.
Director, I'll accept your love too.
- Okay.
- She was thirsty for love.
I'm okay. I'm fine.
You couldn't have one drink.
- Reporter Lee, have one drink.
- Okay.
Hey!
Let's do a cheers.
You came back?
She's crazy.
Hwa Shin, I'll pour you a drink.
You can do it!
Drink with me, okay?
Are you his black rose?
It must be nice for you.
You have a black rose.
I'll have that! I really wanted it.
Here you go, Hwa Shin.
Salute!
You're here again?
I'll drink it.
You should eat something.
- You're back?
- Yes.
I'll do it. I will.
What is she doing?
- Order more. Order more.
- No more.
Director!
I am a tree that does not break
even in the most treacherous storm.
The reason I am living in the world is
because the 21st century wanted it.
In the heat of the south city!
In the heat of the south city...
An empty Manchurian plain!
there is an empty Manchurian plain!
Kye Sung Sook was really cool
back when we were in school.
If only she didn't sing.
That's true. She's a terrible singer.
Who's next?
Hwa Shin. Get up and sing.
If you don't sing,
you'll lose points for your audition.
You'll look better to people if you sing.
All of your seniors did it.
- You're going to sing?
- I'll find a song.
I am always longing for you.
Where have you gone to?
Let's do another song.
Director, don't let her do that one.
My love, please come back to me.
Come back to me.
Return to me.
All my thoughts are filled with you.
I can't escape this
passionate love for you.
My love, come back...
Hey, hey.
Hwa Shin, you have to do
"Wrongful Encounter."
"Wrongful Encounter"!
"Wrongful Encounter." Encore.
I trusted you as much
as I trusted my friend.
I introduced you to my friend
without a second thought.
The three of us met
many times after that.
We had many happy
and joyful times together.
I don't know where things
started to go wrong.
I started to get a bad feeling.
You started to show
more interest in my friend.
You started to distance yourself from me.
That day, you and I...
It was after we had an argument.
Both you and my friend stopped calling.
It seemed like you were avoiding me.
That's when I felt it.
Everything had gone wrong.
You and my friend...
had somehow become a couple.
I cried to myself that this
couldn't be happening...
Hey, hey. He left.
Pyo Na Ri, are you okay?
Are you...
Gosh.
How much did she drink?
I'm right in front of the station.
If you're not busy right now,
can you come pick me up?
I went out with the news department.
Everyone had a bit to drink.
Who was that?
It sounded like Announcer Geum Soo Jung.
- Go and drive Announcer Geum home.
- Me... me?
Go now and take her home yourself.
If you keep this up,
I have my own ideas of what to do.
Do whatever you want.
Do you want me to live like you?
Dad treated you like you didn't exist,
as if he didn't know you.
I'm going to marry someone I like.
Just let me have that.
I can give you 99 other things.
Let me plan your marriage my way.
Then I can let you have the
99 other things your way.
Are you okay?
Should I call Jung Won?
No, it's fine.
Don't call him.
Why? Jung Won can bring a car.
No, I don't want him to see me like this.
I'm embarrassed.
Then, I'll take you home.
No, I have a broadcast
in the morning so I can't.
- Go to the station.
- Okay.
I'm so cold.
I'll go quickly.
Why didn't you dress warmer?
Now you have a cold.
I'm fine. You should go sleep.
Maybe you shouldn't drink either.
It's not like I have cancer
or I'm getting radiation.
Are you the boss of my drinking?
Why would you drink
all that so recklessly?
How much did you drink?
I want to sleep. Just go so I can sleep.
Okay.
I'll be in the dorm rooms.
Call me if you're having a hard time.
Okay?
Why are you being so nice suddenly?
It's really weird.
You're being really weird.
Did you eat something bad?
Will I be able to wake up
tomorrow morning?
Oh, but I'm so sleepy. What do I do?
You don't think you will?
I'm scared but I'm so sleepy.
I don't think I should sleep though.
My head hurts and my stomach hurts.
And why is it so cold outside?
What do I do? I'm so tired.
But what if I can't wake up?
If I miss my shoot,
I'll be in big trouble.
I'll really get fired this time.
I can't even sleep.
What am I supposed to do?
Sleep. Just sleep.
I'll wake you up. Go to sleep.
Gosh, it's so cold.
I'm sleepy.
[Go Jung Won]
I lied earlier.
I was holding my breath before.
Can you make it one inch wider?
I already did.
Did you think I wouldn't know?
Subtitles by DramaFever
Do you like Pyo Na Ri?
Reporter Lee is dating the
weather forecaster, Pyo Na Ri.
I don't like Reporter Lee.
I really, really don't like him.
Do you like her by yourself?
Like a one-sided love?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Were you that easy of a man?
I really like you.
Why would you wait there
on a day like today?
What am I supposed to do?
Please don't be there.
Don't be there.
Don't be there. You can't be there.