Subtitles by DramaFever
When I think about your chest,
it reminds me of my mom.
Can't you just let me
take care of your chest?
[Go Jung Won]
Bye, Reporter! Get home safe.
[Episode 9]
Bye!
- Goodbye.
- Bye now!
Bye!
Get home quickly everyone.
Get in, Director.
Goodbye, Director.
So, how long has it been going on?
I know, right?
Reporter Lee and Pyo Na Ri
left together early?
They sneaked out together?
Did you see the expression
on Reporter Lee's face?
Thank you for coming like this, Jung Won.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Put on your seatbelt.
Are you angry because
I drank and called you?
I can't do these things
once we get married.
I came because I had
something to tell you.
We'll talk tomorrow when you're sober.
You know your friend
Reporter Lee Hwa Shin?
I heard he's dating the
weather forecaster, Pyo Na Ri.
There's a rumor all over the station.
Maybe you already knew.
How can Chef not even have
ramen in the house?
It's Rak's car.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my child.
Don't you have anything to say?
Are you going to pretend to sleep?
Reporter Lee Hwa Shin found at the scene
sleeping in the same bed as Pyo Na Ri.
What is the situation?
What is it that you're thinking?
Do you like Pyo Na Ri?
I was taking Pyo Na Ri back because
she had all those drinks for me.
She has a cold and she was shivering,
so I got a blanket for her.
Then I got sleepy too,
so I fell asleep.
This is what I think.
If you were facing each other
or sleeping in each other's arms
I would have just turned around and left.
If two people like each other,
I don't like to get involved.
However...
Hey.
It was like this.
Pyo Na Ri had her back to you.
You were sleeping while facing her back.
Also, on top of the blanket.
So what?
You were holding her without her
knowing after she fell asleep.
A drunk Pyo Na Ri,
who won't know a thing tomorrow.
I suppose so.
She seemed to be doting on you all night.
But Pyo Na Ri's eyes were like
those of a girl doing her homework.
Women know what that looks like.
Therefore, you like her by yourself.
It's a one-sided love.
Alone... and secretly.
One-sided? Alone and secretly?
Me?
You're saying I have a
one-sided love for Pyo Na Ri?
That's ridiculous. That's nonsense.
Are you talking or farting?
It was a mistake.
It was the alcohol.
This won't happen again.
It won't, right?
It shouldn't.
Also, would you cut your nails?
You nearly poked my eyes out.
I nearly lost my sight.
You and Pyo Na Ri don't suit one another.
Gosh, you smell like alcohol.
She won't be able to get up at 3 a.m.
Where are you?
[Giving up is only an excuse
for the loser.]
Have I gone crazy?
Therefore, you like her by yourself.
It's a one-sided love.
Alone... and secretly.
No, it was the alcohol.
[It ain't over till it's over.
- Yogi Berra]
After a breast cancer surgery
people can experience
mental changes due to hormones.
Is it the hormones?
- What are you doing here alone?
- You scared me.
You started coming here again?
I still have the key that
the manager gave me too.
Jung Won.
This brings back memories.
Should we have a match?
You can't let me off easy.
I have to get my butt
kicked by you today.
I need to take a beating
to pull myself together.
- Why?
So that I can sober up quickly.
We always used to
go boxing after drinking.
Just hit me so that
I can really sober up.
It's been a long time since
I've felt your punch, Jung Won.
You shouldn't go easy on me either.
Should we make a bet?
- A bet?
- We always made a bet.
You're going to win this game.
I'm going to lose to you.
I'm going to let you hit me
until I'm on the brink of death.
What's the fun in that?
There will be trouble
if you're looking for fun.
It's not like we have an audience.
We don't need it to be fun.
- Okay.
Fight back, okay?
What do you mean you'll lose?
You'll lose if you do.
You're going to lose?
Do you feel sober now
that you've been hit?
You feel the alcohol coming up,
don't you?
I deserve to be hit. I deserve it.
Hey! No hitting me in the back.
Don't look the other way.
Sorry.
Hey!
Are you going to keep
hitting me in the back?
Sorry, I got caught up and lost control.
You want to go all the way?
You want to go all out?
Who said I want that? I don't want that.
Hurry up and count.
I'm down. Lee Hwa Shin is down.
You didn't let me win
because I'm a friend, right?
You don't even need to
count to 10. I'm KO'ed.
- You lost?
- I lost.
I really shouldn't sleep.
I can't sleep.
[Victory is determined
outside of the ring.]
Who did you drink with?
It was a newsroom department dinner.
Why did you come here alone?
I won't be able to sleep well anyway.
I was going to exercise, sober up,
then go wake Pyo Na Ri up.
You were?
Yeah, she has to go on at 6 a.m.
It's okay.
- I'll wake her up.
- Huh?
I'll wake her up. Oh...
Secretary Cha, bring over
what I chose for Hwa Shin.
You know that dress we measured out
last time for Pyo Na Ri?
The one I made myself, the blue one.
Yes, bring that one. Okay.
Do you know what size
Pyo Na Ri's feet are?
I'm not sure.
250! That's big for a woman, right?
Maybe it's because she stands for work
but the soles of her feet
are calloused too.
You've seen the bottoms of her feet?
Her feet are cold.
She doesn't have a car,
so she can't even sleep at home.
She's always traveling around.
I want to give her good shoes.
Take a shower and get some sleep.
You shouldn't have to
stay up all night too.
Don't worry about Pyo Na Ri.
I'll wake her up.
There's a rumor that
you're dating Pyo Na Ri.
What?
How did a rumor like that start?
It's wrong, right?
Yeah.
Why isn't this thing coming off?
I'll let her sleep for five more minutes.
Is she dreaming?
"I like you."
When will I hear that from you?
It's almost time. Let's get started.
Check the location of the cameras.
Be careful of your hands.
Tell Assistant Director Choi
to come down.
Let's change the order of these.
This one first and then this.
Here.
I made this myself.
This isn't a sponsored dress.
It's from that day?
My first present.
President Go.
Could I get sponsored by your
clothing company, as well?
- Do a good job.
- Okay.
He's Lee Hwa Shin's best friend, right?
- Give it to me.
- What?
Why?
But... this is mine.
It's a dress that was sponsored
to be on the news.
Didn't you just hear him?
It's not a sponsored dress.
It was given to me.
Also, it was made specially for me.
You're going to be on for five minutes.
I'm going to be on for two hours.
Can't you make a sacrifice?
Hand it over while she's asking nicely.
She's asking you for it.
No, it's mine!
I will never give it to you.
What... what?
Help!
Seriously, this woman!
What was she thinking...
Gosh, she reeks of alcohol.
Oh my goodness!
Oh no! Oh no!
Oh, I must be crazy. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm crazy.
I must be insane. I really am.
What am I going to do?
What should I do?
I'm just too old for all of this.
But I drank too much and
I ended up here. What do I do?
Just kill me now or please save me, Chef.
I'm just so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I don't know what to do.
What should I do?
It was just a mistake.
I will head down first.
Come down for breakfast.
Yes, I will.
Gosh, what do I do?
It's not what you think.
Wow.
I'm going to run away if
you do this one more time.
I'm sorry. It was my mistake.
I feel like vomiting.
I'm sorry, Red. It won't happen again.
- Mom was wrong.
- Get out.
- Red!
Okay, okay. I'll get out.
All right, I said I'll get out.
You're crazy. You're must be crazy.
Oh my goodness!
Oh my!
What do you want, Reporter Kye?
Don't tell me you... already?
- You!
- Oh, I'm so hungry.
Chef, were you that easy of a man?
It's been a long time since
the air has been this clean.
The concentration of fine dust and smog
is at normal to good
in the country today.
There is no rain in the forecast,
so it will be perfect for dates...
Good. Anchor, stand by.
Park Jin, why do you keep
pouting like that?
Hey, Pyo Na Ri looks pretty today.
Enjoy this clear fall day.
That was the weather.
Cue.
Pyo Na Ri, thank you for the weather.
The weather is bright and Pyo Na Ri,
you look very bright, as well.
It seems being in love
makes one beautiful.
They say that intra-office dating
is the flower of dating.
What's she talking about?
I see the flower has bloomed.
That was today's News Morning.
I hope you have a day filled with love.
- What is she saying?
- You didn't know, Director?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
It's good for your hangover.
Thank you, Chef.
It's very delicious, Chef.
Why is everything so salty?
I don't want to eat it.
- What's with him, Uncle?
- It's nothing.
Eat up.
The adults should
live an upstanding life.
They are worse than us.
What's up with Red, Uncle?
You kids don't need to know.
Kids?
There are no kids here.
They should be busy studying and
they're busy kissing each other.
It's a love triangle, at that.
They're very complicated, too.
Why are you treating them
like little kids?
You're all in a love triangle, right?
Reporter Kye!
Give me some stew too.
I drank yesterday too.
I also need to get over my hangover.
Yes, I was going to give you some.
Pyo Na Ri lives up on the roof.
Doesn't your sister ever come home?
Is she sleeping elsewhere?
You shouldn't trust your sister too much.
Why would you say such a thing?
They say your sister is dating someone.
It's Reporter Lee Hwa Shin, apparently.
You didn't know, did you?
You thought she wasn't coming home
because of her morning broadcasts, right?
Your sister is pretty skilled
at other things.
What are you saying?
Reporter Lee Hwa Shin? You mean that--
Come on! Can't you just shut your mouth?
We're all trying to eat.
This is a place for family
to gather and eat happily.
I know you must be a great person
at work with no one to answer to.
No, you go around saying whatever
you please to the entire nation.
You keep going on and on,
making people lose their appetite!
Don't come down tomorrow.
I will not feed you, Reporter Kye. Okay?
He's so cool.
You are not allowed in this kitchen
starting tomorrow.
Okay, everyone stop. Let's talk.
What was that?
Park Jin, are you insane?
Why would you bring up dating in
the office and talk about love on air?
Who cares about who's dating whom?
Hwa Shin, are you...
Are you really...
What is this all about?
Gosh, come on, Director!
- It's not true.
- What isn't?
You always said that the forecasters
were part of the news department.
You said to take care of them.
That's all I've ever done.
How could you think we would...
that is such nonsense.
Why would people say these things?
Hong Hye Won.
Would you please help me out?
Why are you all being like this?
All these people are doubting me.
Pyo Na Ri, don't you feel wronged?
Why don't you speak up?
It's not true, everyone.
I don't like Reporter Lee.
I really, really do not like him.
Director, I won't be dating at work.
That won't ever happen.
That won't happen even in the future.
You don't need to worry.
Wow, seriously.
Let's not be this way
as a broadcast family.
Na Ri, you were really good
at lying back there.
"I really don't like Reporter Lee.
I really don't, Director!"
"I really, really do not like him."
Announcer Park Jin.
Reporter Lee's feelings must be hurt.
Even if you had to put on
a show in front of everyone.
- Na Joo Hee.
- Na Ri.
You got this dress
by dating Reporter Lee.
Didn't you get it from his friend
by flattering him?
Flattering him?
Hey, you!
You just won't stop, will you?
If you're an announcer,
you should act like one.
You should report only the truth.
How could you tell a complete lie to the
entire nation first thing in the morning?
And you.
Do you have to get involved in this
and try to instigate a fight?
You thought I didn't know
because I didn't bring it up?
You purposely spilled that sauce on me
so that I'd have to wear a belly t-shirt.
Then I got fired.
Then you refused to leave
my weather slot as if it were yours.
You caused a broadcast accident.
That was mine! It was mine!
What did you say before?
I was flattering men to get this dress?
Me? I did that?
You're about as loyal as the electric tax
that fluctuates
between summer and winter.
You wench!
Have you seen the impossible happen?
Why would you start a rumor
that I'm dating Reporter Lee?
- Do you want to die?
- It's true, though.
Hey! It's true?
I can only breathe
because I have two nostrils.
If not, I would have died due
to suffocation by now because of you.
Seriously, you...
Na Ri, you're the only pretending
to be so innocent.
Then you go around playing men.
You should have taken it off.
I wouldn't have gone so far then.
Let go! Do you know
what kind of dress this is?
We're really not dating!
That's enough.
Just move it!
It's not true! I don't like Reporter Lee.
He really isn't that great!
Am I crazy? Why would I like him?
I'm sick and tired of him,
just sick and tired!
If I ever end up dating him,
I will just eat my words.
If I end up dating him,
I'm not Pyo Na Ri, but Pi Na Ri.
All right! That's enough!
Even if he's the
last man left in the world
I won't like him again, okay?
Go home and sleep.
Don't sleep in the dorm all the time.
Are you busy?
Are you in a good mood?
Why are you so happy?
Have you gone insane?
Why would you bother
getting into a fight like that?
Do I look pretty, Reporter?
Are you crazy?
I don't look pretty?
You look pretty... you do.
You try some too. Here.
Why not?
It's nice if male anchors
have plump and shiny lips.
Let's go eat. I think you're hungry.
Reporter, buy this for me.
Why would I buy it for you?
To commemorate rumors of us dating?
Pull yourself together, would you?
- Reporter Lee.
- What the...
I am so happy today.
My pride felt so crushed
and now it feels like
it's been revived all at once.
- I'm so happy.
- What?
The entire station knew that I was in a
one-sided love with you for three years.
Do you know how embarrassed I was?
But now people are saying
we are dating each other.
That's a big deal.
"He's finally fallen for Pyo Na Ri.
He likes Pyo Na Ri."
That's what people will be saying.
Before, I was just pretending to be mad
and fighting like it was real.
Honestly, I am so happy.
It feels like my sadness was constipation
and it's gone down like diarrhea.
It would have been better if the rumor
was that you were in a one-sided love.
That would've been better.
That would've been the icing on the cake.
I'm being too greedy, right?
You like her by yourself.
It's a one-sided love.
Alone... and secretly.
Move.
I only did it to borrow this.
Let's go, let's go.
That's a 20 percent discount
for full-time employees.
Contract employees don't get it?
What the heck? That's discriminatory.
I'll just bring you along
every time I buy makeup.
Well...
It's okay as long as
you and I know it's not true.
Why are you so concerned with
what others think?
It will be over so soon.
I say maybe three days.
- You have a runny nose.
- What?
- A runny nose.
- Oh, do I?
Do you find me comfortable?
Yes.
Give it to me.
Should I throw it out for you?
I would be thankful if you did.
It's not like you, Reporter.
I'm not even a man to you, am I?
- What?
- You throw it away.
What's with him?
I didn't ask him to throw it away.
He's the one who volunteered.
Why is he getting mad?
It's the breast cancer.
Pyo Na Ri changed after
my breast cancer surgery.
She wasn't like that before.
Reporter, you should take this back.
Just as long as Go Jung Won
doesn't hear this rumor...
It's okay as long as he doesn't know.
Hey, is Jung Won the only person
you worry about?
I'm the victim of this rumor.
You're the one who set me up with him.
Wouldn't you feel awkward
if he heard this rumor?
It would be weird between friends.
When did you start thinking of
my friend more than I do?
Am I wrong in what I'm saying?
You're the one who set me up with him,
so why are you acting like this?
You said we should give it a try.
If my breast cancer relapses,
it is all your fault.
What?
Am I not allowed to be here?
I'm planning to live here.
Both of you can leave.
We're glad you're here, Mother.
You're late. I thought you'd come
on the day we moved in.
I'll be walking over you.
Why, those little...
All the rooms are full.
You should use the living room, Mother.
There is only one bathroom,
so we have to take turns.
We have to go to work.
I guess you can use it early mornings.
You don't sleep late in the morning.
Can you lift your legs for us?
Hey! Do you think that I'm joking?
Don't use up your strength
on the first day.
We are very serious.
Since you'll be here,
you can cook breakfast for Red.
We can eat too.
You can do our laundry
when you do Red's laundry.
How nice.
Look at the state this house is in.
That's what we're saying.
It turned out this way with just us.
Lock the door, Mother.
Oh yes! Please accept a package for me.
Then, Mother...
- We will go to work now.
Those two!
Why, those two!
Yes, Jung Won. Okay.
Today is your mom and dad's
wedding anniversary.
Your dad will come.
There's no need for you
to come, Jung Won.
I'm already here.
Have breakfast with me, Mom.
Dad told me to give this to you.
You open it.
It's always the same thing,
like another plane ticket to somewhere.
Why is your father always trying to
get me to go somewhere?
[Divorce Notice]
It's our wedding anniversary.
No matter how busy he is
he should at least have
one meal with me today.
How could he just send that?
He sent tickets for a cruise
on the Mediterranean Sea.
Sit down.
Have some good food with an
even more handsome man, Mom.
[SBC's Geum Soo Jung,
L Group's Go Jung Won Dating]
[SBC Public Recruitment Application]
[Announcer]
[Morning News]
We'll do the earthquake story
as the second one.
Do the foreign correspondent
for the first one.
She's so lucky.
No wonder her news is so soulless.
She's dating a rich man.
Yeah, look how happy she looks.
- I'm so envious.
- Me too.
No need to be envious. Let's go drink.
- Let's eat too.
- Pork?
- I'm in.
- Me too.
Just get my dad on the phone now!
Dad.
At least see Mom three times
if you want to get a divorce.
Then if you still feel
you need to get a divorce...
I will help you split up, so please...
don't leave her to wither away
and die like that.
Just go see her three times.
She's my mom, Dad!
What did she do that was so wrong?
Mom forgave you for everything
you've done wrong.
Here...
Your mother ordered this yesterday.
President.
President?
Let's go to the station.
But, Announcer Geum Soo Jung
is there too.
We can't do that.
[Go Jung Won]
How much will it cost
to get all those articles taken down?
What?
She can't see this article.
Contact the meteorological office.
Good work.
- Chief Bang.
- Congratulations, Announcer Geum.
- Are you two really getting married?
- Ah, yes.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
You two are alike
and suit each other well.
He seems like a good fit. Congrats.
Thank you, Reporter Kye. Thank you.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
You should confirm with Jung Won.
Three days?
The rumor about us dating
only needed hours to die off.
What a relief.
Do you think that rumor is wrong
just like our rumor was?
Excuse me.
This is from a Mister Go Jung Won.
Do you know who
Announcer Geum Soo Jung is?
That person.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh!
Wow, they're pretty.
I could pay my rent for a year
with what those flowers cost.
Where are you going?
L Group's Go Jung Won and SBC's Announcer
Geum Soo Jung are said to be dating.
Stockholders are watching
with great interest.
Last night, President Go Jung Won picked
up Announcer Geum from a company outing.
He was seen picking her up.
Both households are
said to be in talks...
You two are alike
and suit each other well.
He seems like a good fit.
Everything Announcer Geum
says is so pretty.
That's why I want an announcer
daughter-in-law like me.
How many points was I lacking compared
to the two people who passed?
Don't hold on to regrets.
Regrets will make things
harder for you in the future.
Who cares if it rains or not?
"I like you."
When will I hear that from you?
Pyo Na...
Pyo Na Ri!
This customer is currently unavailable...
Have you found Pyo Na Ri?
She's not picking up her phone.
Is she here at the station?
Isn't she hiding because of you?
You made her hide,
so why are you looking for her?
It's nothing big.
Nothing big?
I want to see this through
to the end with Pyo Na Ri.
Help me out.
She's getting hurt because of this.
Whether it's going to the end,
middle, or start...
if Pyo Na Ri has to suffer through it,
I take back setting you up with her.
Do whatever you have to do to find her.
Make sure it's you who finds her.
Don't leave her alone
to be sad like that.
Where are you and what are doing?
Oh! Isn't that Geum Soo Jung?
Geum Soo Jung! One moment, please!
No, it's not her.
- I told you it wasn't her.
- Oh, it's not?
Sorry, I got confused.
I'm here to meet Go Jung Won.
He's not here right now.
Did you have an appointment?
No, I just came by.
Please give this to him.
Is she an announcer
or a weather forecaster?
A weather forecaster.
It's President Go! President Go!
- One comment, please.
- Are you really dating Announcer Geum?
Are you acknowledging
that you two are dating?
How long have you two been dating?
- One comment.
- Just one comment!
Can you give us one comment?
Do you have anything to say?
You know your friend
Reporter Lee Hwa Shin?
I heard he's dating the
weather forecaster, Pyo Na Ri.
There's a rumor all over the station.
I hear she's a weather forecaster.
Be good to her.
Lend her nice clothes and good shoes.
However, that's it.
I can understand Dad at times like this.
Go on a cruise instead of
interfering with your son's life.
You're behaving this way because you
have too much time on your hands!
Are you telling me
to divorce your father?
[Taeyang Hospital Appointment]
She can't be...
Lee Hwa Shin, you have an
appointment at 6:30 p.m. today.
Please come to the third floor
radiation treatment clinic.
Please don't be there.
Don't be there.
You can't be there.
If you're there on a day like today,
if you're waiting there...
what am I supposed to do?
I can't let you go to another guy.
What are you doing here?
Why are you standing here?
We talked about it at the hospital.
We have to go for treatment at 6:30 p.m.
We have to go to
the radiation department.
Then we have to go to
the breast cancer department.
We agreed to meet here
30 minutes before the appointment.
You won't go on your own.
What did you do this whole time?
Were you alone?
- I was hungry, so I bought ramen.
- Alone?
My mouth hurts. Don't talk to me.
Where are you going?
We have to go to the hospital.
You're going the opposite direction.
You can trust Jung Won.
There was a rumor about us dating, too.
People said we liked each other,
but are we dating?
We're not.
Just like our rumor is false,
Jung Won's is false too.
We have to go now to get to
your appointment on time.
Are you crazy?
Why are you driving so fast?
Slow down.
I feel like I'm going go crazy
if we delay this by even one minute.
There won't be another chance
for you or Jung Won.
What?
This isn't the right way to the hospital.
Where are you going?
He's  liked you since he first saw you
on the flight to Thailand.
He wished you were sitting
next to him on the flight back.
He has flown so many miles,
you can't even fathom how many.
He's flown around
the world multiple times.
And you were the first person
he ever wanted to sit next to.
Jung Won probably
didnt send those flowers either.
He doesn't like white flowers.
Jung Won, that punk, is a crazy guy
who even sends flowers to me.
He sent flowers to me
when I won a journalism award.
He only ever sends blue flowers.
The dress he spent all night making
for you was blue too.
Let's trust Jung Won.
He's a lonelier person than I am.
He's more thoughtful than I am.
He would treat a girl
better than I would.
He's richer than me.
More than anything... he's healthy.
He's manly and he's tall.
He wants to give you good shoes and
take you to better places than I would.
He's just a better...
Anyway, do you think I
set you up with him for no reason?
Also, Jung Won is a victim!
It may seem like he lives his life
doing whatever he pleases.
He doesn't do anything he wants.
I know that.
Why did you set me up
with such a good person?
He's called you over 100 times.
[113 missed calls: Go Jung Won]
I'll drive you to him.
[Pyo Na Ri]
President.
Pyo Na Ri came to return this earlier.
The reporters left once I told them you
would make an announcement tomorrow.
Go on in.
Why don't we go to the hospital now?
Get out.
You move quickly.
What's the meaning of this?
Why did you return it?
What was the rush that
you didn't even talk to me...
Why did you return it
without even one word to me?
Was someone chasing you or something?
Was I someone who deserved to be
doubted by you, Pyo Na Ri?
What happened to your face?
Do you not trust me at all?
It might be too late.
I might as well say it now.
I like you.
"I like you."
When will I hear that from you?
It's not too late.
Pyo Na Ri was so wrong.
It's raining.
She said it'd be
good weather for dates.
Pyo Na Ri...
so wrong.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Please, just get out of my sight!
Just leave!
Why are you always causing me grief?
So, I cause you grief?
I can't remember
the last time I was loved.
Maybe it's because
I'm not used to receiving love.
I'm going to make an effort
with Go Jung Won.
You can't ever tell him that I was in a
one-sided love with you for three years.
What are you going to do?
Who are you going to date?
I'm going to date Announcer Hong.
You should tell Pyo Na Ri
that you like her.
Don't you feel like your three years of
one-sided love would go to waste?
I'll do everything for you. Let's date.