[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Why isn't he saying anything?
I'm not getting yelled at.
This is uncomfortable.
[March, 2012]
Hello, I'm a rookie. My name Kim Ji Shin.
Hello! I'm a rookie. My name is Go Ho!
I will work hard, no matter
what you ask me to do!
Victory! Victory! Victory!
[August, 2012]
Do I pick this one or this one?
I don't know which one.
Which one?
Thank you!
[December, 2012]
I'll be working on Christmas.
Geez, I hate it.
What about you, Go Ho?
Are you still dating that guy
you got set up with?
It's going well.
I think he might officially confess
his feelings for me on Christmas.
Wow! This is the best time of year!
[February, 2013]
What did he say, what did he say?
He just said that he likes me.
Wow! That's so great.
Let me see, let me see. It's so pretty.
Oh, my! Let me see your hand.
Ho, did you analyze all of the data
that I gave you yesterday?
What kind of a company
makes a storyboard like this?
What are you looking at? Look away.
[February, 2015]
[March, 2016]
Really?
I can send Go Ho to Team B?
What's up with that?
You insisted on keeping her with you.
Now, I think...
she should stop being on my team.
This is the new manager, Hwang Ji Hoon.
He will lead Team B.
Let's all welcome him.
[Episode 10: Waiting]
You're awake?
When did I fall asleep?
You should ask how much you slept.
How much did I sleep?
An hour and a half.
I thought I was driving a corpse.
Because of the Promise account,
I haven't gotten any sleep.
Thanks to you, I got some sleep.
Right.
We shouldn't be talking
to each other like this.
As long as you keep your
mouth shut, no one will know.
Anyway... thank you for driving me home.
Why were you crying?
That...
I can't tell you.
- Why?
- It's personal.
Manager... you're my manager--
Mister, you called me.
Think of me like that and tell me.
Then...
think of me like
an older brother and tell me.
What!
Hey! Do you think I like saying that?
I don't like that
"older brother" kind of thing!
I think you totally like it.
- I think you're a maniac for it.
- No, I'm not!
Forget it.
You should go.
Kang Tae Ho must have gone crazy.
What are you looking at? Look away.
It's always hard to look
Kang Tae Ho straight in the eyes.
But, right now...
all of the cells in my body
feel like they're doing the twist.
No way. No way.
Is he really...
What did you get on your face?
You want everyone to know that you cried?
Why are you closing your eyes?
What kind of wild fantasy
was I dreaming up?
Go on in.
Don't cry while you sleep.
You're already ugly.
You'll really be scary if you cry more.
Don't be a pain in the ass tomorrow.
Come to work looking normal.
Yes.
What?
Does Manager Kang like you?
When I was looking at him in the car,
I was confused for a moment too.
I'm going to assume he doesn't.
No, I don't think so.
Why would he go to
a rest stop in Jukjeon at that time?
Men, especially men like Manager Kang,
don't do things for no reason.
I don't think that's true
for men, these days.
They say they like you, they ask to sleep
with you, and then they date other women.
Kang Tae Ho doesn't even say anything.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
That's why you have to look at
a man's actions, rather than his words.
That's what I'm saying. Actions.
You're on Team B, starting today.
Be happy on your new team.
Is he a sadist?
Then, you need an exorcism.
- An exorcism?
- A sadist after that idiot, Oh Jung Min.
Then you need one.
But... if you think about it carefully
it was Kang Tae Ho who prevented you from
getting fired over that old client issue.
People say you're a good worker now
because of what you learned from him.
He introduced you to all
of the good people in the office.
A boss that opened up
all of his connections to you...
That's not easy, you know.
But... you know how I went to Team B?
That was Manager Kang's request.
- Oh, my. Why?
- That's what I'm saying!
If he had any interest in me,
why would he push me away?
I won't be jumping to conclusions again.
Who put this lid on so tight?
We know we're in a competition.
We're not talking about work.
I have the jam and she has bread.
Hee Yeon. Maybe Kang Tae Ho is a sadist.
I must be a masochist. I must be.
Hey, what was that, just now?
That handsome man with the long legs.
Hey, hey... Was that...
was that Manager Kang?
He's really hot!
Marry him!
I like beef stew better than noodles.
He excites me.
Manager Kang, can you open this?
I'll open it for you.
Senior, we really want
to win this competition!
I don't like that we're called Team B.
Say that we lose...
we'll be treated as the lesser team.
Besides Seo Woon, they all
have really good records.
No. Oh Jung Ming isn't that great either.
Let's get things straight.
Besides Senior Lee Hee Yeon,
they are all just...
I still feel like we're losing.
It's annoying.
- So annoying!
- It's annoying!
- We do not want to lose!
What?
[Four Days Before Final Promise Pitch]
They changed the production team.
The new director doesn't have much
experience, but he has a good record.
He's supposed to be great.
They're going with one plan.
That means that they're confident.
- Ours isn't bad either.
- No, it's not bad. It's not bad.
We don't love it though.
Manager Hwang, we think
it's better to just lay it all out here.
Senior Go Ho hasn't been
on this team for that long.
I know that you have
close friends on that team.
Still, this isn't something
we can just not worry about!
That's why we need
to see what their plan is!
If ours isn't working, we'll have
to stay up all night fixing it!
We need to see what
that team is working on.
- I feel bad, but I agree.
- Me too.
I will give it a try.
- You?
- Oh Jung Min?
Jung Min?
I'll approach Senior Ho.
No.
I understand how all of you feel.
I can be held accountable,
as Team Manager.
We just need to do our best.
If anything happens,
I will take responsibility.
That's how I feel about it,
as the manager.
Manager Hwang!
Is he really being like this?
He's new here. Losing won't
be great for him either.
He's saying to do it.
How can a manager tell us to go
steal another team's project plan?
He's just saying that.
No, no... not you.
Lee Hee Yeon.
He can't approve it
as Team Manager.
How can a manager tell us to go
steal another team's project plan?
But he will take responsibility.
He's saying, "go do it".
She won't roll over easily
but she is hasty.
You might be able to steal her
idea notebook if you have the chance.
You...
don't even go anywhere near Go Ho.
Okay?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Ji Hye, Yoo Kyung, Eun Mi?
If you keep joking around after today,
you're dead.
Why are they acting like this?
You get along, right?
This is work. Put your emotions aside.
Once love ends, works ends too.
I can tell that about you.
You're a sensitive person.
Why? Do you think dating will cause
problems with work?
You and I can't be like that.
At that moment, I saw my heart.