[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
We need to see what
their team is working on.
That's why we need to see
what their plan is!
- No.
- He's saying to do it.
How can a manager tell us to go steal
another team's project plan?
He's just saying that--
No, no.
Not you. Lee Hee Yeon.
She won't roll over easily,
but she's hasty.
If you get the chance, you might
be able to steal her idea notebook.
We just need to do our best.
If anything happens,
I will take responsibility.
As your manager,
that's how I feel about it.
How can a manager tell us to go steal
another team's project plan?
He says that he'll take responsibility.
He's saying to do it.
The most pathetic thing you could ever do
is stare at another person's food.
I didn't drink from it.
You drink it.
Even if we lose,
I don't want to lose by a lot.
No. I want to win.
[Episode 11: Love and War]
Hand it over.
- Hand it over.
- What?
- Your cell phone.
- Why do you need it?
Let me explain, Yongin...
You won't?
Unlock it.
Unlock the text messages too.
I had a really amazing night.
Kate?
She's a friend, we're very close!
You know how foreign people are.
They kiss you hello and stuff.
They say "I love you" like it's nothing.
Young Eun, Ji Hye, Yoo Kyung, and Eun Yi?
All of them too?
They're third-generation immigrants.
Do you want to stop working here?
Why would you say that?
You are much more important to me!
Are you like a third-generation
billionaire or something?
How can you be so cool
about this at work?
That's just how much I think about you.
I told you to give it a rest.
If you keep this up, you're a dead man.
Put this on my desk.
You said that you want excitement!
I really can do a good job.
[Meeting Logs]
My hands were shaking so much
when I was photocopying this.
Good job, good job.
But, which one is it?
I don't know.
I thought my heart was going to explode
when I was making the copies.
[Team A Office]
It's this one, it's this one!
We've been fooled.
Make a great strategy
for our advertisement!
They got us.
[Team B Meeting Room]
Oh, my!
Shit... No more movements.
Really, no more?
No more movements.
Are you going to play dirty?
Seriously, this guy...
[Team A Meeting Room]
[Team B Office]
I was exercising.
[Three Days to
Final Promise Presentation]
Manager.
Let go of me, let go!
Manager Kang! It was them!
They started it.
Didn't you land any punches?
Why is your nose bleeding?
Director.
Why are they acting like this?
Well... they're getting along.
I should have just grabbed it
and taken it from him!
Well, he is a man, after all.
I guess he's pretty strong.
Did I get everything I need?
[Yang Jin Kyung:
Seven-Year Tenured Promise Model]
Account Executive.
Sorry, I had my phone in my pocket.
I didn't see the calls coming in.
No, I'm the one who showed up
without making an appointment first.
The flowers are very pretty, aren't they?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I come here a lot for personal
healing time. The garden is beautiful.
Nothing can bring peace to
a person's heart like living things.
I used to come here a lot.
With my boyfriend.
You were always good to me,
so I thought I should tell you.
About what?
There's a problem with the ad.
Or it's not so much the ad.
I'm the problem.
He wanted to replace the model
and he was very stubborn about it.
They're looking to a new agency so...
- It's something like that.
- What?
It's like they say.
"Hwa Mu Baek Il Hong".
When love ends, work ends too.
Honestly, I was the lead Promise model
because he liked me so much.
You were a good model, Jin Kyung.
At the very least, I took an
opportunity and got some experience.
By the way...
Yes?
It's actually "Hwa Mu Shib Il Hong".
A pretty flower in bloom.
Because flowers don't bloom forever.
Now that they've broken up,
he doesn't want to see her.
Is that it?
I guess I wouldn't want
to see the person either.
Ho!
You're pretty flexible.
I lecture you about the dangers of
walking with your hands in your pockets.
Slipping where there's no ice,
you've very talented.
It's like they say.
When love ends, work ends too.
What are you looking at?
Manager, you've never had issues at work
because of a relationship, have you?
I haven't.
It's not because you
haven't been dating, is it?
What?
Not like that.
You're a scary guy, so I feel like
people might not approach you.
Why? Are you going to start having issues
at work because of a relationship?
No... no. It's not that.
It's about the Promise account.
What about it?
Oh... it's...
But, if you think about it carefully
it was Kang Tae Ho who kept you from
getting fired over that old client issue.
People say that you're a good worker now
because of what you learned from him.
He introduced you
to all of the right people.
A boss that opened up
all of his connections...
that's not easy to find, you know.
What did you get on your face?
You want everyone to know
that you were crying?
Why are you closing your eyes?
So...
Manager, you and I can't do this.
Office competition.
You're on Team A! And I'm on Team B!
Why is she acting like the boss?
That's great news. You did great!
No wonder he was acting so cranky.
That was why!
This works out great.
They've used the same model for seven
years. I never imagined this happening.
We won!
Should we cheers? Manager.
Cheers.
- Cheers!
- Great.
It's right not to tell them.
We're competing with them.
No, we should have told them.
Keeping information to ourselves
shouldn't be how this works.
Information is part of the planning.
The model came to tell you because
of all the work you had put in before.
At that moment, I saw my heart.
If it were a different person
I wouldn't have felt any guilt
over keeping my mouth shut.
However...
Is this how I taught you?
Stop focusing on the data.
How many hit ads lately
have used data analysis?
I guess you don't need
Song Dae Gi's number, then.
- No!
- I see.
Wait!
What kind of a company
makes storyboards like this?
Do it again.
Go in.
Don't cry while you sleep.
And don't be a pain in the ass tomorrow.
Come to work looking normal.
It's working.
I'm going to make people watch my
commercials and spend their money too.
The hardest thing in the world
is moving someone's heart.
I had a past with Kang Tae Ho.
We were enemies during that time,
but we were on the same team.
If Manager Kang Tae Ho were me,
he would tell you that you did well.
I know he was your boss,
but this is work.
Put your feelings aside.
You always say the right thing,
Manager Hwang.
However, there existed a time when you
cared more about feelings than your work.
There were times that you'd come to visit
your girlfriend in the middle of work.
You would tell her that you missed her
and that you were just in the area.
Back then...
I'm sure that girlfriend was very happy.
You're not one to do that usually,
but you made time, and during work hours.
It may seem childish.
She liked it because you seemed like you
cared more about her than your work.
It's okay if I'm not your first.
To me, you are my first.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
You keep acting like this,
so I end up obsessing.
You little fraud.
You're acting like a senior too.
Go Ho is out, doing work for your team.
If you have something to say,
it's best you get straight to the point.
It's immature to use the team to do it.
You work here too?
I know that my Ho is already
dating a good man.
Isn't Section Chief Park just trying
to go on a date with you?
Are you getting jealous?
You're just too smart.