[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
It's okay if I'm not your first.
To me, you are my first.
Thoughts?
I didn't look on purpose.
Not on purpose?
You were just under the desk in an empty
meeting room, minding your own business.
We all came in.
I'll just assume that you had
no choice, and were forced to see it.
So, what are your thoughts?
I had to see it.
There's something I haven't told you.
You know Yang Jin Kyung, the model?
She was dating the client.
It ended.
She didn't want to cause problems,
so she asked us to take care of it.
That's why he hated everything.
So... everything would have been fine
if we just changed the model?
- Yes.
- That was it?
Then wouldn't your team win,
if you changed the model?
I thought that you would
feel that way, Manager.
But...
I would feel a little dirty
if I won like that.
So I watched yours.
If your presentation wasn't so great,
I could feel okay about not telling you.
I would be sure that our team would win.
But?
We lost.
Even if we switched our model
I think that any client with eyes
would have chosen yours, Manager.
He has no brain,
so how could he have eyes?
Why do you look so down?
It was your idea, right?
I can tell these things by now.
It has your touch, Manager.
But... I really can't understand it.
How could you make something
that feels like that?
It doesn't suit you at all.
For a long time,
I was part of a one-way love story.
What are you looking at?
[Episode 12: ... Flirting?]
When I was younger,
it was enough just to like someone.
That was enough to jump
right into a relationship.
Now, I think about the end
before I even get started.
I think about whether or not that end
will make things difficult for me.
I think about making a rational
decision that an adult would make.
Coward.
It's okay if I'm not your first.
To me, you are my first.
It's right not to tell them.
We're competing with them.
I know that he was your boss,
but this is work.
Put your feelings aside.
However, there existed a time when you
cared more about feelings than your work.
She's pretty.
Driver! Wait!
There were times that you would visit
your girlfriend in the middle of work.
Sorry!
You would tell her that you missed her
and that you were just in the area.
I only did what you taught me!
You didn't do what I taught you.
Your research is lacking,
that's why it turned out this way!
The number you have dialed...
Again.
- Hello?
- Where are you?
Ji Hoon?
I'm in front of your office.
I wanted to see you.
Ji Hoon!
Hey!
She liked it because it seemed like you
cared more about her than your work.
Hey. Give it back.
We're done with the competition.
Will you talk to me?
I told you that if you kept this up
then you'd be a dead man.
Then you stabbed me in the back.
I couldn't have done it
if you hadn't stolen my files.
I have nothing to say, so give it to me.
I'm going to get a headache
from sorting these.
I'll help you.
So, just talk to me for a bit.
You ignore my calls and texts!
Seriously! Give it to me now.
Hold on to the documents.
You don't want to drop them.
Hey... hey!
Move, now!
What is your reason for disliking me?
I don't understand.
If you're not jealous,
why do you care about Kate or Ketchup?
If you are jealous,
then that means you like me.
So, why ignore me?
Don't be like that, and sleep
with me, just once.
Try sleeping with me, and if
you don't like me, then that's fine.
I'm very confident.
I can guarantee you that
you will never regret it.
Have you ever been clingy
with a girl before?
Of course, not.
You don't know it, Senior,
but I am really cool.
Then you should be good
at getting rejected.
You said you've never been clingy,
but you are really good at it.
Why are you being so sloppy?
It's really unattractive.
Senior!
Hey. Go put this on my desk.
Put it there carefully. Okay?
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm working very hard on
what you told me to do, Senior.
Oh, my! What are you saying?
When did I tell you to do this?
This is my work!
Your work is my work, Senior.
I'm okay.
Why, you little fraud...
Oh Jung Min, what are you doing?
We're supposed to head out.
Oh, what should I do?
I have to finish this task
that Senior Ho asked me to do.
Wow, Ya Ho! You're acting like a senior.
- No...
- What should I do?
Hey, forget about it. Go over there.
I'll do it.
Let me get this.
Senior... are you mad at me?
I'm so sorry.
I'll do it. I can finish it quickly.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Hey, hey, forget it. I'll go with Ya Ho.
I like Ya Ho better than Oh Jung Min.
Come on.
- What?
- Let's go!
Let's go!
I didn't realize you felt that
your senior's work was your work too.
I'll keep that in mind.
Manager Kang, you don't
need to keep that in mind...
Ya Ho! Ho!
Let's go inside!
I finished talking to them!
- Hold on.
- Okay.
Hello?
Where are you?
Oh, I'm at La France.
Why would you go there?
I don't know.
I'm in the South,
so why does it feel like Siberia?
Is it because my heart feels so cold?
Hello?
Isn't Section Chief Park just trying
to go on a date with you?
Manager Kang.
Are you getting jealous?
Why isn't he cursing me out?
You're too smart for your own good.
I'll buy you dinner
over the weekend, so hurry up.
- Have you had dinner?
- Are you wearing cologne?
Manager Kang!
Ho!
Why? Are you going to have work issues
because of a relationship?
I just want to be with a guy I like,
who likes me back.
Even if it's not like a passionate
and dramatic love...
Were you crying?
I want him to think of me and only me.
Then...
Okay, then just come in.
And as for your type...
let's just say it's my face.
Seo Woon.
Where's Go Ho?
She went out to work
on the Promise account.
Yes?
I heard that Go Ho is out
doing work for your team.
So, what?
I feel like I'm repeating myself.
Go Ho is on my team now.
It's been a while since she switched,
but you seem to think she works for you.
My team member, Oh Jung Min,
is working on documents for your team.
If there is something you have to say,
it's best you get straight to the point.
Using the team to make
your point is immature.
Oh, wow.
[Shameless Hwang]
I can't take your call right now.
Text me.
I'm coming back to the office
once I'm done here.
I need to talk to you.
Call me once you're back.
Wow!
It's great here.
This is the kind of place I should bring
a girlfriend to takes pictures, right?
Wow, it's really so nice.
It's great.
Wow!
There's a reason couples like to
come to theme parks on dates.
It's a place where you
feel like you must be happy.
Out of the many things you share, the
word "happiness" suits this place best.
A theme park that makes you feel
like the main character of a fairytale.
Just stepping inside of one...
That looks really good.
- Is it good?
- It's good.
Remembering past memories
of my time with my ex-boyfriend.
Section Chief, you're eating by yourself?
- The person I came with.
- Do you want this?
What?
It's good. Eat it.
Why isn't she answering?
[Where are you?]
Mother.
Ji Hoon.
Are you here to see Ho?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
I thought you were cute, Ya Ho.
This guy keeps
coming at me very suddenly.
I must have been born to live in pain.
I won't do the meeting and I'll pick up
when you're done.
Have you ever dated in the workplace?
I don't know about dating at work.
It's awkward if you break up.
Were you with Manager Kang yesterday?
You and I have
nothing to do with another.
I hope this doesn't happen again.
Section Chief, you're the best.
Section Chief, you're a better man than
I thought you were.
What brings you here?