[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Here you go.
There are so many
good coffee shops near here.
No need to spend money.
I need to get going soon.
So... you work here too?
Yes. It worked out that way.
Then, does Ho know
that you're working here?
She knows.
Then, are you...
No, it's not like that.
No, no. I know it's not.
I was just saying.
I know that my Ho is already
seeing a really great guy.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Well, they're not in a relationship yet.
Like people say these days,
they're just flirting.
Something like that.
I heard that he's a great guy,
and he's very mature.
Me saying this is a bit too much,
since she's my daughter.
My Ho... my Ho is very likable.
She's very gentle, and she's cute too.
Geez! Where did he go?
Section Chief!
Why?
What? What did I do? What?
Why, why, why, why?
What do you want from me?
Why, why, why, why!
Stop that!
Whoever loses Go Ho
will definitely be filled with regret.
You're right.
Filled with much regret.
- Are you regretful?
- What?
No, no.
I meant that anyone
who loses Ho would be.
My Ho is very gentle and very cute.
She was so pretty.
Your eyes were kind of...
No, no. Never mind. I'll get going.
You are a very decent person.
But... you should visit an optometrist.
[Episode 13: A Fling!]
How many pictures did you get?
This is definitely him
contacting me about work.
Ho!
Isn't Section Chief Park just trying
to go on a date with you?
- Let's go.
Are you getting jealous?
You're too smart for your own good.
- Section Chief.
- Yes?
Have you ever dated someone
that you worked with?
Of course... not.
But, I don't think it's a great idea.
It would be awkward if you broke up.
You're right.
However, there are times in life...
a person must give up their pizza
to protect a chicken they really like.
That is true romance.
Oh! Confusion!
The women I get set up with,
always have that facial expression!
They're always telling me that
I'm too good for them or something!
I'm sure.
Why would they say that though?
I'm telling them that I like them.
Section Chief, can I be honest with you?
Of course.
Section Chief, you were rejected!
Why?
Because you're not that great!
We missed the day scenes
because we got here too late.
We're adding on night scenes.
Just do a rough job.
Theme parks are all the same.
No one pays attention
to the public relations material anyway.
I don't know the meaning
of doing something roughly.
It looks similar.
It seems like this theme park
is going through some remodeling.
It's different than
when I came here last time.
Who did you go with last time?
This guy keeps coming at me...
very, very suddenly.
Why?
Are you going to have work issues
because of a relationship?
What are you looking at?
- Look away.
Look away.
What are you looking at?
What is it?
Just because.
I'm not that great.
[Club Day: Tonight is the Night]
Oh Jung Min!
Go Ho is gone because of you,
so our team needs some extra help.
Could you help us out?
Well, the thing is...
We need to see which of this client's
products could become a trending item.
I feel like you just might
have a sense for this.
This is Oh Jung Min's specialty.
He will do a good job.
I have somewhere to be.
But... I can cancel it.
Where is she, anyway?
Why do you dislike burps?
But it's natural.
Then what about farts?
Neither is okay!
If you have to do it, don't do it
in front of a woman.
Section Chief, it wasn't so great
when I burped just now, right?
I...
didn't mind it when you burped.
It was cute.
What?
Section Chief, you were rejected
because you're not that great!
Section Chief!
Geez, this is all ruined.
Are you okay?
Section Chief!
In what way did he fall,
that he managed to break his arm?
How did the camera get stolen too?
Life is so hard...
I must have been born to suffer.
Oh, you're all in here.
My premonition of sadness
has never been wrong.
Manager Hwang, I've been curious
about something for a long time.
I heard that Zeus made you a great offer
when they tried to hire you as a manager.
Is that really true?
It is true. It is.
Really?
Then, why did you come here?
Wait, I have another question.
What is it?
Manager, why does a person
like you not have a girlfriend?
You're good-looking, and tall. You have
a good voice. You're successful at work.
If I were a women,
I would strip down and just...
I would try something like that.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Are you not interested in women?
I doubt that.
I guess I just don't have the skills.
- Come on.
- That's nonsense.
We should just die then.
- I'll die first.
- Okay, you first.
I met with your mom yesterday.
Why?
Manager, I was supposed
to call you yesterday, but I forgot.
Should we go talk?
Yes.
They are really something...
Can't we just hang out?
Why do they keep working?
But... isn't our manager
a really good catch?
No, I think he's a bit strange.
Why?
No one is that perfect.
He looks like he doesn’t watch porn.
Yes, look at Manager Kang Tae Ho.
He's great at his job,
but his personality is awful.
He seems very human though.
I suppose there could be a secret reason
behind why he rejected Zeus.
For example, he has an ex-girlfriend
he had a bad split with at his old job.
Well, or an ex-boyfriend.
That's a good one.
Something like that.
It's hard for me to get to talk to you
unless I have to bother you like this.
You said you would
call yesterday, but you didn't.
I don't think that's
the problem right now.
I had no choice.
She came to the building.
I ran right into her, so what
was I supposed to do? Ignore her?
You ignored me just fine.
Why can't you ignore my mom?
You two have nothing
to do with one another.
I don't want this happening again.
Were you with...
Manager Kang Tae Ho yesterday?
Is that a question you're
asking me as my boss?
Don't be like that.
It seems like you haven't fully
comprehended what I've said yet.
Working with you is very,
very uncomfortable for me.
I'm just enduring it
because of this job crisis.
So, don't make things
more difficult for me.
Please keep your distance from me.
- Why do I have to?
- Why can't you?
I...
felt like I was going to die,
when you left me, all of a sudden.
I am barely... really
just barely holding on.
Why are you showing up like
nothing happened and asking me that?
I have nothing to say to you.
Oh, and I don't have to answer you.
When I asked you why we had to break up,
you never gave me an answer.
Even if you don't know why
you have to, just accept it.
I should really control my temper.
Was that too much?
He won't know.
What are you doing?
I was thinking about your advice.
Thinking for three seconds before I act.
I don't know.
I'm not sure that I'll ever be able
to fix this personality of mine.
What can you do? You just have
to live your life the way you are.
I have too many regrets to do that.
Manager!
You're supposed to console me
and tell me that I'm not so bad.
Why? I can't deny the truth.
You're quick to act,
thoughtless, and simple.
It makes sense that
you'd have lots of regrets.
Geez...
What do you plan on doing?
I'm going to visit Section Chief.
He wants to have some fruit.
He only broke one arm.
Can't he eat them on his own?
That works.
I'll skip my meeting and pick you up
when you're done.
You're going to pick me up?
What are you looking at? Look away.
I'm glad you're here, Go Ho.
It's a nice house, right?
Want to see pictures?
This is the girl who lives with me.
Section Chief, you have a girlfriend?
Do you have a wife?
Look at how shocked you are.
She's my niece.
My older brother and I
have a huge difference in age.
If you saw us in passing,
we'd look like a couple, right?
I do look very young for my age.
You live with your niece?
Live with her? I raised her by myself.
My brother passed away.
So what could I do?
I had to raise her.
She's my child.
Section Chief... you're a better man
than I thought you were.
Forget it. You told me
that I'm not that great.
Better than I thought!
Better than I thought, okay?
Better than you thought?
Everyone has good sides and bad sides!
Yeah, I suppose there needs
to be a guy like me around.
Everything about me
isn't so great either.
No.
Everything about you is great, Ya Ho.
It hurts... It hurts!
- Bye, now.
- Okay.
Section Chief, you really are the best.
I saw a different side of you today.
I want to become someone
who takes responsibility, like you.
You are very cool. The best, the best!
Then, enjoy the fruit.
- Okay.
- See you at work tomorrow.
Okay.
Bye!
See you at work!
See you.
Ya Ho!
Ho, let's eat dinner together!
Let's... have meat...
Section Chief.
Oh, yes.
Manager Kang.
But... what brings you here?
I was just passing by.
- Passing by?
- Yes.
Then, was he passing by too?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Is there a disease going around?
You can help her not worry
about someone like me.
Am I a fool or something?
What a coincidence this was.
We need to talk.
You were the one who won me over
and then stabbed me with a knife.
What do you want?
The hospital called earlier,
saying that she is sick.
We picked up and explained the situation.
Someone is picking you up.
I am waiting for the person
who will open that door.
I don't even know who it will be.