[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Geez, this girl is so terrible.
She doesn't call, she doesn't text back.
Awful girl.
Petty girl.
[Thinking]
[Different Thoughts]
[Together]
[Episode 14:
Thinking Different Thoughts Together]
In life, there comes a time
when you can't focus on meat.
I'll cook it.
You can do it, Manager Kang.
When did my neighborhood become...
the hot spot to hang out?
I thought I should come visit you.
I followed Go Ho,
but the meeting ran a little late.
It makes sense, but not really.
But it could make sense.
Ah, me?
I came to meet a friend in the area.
I'm glad I got to come eat
some free meat though.
What a coincidence this is.
That won't do at all.
How old are you, Manager Kang?
34 years old?
Wow... that's a great age to be.
It's the perfect age to be for a man.
There are lots of women to meet,
and lots of potential in general.
How should I put it?
It's different than kids these days.
It's an age where you still
have the Confucian mindset, right?
Like "Jang Yoo Yoo Seo".
("hierarchical order based on age").
You can meet other girls.
I'm older than you,
so let me have her.
And you are... 27 years old.
Geez. Geez!
You're a baby, just a little baby!
You should be focusing
on work, not on girls.
You could be creating obstacles
for your future.
Where do you think you are,
you young punk?
You have good taste.
Get lost! Otherwise,
I'll make sure that you get lost.
I do feel that I'm a conservative man.
Although age is just a number.
As every year passes,
one should act their age.
I feel very strongly about this.
Section Chief, don't you feel that way?
Think about how old you are,
you shameless punk.
What are all of you talking about?
Please continue.
Oh Jung Min, you should
listen to Section Chief.
He's such a foul man...
I know that's what you might be thinking.
But it never hurts to listen
to your superiors.
If Section Chief Park doesn't do it,
I will make sure you get lost, myself.
Section Chief Park is a foul man.
I respect you both.
Maybe it was because
I haven't been exercising
but my body feels different
than it did last year.
So, I started working out.
Considering how old the two of you are,
I'm curious as to how you stay so young.
These old people want to date?
Aren't they embarrassed?
Do you know how much
my niece's tuition is?
I paid for her tuition,
and for her to study abroad.
Now that's she's all grown up,
once I send her out...
I wonder to myself,
what I should do with my life.
I make lots of money.
Oh, yeah.
I'm thinking about getting a new car.
Do you know a good place?
I do pretty well, myself.
I started playing tennis recently.
My coach keeps trying to persuade me to
play competitively, before it's too late.
He says that the body can change
so much in just a year.
If I don't go now, I'll...
Become.
An.
Old.
Man.
You old men.
I play soccer every Sunday.
Kids these days, they're so scrawny.
I outplay kids in their 20's and 30's.
Is there a disease going around
that I don't know about?
News, please.
Hello?
Why?
Sit down.
I'm not feeling good today.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Keep it short and get going.
Can't you be a little nicer
when you talk to me?
You're always on the offensive, you know?
Showing up out of nowhere and telling me
to be nicer is very offensive too.
Why are you here?
Mom is very worried about you.
Give her a call.
I know when your feelings started
to get hurt, but this isn't right.
There's nothing she can do.
You're living like
a normal person, but... I...
- From Mom's point of view--
- Are you done?
You would never know when
my feelings started to get hurt.
I would wait and wait to see
when my turn would come.
You have never had to wait,
so how could you understand?
I tried everything to get her attention.
And the despair I felt when I couldn't...
How could you know,
when you've never experienced it?
Mom has loved you
since the day you were born.
How could you know how I feel?
You think I feel comfortable with this?
Nothing works out for me
and I have to watch Mom toiling away.
I want to be good to Mom.
I want to buy her good food,
good clothes, and take her on walks!
But do you know what
Mom says every time I try?
"My Kang likes to eat this too."
"We're in a new season.
Kang needs some new clothes too."
You're having a hard time? Why?
Receiving all of that love is difficult?
Why are you pretending to be so nice?
Call Mom because she's worried?
You do it!
You can make it so that she doesn't
worry about someone like me.
I'm telling you that
Mom does worry about you.
She worries about you eating well because
you work so much, so she bought you beef!
I know she didn't make it for me to eat.
Do you know what makes me even angrier?
Because you're like this
I'm the horrible wench,
no matter what I say.
You have no idea
what you're doing, do you?
Mom says "yes" to everything you say.
You have no idea how it
makes me feel when you act so nice!
You only planned on lecturing your sister
for your worrying mother.
You never thought
about why I act this way!
[Spicy Seafood Stew: Level 5]
I don't want to think about anything.
This is a challenge I have
given myself that I must win.
When I want to challenge myself.
When I have no one to fight,
so I fight with myself.
Hey.
I just don't think
it's right, level five!
Stop eating. I won't accept your money.
It's okay. It's just right.
I'm not okay with it! I'm not!
I just need to forget about something.
Leave her alone!
What's wrong with her?
You're awake?
You still have a fever.
Why am I here?
It happens, every now and then.
People eat spicy food,
pass out, and come here.
Still, you never know.
Would you like a full exam?
No, no.
I can just leave then, right?
Someone called from your office.
We picked up and explained the situation.
Someone is picking you up.
Please wait a little bit.
My office? Picking me up?
Who is?
He said he was a manager.
Where's my phone?
It's a company number.
Manager?
Who's going to come?
What's going on?
What a shock...
Yes?
Where's Go Ho?
The hospital called earlier
and said that she got sick.
She's sick?
If you think about it
of course, another person
wouldn't know how I feel.
Sometimes, I don't know how I feel.
Right now...
I am waiting for the person
who will open that door.
I don't even know who
it's going to be, but I'm waiting.
Are you okay?
Thank you for the ride home.
I'll rest today, I'll get better,
and I'll be at work tomorrow.
We need to talk.
Later. I'm going inside.
- Ho.
- Don't!
I don't want to talk today. Just go.
Let's talk today.
Are we going to keep
being awkward like this?
If we talk now, I think that
I'll say some terrible things.
But I've acted terribly enough today.
So, just leave.
I don't want to be terrible.
You can be.
I don't want to!
Seriously, why are you being like this?
You can stay the terrible jerk
in our relationship!
Why are you acting so cool about this?
You were the one who won me over,
and then stabbed me with a knife!
Why are you making me out
to be the petty one now?
What do you want?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I was wrong, Ho.
It's the people you love the most,
that say things that hurt you the most.
That's what they say.
Who did this person get hurt by,
that they came to this painful epiphany?
Ho.
No. Oh.
When are you going back
to get pictures of the theme park?
Senior Ho is sick.
What?
It seemed like she was really stressed
when we were drinking yesterday.
She passed out suddenly,
and went to the hospital.
Passed out?
How bad was it?
Manager Hwang went to pick her up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
You feel very nice,
and tight inside of mine.
If anyone touches you when I'm not there,
use your elbow to hit him in the nose.
I'll take care it after.
However, reality is much worse.
Strangely, I do want
to go to Hawaii though.
Would we share a room there?
You're too honest.
So, do you not like me?
Sitting with a person
who you suspect may like you
while trying not to get caught
for the fact that I'm falling for them.
Psychological warfare.