[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Ah, it's so cold!
I must be crazy.
So cold.
So cold! Cold, cold, cold.
How can I go to work like this?
Ya Ho, why are you sitting on the floor?
Girls shouldn't sit on cold things.
Did you see my present for you?
Pres... present?
You know that BMG Cars
is producing films now.
I brought all the offerings they made
to the spirits, to give to you.
That's supposed to be really
good for women's skin.
If you boil this and eat it... wow!
It's a present for you. Here.
Oh, Ms. Go...
How did you know that
I was coming to greet you like this?
Director Kim!
Ms. Go, I've never seen you
this way before.
You feel very nice and tight
inside of my arms.
Manager Kang!
Manager Kang, you!
A lot of people are watching.
Why don't you let go?
If you don't let go in three seconds,
I'm going to hurt you very badly.
One, two, three.
Hey, let go!
Okay, okay, okay, Manager!
Director Choi is here
and they're all in his office.
Director Kim isn't even embarrassed,
and he's getting angry.
Wow! Manager Kang has a temper.
How was he able to grab him like that?
Writer, the webzine articles are a hit!
The idol, ex-boyfriend boss, and chubby
section chief are getting lots of hits!
It's a complete turn!
They say there's no answer for you
if an ugly guy falls for you.
Manager Kang, what are you
going to do? Are you okay?
What happened?
Is Director Kim in the hospital?
Why did you actually break his arm?
He has an awful personality.
Who knows what he'll do.
You told me to wait three seconds.
What are you doing this Saturday?
What?
I'm finishing late tomorrow
because I have a meeting.
See me over the weekend.
I'm saying this, just in case.
This, right now...
I'm asking you out on a date.
Manager Kang.
Also, I'm sure this won't happen again.
But if anyone touches you when I'm
not here, use your elbow to hit his nose.
I'll take care of it after.
Kang Tae Ho's ears were so red.
Everything in my mind disappeared.
If I stressed you out at the BBQ place...
I'm sorry.
What should I wear?
[Episode 15: Flirting WAR]
Let me see.
Pink?
Kang Tae Ho will ask me
which circus I work for.
No, this is too average.
This makes it too obvious
that I'm trying.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I was wrong, Ho.
Sorry.
Oh, no! What do I do?
What do I do?
Are you okay?
I don't want to. I don't!
You were the one who won me over
and then stabbed me with a knife.
Why are you making me out
to be the petty one now?
What do you want?
I worked really hard to make
myself look like I didn't try too hard.
What is this feeling, of hoping that
Kang Tae Ho doesn't notice?
Can you explain to me
why you wanted to meet here?
Well, what could I do?
If the thief left the memory card,
he would be a very considerate thief.
I have to submit this by Monday.
So... what does that have to do
with me being here?
My boss said to me once...
"Becoming an advertiser..."
"means to never forget your work,
no matter the case."
This is that boss.
Whoever that guy is, I want to punch him.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
What? I'm asking for the camera.
We'll never finish, at this rate.
Amusement park, which is still fun,
even though it's only been a week.
Just stepping into this place.
I thought that Kang Tae Ho didn't
suit me, but in a way, he does.
Do I like being abused or something?
I must be a pervert.
No! The color isn't great.
You need red, yellow, and some depth.
- That's how you grab attention--
- Stop playing around.
Balance is important.
Does an image change
because of red depth?
What do guys even know?
These ads are targeted to women.
Women care a lot about colors.
I'm too honest with
my opinions, aren't I?
You are too honest for a girl who brought
a guy to a place like this on a date.
So, do you not like me?
Flirting WAR!
Sitting with a person
who you suspect may like you
while trying to not to get caught
for falling for that person like crazy.
Psychological warfare.
Then, do you think I would like you?
I see...
Strangely though... I do have
thoughts about going to Hawaii.
Hawaii?
Yes, I never planned on it before.
I changed my mind, not too long ago.
Don't you have a dream?
I want to retire and buy
a small house in Hawaii.
Living there isn't too expensive.
Wait!
You're not expecting me to earn
everything and take you with me, right?
What are you saying?
Back then, I didn't know any better,
so I chose Hawaii.
It's really expensive there.
If we're being more realistic...
I'm thinking the Philippines.
The Philippines are okay.
Thailand?
Thailand? Okay.
Hey!
The most frustrating thing
about movies or TV dramas is
why don't these characters say they
like each other, when they clearly do?
It would be good if they kept things
simple and expressed themselves.
They make things complicated,
so they have misunderstandings.
I just hate it.
However, reality is much worse.
- Stay still. Don't move.
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay?
- Yes.
Good job.
Ya Ho, Ya Ho! What are you doing?
I thought you'd be at work
so I came, but you're not here.
What the heck?
Did someone cut off your tongue,
Section Chief?
[Shameless Hwang]
You're not coming?
I'm coming!
You don't want any churro, Manager Kang?
Eat as much as you want.
- Did we get it all?
- Yeah.
Good. Geez, that was tiring.
Oh, that scared me!
I'm not used to
the you of today, Manager.
I'm not used to me either.
I've never done this stuff.
Don't lie.
About what?
What do you mean, you haven't?
You must have dated before.
Even if I have dated
do I look like someone who would date
someone who can't wipe spilled coffee?
Then... why are you doing this?
You're shameless too.
You already know, so why ask?
I don't know.
Why don't you know?
Manager, look at the way you act!
This?
Get out!
Why is that my fault?
You should've been better.
When will you act like a human being?
You always do whatever you want
and you never listen.
I get confused because you act like this.
What are you looking at? Look...
Kang Tae Ho warned me.
Think for three seconds.
That's always so hard for me.
By the way...
Whether it's Hawaii or Thailand,
would we be sharing a room there?
[Many thanks to Park Seul Gi
for her guest appearance.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
I thought I could live without you,
but I can't do it.
I like you.
Why are you telling me this now?
Giving you a choice.
It would make me a beggar.
Work must be very easy for you.
I don't want to argue,
but Go Ho is on my team.
You should be sure of your position.
Kang Tae Ho knows.
He knows that Hwang Ji Hoon
is my ex-boyfriend.
He was trying to get him back.
He pretended it was an accident and
poured coffee on Manager Kang's head.
If everything is the same,
I have no reason to start over.
Can I decide on my position now?