[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Working with you is very,
very uncomfortable for me.
I'm just enduring it
because of this job crisis.
So, don't make things
more difficult for me.
Please keep your distance from me.
- Why do I have to?
- Why can't you?
I...
felt like I was going to die
when you left me, all of a sudden.
I am barely... really
just barely, holding on.
Why are you showing up like nothing
ever happened and asking me that?
I have nothing to say to you.
Oh, and I don't have to answer you.
When I asked you why we had to break up,
you never gave me an answer.
[Episode 16:
Ex-Boyfriend's Counterattack]
What are you doing right now?
- You know what?
- What?
It's nothing really, but now
I'm just curious, suddenly.
Why did you send me
to Team B out of nowhere?
I heard that you chose me specifically
and sent me to that team.
I thought you gave up on me.
So, did you curse me out?
No, not necessarily.
It just doesn't really make sense to me.
It's not that I'm dying of curiosity.
One thing's for sure. Just like
an advertiser, you do not give up.
What?
Do you have to...
hear me say it?
I can't be having ideas of that nature
about a fellow team member.
I do like you, after all.
I was in a one-way
love for a long time.
My heart just skipped.
Oh, my!
My heart...
Ho.
Let's talk.
Why would you tell me that now?
Then... should I have told you that
my family was financially ruined?
And that I could no longer
treat you well anymore?
Actually, it wasn't that
I couldn't treat you well.
I couldn't do anything for you.
Should I have told you that?
Telling me that would have been
the right thing to do.
No. I couldn't have told you that.
Even if I went back now,
I still couldn't have told you.
You don't think that
I can have thoughts of my own?
It's something I should hear myself,
and make a judgment on.
Giving you the choice.
It turns me into a beggar.
If you accepted it and stayed with me,
you would have suffered.
If you had thrown me aside and left me,
you would have felt guilty.
How could I put that on you?
Still...
you should have told me.
That's what a relationship is.
Worrying together
and making decisions together.
No matter what the problem was...
first, and before everything else...
you should have told me.
Ho.
Leaving without a word was wrong.
If something was ever wrong...
that was wrong.
It was for your sake. It really was.
Then why are you telling me this now?
I don't know.
I guess I want to hold onto you.
I thought I could live without you.
But I can't.
The moment he held me...
it was just like I remembered.
It took me by surprise, how he
smelled and felt the same.
I thought I had forgotten.
I guess I hadn't forgotten
as well as I thought I did.
However, even though
I hadn't forgotten everything...
I had changed.
Thinking about it,
there was a lot I hadn't noticed.
Ji Hoon.
While I was chasing a person
who turned his back on me
I didn't even see where that person was.
Are we strangers now?
I didn't know that he was in pain.
Even if I went back now,
I still couldn't have told you.
Giving you the choice.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
It turns me into a beggar.
If you accepted it and stayed with me,
you would have suffered.
If you had thrown me aside and left me,
you would have felt guilty.
How could I put that on you?
Why does he have to be
right all of the time?
So annoying...
What do I do?
What should I do? Oh, no.
It's Kim Yoo Chan's doing.
It's an example of the saying, "you avoid
crap because it's dirty, not scary".
He was trying to get him back.
He pretended it was an accident and
poured coffee on Manager Kang's head.
But I guess he has a conscience.
It wasn't hot coffee--
Oh... you're finally getting to work?
Work must be so easy for you.
What's wrong with your face?
What?
What about my face?
Manager Hwang,
did something happen yesterday?
No.
Go out and buy me a shirt.
Sorry, but Go Ho needs
to go out with me soon.
- Can you go instead?
- Oh, yes.
No, I want Ho to go.
Manager Kang.
I don't want to argue about it,
but Go Ho is on my team.
If you don't want to argue about it,
then don't argue.
If you're saying this as her
team manager, I will accept it.
Perhaps, I should ask you
where you are going with Go Ho.
Be clear with your position.
Then I will respond accordingly.
Kang Tae Ho knows.
He knows that Hwang Ji Hoon
is my manager and my ex-boyfriend.
Hey! Why are you two acting like this?
Hey, I'll buy it!
I'll go with Ya Ho
and buy something nice.
- No you won't.
- No you won't
Since I'm the rookie,
maybe I'll go with Senior Ho...
What's going on?
Manager Kang.
Your shirt?
I'll buy it.
Sorry about that.
Director Kim was drinking all night,
he wasn't in his right mind.
Come with me, Go Ho.
I'm sure that women have better taste.
I'll buy you something nice. Let's go.
Hey, you.
Why would you sigh
like that in my nice car?
That's just how life is.
It can be this way
or it can be that way.
I don't think anything works out for me.
What do you mean?
Lots of things work out for you.
You have too many things,
and that's your problem.
It's all the same when it passes.
That's what I was afraid of.
That it would all be the same
after time passed.
I was part of a one-way
love story for a long time.
I do like you, after all.
- What should I do here?
- What is that?
I'm cold.
You should have dressed warmer.
Give me your hands.
It's all the same when time passes.
And if it's all the same, then there's
no reason to start anything new.
Can I make a decision on my position?
It will be that of an ex-boyfriend.
One that has never stopped
having feelings for Go Ho.
Her ex-boyfriend.
[A Day in 2013]
I did what you taught me.
I didn't teach you this.
Your research is so bad that
you turned thing thing into a mess!
Do it again.
- Hello?
- Where are you?
- Ji Hoon!
- I'm in front of your building.
I wanted to see you.
Ji Hoon!
What did you do?
Why did you get in trouble?
I missed you so much.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Wait. Did you sleep well yesterday?
Don't think about anything else
and just look at me.
What is this?
Office competition.
You guys are doing a fun thing.
Go Ho, let's step out for a moment.
When you were dating me,
you hated Manager Kang.
You hated him to death.
If you ended up liking him after that,
you can start liking me too.
I'll make that happen.