[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
- What's wrong with your face?
- What?
What about my face?
Manager Hwang,
did something happen yesterday?
No.
Can I make a decision on my position?
It will be that of an ex-boyfriend.
One that has never stopped
having feelings for Go Ho.
Her ex-boyfriend.
- Ex-boyfriend?
You're her ex-boyfriend?
Manager Kang, you like Go Ho too?
We do too.
[Episode 17: Fevered Times]
Now that I look at this
I think that everyone here
is in the same position.
I'm different.
But I'm different.
This is a shirt.
These are pants, because Director Choi
thought your pants might be wet too.
Here are some wet tissues.
I'll get going, then. Get changed.
Stop.
Did you sleep well yesterday?
Yes.
All right.
How well did you sleep?
Just somewhat.
Somewhat? How well?
But then why are your eyes swollen?
Uh... Manager Kang.
What?
Yesterday...
Is it a good story?
Then don’t tell it.
You can go.
You can stay if you want.
I'm going to change my pants.
Yes.
Writer!
Writer?
[Starry Night]
[Party Boy Idol, Dangerous Temptation]
Excuse me.
What would the typical
pretty boy be like?
A face that's satisfying just to look at,
and makes me think of my mother's smile.
His handsome looks made me think
that he would help me lose stress.
Handsome people like
to use their looks, everyone.
I know that we're a liberal generation.
But still, only tell one person
that you want to sleep with them!
Who is he, to have multiple women?
He spreads his charm everywhere and
thinks women will buzz to him like bees.
Full of crap.
- Be careful.
- Thank you.
If he fools around too much,
he could get the punch of death.
Your entire life is written right here!
Section Chief Park and Manager Hwang
want to see you.
I have lots of money. My dad is rich.
Okay, but how could I only
get five points for my looks?
Am I that low on the scale?
That's nonsense.
Why is my personality less that yours?
Forget it! Just leave it.
What is this?
Office competition.
There are principles to follow at work.
Let's come up with a system
for who gets to ask her out first.
I'm not doing this.
Okay, then Manager Kang
cannot make a move on Senior Ho.
You can't, okay?
The problem with guys
who never do what they hate.
It's nice that they're clear
on everything, but it doesn't excite me.
And the moment he does something
for me that he usually wouldn't
that moment that he breaks
his own rules because of me
could there be anything sexier?
[Personality: 1]
Why do I get one point for personality?
What is time about?
The length of time you've liked her.
We all lose on this one to Manager Hwang.
That's not important.
Let's talk about looks again.
No, we can't do that.
I'm a ten too.
For time.
I've liked Go Ho since
she was a rookie here.
That's long before
she was set up with you.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I should get ten points and Manager Hwang
should get nine points.
Honestly, a relationship with an
ex-boyfriend should be a minus.
Could there be anything worse than that?
I can't accept that her relationship
with Oh Jung Min would be a six.
Go Ho doesn't like easy people like him.
What about a guy who gives the person
he likes a pig head as a gift?
The biggest problem here is, why is my
relationship with her only one point?
We have a much better relationship
than any of you realize.
What are you guys doing?
You guys are doing something fun.
[Choi Chang Seob]
I think it's against the rules
for you to participate, Director.
Against the rules?
This isn't a game with rules anyway.
Haven't you ever thought of me as sincere
since I'm doing an embarrassing thing?
You could just live
the way you are, with dignity.
As a single old man.
I just don't understand
why my score is so low.
You not knowing why is the problem.
Anyway, don't we have the results?
No.
The standards for the relationship
category are a problem.
Isn't that something
to determine with Ho?
Let's discuss it properly, with her.
I would like...
You like caramel macchiatos, right?
Girls like sweet drinks.
Section Chief, are you going
to have a caramel macchiato?
Not me. I meant for you, Ya Ho.
Women want to take care
of their bodies these days.
They don't drink things like that,
with so many calories.
I think she should drink tea.
Have that one.
A brilliant pink that
suits Senior Ho perfectly.
What is that?
Go Ho, drink something expensive.
Expensive is what tastes good.
Let's see. They have shaved ice.
If I'm treating, you should
eat something expensive.
Don't you only drink tea lattes, Go Ho?
What is this?
Tea latte?
- It's good, right?
- So good, so good!
It's good, it's good?
Wait.
Do you like the tea lattes?
Or do you like me?
Answer me.
What is this?
It's good.
Have an americano.
You said you get break out
when you drink milk.
And you'll be sleepy as soon as you
have lunch and don't have caffeine.
So have an americano.
Then...
americano.
Two americanos, please.
The others will have whatever.
Go Ho. Let's step out for a moment.
Client meeting.
Yes.
What are you doing?
Do you have plans to do a commercial?
What?
Our place isn't big enough
to do a commercial.
Why do you ask?
Client meeting.
That's unfortunate.
Sometimes things get accomplished
during meetings, sometimes they don't.
Yes.
If the meeting is over, I'll get going.
Do you like Manager Kang Tae Ho?
You saw everything.
I saw that Manager Kang likes you.
Do you like him too?
- I thought about it and--
- Do you know?
When you were dating me,
you hated Manager Kang.
You hated him to death.
You even made a hate doll of him
that you would stick needles into.
If you ended up liking him after that...
you can start liking me too.
I'll make that happen.
Don't... it's over.
Whatever your reason was...
it's over.
We can start over.
We didn't break up
because we didn't like each other.
If I wasn't stupid enough to let you go,
we would be together right now.
We'll be happy if we start over too.
I'll get going first.
Don't do this.
You're not this kind of person.
I don't know what kind of person I am.
Drinking tea was enough for today.
Manager, you're leaving too?
No.
Then, where are you going?
I'm going to drive you home.
I can tell that you're trying to avoid
being left alone with me.
I want to be with you,
even if it's just for a moment.
I'm just...
Why?
Do you not know that
I'm not asking you anything?
I'm trying hard to leave you
with a good impression.
I don't just lose my temper.
Take a good look at me.
I can hold in my temper.
I can wait, without asking or demanding.
- Really?
- No.
No, no. I can do it.
No...
I can do it.
I can cling onto you if you need me to.
So...
don't think about anything else.
Take a good look at me.
Just me.
Look only at me.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Go Ho, don't you want
to teach me what real love is?
Can you really say that you have
no feelings for me anymore?
You have too many
misunderstandings about me?
Open your eyes wide
and take a good look at me.
Kang has disappeared!
This is usually a case of running away.
I had wished for him to go away.
Manager Kang.
I waited four years.
What are you doing?