[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 18:
The Hardest Thing in the World]
Jean Paul Sartre said this.
"Life is nothing but a series of choices,
starting at birth, ending at death."
What is this?
It's what you told me to bring you.
I can cling onto you if you need me to.
So don't think about anything else.
Take a good look at me.
Just me.
Look only at me.
Don't.
You're not this kind of person.
I don't know what kind of person I am.
But he's not the type
to say such weak things...
Is Manager Hwang going somewhere?
He's going to the hospital.
He left this with me because
he's coming back this afternoon.
Seriously, he's all smiles.
But he's actually quite cruel.
Hospital?
No, no.
Do you need me to do something?
- You should work late today.
- What?
Give me the work now.
Am I your manager?
- No.
- Then why would you do my team's work?
Then, why would you assign
your team's work to me?
Is that something you should say
to your old boss of four years?
Is that something a guy who said he would
cling to me if I needed him, should say?
That's what I'm saying.
If you work late tonight...
I can buy you dinner--
There will be a company dinner
tonight at Mannaso.
Please attend and brighten
the atmosphere.
Manager Kang.
No one's here. They all went to dinner.
No, I mean...
what are you doing right now?
We're at work.
Don't bring up work.
I really wanted to go out
for dinner with you tonight.
Well, but...
You don't want to?
It's not that I don't want to.
We're at work right now.
Fine.
Then let's go somewhere else.
What are you doing?
I think you saw it all.
Which part should I explain for you?
I waited four years.
Now, you like me.
Can you really say that you
have no feelings for me anymore?
I hated you from the very beginning.
I hated you too.
Oh... nice catch, Manager Hwang.
Ya Ho, what are you doing in your sleep?
Let's go to the dinner. We're late.
- Cheers!
- A drink for us too!
Okay, cheers!
Cheers!
Eat up, everyone.
Eat up, eat up!
Eat lots, everyone!
Cheers! Thank you!
- You have a drink too!
- Okay.
Ho, have a drink.
I was thinking about it,
and I think I'm a really decent guy.
There's a webzine that I've been reading,
and it says a man like me is sincere.
Do I know anything about women or dating?
I'd just do what a woman tells me to do!
I feel like I've heard that
somewhere before.
Don't trust that stuff.
It's just an article.
No, this writer is a bit different.
It really got me
in the heart, right here.
Stop poking yourself there
and poke the meat, will you?
Give me that thing.
Go Ho, don't you want to
teach me what real love is?
Teaching isn't a hobby of mine.
Should I tell you how to get rid of me?
I'll take care of it myself.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
If you sleep with me once...
Eat up.
Are you not drinking?
I am not drinking. You can drink, Go Ho.
Meat.
I waited four years. Now, you like me.
Thank you.
Can you really say that you
have no feelings for me anymore?
I can't live without you.
What?
I said that I added mustard.
Don't put in anymore.
Oh, okay.
Oh, crap, I think I have indigestion...
Manager, you eat popsicles too?
Why? Can't I eat them too?
It doesn't suit you.
Why not?
You have so many misconceptions about me.
I guess I misunderstood you
for four years.
Open your eyes wide
and take a good look at me! Really...
- You don't know me well.
- What?
I suppose that I had
my eyes closed for four years.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Let's go out to eat
since we couldn't go today.
I'll show you exactly who I am.
Even if you don't like it,
you'll just have to hold it in.
Let's go out to eat.
Or do you have plans, by chance?
With your mom again?
[Mother]
Pick up.
Ho! Kang disappeared!
What do I do?
"Do not look for me. From Go Kang."
Usually this kind of note
means it's a runaway case.
He doesn't have any friends.
He is thoughtless too.
He has no problems either.
- He has no money.
- He has no ill intentions.
He really doesn't have anything.
If you give us his cell phone number,
we could track him.
- He doesn't have a cell phone!
He doesn't have one.
I tried calling all of them,
but they're not picking up.
Let me know. Thanks.
I think I'm going insane.
He's never acted like this before.
Are you busy? Okay, bye.
What am I going to do?
You're having a hard time? Why is that?
You're always her top priority,
and I'm always last!
Do you know what makes me even angrier?
Because you're like this...
I'm the horrible wench,
no matter what I say.
What do I do?
There is much sadness, as a man studying
for civil exams had committed suicide.
Mr. Go was 34 years old and
was discovered by security guards.
What do I do?
What am I supposed to do?
Kang, what do I do?
[Kang Sociopath]
Kang, what should I do? What!
Kang!
I always wished for him to go away.
I didn't know why he was even alive.
When we were younger,
he was stronger and he pulled on my hair.
I'm sure nothing happened to him.
He's been studying a long time, nothing
was working out, so he needed some air.
That's how men are. I'm sure he's fine.
No, I was really mean to him.
I wanted to hurt him
because I didn't want to see him.
What makes it even worse is...
I meant everything I said.
Why am I so mean?
What if Kang is dead somewhere?
He's so nice...
Is there anywhere he might go
around here? Should we go look?
Kang! Oh, I'm sorry.
- Kang!
- I'm not him.
What should I do now?
He's not here.
Go Kang?
Hey! Let's go!
Let's go home!
With his personality, he's probably okay.
But Go Ho must be very scared.
Are you going to go?
Kang is a good drinker.
I drank with him
a few times, I know it.
He didn't want to worry his mom,
so his family probably doesn't know.
Look in the bars around the area.
Have you changed your position?
My position is not working out...
right now.
Ya Ho!
What's an area with a lot of bars?
Go Kang doesn't like to drink.
He eats udon noodles from street vendors
or goes to the comic book shop.
Or he plays with pigeons in the park.
You don't know.
Look in the bars around the area.
At a time like this,
he might want to drink.
Dad.
What's he doing?
I don't know. Is he praying?
They do that in temples, right?
Dad.
Why are you coming now?
Oh, Dad.
What took you so long?
Oh, my...
Hey, Kang!
Hey!
You get up right now!
Pull yourself together.
Seriously, what are you
doing with your life?
That's enough!
Leave me alone! I'm going to turn
that guy into a human being!
Get over here!
Get over here.
Move it!
You!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
I know I may seem like I have
a dirty and crazy temper.
If you get to know me,
I'm not like that.
How could I have judged
someone so firmly like this?
Come out to eat with me.
When did you come to a place like this?
Who did you come with?
You're very aggressive.
I learned from my boss.
Because I like you.
Isn't it time we started dating?
I keep hating myself lately.