[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
We found him. Thank you.
That's a relief.
You're awake?
[Episode 19: Start and End]
What happened? Did you get into a fight?
Sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Huh?
I said, I'm sorry!
- What?
- Hey! Go away.
I said sorry! Sorry, I didn't mean it!
Were you pouring alcohol into your ears?
Why can't you hear me?
I accept your apology.
Maybe I should learn a trade.
If you want to.
Hey...
If you start ignoring me after you
become a judge, you're dead.
We'll talk about that after I become one.
First, get rid of the game console
and the comic books in your room. Okay?
Yes. I will.
Why are you laughing?
Eat this.
Take this out too.
You should've given this to me earlier.
My insides are hurting.
We're here.
Thank you for today.
You say "thank you" to me a lot lately.
I know.
Then, you'll come out to eat
with me tomorrow?
What?
You don't know this,
but you're supposed to eat with me.
I won the office competition.
Office competition? What was it?
You don't need to know.
How much do I have to beg
to get to eat with you?
Okay. I'll try a little more.
I know that... I may seem like
I have a dirty and nasty temper.
If you get to know me,
I'm not like that.
I've never killed a hundred thirty twelve
people with only two near me.
I don't know why I was born.
But, it's not my life goal to make
people around me uncomfortable.
So, come out to eat with me.
Trait: Temper like a madman.
A insanely nasty temper
that drives me crazy.
A brutal person that could kill a hundred
thirty twelve people with only two near.
A man born to make others uncomfortable.
- How did you know?
- What?
The stars.
I'm sleepy.
Unless you're going to let me
sleep here, give me an answer.
Let's go out to eat.
I'll take you somewhere great.
Sleep well, and I'll pick you up at four.
["A Prickly Personality
That No One Can Put Up With."]
I know I may seem like
I have a dirty and nasty temper.
I've never killed 144 people
with only two near me.
What do I do? What do I do?
He didn't see. He didn't see.
He wouldn't let me live if he saw it.
I don't know why I was born.
But it's not my life goal to make
people around me uncomfortable.
Is he crazy?
Oh, my. I'm totally exposed!
How could I have
judged someone like this?
Why?
No, no. He didn't read it.
He didn't, he didn't, he didn't...
Why are you acting strange
when you're dressed so pretty?
I keep hating myself lately.
It's okay. Because I like you.
- Manager Kang.
- What?
Can you act in a way
that I can get used to?
Don't smile at me like that either!
Stop smiling like that!
Wow! It's the spring now!
When have you ever come
to a place like this?
Who did you come with?
You're pretty aggressive.
I learned from my boss.
Follow me.
What do you want to eat?
Anything.
What do you mean, anything?
Pick something.
The grilled meat and rice meal.
What about drinks?
Oh, are we drinking too?
I'll have rice wine...
Excuse me.
What are you looking at? Look away.
Look at you!
I don't know if we're
on a date or if we're working.
Let's have a time
where we drop honorifics.
What?
We don't have to if you don't want to...
I knew you wouldn't want to.
Senior, I'm sorry to bother you
on the weekend.
Do you happen to know Manager Hwang's
secret pin for the Promise picture book?
I can't reach him at all.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I'm not sure.
Try 1-0-1-1.
Oh! It worked. Thank you!
What is it?
Nothing.
Let's drop the honorifics.
- What?
- Go on.
It seems like you have a lot to say.
No, it's okay.
You're going to get mad later
and take it out on me.
Even if I wanted to, I couldn't.
Why is that?
I like you. How could I do anything?
Then...
What are you looking at? Look away.
You! Why did you act
like that, back then? Huh?
The day after I was sick in the hospital,
the next day, you were all angry.
It was because I didn't
go in that day, right?
Is work so important
when a person is sick?
- No, it wasn't.
- Then?
Senior Ho is sick.
She passed out and went to the hospital.
Passed out?
Manager Hwang went to pick her up.
No, it wasn't.
I was upset after I heard you were sick.
You could've just said so,
if you were upset about it.
Why? Why were you angry?
You need to fix that temper of yours.
It really made me feel bad. You were
very obvious about your feelings.
I was angry that it wasn't me
who went to the hospital.
I was always the one
who took care of you.
It wasn't just anyone, but it was
Manager Hwang. It made me very angry.
I suppose it didn't have to me who went.
But in that moment... I felt that way.
Me too.
Are you okay?
You're just a player.
Where did you learn about this?
Didn't you say that this didn't suit me?
So, I'm telling you that you
don't know that much about me.
And you know everything about me?
Pretty much.
What do you know?
Birthday, October 11.
You turned 29 years old this year.
The youngest of one son and one daughter.
You really liked Creative Director Moon.
You like to go around cursing your boss
who has a insanely nasty temper.
You have a lot of affection
and enjoy analyzing things.
You like to focus a lot on data.
You always eat spicy food
when you get angry.
Then you eat a popsicle.
Even when people tell you
there's no hope, you never listen.
And... you broke up with
your boyfriend just over a year ago.
While you were dating him,
my temper got worse because of jealousy.
I do know a lot about you.
If there is anything I don't know...
I'm saying I want to get to know it all.
That's why I'm bringing this up.
Isn't it...
time we started dating?
Thank you for coming.
It's nice seeing you again.
It reminds me of good times.
Mu husband loved you so much.
Things were so good back then.
Mother.
I keep thinking of those days.
It wasn't that long ago, right?
Drink this. Be strong.
Be strong.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
What is it?
Let's leave work together later.
I need to talk to you.
"I have no reason to go with you."
Is that so hard to say?
Everything's so complicated right now.
Hearing that things are complicated
for you is the most annoying thing.
He's a person that
I once had feelings for.
There's another person my feelings
are now yearning for.