[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 20: A Day of Many Stars]
- Thank you for the food.
- Enjoy.
You're so cute.
It's all right.
Geez, now...
Go on. Go on and eat.
[Eat at home, even if you're busy.]
[Your bones get worse as you age.]
You can't go back to the good times.
Even if it was something that hurt me,
it hurts me to see mold growing on it.
It's me, Go Kang.
These were saved on Mom's phone.
They were all the commercials I made.
She filmed the TV,
so they weren't good quality.
Not to mention, they were
all filmed from the middle.
Ho bought me this. It's made from plants?
Let me try.
Geez, getting old gives me
all of these wrinkles on my neck.
Go, away wrinkles...
Oh, it's on, it's on. It's on.
It's on...
Let me see.
Wow...
Looks great.
She must be getting better.
It seemed a bit awkward, at first.
The ones she makes lately are really...
I can tell that my daughter
made these, just by watching.
Cool, right?
I need to become a proper human being
in order to make you comfortable.
She doesn't even make a lot of money.
She work all day and night and that's it.
Is that why I sent her to school?
Let's be honest, let's be honest.
A daughter is gone once she gets married.
Mom...
trusts you and only you.
There were many things that turned out to
be different than what I thought of them.
It's on... it's on...
I can't see very well.
Who is it, at this hour? Who is it?
Mom.
Ho.
Mom...
What's wrong with you?
Come here. Come here.
- Come to Mom.
- Mom.
- What is it?
Did you finally get fired?
You didn't know your place
and you were too reckless.
Right?
Mom!
Mom...
Come down. I'll hold you.
It didn't break because I'm too heavy.
Let's leave work together later.
I need to talk to you.
Manager Kang!
Are you... busy?
Say it.
About Manager Hwang...
I heard it too.
Are you leaving work with him?
Should I say I can't?
Why are you asking me that?
I don't know.
What did you do right,
that you're pouting?
"I have no reason to go with you."
Is that so hard to say?
Are you keeping your options open?
Why can't you say,
"Why are you leaving with him?"
"Don't do it."
Is that so hard to say?
You didn't say anything before,
so why are only getting mad at me now?
I'm sorry.
Everything is so complicated
for me, I was wrong.
The most annoying thing possible is
hearing how complicated your things are.
How can this not be complicated
for any normal person?
If we think about the revenue,
it's right to choose this account.
Still, there is sentimentality here.
We were with them for so long.
We're not the only
advertising company that exists.
They can work well with another company.
Make your choice quickly.
Still, it's different than
when they worked with us.
How are you not sentimental at all?
It doesn't put food on the table.
I don't understand why you're conflicted.
Sir, of course,
this is the right choice.
Still, they can't be without us.
I think they can go
with someone else, besides us.
Who gets to decide that?
- Just look at them.
- What do you see when you look?
When I look at them,
this is the obvious choice.
Why are you stalling, not choosing,
and making them angry?
Are they angry?
Shouldn't they be angry?
Look at this situation.
Fine, then. I will go tell them clearly.
Do not leave work together.
Leave work? What?
Hey, where are you going?
It doesn't seem like you're going to
decide today, so I'm going home.
Tell me when you've decided.
Hey!
"Why are you leaving with him?
Don't do it."
Is that so hard to say?
- By the way...
- I...
- You go first.
- Why don't you...
- I...
Oh! How did you two
end up coming in together?
All of the many stars in the sky
look the same to us from Earth.
They say, stars are all different shapes
and sizes when you see them closely.
Also, the star reviews
I've given were no different.
[Getting A Woman]
[Last Star]
Hey, what is this?
It's the last article.
Ho.
You guys are doing something fun.
He seemed like a man
who was perfect since birth.
He was like a kid.
I won't do this job.
You can't do this!
Do you want to be sued?
Just try it! I'll protect my own.
However, he was also
an adult you could depend on.
Hey.
The man who was so unlikable
and seemed untalented.
My niece, she's really smart and so nice.
He was actually a warm family-man.
[Men Who Exercise]
He was a bit awkward,
but he made an effort to try.
He had the perfect exterior.
Ho, we ran into Oh Jung Min.
Wow, I caught him playing hooky.
But he was a total player.
However, there could
have been a moment of sincerity.
Why are you being like this again?
Even the madman with the worst temper...
ended up having depth and a nice
fragrance I never could have imagined.
He might even have pure love.
I was in a one-way love story
for a long time.
Because I like you.
[Madman's Pure Love]
[Considerate Manager]
A deeply considerate manager.
I'm sorry! I'll be better, okay?
[Cold Ex-Boyfriend]
I'll change for you!
He was a cold ex-boyfriend that
made me fall to the ultimate low.
Ji Hoon, Ji Hoon. You have to talk to me!
He was just stubborn.
His love had not changed.
[Ex-Boyfriend Whose Love Remains]
More than anything...
he was a person that
I once had feelings for.
Now there is another person
my feelings are yearning for.
Also, these are the people
I spent most of my days with.
And will spend many more days with.
Regardless of any star reviews.
The client wouldn't stop talking,
so the meeting ran late.
I told him clearly.
The person I like now is...
you, Manager Kang.
I want him to be happy.
But...
I want... you, Manager.
You can't go back to the good times,
but better times will come.
New memories will be made.
Are you coming?
[A sincere thank you to everyone
who watched "Go Ho's Starry Night."]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Thank you, Dad.
It's so good!