[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Oh, my!
I'll be going to Team A to replace you.
Seriously, why are you doing this?
How can you be so sexy and dance so well?
You're my style.
Well, you are not my style!
[Episode 5: Memory's Temperature]
It would be best if you took those off.
That's right.
They say that you're a vampire,
Director Seo Gook Jin.
What are you talking about?
We've done these Promise ads for
seven years, and haven't aged at all!
Section Chief Park!
For your sake,
I really don't want to say this.
It really doesn't feel right.
Yeah, I need to know what it's about!
There's an ugly woman who is running,
and then you show the sky.
- What is this, you know?
- You're right!
It's no good. It's no good.
It should be something you like,
something you like.
Hey, now! What are you doing?
That's right! I like funny things!
Also, how are we targeting sportswear
for women with this advertisement?
This is how we do it! Okay?
Then, work on it a little bit more!
I will trust in you, Section Chief Park.
All right, sir.
Good bye.
Hey, Ho. Get me a towel.
Geez, even my underwear is wet.
I don't care about
the state of your underwear.
Hurry.
Yes, yes.
Why?
Yeah, what are you doing?
You, you...
Wow!
Wow! Look at Ho walking backwards.
Walking sideways too. Wow, awesome!
Geez, really...
I wasn't late today and I didn't do
anything wrong at the meeting.
Is he still angry because
I was being so rude?
When was I being rude again?
I do it so often...
How did it go with
your mom the other day?
My mom?
Go Ho? Go Ho?
Oh, that...
Not well.
Why? Your mom seemed okay.
He was good-looking, and manly.
Looked like he had a good personality.
In my relationship with my mother,
there's a river we can't cross.
With my real mom.
Then, what about the fake mom
that you met with at the hotel?
It sounds strange if you say
that we met at the hotel.
What are you thinking about?
You met your mom at a hotel.
I met you there too.
Why didn't you come out last night?
Oh, about that...
I fell asleep at home
because I wasn't feeling very well.
What about the ice cream shoot?
It looks like everybody is giving up.
Is that what I taught you?
I was working on it all of last week!
If I knew his home address,
I'd go there and get on my knees to beg.
Is the home address of a Hallyu star
top secret or something? Why?
Am I at a hearing or something?
I don't have to answer you...
Then I guess you don't need
Song Dae Gi's number.
- I don't!
- Oh, I see.
Wait! Did you... just say
Song Dae Gi's number?
His personal number?
If I call, he will personally answer?
The number where I can call him
to get him to shoot the commercial?
Yes, that number.
Of course, I need it!
Oh, please. Please.
Manager Hwang!
Why is my life like this?
Please do this favor for me.
Yes.
I found out Song Dae Gi's
personal phone number.
What?
Yes... yes.
I have confirmed that.
Thank you. Yes.
What are you doing, Senior?
You scared me.
The wheels on this
must be broken. It rolls so fast.
What did you do yesterday?
We went clubbing.
We?
We had meat for dinner,
then we all went clubbing.
Then he wasn't the only one there?
Him, him... even he was there?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
It would have been fun
with you there too.
It seems like he doesn't
remember anything.
That's a relief.
What do you think?
About what?
About how I said it would have
been fun if you were there too.
Well, I wasn't so...
Is that so?
You submitted that report
using hamchorom font.
I'm positive that I told you
to use hamkum font.
I'm sorry.
While you're changing the font,
change the content of everything.
You just threw together ideas
that you got from somewhere else.
We'll be changing the product for
Promise. Confirm, get it to production.
I'll do that.
Go Ho, let's head out.
Song Dae Gi would like to meet.
[Hanchorom font]
[Hankum font]
Make sure to align the images
and charts properly as well.
Make it look unified.
I'm sorry to worry you.
There won't be any issues with the shoot.
Just send a person that day.
Of course, we will.
You don't need to worry about that.
Thank you.
I must have made you two worry a lot.
No! Not at all.
We trusted you, Song Dae Gi.
Yes, we never doubted you,
and we waited.
Wow, you two make a good pair.
You two are very cute together.
I'll buy drinks some time.
Let's meet again soon.
- Thank you.
That worked out well.
Let's go back together.
I'm going to drop by the studio and
make sure everything is ready to go.
We can talk comfortably if it's just us.
No... this is more comfortable for me.
Nothing...
[Studio Meeting, 7:00 p.m.]
That worked out well.
This is all because of that damn guy.
Pull yourself together, Go Ho.
Pull yourself together! Do it!
[West Wind Park: Effective for Healing]
Why is it so cold?
Director Choi:
When do you have to go to Yongin?
Madam Joo is back from Norway...
Oh Jung Min: Senior, where are you?
Manager Hwang is...
Mother: Hey! What right
do you have, to not call me?
Did you come home, by any chance?
Shameless Hwang: Thank you.
I've always been thankful to you.
That's all I can say to you. Sorry.
Saying thank you, saying sorry.
Basic manners of work life.
But they can sound like curse words
when you hear them from an ex-boyfriend.
If he was always thankful to me,
why did he break up with me?
Why is that all he can say to me?
What does he want?
Hello?
So it is you, Senior Ho.
What are you doing here?
All day... wow.
Manager Kang was picking on me.
I didn't even have time to eat.
I thought I was going to die.
How did you manage to survive, Senior Ho?
If you get me started, talking about it,
you won't be able to go home tonight.
I don't have to go.
Does he know?
He knows!
If you have something to say,
get to the point.
I despise people who talk in circles and
try to get a feel for the other person.
Okay. I'll get straight to the point.
I like it that way too.
You should eat this.
You look very hungry.
I'm not hungry.
Were you really home last night?
- And if I wasn't?
- If you weren't...
that would be a good thing.
I think I would like that.
I think I'm going to
start liking you, Senior.
You need to dress warmly.
They say women need to stay warm.
See you at work tomorrow.
I told him to get straight to the point
and it hit me harder than I expected!
Jung Min: You have eat that with milk.
Warm it up before you eat it.
Senior.
Do you want some coffee too?
Exterior.
The confidence to get
straight to the point.
Is a party boy capable
of showing sincerity too?
- Hello.
- Yeah?
Manager Kang, it's Go Ho.
Thanks to you, I was able
to resolve everything.
- I'll buy coffee tomorrow.
- I'm out, bye.
Hello? Hello...
Oh, my!
What kind of phone mannerism is that?
This good-for-nothing loser!
I've never seen such a rude bastard
in my entire life!
What?
Oh, my.
If I knew you were coming, Manager Kang,
I would have kept Go Ho here.
No, I'm sure that she had
her own things to do.
Still, I feel bad that I sent her home
after all we did was talk business.
I should've kept her around a bit longer.
What unfortunate timing...
Why don't we go get a drink, at least?
Okay? Okay?
Let's go.
Why did you come here without calling?
Did you come because of Go Ho?
No, I didn't.
Then, did you come to see me?
Let's just say I came to see Ho.
Geez, you're so stingy
with your feelings.
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
- I'm telling you, it's all the same.
- What are you doing?
Oh, my!
Senior Go Ho, Manager Hwang
is treating us to a meal.
It's not Manager Hwang Ji Hoon,
but it's Oh Jung Min?
Do you still have feelings
for Manager Hwang Ji Hoon?
Because you are my woman.
It's normal to fall for a young guy who
looks like that if he just talks to you.
Kang Tae Ho has a decent side to him.
He always says what's on his mind.
He smells good too.