[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Special trait: Temper like a madman.
A insanely mean temper
that drives me insane.
A brutal man that could kill 144 people
with only you in his line of sight.
A man born to make others uncomfortable.
What are you looking at? Look away.
- Manager.
- Huh?
What are you doing?
I was picking up the ball.
Ball?
- Ball.
- Oh, yeah.
[Filming on location, oceanfront.]
[Episode 6: Heart's Direction]
It's cold, right? We set up
this scene just for you.
Please do a good job.
I know it's cold. Hang tight,
just a little longer. Good luck.
Okay, let's pick up the pace!
- Let's go!
- Good luck.
Okay. Stand by!
Let's try to get this done in one take!
Okay, action!
Big bowl of rice stew.
For the cold winter, when you feel
like your body might be frozen.
[Mother]
It was amazing when I imagined it,
but now it doesn't feel so great.
I'm sure Seo Gook Jin is going
to say something about it.
And then I'm sure that
I'll go crazy once he does.
This broth is amazing.
Right?
I found this place when I was traveling
the country on my bike back in college.
I was worried it would be gone.
But it's still here!
Traveled the country on your bike?
It took an entire month.
My butt hurt so much,
I thought I was going to die.
I wouldn't do it again,
but it was a good experience.
I met a lot of good people too.
I still ride my bike.
So, my thighs are...
I'm confused. Is he implying something?
Or am I just hearing things?
Ma'am, can we get some salt?
You can take the salt shaker
from that table.
You don't want any salt?
Huh?
Oh. Yes, yes, I do.
It's so cold here at night.
Let's go in and rest.
Why? At night, the beach is so nice.
What's so nice about it?
I can't even see anything.
We shouldn't be here. Let's go inside.
Senior. Are you aware that
you're really cute sometimes?
The poet Kim Choon Su once said this.
"When I called out that person's name,
that person came to me and seduced me."
The moment Oh Jung Min called me cute,
I felt like I became a cute girl.
We really are becoming a good couple.
Stop playing around.
Why not? You know how I feel, Senior.
Why do you think I followed you here?
Yes, Manager?
Yes.
You're changing the subject again.
No, not... yet.
No, that's because...
Was that Manager Hwang Ji Hoon?
It was Kang Tae Ho... Manager Kang.
Why would Manager Kang call you?
You're on Team B now.
I know, right?
He's been my boss since I was a rookie.
He can order me around,
no matter what team I'm on.
I envy that relationship.
Envy? You suffered through it recently.
I went through it for four years.
I think that's good for now.
As for the end of the bridge...
we should pan left to get a wider shot.
Okay, I think we can get started.
Sit down.
Okay, action!
You were the manager in charge
of the private plane ad, right?
It made me change
my career to advertising.
I was so moved by it.
I really wanted to buy it.
So, did you buy it?
No, I didn't have any money.
I failed.
You should've wanted to take out a loan
from a loan shark and gone out to buy it.
What?
That's my dream. Don't you have one?
I want to retire and buy
a small house in Hawaii.
It's not even that expensive there.
Not that kind of thing.
For when you make an advertisement!
I'm going to make people spend money
after they watch my ads too.
It's not easy to move a person's heart.
I can do it.
Who says you can?
There's nothing harder than
controlling a person's feelings.
No. I'm telling you that I can do it.
Manager Kang watches over you
like you're still on his team.
So why is he cold to me?
Hey, what are you doing? What?
What do you think you're doing?
Senior, if you keep acting so cute...
Seriously, you're way too harsh!
Why won't you believe
how I really feel? Senior!
Senior!
Yellow Sea, first shoot.
When I remember
all of my exciting first times.
When it's so cold that memories
of my past seem like they could freeze.
Idols are everywhere.
They can have looks, they can
have personality, they can have talent.
Whatever they have,
no one will put that person down.
A person who only receives love.
At our company, she is that person.
Senior Go Ho, have some coffee.
Gong Gong Hee: 25 years old.
Traits: God is unfair.
Thank you.
Pretty height, pretty body.
Pretty legs.
- Hazelnut for you.
- Okay, hazelnut for me.
You're like a little hazelnut.
More than anything,
she has a pretty personality.
You're like a hazelnut.
If you look like that,
shouldn't your personality suck?
He's here, he's here.
Also, there's always an outcast.
Him.
Good morning, good morning, good morning!
Good, good, good.
Guy who got in with connections.
Good morning.
Ms. Song. Ms. Park. Ms. Kim!
Good. Oh, so nice.
You're all pretty.
Still pretty, very pretty.
How long are you going
to continue being so pretty?
[Kim Yoo Chan: 40 years old]
It's an insult to give him a star rating.
Put aside his mistaken
usage of the title, "Miss".
It's a mystery to me why he only
greets those who are a "Miss".
Ms. Go, your face looks great today.
Ms. Seo.
Oh, my...
Your dress is hugging your hips today.
It really accentuates your butt.
Miss...
Mrs. Lee.
Good work.
Ms Gong!
Our Gong Hee is a "Miss".
Oh, but...
why are your shoulders so tense?
Is someone... giving you...
too much work?
I believe I gave her lots of work.
You have lots of work
to do too, Director Kim.
There's plenty to do.
Isn't our Manager Kang so scary?
Sorry. I have to go, baby.
I can't beat Manager Kang.
He has a personality like a madman.
- Director Kim.
- Okay.
All right! Let's get to work.
I know that Kang Tae Ho
has the meanest temper of them all.
But the reason that people
think so highly of him is...
he's fair. He doesn't discriminate.
Everyone gets a bite of his mean temper!
Whenever I see him, I feel suffocated,
like I'm being strangled.
It's because of your necklace.
You made it too tight.
Really?
Why does he always come to work?
He doesn't do anything!
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay now.
But you had to eat
porridge because of me.
It's not because of you.
We all get sick when we see him.
He turns everyone into a patient.
Welcome.
I think it's our first time eating
with Manager Hwang, right?
Yes, it is.
Why are you joining us?
Let us eat in peace.
I should have treated you guys
to dinner before this.
We've all been so busy, haven't we?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
That's why I'll be treating
all of you guys today.
Wow! I feel like my cold is disappearing.
Senior Go Ho! Manager Hwang
is treating us to lunch!
That's nice.
Oh! Are you okay?
What!
That was Manager Hwang,
not Oh Jung Min?
Wow, awesome!
Now I've seen everything!
Our company idol likes you?
Our company idol?
Oh Jung Min?
The female idol is Gong Gong Hee!
The male idol is Oh Jung Min!
Aren't they similar?
He's not my style.
I guess people all go
through the same thing.
There must be a madman in every office.
How could he be so similar
to the one in our office though?
What's the name of this webzine?
- "Starry Night."
- Awesome.
It is, right?
I thought maybe it was
a prophecy or something.
This is amazing.
This guy is tall too.
Work? Undisclosed.
He's a workaholic.
He has a crazy temper,
and when he glares at you...
- Who?
- Who else, who?
Oh, my!
Oh, so this is an article
about another company!
I guess there must be a boss
there with a really bad temper!
Yeah?
It's a relief that we don't
have anyone like that here.
- You're right.
- Yes!
So right!
Hello?
What is it?
So... what do you want?
Do you not understand?
Who do you think you are,
changing the creative director's plans?
If you think there are no mad men near
you, that means that you are the madman.
This is how you're going to work?
You can't handle it yourself?
Hang up now.
By the way, are you guys talking about
another company during work hours?
- No, no, no!
- No, of course not!
- Get back to work.
- Work hard!
[Why isn't Go Ho coming back?]
Where's the team that went to lunch?
Look at the time!
By the way, why aren't you asking?
What?
Gong Gong Hee asked me earlier
why I followed you guys to eat there.
Go answer the person who asked you.
No, I'm going to answer you.
Gong Gong Hee may have asked,
but you're prettier.
I followed you because
I wanted to eat with you, Senior.
Hey! You...
What? Style?
You're crazy. Crazy!
When a young guy like that even talks
to you, falling for him is normal!
Wait.
Is it that you still have feelings
for Manager Hwang?
No, never!
Never what?
You better never drop honorifics.
You're a funny guy, huh?
Why are you dropping honorifics?
Because you're my woman.
Because you're crazy about me.
Hey!
What?
What is this?
What's wrong?
Does he use cologne?
There.
I told you to take computer classes.
I passed level one.
Why are you still so bad at computers?
Reality is different than class.
Did you eat dinner--
Manager, are you wearing cologne?
I have dinner plans,
so I'm leaving after I finish this.
Manager, I really like your cologne.
Whether I spray cologne or money
on myself, what's it matter to you?
I tell him I like something about him
and he still throws a temper tantrum...
Even though he has a bad temper,
Kang Tae Ho has a decent side to him.
He leads confidently.
He always says what he's thinking.
He has a good sense of style
and a good taste in cologne too.
Trait: Madman who smells good.
There he is.
Have fun.
Good luck!
No, no, no! Hold the elevator.
- What did Kang Tae Ho do?
- Hee Yeon.
So, what did Kang Tae Ho do?
No... he just smelled so nice
so I asked him what cologne he used,
and he threw a tantrum at me.
He really did smell nice.
Are you sure it wasn't his natural smell?
If you fall for the smell of his body,
you're done for.
Manager Kang must be your style.
The new manager is your ex-boyfriend.
Your new love is your ex-manager.
Don't even joke about that, Hee Yeon.
It's hard enough being
around my ex-boyfriend.
Do you know why I worked late today?
Hwang Ji Hoon made me
do work that wasn't even relevant.
He's picking a fight, right?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
What do you get out of
not listening to me?
Kang Tae Ho is a full frontal psychopath.
Whether it was a date with him or not,
let me live vicariously through you.
This is really entertaining.
Those two are fighting.
Why?
Honestly, I don't know
why they're fighting.
I'm thinking of reinstating you
back onto my team.
Reinstating me?
I reject that. She's a member of my team.
I like you, Go Ho.