[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
If you have no feelings for your ex,
then why push away a guy that likes you?
All you're doing is going out with him.
If you don't like him, then stop.
Pretty Go Ho Senior,
what do you want for dinner?
- Something good?
- Good?
I know the perfect place.
- Where?
- Let's go there now.
[Episode 7: Things Unknown
to Those Who Don't Dig Deeper]
Manager, the Promise ad was rejected.
[Go Ho]
Our Promise client has rejected the ad.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Where are you right now?
Does this have any meaning?
Will it excite a consumer?
Did you think about this at all
before you brought it to me?
Well, the client wants something
very direct and straightforward.
He says that, but you should know by now
that when he sees this, he'll hate it.
However, he's continuing
to turn us down...
According to the data analysis...
I told you to stop bringing up data.
What do you get out of
not listening to me?
Out of our recent hit ideas, did I not
say that none of them followed data?
You never told me that!
When did you ever tell me that?
What will you do if I find one?
What if I find a hit commercial
that does follow data analysis?
What will you do if I find one? Huh?
And I'll do what the ten million won
client asks me to do!
He might hate it,
but he could like it too.
Why are you giving me all this crap?
I'll fix it and bring it back.
Kang Tae Ho is a full frontal,
absolute, class A psychopath.
Oh, hey! You don't need to go that far.
After I got the text about the rejection,
I worked until the sun came up.
Most people would praise me
for submitting a new project plan.
Is he even human,
yelling at me like that?
I'm positively certain that he's single.
- He's just trying to eat me alive.
- Hey, hey, hey.
How can you say that when you saw
him win all those awards last year?
You can say it. Say it twice.
Okay, okay, okay. Forget the bad stuff.
Tell me about yesterday.
How was it? How was
your date with the idol?
What date?
I got the text about Promise
on my way to dinner.
Come on! Tell me the details!
Let me live vicariously through you.
How was it? What did you do?
- We had kimchi stew.
- Huh?
Kimchi stew?
I think we suit each other very well.
The line started to build up
after we got here.
This place is really
well-known for their food.
It seems that way.
- It's so good!
- Right?
Full-bodied taste that can't compare
to anything made at home.
When you have high expectations
about a first date.
It's better to eat this at night.
When I realize that this guy is counting
chickens for me before they hatch
[Kimchi stew?]
So, was it not a date?
I guess not.
Did I get rejected while
being fed kimchi stew?
No, he bought you the kimchi stew.
He's saying that you should
be delusional, all you want. No?
I don't know.
Anyway, I went with him,
and he's not right for me.
I wasn't having any fun with him.
We couldn't even take a car there.
We had to walk around and around.
My legs hurt, it was cold.
What's the point of having a car?
Does he have more crap to say to me?
Stay back.
Keep your distance.
Did you have plans
with your mom yesterday too?
What?
Are you busy being
a good daughter to your fake mom?
Whether I'm being a good daughter
to my fake mom or out on dates--
I'm worried it'll keep you from working.
I was thinking of reinstating
you onto my team.
Reinstating me?
Can you do that? I only
switched teams recently though.
You aren't the one who
needs to worry about that.
Well, am I not even
allowed to be curious?
You told me that
in advertising, curiosity is everything.
Why do you keep cutting the roots
off of my curiosity?
Why... am I cutting--
Should I... should I tell you...
every single reason?
No. I'm sure you have your reasons.
It's just that I'm really sick.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I have a cold and a fever.
So, what's your answer?
I refuse.
I'm still new here,
so I need Go Ho with me.
You can have Lee Hee Yeon on your team.
She's Go Ho's senior
and she'll fit in with your team.
There's an issue with Promise.
Go Ho has a lot to learn.
I was very impatient.
Then I will teach her.
Now that you mention it,
I wanted to talk to you about Promise.
Go Ho is on my team, so why is she
reporting to you, Manager Kang?
Because I've directed this project
from the very beginning.
Back when she was on your team, that is.
She's on my team now.
Why, I ought to kick him in the balls!
I should get a team of eighteen people
and we should all kick him in the balls!
Look it over and take it away now.
Why don't you ever consider me,
and always just do what you want?
I always do what I want?
Don't you? You can't tell that
things are uncomfortable for us?
If you didn't know that,
let me be clear with you right now.
I find it uncomfortable to work with you,
Manager Hwang Ji Hoon.
If you do know that, say that
you will send me to the other team.
Whether you believe me or not,
I haven't done anything I wanted to do.
I have never not thought of you.
Then go give the green light
for me to switch teams.
Why don't you try thinking of me?
Why do I have to send my team member
to another team for no reason?
Nothing is getting resolved.
When one bad thing happens after another,
they call it Murphy's Law.
Manager Kang.
I am certain that Murphy's Law exists.
That nasty temper... he should've held me
to the end if he was going to catch me.
Go Ho, you're here?
This is really entertaining.
Those two are fighting.
Why?
They say it's about the Promise account.
Honestly, we don't really know
why they're fighting.
They're probably the first two
to fight over that dreadful client.
Are they crazy?
I knew Manager Kang had a bad temper,
but Manager Hwang is no joke either.
He refuses to lose. Wow!
He's always been that way.
When you get down to their cores,
they're really the same.
One has a bad temper on the surface,
the other just pretends he's losing.
They are both extremely stubborn
and only do what they want to!
I... I have experience,
working with both of them.
Who here has more experience
working with them than I do?
How petty...
Wow, amazing.
Did he just glare at me
for looking in there?
[Kang Tae Ho vs. Hwang Ji Hoon]
So, who will win?
Cheers!
For when work isn't going well, a break.
Director Choi,
you chose the wrong person.
Manager Kang is tall but he can't fight!
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I want to change mine.
- He has a strong name though.
Height is nothing, and I've seen
Manager Hwang's body.
- He has muscles.
- What the heck?
- When did you see that?
- I'm married, I'm married.
I have special powers.
You are so disciplined.
You really are.
Having a boss that gives us
time to relax like this.
He has muscles like you wouldn't expect.
Two bosses arguing downstairs.
[Who will win?]
When things aren't working,
I can only do so much.
- Section Chief!
- I'm busy, I'm really busy!
I have a bad back!
I can't pick up heavy things! I can't...
I don't know...
Stretch... it... out...
You... you.
Feels good, right?
I was upset, seeing you sick all day.
I'm good at stretching.
Should I help you?
You'll feel much better.
What are you doing? Something good?
Oh, stretching! I want to do it too.
Do it for me. Do it for me.
Hurry, hurry. My spine hurts so much.
My back hurts so much.
Yeah, stretch it, stretch it.
I wasn't slacking off!
I have a bad cold but I didn't
go home, I stayed at work.
Now, it's gotten worse.
We're going to the studio.
Shut your mouth and follow me.
What about the project plan?
I'm working on it.
I still think the other one was better.
- Is it a cold?
- What?
Yes.
Hold on.
Get out.
What?
I'm busy enough, as it is.
What if I catch your cold?
You should've said this earlier.
Wait... I did tell you.
Go home and sleep.
Don't you know that taking care of your
health is part of being a professional?
When will you learn
to be a human? Get out.
Get out!
That jerk!
A person is dying of a cold
and all you care about is yourself?
You're a long way from
being a human being, yourself.
But there is something you don't know.
This is my neighborhood.
You basically drove me home, dummy.
Dummy.
Are you sure this is good for me?
Of course! Your back will be much better!
Yeah, I think it's really getting better!
I'm going to do the next part.
- Seo Woon.
- Yes?
Where did Go Ho go?
Go Ho?
I think Manager Kang
took her to the studio.
Studio?
Seo Woon! Where's Manager Kang?
He called me and said that
he would be here soon. Where is he?
There you are, Manager Kang!
I waited a long time for you.
[Many thanks to Ahn Sang Tae
for his guest appearance.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
This presentation will be
a three-stage competition.
Why do we have to fight
amongst ourselves?
If it's a three-stage competition,
I'll vote for you two.
The car is in the garage.
Are you going to keep acting like this?
It's uncomfortable for me!
I don't like you.
You don't excite me.
I'll make you feel excited.
Sleep with me.
Go Ho.
I don't intend on losing...
I don't intend on giving up...
at all.