[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
[Promise Battle]
[Episode 8: Simple Things
and No-So-Simple Things]
As for the Promise account...
this presentation will
be a three-stage competition.
We'll set up a wall to keep information
from leaking from Team A to B for now.
Only one team's plan will be used.
If you let your guard down...
things won't be fun anymore.
- Especially...
- You.
- Go Ho.
I do not intend on losing...
I do not intend on giving up...
- at all.
Geez, I'm tired.
Why do we have to have a civil war?
Yeah, right?
So I was thinking about it.
Should we share information?
What's your team planning?
[Share?]
What is this?
Eat at home, no matter how busy you are.
Once you get older,
your bones will get fragile.
Okay.
She thinks this is going
to make me feel better...
She's creating more work
for me to do. I'm busy, as it is.
She's pretending to be thoughtful.
Geez, seriously.
Why is she so over-the-top?
She's so thoughtless!
And all this stuff is store-bought!
She doesn't even know
the size of my fridge.
What am I supposed to do
with all of this?
I wish people's feelings were simpler.
I don't know.
Either you like a person,
or you don't. That's it.
However, sometimes you like someone,
and then dislike them thereafter.
Or you dislike someone, and then
you start to like that person.
Life is screwing me over today too.
It's screwing me over more now.
Did you wait long?
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm only bringing it up
because it came up.
If this is a work competition,
then I will be on your side.
I'm sure you know very well, Go Ho.
Manager Kang Tae Ho is a bit...
He just isn't very flexible.
He never listens to others, right?
That guy is really uncomfortable.
He's uncomfortable!
He doesn't let me talk.
What is advertising? It's about people!
It can be this way, it can be that way.
But he only wants to do things his way!
That's true.
You and I agree on
the philosophy of advertising.
Yes! Philosophy!
There needs to be philosophy!
Manager Kang just has to have it his way.
Just thinking about him makes me tense!
It's so uncomfortable that this
comfy chair is suddenly uncomfortable!
Get me a new chair!
[Seo Gook Jin: Director of Promise]
Just do your job properly.
My car is in the parking garage.
I'll take the bus to work.
Stop it with the nonsense.
Is that an order?
If I have to take orders from my boss
about how I should get to work...
I have no choice.
- Are you crazy?
- Yes.
I'm going crazy because of you.
Are you going to keep acting like this?
How am I acting?
I find it uncomfortable being in the car
with you, so I want to take the bus.
- What's the issue?
- Why are you turning nothing into...
Why are you making things uncomfortable?
Why do you get to decide
if it's nothing or something?
Nothing has changed.
When we broke up,
you gave me no reason.
I didn't understand why
you wanted to break up.
It's nothing, so I don't need
to be uncomfortable?
But I am uncomfortable!
Oh... and this meeting
was really not great.
Even if we're competing with colleagues,
how can you side against a co-worker?
Who are you accusing of taking sides?
Can you not tell the difference
between work life and personal life?
- When you work...
- Ah.
You were always so damn good at
separating work life and personal life.
You must be proud.
What should I do for you?
What can I do to put you at ease?
You should never have come here.
Why bother asking now?
Do you hate me that much?
I hate you.
Ah, should we try
switching out the production?
Unless we completely change the mood,
this is the best we can do.
Developing a new storyboard
would be better.
Let's start again, from the storyboard.
- Wouldn't the director say something?
- Is this going to include the product?
Honestly, wasn't the model okay?
- Yeah, honestly she was.
- Yeah.
Go Ho.
Okay.
- Oh Jung Min.
- Yes?
Well...
I'm going to head out now.
I want you to photocopy this.
Do you need anything else?
One moment.
Here.
With the discount, that is 2,540 won.
Your change is 7,460 won.
Writer! Your payment has been deposited.
The response was great for this column.
There are talks of expanding
the Starry Night column!
Please continue to fight!
Suddenly, I have money!
I don't like how easy I am.
You are the only one who understands me.
How about we do a love story?
- Love story?
- Yes.
Let's be honest. Women in their 20s
and 30s are won over by romance.
A woman has been dumped by her boyfriend
and that woman has been lifted up by...
Promise.
After her break up,
she was wounded deeply.
She puts it all behind her.
She puts on her Promise gear
and she starts to run!
Her frayed breath, her sweat,
her second wind.
And at the end...
her boyfriend is waiting for her.
He spreads his arms open wide
and... "Honey"!
Promise.
What a freaking joke.
What kind of dumb concept is that?
Geez... this isn't 1988.
It's so awful!
Why? Using romance gets us halfway there.
If women are the target,
this is how you have to do it.
A man that was lacking dumps a girl.
She starts to run, and she wears Promise.
Men stop in their tracks
to stare at this girl.
The man at the bakery drops
the baguettes he was holding.
A driver rear-ends the car
in front of him because he loses focus.
A man walking with his girlfriend
turns to look at her and
gets slapped!
What is that?
Women also like being
committed to one man.
Statistics show this, okay?
Even women don't like to see
women with lots of other men.
They see that in a negative light.
They dislike it.
No, no. You are very mistaken.
Just think about it.
Whatever the case,
he's a man who dumped me.
He turned his back on me.
His reasons don't matter.
He turned away from me,
neglected me, and abandoned me!
A man who declared that
he didn't care what happened to me.
Is the woman stupid?
Why would she go back to him?
Still, how can love change?
Why do you think that love
in a woman can't change?
Then you should be good to her!
Women like men who are good to them too.
I like guys who treat me well too!
Don't think that a woman
will stand by and do nothing!
We're talking about
the commercial... right?
Manager Hwang?
I'm still having lingering feelings.
I think Go Ho's idea is much better.
Let's think about it and meet again.
Senior Ho.
Hey!
Oh. I'm sorry.
Go away!
Don't you know that our teams
have walls up to prevent leaks?
Get going.
Senior, it's just company business.
Why bother working so hard?
You're going to get paid the same,
no matter what happens.
What?
Don't you think that
you're being too hard on me?
We even had kimchi stew together.
Do you like me?
You already know that.
I don't like you.
- Why?
- I don't know.
I don't like you. You're just my junior.
I know you're cute, you're handsome.
I know you're really friendly too.
You don't excite me. So stop.
I'll make you get excited.
Sleep with me.
What did you just say to me?
I want to sleep with you, Senior.
I can't sleep because
I keep thinking about it.
I'm quite good at it.
You won't ever regret it.
You will feel excited.
You'll end up liking me too.
Let's keep it simple. Okay?
We can't have information leaks,
don't you know that?
I told you not to let your guard down.
Go.
What are all of you doing?
I'm glad I ran into you, Go Ho.
Let's go to Yongin tomorrow
to see Madam Joo.
I have a lot of work to do tomorrow.
We're in the middle of a competition.
I'd rather not lose a team member.
Oh, I'll be working off-site tomorrow.
That works out, then.
I approved it without
thinking about the competition.
Now, we can each
lose a person and it will be fair.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
It's the best.
You're eyes are dripping with honey.
I would have hearts in my eyes
if I had a young girlfriend too.
Ho, we ran into Oh Jung Min.
Are all men liars?
If he didn't really like me,
he shouldn't have said things like that.
I love you.
Some guys can't say anything
when they like a girl.
There's a time and place for you
to take your temper out on me.
- Where are you?
- Honestly, who can handle you?
Is it because I'm waiting for someone?