[This program has been sponsored
by Ministry of Culture and KOCCA.]
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Subtitles by DramaFever
You should have slept with him!
- Hee Yeon!
- Okay, okay, okay.
Still, why didn't you
just sleep with him?
When will you find a guy like that again?
What are you talking about?
Think about it.
A face like that, with that body,
and a guy that age.
Do you think you'll have many more
chances to sleep with a guy like that?
Now that I'm married,
I'm filled with so much regret!
It's illegal for me
to do that with other men!
So before you get married,
you need have many... many...
Hee Yeon! Please!
Why? Is it because of Manager Hwang?
I told you it's not!
I just want to be with a guy I like
who likes me back.
Even if it's not like
passionate and dramatic love...
I want him to think of me and only me.
Ho.
Not you. I mean, Hee Yeon.
What? Don't you know
that we're in a competition?
Oh, we weren't talking about that stuff.
- She needs to do something--
- Oh!
She's just so frustrating.
It wasn't that.
[I want to think of me and only me.]
Someone stupid like that.
[A Foolish Person...]
About that...
[Episode 9: A Foolish Person...
Madman Awakened]
Aren't those two funny?
I'm the director.
They're going on about
whether or not you can go.
It's up to me!
What's with you?
Life is just hard...
You got to leave the office thanks to me,
so think carefully about what I said.
Director, before you hire rookies,
don't you analyze their character?
Do you hire crazy people too?
Well you got hired.
What's wrong with me?
You look normal, but you argue
with directors and managers.
You don't even have a driver's license.
We have to chauffeur you around!
I will drive you around when
I buy a car like this for myself.
How much does it cost?
Why is this car so nice?
It's even better when it's moving.
Put on your seat belt.
A drive when you're too stressed out.
When you start thinking you want
to work hard and earn lots of money.
[If you're constantly thinking about
earning lots of money by working hard.]
How many years will it take me
to buy a car like this?
Five years, if I only breathe and work?
Hello.
I am here to sing for you.
My name is Go Ho.
I will get started.
Madam Joo, Madam Joo!
I love you, Madam Joo!
Forever!
Madam Joo!
Koong koong da!
Madam! Joo!
Sign... Right now...
Madam Joo, I'm getting old.
You have to stop asking me
to come dance at your house.
Then... should we do it at the office?
I meant to say that you should call me,
even when I'm not working.
Now, everyone knows the rest.
Director Choi is never stingy
with his reward.
Satisfaction of the eyes
and the mouth at the same time.
Bon appetit!
This is a famous place.
They only take a certain amount
of reservations every day.
I told the kids to look into
a good, expensive place.
Is it good?
It's the best!
Wow! Your eyes are just
dripping with honey.
I suppose I'd have hearts in my eyes
if I had such a young girlfriend too.
Hey, Chef obviously knows
who's paying for this.
If my first love hadn't failed,
I'd have a daughter like you, right?
The person with the wallet
is my customer.
- You don't want any coffee?
- No.
We do have our age difference.
But I think I know why the chef
thought we were dating.
Director Choi treats me like a woman,
and not like a employee.
He never crosses the line,
but it's strange.
He makes me remember that I have
the right to be treated like a lady.
I can dance well the next time too.
I'll expand my repertoire.
Yes, yes. You did very well.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I trust that you'll do well
the next time around too.
What are you doing here?
[Missed Call]
[Missed Call: Kang Sociopath]
You said you'd be working,
but here you are, on a date.
Hello.
I thought you were working hard,
but you're dating hard.
Please watch over my Jung Min.
Ho, I ran into Oh Jung Min.
I caught him playing hooky.
What should we get out of him?
What's with you?
Do you, by chance...
like Oh Jung Min?
What are you talking about?
He's the one who liked--
Nothing. Never mind.
Are all men liars?
What do you mean?
All people lie.
I don't know. Men seem
to be the ones lying to me.
I...
love you.
Oh, really?
I think I would die without you.
I'm sorry. I'll be better. Okay?
I'll try to suit your needs. Okay?
If you really like a person,
you shouldn't say things like that.
Why would you say things
you don't mean, seriously?
That's just how life is.
Some guys freeze and can't
say anything when they like a girl.
Hee Yeon, is Ho...
I mean, when is Director Choi
getting back into the office?
He has an appointment. He said
he was coming back in after five.
He's late.
What?
You want me to drop you off?
You feel like vomiting?
I need to get back to the office now.
I think I'm going to die.
My indigestion is so bad...
It was expensive meat too.
I wanted to be a tree that didn't sway.
I'm just a weed.
Every time the wind blows,
I get so cold that I start crying.
What crap! I don't like any
of the guys out there!
They all have so much to say!
I still tend to have lingering feelings.
What? Lingering what?
- Sleep with me?
- Sleep with you?
- I want to sleep with you.
- You want to?
- I'm good at it.
- Oh, my...
Wow, really?
[Oh Jung Min]
What?
It's a misunderstanding!
She's just like a little sister I know.
I don't care who she is.
Guys like you who just keep talking
need to have their mouths ripped out.
What did you say to her? Huh?
You told her, she might not be social,
but she hangs on well, like a koala bear?
She is very sociable.
Are you jealous right now?
Jealous? Are you serious?
You little! Are you done talking?
I'm not done.
Stop getting upset and listen to me.
Listen? Yeah, right. Don't call me again.
Do you know how to get out of here?
- Without a car?
- Yes.
Isolated at a rest stop near Seoul.
Can I...
cry?
[Kang Sociopath]
Why aren't you back at work yet?
There's one more thing
that Kang Tae Ho is good at.
Slapping a person in the face
when they feel like crying.
Why? What's it to you, Manager Kang?
I'm on Team B now.
What?
You said you're not my manager anymore.
You're just a random guy.
So, why are you picking on me
about every little thing?
We're in a competition right now.
We're not even supposed to talk.
All of my close friends are on Team A!
So then, why are you checking to see
where I am every day, and what I'm doing?
Are you a stalker?
Are you crazy?
Yes! I am crazy!
Geez, seriously...
You should keep your temper in check
for the appropriate times and places.
You awful, cruel human being!
Honestly, who can
handle your personality?
Only I can deal with it.
Kang Tae Ho had warned me.
Think for three seconds before speaking.
Truthfully, nothing that
he says is really wrong.
Where are you?
I would give in right about now,
but this time I really don't want to.
Tell me. Where are you?
You don't want to tell me?
Just let it go this time and tell me.
Where are you?
Jukjeon rest stop.
Hello?
Stay right there.
The hardest thing about Kang Tae Ho
is that I don't know what he's thinking.
When he says to stay here,
is he saying he'll pick me up?
Or is he telling me to freeze to death?
I'm starting to get confused.
Or is he angry
and coming here to get me?
Which one is it?
Is it because I'm waiting for someone?
I feel much better than before.
Even if it's Kang Tae Ho.
No. Because it's Kang Tae Ho.
Boy, I'm sleepy...
You're going all-out.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Ho's Starry Night]
Go Ho.
Men, especially men like Manager Kang,
don't do things for no reason.
No way.
Oh, my!
Do you think Manager Kang likes you?
We really don't want
to lose this competition!
I can't be held accountable,
as a manager.
It wouldn't be good for him
to lose, when he's new here.
He's saying to do it.
He said he'll be held accountable.
Don't go anywhere near Go Ho.
I don't know if Kang Tae Ho is a sadist.
I must be a masochist.
I must be.