(Episode 17)
It brings back old memories.
It has been forever since the three of us got together.
Let's talk upstairs.
Since when did you come back to Korea?
I heard you went to the Philippines after that incident.
I don't know.
You must have known Chairman Song for quite a long time.
Okay, fine.
I can get you to answer me later.
Where's Jang Young Mi?
I remember that incident...
from time to time...
If you're thinking of playing a trick or running away,
you should just give up.
Why did you call me?
Where is Jang Young Mi, you jerk?
I changed...
my mind.
Did you get him to change his mind?
Stop blaming the innocent.
Jang Young Mi has nothing to do with this.
No.
I'm the one who will decide if it has to do with her or not.
Let me ask you one last time.
Where is Jang Young Mi?
(Police Station)
I'm Prosecutor Han Ju Deok of Criminal Division Three...
of Seoul Central District Prosecutors’ Office.
Mr. Cho Hyun Woo, you are under emergency arrest...
as a suspect for Cha Eun Bi's murder...
and Jang Young Mi's missing case.
Are you with Prosecutor Seo Yeon Ah?
Mr. Cho, you have the right to remain silent.
Everything you say can be and will be used against you in court.
You may also consult an attorney.
Let's go.
Was this your plan?
You're very quick with these things.
How did you come up with this plan in such a short period of time?
This has nothing to do with Jang Young Mi.
You need to take your hands off now.
Yes, no one is going to care about a nameless actress's...
missing case.
But...
wouldn't you feel really sorry if no one actually looks for her?
Let's be humane.
He's Prosecutor Han Ju Deok of Criminal Division Three.
I'll meet with Cho Hyun Woo.
Please stall some time.
Sure.
(Seoul Central District Prosecutors’ Office)
Why did you arrest Cho Hyun Woo?
Him? He's a suspect of the missing case of that actress.
Exactly.
Since when did you know of that case?
What's the reason of his emergency arrest?
Seo Yeon Ah. What are you doing right now?
I'm sorry.
But this is my case.
I can't understand why he arrested him.
You couldn't find Cho Hyun Woo,
and Han Ju Deok did.
That's why I told you numerous times...
to make an accurate report.
You never made an official report.
How can you claim that this is your case?
But if by any chance you let him go,
he might bring about more victims.
Please change the prosecutor in charge to me.
If you don't, I will file an official complaint.
I heard the information on the recent articles...
about Cho Hyun Woo is from you. Is that correct?
I should make an official complaint...
for leaking information to the media...
without reporting it to your superiors, right?
Articles?
Did someone leak the information? It wasn't me.
Begin your investigation.
Bye.
- What are you doing? - What's the reason...
for Cho Hyun Woo's emergency arrest?
Why should I tell you?
Are you my boss?
Move aside while I'm still nice.
Who gave you an order...
to arrest Cho Hyun Woo?
I've been doing this far too long to be ordered around.
I'm busy. I have no time.
I heard there was a connection...
in Hanjoo Hospital's medical malpractice case.
Who says so?
I heard a lot of bad things about you lately.
There are a lot of rumors too.
Rumors?
It's all nonsense, so don't mind it.
But...
I think those up there heard some things.
Did your father hear anything?
What's the rumor?
Oh, well...
It's probably all false.
Hello, I'm the attorney for Mr. Cho Hyun Woo.
Sure.
You need to answer me now.
Where is Jang Young Mi?
Why did you take her?
I saw what's in the USB.
I know why...
Soo Jeong and your brother died.
It's because of the USB, isn't it?
My brother and Choi Soo Jeong died seven years ago...
because they watched what was in it.
And Jang Young Mi watched that too.
Did you kill her too?
Jang Young Mi?
She's not it.
Come on, it was the USB.
I saw it too.
You did? Namwon Restaurant?
Then why are you still alive?
But since you've seen it,
you'll die as well.
I'll die?
Where's Jang Young Mi?
Where is she, you dirtbag?
Who is he?
What was his name again? Cho Hyun Woo?
He'll be released soon.
I owe you one, sir.
Don't say that.
And you always pay me back.
Every deal has a price.
By the way,
is he related to Jang Entertainment's actress?
Yes, he's in a pickle right now.
Exactly.
This isn't a blockbuster.
They're saying that those girls from Jang Entertainment...
were killed or have disappeared.
It also doesn't make any sense that Bumjung's funds...
have been sent to that agency.
What do you mean?
Prosecutor Seo seems to be digging into something so ridiculous.
I was concerned that such rumors...
might get you in trouble.
It seems like you want to ask me for something.
Well...
My car seems a bit too small,
and I'm getting sick of the girl.
I'm not very happy with my life these days.
The personnel appointment...
for the next public prosecutor general will be soon.
(Candidates for the Next Public Prosecutor General)
(Candidate Park Min Pyo's Profile)
(Candidate Lee Woon Geum's Profile)
I'm in a dilemma whether or not...
to put your profile in that envelope.
Did you meet Cho Hyun Woo?
He said Namwon Restaurant was in the USB.
Chairman Song and the high-ranking officials...
went there.
Jang Young Mi was also nearby.
Doesn't it seem fishy?
You said the table seemed full...
but that you only saw Director Do, right?
Yes.
Hyun Woo will be released soon.
I need to follow him and find out where Young Mi is.
Detective Ma and Mr. Guk are on their way.
Where is Cho Hyun Woo?
The interrogation was done, so he just left.
Darn it!
Sir!
I lost him. I swear he came this way.
Get out of the car, you scumbag! Get out!
You took him, didn't you?
Where is he?
- I have no idea what you mean. - You little...
Yes?
Okay.
Just in case, check the CCTV footages.
If he's on it, please let me know.
I doubt he's on it.
It was part of their scheme to bring him in and take him out.
This is driving me crazy.
You'll be able to reach me whenever.
Since you've been formally interrogated,
the articles will be taken care of.
It was nice.
I got some fresh air.
What did Tae Kyung say?
He didn't know anything.
He didn't even know why Young Mi disappeared.
The dust will settle.
It'll be wrapped up soon, so be patient.
Oh, right.
He said he opened the USB.
The USB?
He asked me if that was why his brother died.
Will Tae Kyung die as well?
After all, he saw Namwon Restaurant.
(Namwon Restaurant)
You did? Namwon Restaurant?
[VIU Ver] KBS2 E17 'Justice'
"Secret Path of Namwon Restaurant"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Namwon Restaurant)
I should take care of that camera.
What could've happened in here?
Woo Yong, after about 10 years,
let's build up a 150-story building in the middle over there.
Can you do that?
You crazy idiot.
Why not? Are you scared?
We should remember this day. Let's take a picture.
Stop eating.
All right. In 1, 2, 3.
Will you show a smile?
He said he opened the USB.
He asked me if that was why his brother died.
Oh, no! What was that?
A cat. It was a cat.
How are you working as a prosecutor when you get scared that easily?
It jumped out of there suddenly.
Come on.
Wait up for me.
When I came here last time, I heard these houses were vacant.
Why did Jang Young Mi come here?
(Untitled)
Look at this.
Those are Jang Young Mi's missing diaries.
(Did Soo Jeong come to this place too? Who killed her? I'm so scared.)
Did Soo Jeong come to this place too?
Who killed her?
I'm so scared.
(Do everything to find Jang Young Mi.)
(Since I can't trust you yet,)
(I'll give you the rest of the clues depending how well you do your job.)
The number you have reached is not in service.
I don't think these are from the culprit.
Who could it be?
You haven't contacted Jung Hae Jin yet, right?
The girl who came here with Jang Young Mi.
Not yet.
I was being careful because of Jang Chi Soo.
I need to meet with her.
Soo Jeong told me...
that she met men in a place where it looked like a maze.
She cried all night because she was scared.
Did those men kill her?
(You'd better send back Jang Young Mi.)
(Or these diaries will be disclosed to the public!)
- Who sent these? - It was sent...
from a computer at an internet cafe, so I couldn't track it.
Anyone from Jang Young Mi's social circle who would do this?
Is it possible Lee Tae Kyung sent these?
If Tae Kyung knew about these diaries,
he would have done something.
I'll look into her social circle.
Find out who sent this. Hurry.
(You'd better send back Jang Young Mi.)
(Or these diaries will be disclosed to the public!)
On July 27...
No, not that case.
Hold on.
I'm here to see Lawyer Lee Tae Kyung.
Okay.
Hello.
Lawyer Lee.
We spoke on the phone. My name is Lee Tae Kyung.
- Hello. - Take a seat.
Just like I said on the phone,
I don't know much about Young Mi.
I don't know what you like,
so you can drink everything here.
I wasn't very close with Young Mi.
If what you say is true,
why did you go there?
Just to have a meal.
At which restaurant?
I don't remember.
You came here at least twice a month.
But you don't remember?
Have you been to Namwon Restaurant?
No.
You must know Chairman Song from Bumjung Construction though.
Not really.
I'm sure you do.
You've met him at the place you went to with Jang Young Mi.
No, I have not.
Ms. Jung Hae Jin.
If we don't find Jang Young Mi quickly,
something might happen to her.
I'm sure you know the cases with Choi Soo Jeong...
and Cha Eun Bi.
I'm worried about Young Mi,
but I really don't know anything.
I don't think that's true.
I think you just don't want to tell me.
Call me if you want to talk.
I'll compensate you amply.
He does keep his promises.
I must survive.
I must survive no matter what.
Hey.
Please help! I'm locked up here!
Please help! Is anyone out there?
Please help!
Please let me live.
Please spare my life. I... I don't want to die.
I'm not going to kill you.
Please just let me go.
I won't tell anyone else once I get out.
I'll live quietly until the day I die.
If you let me go, I'll do anything you say.
So please spare my life.
Please.
Do you want to get out?
Yes.
I'll do anything. Anything.
I'm also annoyed...
to be stuck here too.
Where's Cho Hyun Woo?
It has nothing to do with Jang Young Mi.
If it has nothing to do with her, why are you covering it up?
I just don't want to complicate things.
He's the guy who killed my brother!
Why do you keep hiding him away?
Why are you not letting me look for Jang Young Mi?
As you know, Cho Hyun Woo isn't in his right mind.
If you rub him the wrong way, everything we did...
It should get exposed now.
Shouldn't we expose what exactly happened at this point?
Why did my brother die?
Who really killed him?
Are you sure you can handle it?
Why? Don't you feel confident?
(Episode 18 will air shortly.)
It looks like something complicated happened.
Did it go well?
Let me know if you need help.
It's no use crying over spilt milk.
The best I can do is clean it up so it doesn't leave...
a lot of marks.
While we're at it,
you should probably close down...
Namwon Restaurant.
Why?
Did Lee Tae Kyung catch on?
You should be careful for a while.
Things aren't looking great...
in many ways.
I have never lived carefully in my life.
You can't live your life only doing what you want to do.
Bumjung became this big thanks to Namwon Restaurant.
Are you sure it'll be okay?
Jungjin Group was saved from danger seven years ago...
thanks to Namwon Restaurant.
Exactly.
Why would you close down something that awesome?
You just have to get rid of Lee Tae Kyung.
(Daily Records of Acute Methanol Intoxication)
(2012 Delivery Car Accident Investigation Records)
(Yeongdeungpo Police Station)
Mr. Nam.
- Yes? - Wait.
Look at these pictures.
What? Yes.
What about these pictures?
What are...
those pictures?
You know, pictures related to a case.
With which case?
Just...
Why do you ask?
I think this delivery man is someone that I know.
Mr. Lee's younger brother?
His younger brother?
Father.
Hey, you're late.
It's Tae Kyung's younger brother.
That was Tae Ju.
What do you mean?
Oh, do you remember?
After that happened and my legs...
became like this,
I told you about a friend of mine who always helped me carry my bag.
That friend who died in an accident.
That was Tae Kyung's younger brother.
Did you know?
Well...
No.
It looks like Tae Ju...
helped me meet Tae Kyung.
I was bullied at school,
then this happened to my legs,
so I once had a terrible thought and jumped in front of a car.
But Tae Ju jumped in to save me.
I mean, he could have died too.
But...
it looks like Tae Ju didn't die in an accident.
Who could have killed him?
He was such a good kid.
Did anyone ask you about Jang Young Mi?
Or about going to that place?
No.
Did something happen?
Darn it, this is giving me a headache.
Do you know anything about Jang Young Mi's diary?
Young Mi's diary?
What about it?
She must've written in her diary about going there.
It's too complicated to explain everything,
so inform me immediately if something happens.
Who's looking for it?
Her diary.
I don't know.
Hey.
Do you really not know anything?
You were close with her.
Exactly. So what's with her diary?
What's going on?
Forget it.
Anyway, be careful.
Don't run your mouths either.
Go.
What is it?
What happened to the movie audition I attended last time?
The one where I drank with them.
Oh, that?
They're having money issues. Be patient.
You were sure that they'd film it.
I am. I really am.
They don't think you're young enough.
If this falls through again, I won't stand still.
You know very well what I had to go through.
You can't do this to me.
I know. That's exactly why I'm doing my best.
Let's be patient.
I mean...
Why didn't you accept the sponsor offer?
Why are you trying so hard?
Live a more comfortable life.
If I'm not cast for that movie, I'll disclose everything.
I'm not going to meet the same fate as Young Mi's.
Was it you? Was it?
You were the one threatening with her diary, weren't you?
Is that what's going on right now?
I couldn't sleep.
I thought that perhaps, Young Mi was confined...
somewhere in here.
Once you've set your mind on something...
You haven't changed at all.
Speak for yourself.
You're the one who is tenacious.
Except for when it comes to dating.
I wonder what happened to her in here.
(Smile Cart Bar)
I'm sorry.
I could trust neither the police nor the prosecution.
I wanted to test you...
to see if you could truly find her.
That's why I sent you those texts.
So why are you here?
She wrote about something that happened here.
I thought maybe she was trapped in here,
so I came to find her.
Where are her diaries?
They're gone.
I had them in my bag at all times.
They were in here right before I left.
What are you doing here?
What?
I have to go somewhere for work.
The president is looking for you. It must be about Young Mi.
(I keep practicing my line...)
You know who sent those texts regarding her diaries?
I do.
So why are you here?
You're the one who calls me over there.
Your secretary...
stopped by the agency.
He needs to find out who did it.
I read them.
You cast her as the lead of a web drama.
Will that do?
I'd appreciate a suitable compensation for my silence.
Silence?
That's great. You have quite a capacity.
With that strong ambition of yours, you could do anything.
What do you want?
Success.
I finally found out...
what Soo Jeong had to go through.
She had come to this place and met those men.
She met them in this eerie and strange room...
at the end of a maze-like alley.
Namwon Restaurant.
Wrap it up this instant.
Other than Jang Young Mi and Jung Hae Jin,
who else came here?
Those two were the only ones.
Since they were rookies, they were vulnerable.
The other actresses are too famous to do anything to them.
So on the day she disappeared, she was supposed to come here?
Yes.
Please find her.
She's a poor girl.
Don't worry. We will.
Do you know the man she had met?
I'm not sure.
Did you hear anything about her going to Namwon Restaurant?
No, I didn't.
So there's a room in this alley,
and that's where she met a man, correct?
Correct.
At times like this, you need to grab the bull by its horns.
Goodness.
You see, this situation is a bit uncomfortable.
Yes, you're right.
I'll take full responsibility.
Please open it.
You must keep your word.
[VIU Ver] KBS2 E18 'Justice'
"Relationship Between Dae Jin & Tae Ju"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
I think this is it!
Is this it?
Yes.
She wrote that there was a blue hourglass in the room.
So this is the place where the sexual favors were exchanged.
Scumbags.
Then, that day, Do Hoon Jae also...
I think Namwon Restaurant from the USB means this place.
Whatever happened in this room was recorded on that UBS.
The sexual favor video?
They pretended to eat at the restaurant,
but they received sexual favors.
Does this mean the murder of Choi Soo Jeong...
is related to this place too?
But why was your brother murdered?
The package my brother tried...
to deliver to Choi Soo Jeong that day...
was that USB.
The USB she gave to Jang Young Mi?
That's why.
Someone accidentally saw the video that was never...
to be revealed to the others.
Your brother.
Do you think Chairman Song had him killed?
(Bumjung Construction)
Seo Yeon Ah and Lee Tae Kyung stayed there the whole night.
I'm sorry.
Get out.
Seo Dong Suk.
We must use his card now.
("The Very First Father and Daughter Prosecutors")
I'm sorry to have asked to meet with you at the last minute.
What is this about?
What was so urgent to discuss?
I had something to discuss with you.
It's about time.
We can meet some other time.
I don't see any reason to have this meeting with him.
I'm quite disappointed.
Have you already forgotten about me?
I think today's meeting will be very important...
for the sake of your daughter.
Dad.
What were you thinking about so deeply?
You didn't even see your own daughter.
Where are you coming from?
From the court.
It seems like I have a lot of hard cases.
It's hot.
Do you want to have patbingsu?
Patbingsu?
I'd love to.
This is good.
I didn't know we had a place like this near our office.
Your father has been coming here for 20 years.
Please enjoy.
Goodness. You've kept this nice place...
to yourself for two decades.
I feel so betrayed.
Isn't work...
tiring?
It is tiring.
It's so exhausting.
I hope you can resign from your job...
and get married now.
No way.
Are you serious?
You wanted me to become the first female public prosecutor general.
Do you want to?
Well,
I might not be a good public prosecutor general like yourself,
but I want to be a prosecutor the people aren't ashamed of.
That will be hard.
I just want you...
to see only beautiful things...
and eat only delicious meals.
That's the life I want for you.
Dad, you must be getting old.
You're getting old.
(Lee Tae Kyung)
(Do not smoke in the toilet.)
You're here.
This is your favorite restaurant.
But why is this restaurant always closed?
They should just close it down if they don't open regularly.
Woo Yong.
Do you still have nothing to say to me?
I guess so.
I have nothing to say to you.
And I'm getting tired of lying.
Tae Kyung.
Should we just quit everything,
open up a fancy bar,
and...
drink every day like this?
Goodness, you're talking nonsense again.
You can't stop now.
You ought to go to a higher place, Chairman Song...
As you get rid of people who are in your way...
and kill people who are bothering you.
You ought to go all the way to the top.
Is that why you killed my brother too?
Because he would stand in your way to the top?
Back then, should I...
have killed you too?
Then we wouldn't have had to face a day like this.
Exactly.
You made a mistake.
You should have killed me and finished the case perfectly.
You should have killed my brother and killed me too.
Then you would have gone way up high without getting stalled back.
Isn't that so?
It was all to cover up something disgusting like that.
Why did you do that to that innocent kid?
That poor kid was aching all over...
because he was busy making deliveries from the dawn.
Why?
What did he do wrong?
What?
Why did you kill him? Why?
Why?
So...
why did you get this far, Tae Kyung?
So why...
did you make me come this far?
Why?
Darn it.
Did you kill Jang Young Mi too?
Just like what you did to my brother?
I'll find her no matter what it takes.
I'll find her and deal with the jerks who did that to them.
You better get ready.
Hello.
(Justice)
Why did you bring me here?
I thought it would be fun.
Who do you think you are? Don't you know who I am?
Why did you go to Namwon Restaurant?
- What? - You'll get hurt if you go further.
How can I get even more hurt at this point?
Bring Jang Young Mi here now...
unless you want Dae Jin to find out.
I looked into the real owner of Namwon Restaurant.
Long time no see.
It won't be easy to find an answer to this case. You should stop.
Young Mi is still alive, isn't she?
Please find her.
So who's the one that filmed the sex video here?
Where is that USB?
The music box. I think I know where the USB is.